My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
How many more terrible things
are you gonna do to protect me?
That's my job. That's all that matters.
It's my turn to go out on my own.
Don't come looking for me.
Everything seems to be telling me
that Barry and I are
meant to be together.
Somebody please help!
There's only one person
who can help you now.
YOUR SPEED FOR WALLY
The Flash.
Barry, I know you can't give
up your speed to that monster.
That's not your decision.
Hand him over and it's yours.
- He's slowing down.
- He's becoming human again.
I know some piece of
you did care for me.
Please let him go.
Caitlin!
It's a regular day in Central City.
Nothing out of the ordinary.
People wake up.
Roll out of bed.
Suit up for the day.
Get to work as fast as they can.
Make sure they get a
caffeine fix along the way
so they can make it through the
mountain of work that awaits them.
Yup, it's just a regular day.
And I'm just a regular guy.
♪♪♪ The Flash 2x19 ♪♪♪
♪♪ Back to Normal ♪♪
♪ Original Air Date on April 26, 2016 ♪
Z!@  ~   Am@n
I really wish we didn't have
to keep Jay's helmet around.
- I hate this thing.
- Well...
Just want to put a dent in it.
Cisco, did you see Caitlin in your vibe?
Zoom's got her in his lair.
She's scared, but she's okay.
Oh, thank God.
All right, we need to get her back.
I know.
But without your speed,
there's no way any of us
can get through that breach that
Cisco found at the hospital.
I just don't think there's
anything we can do right now.
He's right.
And it's thanks to you, Al.
Enough. We're all suffering here.
That's right. That's right, Detective.
We're all suffering. We've lost Snow,
you've lost your speed, and now...
now Zoom can come through
that breach anytime he wants.
And that, Allen...
that's on you.
Hey, that's on all of us, okay?
We made these decisions as a team.
No we didn't.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go find Jesse
before Zoom does... again.
Wait, you found her? How?
Cellular dead zones, remote...
people from my Earth vibrate at a different
frequency than people from your Earth.
They leave cellular dead
zones wherever they go.
That's why I'm always
dropping calls around you?
Okay, so... so wait, how did that help?
I track the dead zones created
by Jesse since she got here
and I follow the trail.
It's easy.
What, so you think you're gonna need that
gun to convince her to leave with you?
You're full of questions
today, aren't you, West?
The gun is not for my daughter.
She's not the only person from a
different Earth, hiding out on this one.
If I run into them, I'm gonna need this.
Okay, but you're also
gonna need some help.
Really?
You know anyone with the
speed to help me, Ramon?
Great. I'll be in my workshop.
Don't listen to Wells, Barry.
This ain't all on you.
Yeah, I know.
You need a ride back to the station?
No, I'm good.
I'm gonna stick around, actually.
Finished all my cases this morning.
Damn, that was fast.
That was a poor choice of words.
You do know it's okay to ease back into
the way you used to do things, right?
Well, this is the only
way I can fight crime.
If I'm not The Flash,
that's what I got to do.
You need to eat.
Caitlin.
If you want to speak to me,
then take off that mask.
Does this make you feel better?
Nothing you could ever do
would make me feel better.
You don't need to be afraid.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I care too much about you to do that.
You only care about yourself...
Hunter.
You're gonna want to see this, son.
No!
I know you think that I'm a monster.
I understand why.
But that'll change.
- Please, Cait...
- Do not call me that.
Why are you keeping me here?
You're cured.
You don't need me for anything.
You're here because I love you.
It may take a while, but
someday, you'll start
feeling that way about me again, too.
Make yourself at home.
You're gonna be here a while.
Okay?
I-I don't understand.
Well, hello, doppelganger of mine.
What do you know?
I can still pull off brunette.
CENTRAL CITY POLICE
Dad.
Oh, hey, son. What a surprise.
What's up?
I wanted to ask you about something.
Someone, actually.
The Flash.
What about him?
Well, he showed up at my street
race when Iris got hurt.
Then, when that man-shark
thing attacked our house.
And when Zoom took me, he said,
"Someone The Flash knew cared about me""
Yeah, it doesn't take a genius
to figure out that that's you.
You want me to tell you who he is?
I can't do that.
No, I know. I know.
I was actually hoping that you
could set up a meeting for me.
A meeting? Between you and him?
I... I don't know if I can
do that either, Wally.
Well, why not?
Joe?
Singh wants to see you.
Okay.
Look, maybe one day,
but, I mean, not now.
I got to get to work.
See you at home?
All right.
The laser tag club's in 2D.
The...? Oh, no.
I'm looking for Jesse.
Come on in.
Thanks.
Jesse!
You're, like, the first person
who's ever come to visit her.
- What?
- How'd you find me?
Jess...
Cellular dead zone.
I told you, I'd find
you wherever you went.
Wait, so you're a runaway?
So you're her dad?
Great, let me know if I need
to find a new roommate.
Listen.
We need to go.
So, what?
You think I'll be safer with you?
Yes.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna pass.
Jesse.
We need to leave.
No, okay?
No, I'm not going anywhere
with you ever again.
You are...
you are in danger.
Do you understand? You
are in grave danger.
I know!
I'm in danger because of you.
- Because of me?
- Yeah!
Okay, everything that's
happened, it's your fault.
Zoom hunting us, the metas...
moving here.
I'm done with it.
Okay, you wanted me to start a new life,
and that is exactly
what I'm trying to do.
- No, Jess... Jess...
- You killed a man!
I can't just forgive you for that.
And I may be afraid of Zoom, but...
but I am just as afraid of you.
Please, just... just go.
CRIME RATE CLIMBS HIGHER
And a new report shows that petty
crimes have risen slightly this month,
sparking concerns that The Flash...
Don't watch that.
Cisco, everybody's gonna realize sooner
or later that I don't have my speed.
The later the better. The
last thing we need is
every criminal in the city thinking
they're untouchable, right?
What is that?
Case in point.
What?
What is that?
It's Harry.
What about Harry?
The camera in the lab van
recorded an accident.
See, this is my version of crash assist.
It's like those Russian
dash cams, but, you know,
without attack helicopters and
bad pop music on the radio.
That does not look like an accident.
First Caitlin's taken, now Wells.
- CRASH ASSIST ACTIVATED
- This is where he got taken,
but there aren't any
traffic cams in that area.
I'm gonna head out there,
see what I can find.
I'll analyze this footage and see
if we can figure out who this is.
All right.
Wait, what was the last
place the van stopped?
Woodmen and Shore for about 15 minutes
before heading back to Central City.
- Why?
- That's where Jesse must be.
She should know if something's
happened to her dad.
Iris, hey.
I need your help with something.
You're... Killer Frost.
And you're Caitlin Snow.
Your little friend, Cisco,
wouldn't shut up about you.
Made you out to be some kind of a saint.
So tell me, why hide the girls?
I mean, you've seen our body, right?
If I could get my powers to
work through this carbine wall,
the first thing I would
do is shut him up!
Who is he?
Don't know, don't care.
But if he's here, Zoom must need
something from him.
So what does Zoom need you for?
That is an excellent question, Caity.
You know, I've been asking
myself the same thing.
But doesn't matter now.
I'm not gonna stick around much longer.
Wait, I... I thought you said your
powers don't work inside this cell?
They don't. You're right.
So you're gonna help me get out of here.
Why would I help you?
Listen, honey, there's no way you are
making it down that
cliff all by yourself.
So let's make a deal.
You get me out of this box,
and I'll help you get home.
Might even throw in some
wardrobe tips for free.
So what do you say, Caitlin?
Do we have a deal?
I don't understand.
There's nothing around here.
What did the van hit?
I don't know.
Something strong enough to exert an
equal amount of force back on the van.
Someone was definitely here, though.
You think maybe a meta-human?
Yeah.
And if it's a meta that's after Wells...
Then they could be from Earth-2.
Probably.
We got to get Jesse.
Find Wells. Fast.
Dr. Harrison Wells.
Yup. And who are you?
Name's Griffin Grey.
Griffin Grey?
Do I know you?
Nope. But you should.
I'm one of your mistakes.
One of your sins coming home to roost.
All right, you think I...
I'm from...
I'm not... I'm not who you think I am.
I know exactly who you are.
And you're gonna fix what your
particle accelerator did to me.
What did the accelerator do to you?
That.
Well, that's impressive.
And all things considered,
I don't know that having
that kind of strength is the worst
thing you could have been given.
Yeah, that's what I thought at first.
And it was a lot of fun.
Till I learned it did
something else to me, too.
That's me.
Last year.
You're...
you're ageing.
If this keeps happening, I'll
be dead in a few months.
How old are you, Griffin?
I'm 18.
Look.
I'm sorry this is happening to you.
But there's nothing I can do to fix it.
Well, that sucks.
'Cause if you can't figure out
a way to help me, Dr. Wells...
You're gonna die soon, too.
I never should have left.
No, this isn't your fault.
Do we know what took him?
That's where things get interesting.
That fingerprint that
you guys brought in,
the one from the van, I mean.
Yeah, yeah.
Belongs to this guy.
Griffin Grey.
A senior at Central City High School?
No, wait, I've seen this
kid's picture before.
He went missing, like, six months ago.
That's right.
That doesn't make any sense.
An 18-year-old didn't kidnap Wells.
That's what I thought at first,
but feast your eyes on this.
It's the same guy.
Yeah, the blood sample confirms it.
How is that even possible?
I'm not sure yet.
Without Caitlin here, I can't
really analyze the cells
on a molecular level to see
what we're dealing with here.
You know, I might
actually be able to help.
How?
Bio-chem was one of
my majors in college.
One of your majors?
How many did you have?
Five.
What, is that not common here?
Girl, no, that is not common anywhere.
All right, let's search for that Grey,
see what we come up with.
I'll see if facial
recognition brings him up
and I'll have Joe check CCPD's database.
Cool.
See what you can do.
I'm going as fast as I can.
Well, you better go faster.
Zoom will be back any minute.
I could just leave you
in there, you know.
But you want to go home so badly.
So how did this happen to you?
Woke up one day, cold, pale.
Thought I was sick.
Turns out it was
something else entirely.
You got hit by the dark matter from
the particle accelerator explosion?
Yes.
Right after I flunked out of med school.
Had to move back in with my mother.
That couldn't have been fun.
If she's anything like mine, I mean.
Why?
Is yours a frigid narcnasist, too?
Cold as ice.
Yeah.
Mom was like that ever
since Charlie died.
Who's Charlie?
My brother.
- I never had a brother.
- No?
Then why was Mom such a
bitch on your Earth?
Honestly, I couldn't say.
So...
how is this going to get me out of here?
The electrical current in
the cable should heat up
the carbine, which in turn
should speed up the electrons
and the faster they go...
The weaker its molecular
structure becomes.
Exactly.
I studied every once in a while.
Well, when it gets hot enough,
it should make the carbine
as fragile as glass.
And then we can both get out of here.
- Wally.
- Hey, Joe.
What's up?
You look like you got
something on your mind.
Yeah, I do.
Please don't tell me you
drove all the way over here
to ask about The Flash again.
It's...
it's not happening, Wally.
But... it's just one time.
That's all I'm asking.
It's impossible.
He saved my life, Joe.
I owe him a thank you.
Look.
I've been reckless my whole life.
Racing cars, pushing limits.
I did everything at full speed
without a care in the world.
But it wasn't until Zoom took me that...
that I really thought I was gonna die.
And I was going to die,
if The Flash didn't do what he did.
He gave up his powers to save me.
A guy he didn't even know.
No one's ever done anything
like that for me before.
I need to tell him how
much that means to me.
Well, all right.
Just give me a little while.
I'll see what I can do.
I got to go.
Hey, Dad.
Thanks.
- Yo!
- In here.
I got your text. What's up?
All right, facial recognition
just picked up Grey breaking into
Ace Chemical down on Newbury Road.
- Is my dad with him?
- I don't know yet.
- But we have to go.
- You sure about that?
Yeah, I'm sure. Look...
we can't just sit here.
Regardless of whether I
have my speed or not,
I have to try to help.
That's never gonna change.
Okay. I'm with you, but we're
gonna need some backup.
- Joe's on his way.
- I'm coming with.
No, look, please just stay here.
We don't know what we're
dealing with yet.
Just finish running the
test on the blood sample.
I'm sorry. Thank you, Jesse.
-T-U-(SUB)-TITU-LO-.-CO.-M
Griffin Grey, CCPD!
Stay right there.
The man that you
kidnapped, Harrison Wells,
you need to let him go.
I can't do that. Not yet.
Then we'll have to do this the hard way.
I guess so.
Okay, He-Man's got some power.
And accuracy.
All right, keep him distracted, okay?
What?
Barry! Barry!
I can do this all night.
We just want Wells. Just let him go.
Not until I'm done with him!
Too slow.
- Barry!
- Hey.
Oh, I think I need some
medical attention.
So his genes have actually mutated.
I ran the DNA from the
blood sample Barry found,
and the functional myostatin in
his cells is essentially gone.
I mean, giving him super-strength.
Guys, there's something else.
I saw him age.
Right in front of me.
He's suffering from oxidated stress.
It means the protein in the DNA in
his body are being ravaged by oxidants.
So, what, he needs to up
his blueberry intake?
No, it means... the
more he exerts himself,
the faster he ages.
So if we can get him to
exert too much energy...
Then he'll become old and weak.
And how do you think
we're gonna do that?
I can't watch you be a human punching
bag until he turns into Grandpa Simpson.
I think we can fix that.
Jesse, I'm gonna need some of
that quick thinking of yours.
Iris.
I got to get back to the station.
You okay?
No, not really.
You know, you were the first
person I saved after I got my powers?
We were out on a walk
and we were talking about Eddie
and how you were with him,
and I was thinking to myself
how I missed a lot while
I was in that coma.
And then all of a sudden,
those cars came at us.
And it was like the world froze.
Like... you and I were the only
two people in the world.
I didn't even know what I could do yet,
but I knew that I could save you.
And I did.
And now, I don't know.
I don't...
I just don't even know who I am anymore
or who I'm supposed to be.
Barry, you're supposed to be the
same guy that you've always been.
Suit or no suit...
that guy is a hero.
That's everything you asked for.
How do you sleep at night?
Knowing you've destroyed
so many people's lives?
I don't.
Do you have anyone in your
life that you care about?
I have a daughter.
I used to have someone in
my life that I cared about.
My girlfriend, Jenny.
We were gonna get married,
have kids someday.
But after I got hit by that wave
from the particle accelerator,
all my dreams ended.
You know, I see her sometimes,
walking down the street.
She doesn't even recognize me.
But why would she?
I look as old as her dad.
- You robbed me of her.
- Griffin.
Stop talking.
So I can concentrate.
Wake up, man.
This city is screwed up because of you.
It was quiet and normal.
10000000
Z!@  ~   Am@n   :-  S2-19:Back to Normal
10000000000000000
Z!@ ~ Am@n
Until you rode in on your high horse,
talking about science and
changing the future.
You didn't stop to think about
what your particle accelerator
could do to others. You
only thought about
what it could do for you.
Enough!
Enough.
I hope it was worth it.
Doc.
Stay away from the wall.
Let's give it a whirl.
The Flash visits T=U=SUB(T.ITU)LO.(C.O.M)
Well...
looks like you have a little
badass in you, after all.
What are we gonna do about this guy?
Oh, Caity.
I don't think he's ever going home.
And neither are you.
What are you doing? I
thought we had a deal.
Is everyone on your Earth this gullible?
Heels aren't the best on ice, are they?
You know, once I saw you,
I realized why Zoom didn't kill me.
Because I look just like you.
Now he won't need me anymore.
No.
I don't.
Try that with him...
he dies, too.
Not picking up anything
from facial recognition.
The only cellular dead zone I
can find is the one in here.
No offense.
No, wait a second, was he wearing
his watch when he left to get me?
Already tried that. GPS isn't working.
Okay, no, but the meta-human
activity would be.
I mean, the watch is designed
to track metas, right?
And since Griffin Grey is one,
it'll keep sending a message
to a server till it goes through.
But since we're on a different
Earth, it'll never go through.
So it just keeps sending
the same signal.
DEVICE LOCATION
There he is, Central
City Amusement Park.
Yeah, and I'm coming with this time.
Okay, great, we've found Harry,
but how are we gonna stop Grey?
I'm so glad that you asked.
Jesse and I upgraded the
internal lining of the suit.
Felicity hooked us up with
some dwarfstar alloy.
Wait, dwarfstar alloy?
It's the same compound that's used
to protect Ray's A.T.O.M. suit.
That's right.
Super strong, super lightweight.
Only thing is, we
couldn't get much of it.
All right, what does that mean?
We could only cover the
chest portion of the suit.
Yeah, sorry.
Here's the other thing...
probably not a big deal...
I'm guessing the suit
will only absorb one of Grey's punches.
Anything more than that,
you'll be like a piñata.
Only it won't be candy
coming out, it'll be...
- Me.
- You're... yeah, you.
Yeah.
All right.
Hopefully, one gimme
punch is all I'll need.
Finished.
This is gonna cure me?
As we say in science, I'm
cautiously optimistic.
You know, I learned a
lot about chemistry
in the past two years.
Is that right?
And I know all you've been doing
is diluting that compound
for the past half hour.
You don't know how to help me, do you?
There is no helping you.
I told you you were gonna
fix me or you were dead!
Created by (TuSub)(Titulo).(co)m
Why is it that bad guys always insist
on having the creepiest hideouts?
'Cause they crazy.
Right.
Hey, Barry.
Grey's headed your way.
Come on. Hey, come on.
You ready?
Okay, Iris.
On my mark.
Three...
two...
one.
Now!
That all you got, Flash?
I just want Dr. Wells.
And I wanted him to fix me.
But he can't.
So once I finish you,
I'm gonna finish him.
Freeze!
Come on!
Okay.
I think one more punch, and
we get this guy a walker.
Hey, guys, we got him.
He's over by the Ferris Wheel.
Look.
We can help you.
It's too late for that.
Not everyone got the
powers you did, Flash.
Some of us weren't so lucky.
That was the gimme.
Griffin.
Please stop.
I might be getting older,
but I'm stronger than ever.
Barry!
You okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Could've used more of
that dwarfstar alloy.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Home sweet home.
Yeah, well...
to be honest, it hasn't felt
much like a home in a while.
At least, certainly not since you left.
Yeah.
Look, I'm sorry, Dad, for
just leaving like that.
But...
I mean, you have to understand,
I'm the reason you killed that man.
And that's a really
heavy burden to bear.
I know.
I know... I also know
that what I've done,
it's unforgivable.
When you're mother died, honey...
something inside me broke.
I couldn't protect her.
And I swore... I swore
on her grave, no less,
that I would protect you,
and then Zoom took you,
and I snapped.
I just snapped.
I couldn't breathe, I...
I couldn't lose the only other person
that I love.
Yeah. Yeah, I get that.
I understand why you did everything
you did to protect me.
I mean, you were only missing one day,
and I would have done
anything to find you.
But, I mean...
I need to know that that's
never gonna happen again.
Okay?
Every time I stay out
late or get in trouble,
you can't track me down or hurt someone
'cause you're trying to save me.
Yeah, but you're in danger.
- I know.
- Okay.
I will make you a promise.
I promise you, I will be the kind
of father that you will be proud of.
If you promise me you will
never run away from me again.
Okay.
Okay, deal.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, too.
My little Jesse Quick.
Relax, he'll be here.
What should I say?
I don't even know where to start.
Just be honest.
Speak from your heart.
Okay.
Wally West.
I'll see you at home.
You wanted to see me.
Yes. I did.
I mean, I... I do.
I just wanted to thank
you for saving my life.
And I know that that came
at a huge price for you.
And I don't know how
I'll ever repay that.
I guess, what I wanted
to say was that...
I'm not gonna waste this chance
that you've given me.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Wally.
You okay?
Stay away from me.
Killer Frost tried to kill you, Caitlin.
I saved your life.
You should thank me.
I just want to go home.
No.
Stay.
I want to leave!
Stay, boy!
No!
Please.
Take me back to my Earth.
You know...
I've always measured my success
by counting the number
of victims I've had.
But now I think I'm going
to widen my scope.
Start counting the number of
Earths I conquer, instead.
You want to go home?
Let's go.
After all, this Earth has already
been brought to its knees.
-IS NOT OVER YET-
You're here early.
Yeah.
- I couldn't sleep.
- Me neither.
I know that we just took down
Grey without my powers, but...
I have no idea how to get
Caitlin back without them.
We can't, Allen.
Then what are we gonna do?
You know, Grey...
Grey kidnapped me because
he thought I was the Harrison
Wells from this Earth,
and I know he was talking
about another guy,
but I just...
I can't help but think...
I still haven't paid for what I've done.
What does that mean?
I thought, you know, when you...
when we closed the breaches,
I could just forget about
everything I've done,
but I can't.
I realize what I can do.
You are gonna get your
speed back, Allen.
And I'm gonna help you do that.
How?
By creating another particle
accelerator explosion.