Previously, on "Arrow"...
You have but two choices-- ascend to the calling of Ra's Al Ghul,
or you will spend the rest of your days in a cage.
I love you.
Lance knows.
The whole city knows, Oliver.
Mr. Queen should be considered armed and highly dangerous.
Captain Lance...
I'm here to turn myself in.
What the hell are your men doing?
I told them to stand down.
Get down on the ground!
You've got the wrong guy. Oliver Queen isn't the Arrow.
I am.
To repeat, we're just getting word
from the authorities that Roy Harper,
a Glades resident with a long history of run-ins with the police,
has been identified as the vigilante known as the Arrow...
What the hell was that?
Probably just a power surge.
That wasn't a power surge. Check it out.
There were earlier reports implicating Oliver Queen,
now appear...
transported to SCPD by police caravan,
and should be arriving imminently.
We're now going live to the SCPD.
All right, let's go. Get him, come on.
All right, bring him, come on, come on.
Is it safe to assume you're calling off the manhunt for Queen?
No comment. Come on, bring him through.
You proud of yourself? Letting the kid take the fall?
I'm not going to let him do that.
Give me a pen and paper, I will sign a full confession.
Oliver, not another word. Uncuff him.
Sure, in 25 to life.
More like right now. Habeas writ.
The district attorney's office
won't be pursuing charges against Oliver Queen
while it's charging Roy Harper with the same crime.
Nice try. Five hours ago, Queen turned himself in.
He confessed!
To you, alone and uncorroborated.
And then the Arrow turned himself in.
Your so-called confession
is looking rather fabricated right about now.
That's just crap.
The D.A. is ordering Oliver to be released.
Are you the only one
who's allowed to put themselves above the law?
This isn't over.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm just making sure you both don't end up in prison.
What are you doing here?
Proofing the quarterly earnings report.
And finalizing the subsonic ionizer patent application,
and I'm trying to debug the sequential--
I mean, what are you doing here?
Oliver and Roy Harper are both in handcuffs.
I have a lot of work to do.
And Oliver was released.
How do you know about Roy Harper?
Apart from it being plastered all over the television,
I'm able to put one and one together,
and I get that Oliver's sister's boyfriend
is obviously part of your team.
Obviously.
- You ok? - Yes.
How are you?
Pss, yeah.
Let's--let's not get into that.
I said "I love you,"
but it was like, heh, it was like with a lowercase "L,"
you know, not, so let's not make it a thing.
You know, you had just saved my life,
I had 6.2 billion nano-robots coursing through my epithalamus,
and my emotions were a little all over the place.
Well, I'll let you get back to work-slash-worry,
and...
keep a good thought for Roy.
OK.
What were you thinking,
Roy?
Tell me why.
Do you remember what I told you
when I found out you were the Arrow?
Yeah. You told me I saved your life.
Now I get to save yours.
I can't let you do that.
Oliver, ever since I found out
that I killed that cop,
I have been trying to make it right as Arsenal.
But maybe what I need to do is make it right as the Arrow.
- No, Roy... - I killed a police officer.
Mirakuru or not, I should be punished for that.
I should be in prison.
That won't bring the officer back.
This city still needs you.
It needs you more.
For the first time since I remember what I did...
I'm OK.
You sure this place is safe?
Safe as I can manage.
Who's that?
Someone eager to repay a debt.
OK, but for how long?
Waller has men all over Hong Kong looking for us.
Even if we could make it out of the city,
there's nowhere we could run where Waller won't find us.
So, what are we going to do?
I'm going to find Waller first.
You're going to break into A.R.G.U.S. by yourself?
No.
He's going to walk in.
My passcard to the Field Office.
What do you want?
Setting Harper up as your patsy. I applaud the gamble--
I had nothing to do with Roy turning himself in...
But I will get him out.
And then what? Ra's won't stop
until you're wearing the demon's head ring on your hand.
It's not going to happen.
People are being murdered.
Your days as the Arrow are finished.
But of course, no one close to you has died.
Have you considered that leading the League of Assassins
might be a preferable outcome as to what alternatives
Ra's might devise?
I have a lot of work to do.
I'm going to break Roy out of prison.
Ironically, before turning to vigilantism,
Harper was a career criminal,
with an arrest record for breaking and entering,
petty theft, and grand larceny. Until recently--
Thea...
Please tell me it wasn't you that put him up to this.
Of course not, but I'm going to do
everything in my power to make it right.
- Are you OK? - I'm fine,
but we need to get Roy out of prison.
Well, it looks like we might have another problem
to add to our ever-growing list.
...multiple homicide at Starling National Bank.
Channel 52 has acquired surveillance footage of the incident...
Makes sense. As a bank-robbing meta-human,
why stay in Central City
when you have plenty of banks and no Arrow?
OK. OK, we need a plan
to extract Roy. In the meantime,
Felicity, call S.T.A.R. Labs,
see if they're tracking
any meta-humans that have left Central City.
SCPD. According to city records,
you got a basement down here.
You already have Roy Harper in custody.
Yeah, and I got a warrant that says
I can search that basement.
Sorry for the rush,
but I didn't want to give you a chance to turn that place
into a storage room again.
Gentlemen.
Here you go. Break it down.
I got you now, you son of a bitch.
Oh, my Chinese is a little rusty,
but this looks like a crate from the north China sea.
You've spent some time there, right?
And this is my favorite.
You actually put those things on display?
Captain, we have fingerprint matches
for the latents we lifted off all this equipment.
Hold that thought.
What do you got?
We only got one match.
What is it?
- Roy Harper. - Roy...
Just...
Did you check the other computers?
Captain Lance, it's clear--
Shut up! Whatever line of crap you're thinking about giving me,
you just save it.
Smart as you all are,
you are bound to make a mistake eventually.
And I'm going to be there when it happens.
You wiped the entire place?
And moved some of your more sensitive trunk items.
You're welcome.
But you didn't wipe Roy's prints.
Oliver, Roy already confessed.
We didn't see any point in losing both of you.
I'm not losing... Roy.
What about that meta-human that is out there killing people?
We need to grab my back-up weapons cache in the secondary layer.
You see those plainclothes?
Lance will have them follow you everywhere you go.
You try to nab even so much as a purse snatcher,
and they'll pounce.
Somebody needs to protect this city.
We are dealing with a meta-human.
Call Barry.
Oh, he can't help right now, mm-mmm.
He's got on a lot on his plate with Dr. Wells, I think.
It's really hard to keep up with him.
But...what if there's someone else that could help?
Oh, hey, Felicity, check this out.
I finally got the neural network online,
so when my brain tells the gauntlet to wave, and...
Sorry to hear about what's happening to you.
Uh, if there's anything I can do to help...
Well, actually, that's why we're here.
You know how I try to keep my work life
and my other work life separate.
I meant to tell you that. Did I tell you that?
- Well, there's a-- - There's a meta
in Starling City that's killing people.
- A meta, as in human? - Yeah.
So, obviously we need to catch
this plasma death thing guy.
Ugh, now I see
why Cisco gives them all names.
The police are all over Oliver,
so...we need you.
And you're ok with this?
We need your help.
So it's a team up. High-five!
- Don't shoot! - What the hell is going on?
They've been holding me here for weeks.
What, you don't trust me?
Look at him.
He's army, not A.R.G.U.S.
Oh, so you're saying this is General Shrieve?
He held me hostage.
Targeted you and the Yamashiros, for death.
Why would he do that?
The Alpha Omega.
Shrieve plans to unleash it on Hong Kong,
Claiming that the Triad mishandled
a bio weapon they never should have had.
That's insane.
Well, Shrieve seems to think that
China is a military and economic threat.
So he'd kill himself and his men
just to hurt China?
His team has developed a vaccine
they can inoculate themselves with.
Run.
Get as far away from Hong Kong as you can.
If you make it...
I hope we meet again someday.
Now go!
How are you?
I told the guards I didn't want to see you.
Why?
Roy, please.
Tell me what is going on.
When we got back together,
hell, even before that, I...
I made a promise to myself
that I would never lie to you again.
Ok.
That's why I didn't want to see you.
I don't want to break that promise.
Why would you?
- Roy! - Thea...
Thea, please just...
know that I'm going to be fine.
Is that a lie?
Thea, don't worry.
Roy's not going to be in there much longer.
I'm working on it.
Bye.
- Roy holding up? - For now.
Hot off the presses.
What are those?
I visited the bank today.
Uh, manager's a friend of mine.
I beat him at squash every Tuesday.
And I took a few photos of the crime scene.
Actually, "Photos" is a bit reductive.
These are enhanced resonance scans.
It occurred to me that if we can't see his face
because of the radiation,
we need to remove the radiation.
Oh, I could kiss you right now. Awkward, sorry.
Boundaries. We're working on it.
So, if we interlace the resonant scan's frequency
with our news footage, we get this.
- There he is. - Run a facial recognition.
Way ahead of you. Jake Simmons.
He's already in the system.
Serial bank robber, which explains Starling National.
Last known address,
- Central City. - Where is he now?
He was last seen on a traffic camera
at the corner of Gantner and Yount.
There's a processing plant there;
- He went in, never came out. - On it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, hold on a second.
I thought the whole point of this team-up
was you not being spotted out as a vigilante.
Stop calling it a team-up, Ray.
This Jake Simmons is not just a meta-human,
he is a killer. And you're not ready for that.
Look, I'm-- I'm not going to try to equate our experiences,
but superpowers are based in science,
and I am a man of science.
So if there's any way to defeat this guy,
I'm the one who's best able to figure it out.
Fine.
The second that you get in over your head...
I'll run.
Fly, probably.
How many abandoned warehouses do you think are in this city?
No, no, I'm -- I'm genuinely curious.
Stay focused, Ray.
Maybe Simmons isn't in there.
Do you get this anxious when I'm out in the field?
I honestly can't think of an answer to that question
that doesn't get me in trouble.
Still nothing.
Not a visual sighting or any other reading at all from the ATOM.
And when I say ATOM, I mean the suit,
not myself in the third person.
There's a decent chance that you and Palmer are related.
Well, that's equally fascinating
and terrifying.
Be my eyes, Ray, what's going on?
Oh, tin man? You shouldn't be here.
Actually, I should. See, you're the bad guy,
and I am--
Ray?!
Thanks for the top off.
Ray!
Ray, ray!
Oh, my God, ray, are you hurt?
Heh, "Hurt" would be a step or two up
from how I feel right now.
But... just a second.
You're lucky to have gotten out of there alive.
It wasn't that bad, was it?
It was way worse, Ray.
Right. I need shields!
That's not the answer. You need to anticipate your opponent.
You need to trust your instincts
and not just your tech.
My instinct is to trust my tech.
Ray, when I'm out in the field, my bow, my arrows,
those are just tools.
- I'm the weapon. - That's poetic.
My point is that if you rely on that suit
more than you rely on yourself...
it's going to get you killed.
So when is Shrieve going to distribute the virus?
- I don't know. - If he's going to pin it on the Triad, though,
he'll have to do it soon.
We need to get out of Hong Kong.
My contact says Shrieve has men everywhere,
with even more resources at his disposal than Waller ever had.
Shrieve has assured we won't get off this island alive.
Well, if we can't run, Waller said
Shrieve had a vaccine for the virus.
You want to steal some of the vaccine?
He has to have it somewhere in Hong Kong.
Get down!
Let's see how good you are without your arrows.
Good enough.
Just remember... that was without arrows.
Get down, on the floor!
All right, turn this place inside out.
We know how this guy loves his secret hiding places.
Hey, Frank.
What brings you out of your downtown office?
The chief of D's asked me to have a word with you.
Yeah? What about?
He wants to know why you're still going ahab
on Oliver Queen when we got
a different suspect already in custody.
We got a patsy in custody.
Trust me, Queen is our guy.
Well, there's no evidence against Queen.
Why do you think I'm searching his condo?
Friend to friend...
You've come so far. You're a Captain.
Don't throw all your hard work away on something personal.
Look, I don't know what it is
you think that you're going to find,
but it's not here. There's nothing here!
Kind of like how there was nothing in the basement of your club?
You're either complicit
or just about the most naive girl I ever met.
You know that your brother is letting your boyfriend
rot in prison for his crimes, right?
Get out of my home.
I know you went to visit Harper yesterday.
Does he even know why he's throwing his life away?
Lance.
Is he all right?
All right, I'll be right there.
Your boyfriend was just attacked.
He's all right, but I can't imagine it'll be the last time.
Your brother dropped a lot of bodies.
And when, and it's not if,
it is when Roy gets a shiv in the back,
that body will be on him, too.
The suit recorded over ten terabytes of data,
which were uploaded in real time
to a geosynchronous satellite.
That is a huge energy suck.
This is all fascinating.
- How do we find Simmons? - Light bulb, literally.
I--no, actually, figuratively.
Uh, just before Simmons beat me,
I blasted him with my compressed light beams,
and he thanked me for topping him off.
He absorbs energy and turns it into weaponized plasma.
And if we can manually get into the city's power grid,
we might be able to track where he's getting his extra juice.
Ollie!
What's going on?
It's Roy!
He was attacked by a bunch of inmates.
He's fine, but there's hundreds of them in there!
I'm going to break him out.
Oliver. You can end up in a cell right next to him.
John, if you know what's good for you,
you'll get out of my way.
Oliver, if you know what's good for you,
and for Roy-- you're going to need to stay put.
- I can't do that. - Oliver, listen...
Get your hands off of me!
Listen, I know what you're going through, man!
You have to rely on Palmer to take care of this meta
while Roy sits in a prison.
But listen to me, man, you have to throttle this back,
Oliver. You have to.
Before you lose everything.
I've already lost everything.
I'm not going to lose Roy.
Oliver!
I can't believe that you and Diggle are ok
just sitting on your hands while Roy fights off
- all of Iron Heights! - It is not that simple!
No, Felicity, if anything was ever simple,
it's this.
Then what? You're going to jail, too?
I can't just do nothing.
I think John's right.
I think you're struggling with doing nothing
with Roy, with Ray, but right now,
you need people to help you. You need to let them.
Maybe...there is something more
going on with you than just what's happening with Roy
and this meta-human.
You have sacrificed everything to be the Arrow.
Even you and me.
But...
whether or not you break Roy out of Iron Heights,
there is no more Arrow.
Ra's took that from you.
I was told once that a man
cannot live by two names.
Well, right now,
I can't live by either.
So I don't know who I am.
I know who you are.
Whether you're in a... in a suit
or under a hood, you're the man that I...
you're the man that I believe in.
Ray finished the transponder.
I have to upload it to a power source
and, hopefully it'll bring us right to Simmons.
- I'll go with you. - It is adorable
how you keep forgetting that Lance is after you,
but, it's a quick errand
and you need practice in letting people help you.
You sure this is it?
It doesn't look like a typical army base.
Matthew Shrieve isn't a typical army general, apparently.
Quiet!
Where's the vaccine?
You can end up unconscious
or you can end up dead.
Two lefts,
second door on your right.
Good choice.
Somebody coming.
10 seconds.
Up there.
Thank you.
Can you give us a minute?
I already signed my confession.
Yeah, it's a hell of a story.
All that stuff about setting up shop
under your girlfriend's club.
And I particularly like how you managed not to implicate her.
What are you doing here?
You remember that,
that corpse I showed you?
The one that the Arrow killed?
I knew you had an obsession with the Arrow.
And, I was trying to wave you off
'cause I knew, just somehow I knew,
that if you stayed obsessed with him,
that you would come to a bad end.
And here I am.
Two years later, I'm still trying to save you, son.
I don't need saving.
Look, I know you got to be doing
this 'cause you think you owe Queen something.
But you don't. You don't deserve to be here.
Patrol Officer Gabe Vincent
left behind a wife and a nine-year-old boy.
I know.
I killed him.
I stabbed him in the chest with an arrow.
So don't think for a second that I don't deserve to be here.
No. You don't think for a second
that what you're doing here
makes up for any of what you did out there.
Guard.
We have take off.
I'm sorry, miss,
but I don't think you're supposed to be here.
I'm supposed to access your grid for the city.
Think you can help?
Sure. It's this way.
Thank you.
So,
what's with the sunglasses, man?
We're indoors and it's, well, night.
- Do you have a sensitivity to the... -To light?
No.
I love the light.
Do you think the plan to find Simmons will work?
Well, it's Felicity, so, yes.
Except the tracking firmware seems to be malfunctioning.
What?
It's not a malfunction.
It's Simmons. He's drawing energy
- directly from a power station. - Which one?
The one Felicity just went to.
Come on, Felicity, pick up.
I'm sorry, but the blonde can't come to the phone at the moment.
I swear to God, if you hurt her...
You'll what... fly away again?
I am talking to the man in the suit,
right? The one who thinks a piece of scrap metal
makes him some kind of hero?
It doesn't.
I am sorry for the interruption.
Where were we?
Waiting for you to come closer.
- Oliver, you can't go out there. - It's Felicity!
Oliver, you won't make it in time.
Power station is still eight minutes away
going 60 on the Ducati.
But the Atom? Well, the Atom can fly.
You need more than your tech this time!
You're right.
My tech and your instinct,
maybe there's a way we can get him.
Ok, I'm entering the power station now.
Activate the link.
It's working! Oh, I'm just a passenger now.
Ooh. Let's get this guy.
Sorry.
But I have to kill you now.
No, and you're going to leave her the hell alone.
Kick his ass.
You ok?
You got to get out of here!
No! I'm not going to leave you here alone.
Ray, get her out of there!
I'm not alone, but I can't fight him
and worry about you, now, go, Felicity!
- No! - Felicity, go!
Get out of here!
I'm really hoping you played video games as a kid.
- I'm trying to concentrate. - Sorry, sorry,
It's just, I'm trusting you with my--
Ray, can you take this beating? I can pull you back.
I'm fine. Get this bastard!
Ray, I've lost control.
The transmitter's been severed.
Get up.
Get up, Ray!
Fight back, Ray, fight back! Ray!
He's too strong!
This is not about strength.
This is about heart.
When the mayor was killed,
you put yourself in harm's way to save Felicity.
Normal people, they don't do that.
Heroes do that.
Come on, Ray!
Take him out, Ray.
Oh, I'm sorry, sorry!
No, it was totally worth it.
Are you ok? I was so worried.
I'm fine. Everything's ok now.
Eyes front, Harper.
I told you, eyes front.
My instincts are to keep my head on a swivel.
Won't happen again.
No, it won't.
Thea?
It's Roy.
Harper was killed an hour ago.
I'd say I'm sorry, but I think we both know
whose fault this is.
I shouldn't have listened to either of you.
I might not have been able to save Roy...
but I'd feel better right now if I tried.
We know that, Oliver.
We also know you may never forgive us.
I make my own choices, John.
I made this one.
He doesn't mean forgive us for that.
He means...
forgive us for this.
How?
Don't be mad at them. This was my idea.
If any one of us were in there and Oliver was here,
- He would think of something. - You're right.
If one of us deserves to go to prison, it's me.
Roy, we can't allow you to do that.
There's no way in hell Oliver's going along with it.
That's why you're not going to tell him.
You could have gotten yourself killed for real.
I figured that I could hold off
until Dig's guys got into position.
One of Lyla's contacts,
an A.R.G.U.S. freelancer.
Has a special talent for knifing people in just the right way.
Leaves a convincing amount of blood without the kill.
He laces the blade with a beta blocker, crawl the heartbeat.
Gives the illusion of death.
Everyone thinks the Arrow is dead.
Which means Oliver Queen is innocent.
You did all this without asking.
How many times have you saved one of us without asking?
This time we had to save you.
If everyone thinks you're dead...
then what happens to Roy Harper?
Tell Thea, well, tell her I'm alive, first.
Then tell her that
I'm sorry I had to leave without saying good-bye.
I feel like you're throwing your life away.
I'm not.
I'm starting a new one.
Anywhere, any time.
You need something, you call me.
Take care of yourself, Roy.
I'll miss you most of all, scarecrow.
Just be ready to get a million calls
on that untraceable satellite phone
I stuffed in your bag.
Thank you.
So, on a scale of one to ten,
how... mad at us are you?
I need to learn to let people help me.
You could use the practice in that.
I just think sometimes you're so focused
on people you love, you forget...
to see that there are people who love you.
Just enough inoculant for us.
And Akio.
What about her?
We need to inject Akio and ourselves
and then the three of you need to get somewhere safe.
And what about you?
I lifted this when I took the vaccine.
And clearly, it belongs to one of Shrieve's men,
because it has the plans
for how they are going to distribute the virus.
I'm going to use it to stop them.
No. You won't.
- We are. - Tatsu!
What example are we setting for our son
if we have a hope to save millions of innocent people,
- but only save ourselves? - Listen to me--
The two of you need to take care of Akio.
I am not going to be responsible--
You need to learn to let people help you.
And Maseo and I are going to.
What about...
Deathbolt.
Nice!
You know, you're the only other person
who's good at the names.
So, how do they get fed?
And, you know, complete the transaction,
so to speak?
Cisco?
You said Simmons is from Central City, right?
Yeah. Last known address,
4160 Dixie Canyon. Why?
According to this, Jake Simmons was a guest
of the Opal City Police Department on December 11th, 2013.
What do I know that date from?
That was the date of the particle accelerator test.
But if Simmons wasn't in Central City
the night of the dark matter explosion, then...
how can he be a meta-human?
Do you know who I am, child?
You're the demon.
I am the demon's head.
As those were before me,
and very soon, your brother.
He will never take your place.
He will.
Once I've given him sufficient motivation.
Oh, my brother's going to kill you!
No.
He's going to beg me.