YYeTs.com
My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home with only one goal--
to save my city.
Now others have joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
To the rest of starling city,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
There's a lot of good people, they lose someone,
they lose themselves,
which is why they come in here to work off that rage.
Roy, are you ok? You look a little tired.
I just haven't been sleeping much lately.
If I had accepted my life, I would be a cocktail waitress
in Vegas like my mother,
and I never would have believed some crazy guy in a hood
when he told me I could be more than just some IT girl.
You're not moving very quickly this morning.
I just didn't sleep much last night.
You're not boxing, girl.
You're not even fighting.
You're just lashing out. Come on!
Impressive.
How do normal people spend their morning?
Eight, nine...
Come on, ladies, we are almost there...
And ten.
- Five. - Good, very good.
Yes!
Mrs. Fernandes!
I already told you, I haven't seen
your...cat.
I haven't seen him, either.
Or is the cat a girl?
Was I being misogynist just now?
Or is it misogynistic? I never know.
Ray...what are you--
Nice place you've got here. Lots of space.
So it occurred to me this morning,
What's the one thing that Queen Consolidated has
that we don't use to its maximum potential?
A doorbell?
Have you heard of a process called cogeneration?
I haven't even looked at a cup of coffee yet.
- Well, cogeneration is-- - The repurposing
of waste heat given off by electricity production.
Exactly. It's a principle of thermodynamic efficiency,
which occurred to me could be applied to a building
which generates over 240,000 watts of electricity.
Like Queen Consolidated.
I did some preliminary calculations on the drive over.
You want to sell QC's excess energy back to the city?
If by "Sell" you mean "give away for free," then yes.
Energy is something that should be given freely to the masses.
Uh, you still haven't found Mrs. Fernandes' cat, I'm guessing.
Oh, my beautiful girl!
Very friendly with your neighbors, I see.
- Mom... - Mom?
What are you doing here?
Honey, I came to see you.
For a visit. Look, look, look.
Didn't you get my text?
Mom, to send a text, you actually have
to press "Send" on the text.
Oh, ok, not a big deal, I'll do it right now.
Are you adopted?
Oh! I'm so sorry. I didn't know you had somebody staying over.
Oh, no, he's not staying over.
He's not, like,
we're not-- this is my boss.
It's a pleasure to meet you, Miss Smoak.
Hi. You can call me Donna.
- Mom... - I'm Ray.
Oh, my god. Palmer?
You're that watch guy.
We like to call them smart wearables.
I bought one of your watches! Look!
See? Felicity here thinks I don't
pay attention to all of her tech-y things.
Yeah, I see you've got a 3GS.
I'm actually wearing a prototype for the new six.
Yeah, it basically replaces your computer.
- Very fancy. - You know what? It's yours.
Oh, no. Seriously?
I'll let you two catch up.
Let me know what you think about those cogeneration numbers,
and Donna, hope to see you again soon.
Well, don't count on it. She'll probably be really busy...
planning my funeral after I die of embarrassment.
"You are standing in an open field
"west of the White House
with a boarded front door."
What are you doing?
I just finished coding a Linux emulator for Zork.
"It is pitch black.
"You are likely to be eaten... by a grue."
I guess you'll have to protect me.
Why can't you just quietly have sex under a comforter
like most college students?
You found an exploitable note?
Now I just need your super computer virus to crack the firewall.
I really wish you wouldn't call my X-axis bi-numeric algorithm
a "Super-virus."
Spoofing the IP, switching to MD6, and...
Somebody take a screenshot. We have to post this to hackerforum,
to brag that we actually got in!
Hold on. 30 seconds until the firewall goes back up.
Cooper, what are you doing?
I think the world would be a much better place
if there weren't any student loans, don't you?
You can't wipe out all the loans,
they'll never think it's a glitch.
They're going to track us down and find us!
- 10 seconds. - Cooper!
I'm not going to jail for you, Cooper,
and you shouldn't, either.
Coop!
- I almost had it! - What were you thinking?!
Ever heard of hacktivisim?
Instead of posting to web forums,
we could be doing some real good in the world.
And going to prison in the process.
It's all about what you want to be when you grow up, babe,
a hacker, or a hero?
Hello?
Speedy?
Just signed the lease.
What do you think?
Thea, you're signing a lease on a spot
that you can't possibly afford.
- I can, actually. - With whose money?
Malcolm Merlyn's. His estate, I mean.
When I left Starling City, I mentioned something
to Ned Foster about Malcolm being my father,
and there's a lot of legal stuff I didn't understand, and--
He left you money?
The entire world thinks he's dead.
So, yes, legally, his estate
goes to his last living heir.
And last week when you told me
that you had investors for the club, that was a lie?
I was afraid you wouldn't react well
to the idea of me taking his money.
It's blood money, Thea!
You don't know what Malcolm Merlyn is capable of!
I know what his money is capable of,
renting me this really sweet loft.
Listen to me. He's alive,
and if you take his money, he has a hold on you.
I think you're being a little melodramatic.
I'm his daughter, ok? He's not going to put me in danger.
He's responsible for the death of 503 innocent people,
including your brother.
Now that is a card that you do not get to play.
You are my brother,
but that does not mean you have the right to tell me
what I can do with my life.
I am my own person.
The movers are coming tomorrow,
so you can stop by with popcorn
or not stop by at all.
Oh, please.
What is going on?
Ollie?
You ok?
We are Brother Eye.
Judgment has been rendered against this city.
Its sentence carried out.
An earthquake. A siege.
This is what comes next,
a new life you will live on your knees,
and it will take nothing more than a push of a button.
We are in control now.
And this is just the beginning.
Let there be light.
Oh, a nightclub.
You know, I'm really not dressed for a nightclub.
- Really? - You think?
My friend owns the place. He just needs
a little help turning the power back on, so,
why don't you... come, come.
- Stay put. - Stay here?
- Right here. - Ok.
Hey. Any luck tracking this--
Hello.
Hi.
Please tell me this is your friend.
- No. Mom, this is Oliver - Queen.
Very nice to meet you.
Yes, it's so nice to meet you, too.
How many billionaires do you know?
Diggle, meet Felicity's mom.
Mom. John Diggle.
Hi. Very nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too. Oh! Hello!
Who is this little nugget?
This is my daughter Sara.
- Mom. Mom. mom! - What?
We have to go downstairs.
Oh, I'm so sorry. I didn't mean to stop you.
I'm so sorry. Little baby moment. So sorry.
It's great to meet you, finally.
Yes, yes, definitely.
Why is Sara here?
Lyla's on an assignment in Santa Prisca
and the nanny called in sick.
But we can't bring her down there.
Why not, Oliver, who's she gonna tell?
Well, she,
I'm not comfortable with her down there.
God help me.
My mother loves babies. Just...
Really?
Whoever this Brother Eye group is, somehow got access
to the city's protected network
and uploaded a system-wide virus.
Any way to trace it?
No, it deleted itself as soon as
it completed its task.
They said the power outage was just the beginning.
Then let's find them before there's a next time.
Hey, Laurel, are you all right? Did you get here ok?
I'm fine. I was close.
But why do I get the Emergency Services Alert?
Why don't they call the district attorney?
Cause he's visiting his niece in Coast City.
You are the acting district attorney. Congratulations.
Hello, detective, captain.
Look, you're on this Brother Eye thing, right?
- We are. - Good,
cause there's no one here knows computers better than you.
No, for the last time,
I am not interested in buying a fake ID.
I am hanging up now. Bye.
My mom says hi.
You still angry at me?
I was past the firewall and into the account network.
I had 3,000 debts wiped
by the time you pulled the plug on me.
Well, think of how many accounts you could go to prison for
if I hadn't stopped you.
Relax.
The DNS wasn't configured.
They can't backtrace me.
They can. The subroot was configured.
By accessing the accounts,
you set off a packets feedback that anyone could trace back to.
You are gorgeous when you're being a chicken.
- I'm serious. - I'm serious.
Cooper Seldoel that's enough! Don't move!
- You are under arrest. - What?!
No! Let go of me.
No, no, no!
- You're under arrest for violation - Cooper!
- of U.S. Code title 18, section 1030. - No. Don't!
You have the right to remain silent.
Let go of him, let him go!
We said this was just the beginning.
Electricity is not the only power in the city.
Consider money, for example.
The banks are next to go dark.
Your beloved dollars wiped away
as your accounts will finally all be equal,
at zero.
Felicity...
I'm working on it. I set up some trace IP packets
before brother eye's last broadcast.
As soon as he opened up the channel,
I scooped up the bread crumbs.
Bread crumbs we can follow?
I hope so.
Where's Captain Lance?
Coordinating squad car patrols for dispatch.
Why? What's wrong?
There's a situation at Starling National.
Send in an ESU squad.
Sorry, ma'am, but you don't have the power to--
I'm acting district attorney.
The City Charter gives me operational authority in times of crisis,
which this clearly is.
I'm not letting anyone get hurt.
Send in an ESU now.
What's going on?
SCPD just dispatched a riot squad to Starling National.
It's like fighting a fire with gasoline.
Suit up.
This group is ordered to disperse!
Get back!
Behind the line!
Oliver, the riot is getting out of control.
You need to hurry up.
Get away from the bank!
The teargas is dispersing them,
but we can't calm the entire city, Felicity.
The trace led me to the virus they're using.
It is a mile past complex.
I'm coming through now.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
What's wrong?
The virus... I can't stop it!
How do you know?
Because it's mine.
I wrote it five years ago.
Ok, ok, before you say anything,
just know that I never imagined the virus
being used for something like this.
I mean, sure, I could have imagined it.
I actually have a very vivid imagination.
Like cronuts!
I had a vision of them before--
Relax. Take a deep breath.
Good.
Now start at the beginning.
I was in this,
I guess you could call it a group,
in college.
We were "hacktivists."
For lack of a better word.
Civil disobedience via the world wide web.
I created this.
This
super virus.
That could give us root access to any infected server.
We could expose government fraud
and start virtual sit-ins
and digitally deface criminals.
I guess you could say it was my first attempt at being a hero.
Felicity.
Why didn't you tell me about any of this?
Do we even know a fraction
of what happened to you the five years that you were away?
Who else had access to the program?
Myron Forest. He was my...
I had a boyfriend in college,
And Myron was his roommate.
And he was a member of this hacktivist group?
What about the boyfriend?
Oh, he couldn't have done this.
He's...not in the picture,
but Myron always had somewhat of an edge.
Can you get me an address?
Sure.
Just one small problem--
not small, necessarily, but short.
Just take the alleyway entrance.
Are you ok?
I've been better.
I talked it over with Myron,
and I'm going to tell them I wrote the super virus.
You can't do that.
I can't let you rot in prison, Coop.
You can't tell them you wrote that virus...
cause I already told them I did.
Cooper...
I always said I'd protect you from the grues.
- This isn't-- - It's better this way.
I wiped out those loans.
There's no reason both of us should be in prison.
I love you.
Love you, too.
Hey. Got a minute?
Congratulations, you called in a riot squad,
you nearly started one! And! You did it behind my back.
You were busy,
and the situation at Starling national was escalating.
You escalated it, Laurel!
Please tell me you can at least see that now.
Ok.
I'm sorry.
Laurel, baby...
What's gotten into you?
You're angry, you're distant, you're reckless.
Tell me you're not boozing again.
No.
Then what the hell's going on? Because this isn't you.
Look, I haven't said anything
because I was hoping that you would say something,
Because you, sweetheart, you are in ten different kinds of pain,
and you won't talk about it.
I can't talk about it with you.
Ok. But listen, you don't have to talk about it with me.
But talk about it with somebody.
Cause secrets hurt, baby.
Sometimes more than the truth.
Back-up generator keeps that locked.
Or...so they told me.
I could never get that stupid door to open.
Contractor says the entire sub level is flooded, though.
It was a water main break.
What are you doing here, Ollie?
A super hacker is trying to
take over the city and I'm worried about you.
I still get to be worried, right?
Yes. And if you really have to,
you can even be judgmental--
occasionally.
Someone told me recently
that a family is pretty precious.
And love, in spite of everything,
is what makes it precious.
Right now, the Queen family is just you and me.
So let it just be you and me.
And don't take Merlyn's money.
I'm trying to meet you halfway here, Ollie.
The other half is up to you.
Myron Forest.
You have failed this city.
Tell him he has to retract all the infected packets
from subsystem mainframes within the city.
Tell me how to shut down the virus.
Do it now.
You think I'm behind the cyber attacks?
Sounds like a Brother Eye to me.
I swear to god, I'm not.
I head up the IT department of an accounting firm.
I drive a hybrid. It's blue.
I'm one of the sheep lunatics like these guys hate.
Why would I do this?
Digital fingerprints are all over this code.
There's an x-axis bionumeric algorithm.
The code's an x-axis
bionumeric algorithm that you've used before!
In college.
My roommate and his girlfriend.
Yeah, yeah, sure, we developed it.
We called it a super virus,
but that doesn't mean I'm the Eye guy!
Have you tried Felicity Smoak?
She's innocent.
Then it's got to be someone else.
After we graduated, I might have showed
the code off to a few people.
- Who were they?! - I don't remember.
It was five years ago. I didn't think it was a big deal.
We were just kids playing with matches.
I am running out of expletives!
We need to track down whoever Myron shared your code with.
I hacked all of his emails
and all his text messages from five years ago
and all I got was depressed.
Ok. What about your ex?
I already told you, he didn't do it.
Why? Because he's your ex-boyfriend?
Because...
my senior year of college,
Cooper and I did a stupid thing.
He got arrested and he went to prison.
So he went to prison. Maybe he got out.
He didn't.
How do you know?
Because he's dead.
He hung himself before sentencing.
Felicity, I...
I just really need to be alone right now.
I'm glad you're here.
When I launched my plan to rebrand
Starling into Star City,
I didn't count on cyber terrorism.
I'm looking for a partner
with whom to drown my sorrows and you
definitely look like someone who could use a drink.
I'm sorry.
My mother...
I didn't have anywhere else to go.
You ok?
You're an inventor.
Did you ever create
anything that you didn't think was important,
turns out,
it's very important?
Of course.
Those turn out to be the best inventions.
Not always.
You want to talk about it?
Of course I'd find you here.
- Could you just wait one second? - Wait?
I'm sorry; i've already waited two hours for you at your apartment,
and before that, it was two hours in the club.
Is there any way that you could be anywhere else but here?
Thanks, mom.
That wasn't the least bit mortifying.
Only half as bad as parents' week in freshman year.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I've been reduced to stalking my own daughter.
Because you can't seem to comprehend that
I can't make the whole world stop
because you decided to show up on my doorstep.
I have responsibilities!
Yes, I know, Felicity.
You have work. You have work, work, work, work.
No, no, no, you don't understand.
It is so much more than work.
But all you care about it my love life
or how much cleavage I don't show.
That is not true!
That is completely true!
And I'm sorry. I'm sorry that I'm terminally single.
I'm sorry I have an actual job.
I'm sorry that I don't dress like a porn star!
Which I realize is a compliment to you.
So I'm so sorry
that I am such a disappointment to you!
I'm not as smart as you, Felicity,
or your father.
I know that.
Even when you were only six years old,
I could barely keep up with you two.
And...
Maybe I wasn't always the mother you wanted,
but I was always there.
I stayed and I tried.
He...
he left me.
He left us.
But when I look at you,
all I see is what he gave you.
There is nothing of me...
in you.
You know, it's so funny. I was--
I was always so afraid that one day,
you were going to leave me, too.
But now I finally realize...
you already did.
There are people on the other end of this thing, right?
People we can hit?
We need Felicity.
I'm here.
The super virus has 3,407 traceable access notes.
Hopefully I didn't put a firewall in every one, though.
Of course I did, because I'm smarter than that.
Seriously, if I had two less IQ points,
we never would have gotten in this mess.
Are you all right?
- Where's your mom? - I don't know.
Probably back at my place,
wishing she had a different daughter. It's a long story.
So go see her. Take an hour.
The city is under attack.
You're our best chance of stopping it,
but not like this, Felicity.
Your head's not in the game.
I will get it together.
Your tracer hack's running.
Take an hour. Go talk to your mom.
I do not have anything to say to her.
You know, earlier today, Thea told me that
she literally has to put up with me
because family is precious.
And that it's love,
in spite of everything,
that makes it precious.
Go.
Where's Sara?
The nanny came to pick her up.
Said he was from a company called A.R.G.U.S.
I don't know, I've never heard of it.
I think that's the point.
Well, I'm glad you're still here.
You are a terrible liar, Felicity.
Might be the only thing we have in common.
I have blonde hair.
You dye it.
You're right.
We're different, and it's always going to be that way.
And it's not easy--
No, you know what, it's--
it's totally my fault for just showing up here uninvited.
Seriously. I think I just got so excited about this free flight.
What?
My plane ticket.
I got an email that said I'd won some contest.
Free first class round trip to Starling.
Email?
Mom.
Someone wanted you to be here.
Mom!
- Baby! - Mom!
- Are you ok? - I'm ok.
Oh, thank god!
Where are we?
Felicity Smoak, just the woman I wanted to see.
What the hell do you want from me?!
Who are you?
You really don't know?
I thought you'd never forget your first love.
You died.
- They told me-- - That I committed suicide, right?
The N.S.A. needed a hacker with game for cyber espionage,
and I needed to not be in prison
for the rest of my life.
Because of what the N.S.A. wanted me doing, it was...
advantageous for me to be dead.
When I found out you died,
I was devastated.
I loved you.
I loved you, too.
After I finished my time with the N.S.A.,
I was going to find you.
To let you in on this.
And then I discovered you'd become this corporate
lap dog.
Broke my heart. You changed.
If you ever thought I was capable of doing something like this,
you never really knew me at all.
When you wrote this virus, Felicity,
you knew exactly what it was capable of.
All I'm doing is unleashing the true potential
of what you made.
Why?!
This isn't who you are!
Five years with the N.S.A.,
you learn a lot about how the world works.
How we can't be saved or salvaged.
How it's every man for himself.
You also learn that when a city bank goes under,
say, financial cyber attack,
the mayor will reach out to the Treasury Department
and request an influx of fresh cash.
Cash which is transported by armored trucks.
Navigating according to a closed-end G.P.S. system,
which directs them to city deposit.
If the drivers deviate from the route,
The trucks are shut down.
But you're going to hack into the system
and direct the cash to come here.
It was about money, and I'm the sell-out?
No.
No, babe.
You're the one who's going to help me.
See, breaking into the Treasury's asymmetric encryption
is beyond even my capabilities.
I'm going to politely decline.
Don't!
That's why I flew some motivation into town for you.
She's been MIA for over an hour.
Well, you did tell her to go home.
I just had an A.R.G.U.S. agent
pick up Sara there.
I could have them go back, check things out.
Yep.
Felicity's never more than five feet from her phone.
Something's wrong.
No! No!
That terminal's configured to only connect with the Treasury's IP.
I mention this so you don't try to do anything stupid,
like alert the police.
I'm so sorry.
Mom...
right now's not really the best time, ok?
But it might be the last time, hon,
And I want you to know
that all I've ever wanted...
is for you to be happy.
Let's say we hit pause on the Dr. Phil episode.
It's done! It's done.
That quick?
There's a reason you wanted me, right?
They'll be at your front door in five minutes.
- Guards will be armed. - Let's go.
Stay put, ok?
Just because we used to screw
doesn't mean I won't use this gun.
What's that?
Huh?
Oh, that, that's the watch.
It's the watch Mr. Palmer gave me.
It chimes on the hour, and I guess we're about to be killed.
We're not going to be killed.
We're going to get out of here.
It basically replaces your computer.
You know I don't know what that means.
It means it has wifi.
Really?
When they're in range...
You know what to do.
I did what you wanted.
You don't have to kill us.
Really?
Who would have thought
that I'd become the grue?
You want to wave that gun at me, fine,
but don't you dare threaten my daughter.
Here I thought you were all nails and hair.
Try single mom who's worked 60 hour weeks in six inch heels
for tips in order to raise that genius child
you see right there.
I may not understand all this cyber whatever,
But I know without that gun,
you wouldn't last 10 seconds against my girl.
Too bad she doesn't have 10 seconds.
I disagree!
Put the gun down.
You were always good, Felicity.
So good.
But so am I.
Motion sensored.
They can hit most any target.
Come on.
Something's wrong.
Clear.
This is all your fault.
Mom! Mom, are you OK? Are you OK?
Before,
you were right to keep pressing on Cooper.
Turns out he's not as dead as I thought.
I've had some experience with that.
And you learn not to judge.
Yes.
Are you OK?
I guess so.
Old lovers have a way of opening old wounds.
Lovers...
sounds creepy no matter how you say it.
Felicity...
I want you to know that
whatever experiences you had to go through,
I'm glad that you did.
They shaped the person you are today.
And you know how I feel about her.
I should head out.
You were right.
We have to love our families.
No matter what.
Felicity.
You here?
What happened to you?
This is me now.
You were right.
Something is going on with me.
And my father, he-- he noticed it as well.
He told me I should open up to someone.
My sister, she--
She died.
Well, she--
She was murdered.
- Did they ever catch the-- - No.
No one knows that she's gone except for me.
And I can't tell anyone. So, yes.
Yes, I am angry.
I'm going to help you with that.
See, before, Laurel, you were swinging at your sister's killer.
That's a target you're never going to hit.
Don't train for that.
All right, train for yourself.
See, now I know how to teach you.
So what's it going to be?
Red or black?
Black.
Definitely black.
It was popcorn, right?
You said you were meeting me halfway.
This is me doing my part.
I missed you, Speedy.
Let's not miss each other anymore.
I mean, it was so much easier to be in each other's lives
when we were underneath the same roof.
So...why don't you move in with me?
I mean, clearly I have enough space.
And I...
I swear once the club starts making a profit,
I will donate all of Malcolm's money
to an earthquake relief charity thing.
I can live with that.
You got a TV in here?
Well, I'm officially off.
I mean, my flight doesn't leave till tonight,
but I figured you'd be working, so we can--
We can just say good-bye now.
You were right.
About what?
I haven't always been appreciative of you.
You were always there for me every day, and night.
So if I haven't said thank you enough,
thank you.
But you were wrong, too.
Mm-hmm?
When you said all you saw in me was dad;
There was nothing of you in me.
Well, I can't really explain it,
but over the past two years, I have been through a lot.
And I have learned that I am a lot tougher than I thought.
That... I get from you.
Don't cry.
So I took another look at those cogeneration numbers.
You want to...
- Hi again. - Hi.
How's that new smart wearable working out for you?
Oh, it's, um,
it's a real life saver.
Yeah.
Ray, I can't come into work today.
I am...
Calling in sick.
"Feel better."
Thank you.
See you later.
That's actually pretty genius.
Hello, Sara.
What are you doing here?