Previously, on "Arrow"...
That woman running around
in black leather tonight, that wasn't Sara.
Sure it was. Who else would it be?
That's why I'm talking to you.
Who are we running from?
His name is Ra's Al Ghul,
and he's marked me
and my family for death.
I heard a rumor you were leaving town.
Happy to say that those rumors were false.
Ra's is going to come for me,
and he will learn the truth about Sara.
Then he will come for Thea.
That's why I have to kill him.
You couldn't before.
This time, I will have you to train me.
Dinah Laurel Lance...
Selfish bitch.
You're not a hero.
You're a liar.
A fraud.
And an addict.
Sara...
Sara, please, please.
I'm your sister.
Then why are you trying to take my place?
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Your job, apparently.
I told you that I didn't want you out here.
And I told you that it wasn't your call to make!
Will you think for a second about what it would do
to your father if something happened to you?
What you're doing is selfish.
Fighting for your city isn't selfish.
It's what a hero would do.
You're not a hero.
Maybe it's best if we stay out of each other's way.
How did it go out there?
We ran into Laurel.
Again.
Diggle, how could you sign off on her doing this?
Oliver, you might not notice,
but she's not exactly lobbying for anyone's permission.
She has yours.
Well, not at first,
but she can definitely hold her own out there.
You have a visitor.
Or as I like to call him, your new BFF.
I see things are still running smoothly down here.
What do you want?
It's been weeks since your return.
I thought it past time we spoke.
Nanda Parbat is remote,
but I wouldn't delude yourself into thinking
that Ra's Al Ghul missed your televised return
to Starling City.
Your point, Malcolm?
We can't merely wait for Ra's to mobilize his forces.
It's time to bring Thea into the fold.
She's not ready to know my secret.
I disagree.
But in any case,
if we have to protect Thea
and to defeat the League,
the three of us need to join forces.
But I don't see how we can do that
if she is still to believe that her brother
is a reformed playboy and failed businessman.
Oliver, I told you before,
if Thea finds out you've been lying to her all this time,
you will lose her...forever.
How's Tatsu?
She'll be better when we're far away from here.
Your bow. If you want anything else,
take it quickly. We're leaving in five minutes.
We're not coming back.
We can't just run.
Waller knows I tried to steal the virus
to get Tatsu back. Even if she didn't,
Chien Na Wei knows where we live.
We have to go.
Look, Maseo, we--
You stay, Waller will torture you to find us.
Contact your family, contact the press.
Once the world knows Oliver Queen is still alive,
it will limit A.R.G.U.S.'s options,
make it more difficult for Waller to assassinate you.
Well, that's reassuring.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to take Akio and Tatsu
on the ferry to Shanghai.
And from there, we will disappear.
You saved us.
Now save yourself.
Reaction to sentencing, Mr. Zytle?
The Roman governor Porcius Festus maintained
that the accused
has the right to face their accuser.
Now, where is my accuser?
I speak, of course, of the Arrow.
Excuse me, Mr. Zytle has no further comments.
A.D.A. Laurel Lance. Take him to the van. Thank you.
Stay back!
Alderman, stay back!
Where's Zytle?
So you still haven't told me...
what did you think of my set last night?
Because fangirls on Vine called it "Epically epic".
More like epically profitable.
It's kind of hot when you talk business in numbers.
Chase. God, if you ever really want to kiss me again,
you're going to have to work on your game.
Later, Princess.
Ollie.
Hey, Speedy.
I'm so happy you're home.
What?
I have to show you something.
Where are we going?
Basement.
I thought that you said that it was flooded.
I lied.
Ollie...
What's going on? You're kind of...
kind of making me nervous.
I know that this isn't going to mean much.
I've given you no reason to believe me when I say it.
But I lied all of this time
to protect you.
You're...
you're him.
Yeah.
That night with the... the hoods, and...
that woman in black, that...
Was Ra's al Ghul's daughter.
That was you.
All those times I got so mad at you
for being... a flake,
or telling me something I knew
that had to be a lie.
You were saving someone's life.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ollie.
You know how many times I've wished
that I could thank the Arrow for things he's done for the city?
Probably as many times as
I've wished we could have this conversation.
Did mom know?
The night that she died,
she told me that... she'd known for a while.
I was worried that you'd be angry.
Only 'cause you broke my window.
Although I did kind of kick your ass.
You didn't.
But you did have a good teacher.
You were looking for Malcolm that night.
We know about each other.
Wait, Malcolm knows that you're the Arrow?
I am amazed that he didn't tell you.
Then why did you... tell me?
Why now?
Because Ra's Al Ghul is coming for us.
All of us. And the only chance
that we have to survive
is to work together.
To trust each other.
He's right.
No.
No, no, he's not.
I turned my back on everyone I know,
including my own brother,
because you told me there was nobody else I could trust.
I was only trying to protect you.
Yeah, by driving a wedge between me and Ollie?
You manipulated me.
- Thea... - Let her go.
Yeah?
You've reached Moira Queen.
Please leave a message.
Mom, it's me. I'm alive.
I'm, uh, I'm in Hong Kong.
I know it sounds crazy, but I'm alive,
I'm in Hong Kong, and I need your help.
I want you to call Ned Foster,
you tell him to issue a press release.
Tell everyone.
And you tell Thea.
I'm coming home. I love you...
What do we know?
Apparently the Federal Marshal guarding Werner Zytle
just started shooting while Zytle waltzed off in the panic.
This is my favorite part.
That's pretty convenient.
Guy decides to wig out, and Zytle takes advantage.
It's not convenient, it's planned.
Those are the affects of his vertigo.
Zytle was in a full set of restraints.
How did he even manage to dose a federal agent?
He didn't. One of the reporters did.
What's wrong? Was my form off?
She's right. About the reporter.
- We need a name-- - A name and address on our clumsy reporter.
I'm on it.
What do you think you're doing?
- I'm coming with you. - No, you're not.
I just gave you your only lead!
Can I talk to you for a second? Alone?
I know what you're going to say,
but I risked my life for this city while you were gone.
That should earn me some respect.
This isn't about respect,
and it's not about you risking your life.
I understand that you miss Sara.
And I understand that when you go out there like this,
all of that pain goes away.
It's the only time it ever does.
And that relief isn't real.
It's a drug.
If you're implying...
You are an addict.
And just like with booze and pills,
that high that you're chasing every night
is endangering your life.
Go to hell, Oliver.
You don't get to play that card with me.
Ever.
And if there is anyone who is using adrenaline
to hide the pain of real feelings and real life,
it's you.
Oliver, Felicity tracked down the reporter's work address.
Anthony Walker! Where's Werner Zytle?
He's not, he's not here.
You helped him escape today!
Zytle, he threatened my wife.
Said he could get to her, that he'd kill her
if I didn't do this, then--
Do what?
Kill you.
- I'm so sorry. - Anthony...
Give me the detonator.
He'll kill my wife.
We can protect her.
I promise.
Now hand me the detonator.
God forgive me.
I will weep for thee.
Ollie?
I'm sorry, did I wake you?
Can't sleep.
Apparently insomnia is a common side effect
of finding out your brother is a vigilante.
You smell like smoke.
Korean barbecue?
C4.
It's nice that we can tell each other this stuff now.
It is, actually.
You always had the lamest excuses.
Lame excuses are sort of an occupational hazard.
What was tonight's hazard?
Roy and I were looking for the man
that escaped from the courthouse earlier today.
Found a bomb instead.
Yeah, I don't know how you do it.
Just risk your life out there for people every night.
It's my job.
It is my job to keep the people of this city safe.
And that includes you, too, Speedy.
Listen to me.
I'm always going to hate Malcolm Merlyn.
But right now, he is a necessary evil.
We can take care of ourselves--
Not against Ra's Al Ghul.
You have to trust me on this.
I do.
But I don't trust him.
I can't.
And I won't.
Ten minutes.
I'm impressed.
I know special forces who can't last longer than three.
Eventually, though,
everybody breaks.
Tell me where the Yamashiros are, and it will stop.
My family's going to be looking for me.
Everyone is going to be looking for me!
Because your mother issued a press release?
We erased your message before she could hear a word of it.
Be glad.
If she had heard it, your mother would be dead right now.
You would never risk the exposure.
You're right.
Your mother's too public a figure.
But your sister, on the other hand.
What's her name? Thea?
Did you know she's developed something
of a substance abuse problem since you've been gone?
I guess the strain of losing two family members
must have been too much for her to bear.
One day, someone may just find her in the back of a car,
dead with a needle in her arm.
Poor Speedy.
You stay away from my sister.
I will, if you answer one question.
Where are the Yamashiros?
The ferry to Shanghai.
Knock knock.
You know, half the department
is still talking about the way you clocked that marshal.
Those boxing lessons look like they're paying off.
Yeah, I guess so. Are those the cargo manifests
- for the whole city? - Yeah, yeah.
Although, you know, I got to ask, what do you need these for?
Just a RICO case that I'm second chairing.
Right.
- Dad? - Yeah, sorry. I just...
Have you heard from Sara lately?
No. Why?
I ran into her a few weeks back.
And something just felt a little... off.
Then I ran into that friend of hers.
You know, the one with the, the boy hair?
Sin.
Yeah, Sin, that's it.
She said something strange.
She said that the woman in black isn't Sara.
That doesn't make any sense.
No.
I mean, look, I just want to talk to her,
you know, Sara or not.
But look, don't worry, I said I'd start taking it easy,
I meant it.
I'll get out of your hair.
Now I've been wondering,
how do you decide between the red hoodie
and the one with the mask?
I'm glad you know.
I feel pretty lame
for not recognizing my own brother
just because he's wearing a hood.
I can't believe you knew before I did.
He saved my life, Thea.
He saved a lot of people's lives.
He thinks we need Merlyn's help.
And what do you think?
I think I want to get as far away
from Malcolm Merlyn as I possibly can.
Well, there's your answer right there.
Sorry.
May I borrow him for a second?
Apparently, he's been more yours than mine lately, so...
What happened?
One of our trackers sent a signal from the Starling City Docks.
Except we don't have any tracking devices in the field.
Unless we do.
It's Laurel.
You tagged Laurel with a tracer?
If she's going to be reckless, I need to know what she's doing.
Well, she's definitely doing something.
I'm just not exactly sure how reckless it is.
I ran the manifests on all
these shipping containers that you see here.
One of these leads back to Zytle's old supplier.
Looks like Vertigo's back in business.
She's going to get herself killed.
Suit up.
Wonderful seeing you again.
Ooh, I fancy the new outfit.
Feeling my Vertigo, dear.
Wonderful.
Dinah Laurel Lance.
Selfish bitch.
You're not a hero.
You're a liar.
A fraud.
And an addict.
Sara...
Sara, please, please.
I'm your sister.
Then why are you trying to take my place?
Get away from her!
You should be dead!
I salute your persistence!
Help me!
Help!
Help me, please.
Need an IV.
- Watch her. - You're going to be OK.
It's going to be OK.
Why did I have to die?
Sara?
If you wanted to be me, you could have.
I didn't have to die.
I am so sorry! I am so sorry!
Sara! I am so--
Ollie?
I'm-- I'm sorry, I just wanted to talk.
You need to go back upstairs.
Now!
Don't talk to her like that. You brought her in;
you don't have the right to kick her out.
I'm not. I'm protecting her.
By telling her what to do?
Work with Malcolm Merlyn, let him get his hooks deeper--
Enough. She's my sister.
She makes her own choices, Oliver!
It's OK. I-- we can talk later.
I just-- just, is Laurel OK?
Is she a part of this, too?
She's going to be fine.
I promise. Just...
please go back upstairs.
What the hell was that?
You think you're the only person who can stand up to Thea?
I'm trying to figure out why you're standing up to me!
All right, maybe we just need to throttle back.
No. We need this. Oliver, you were gone.
Dead. At least we thought you were,
and we had to go on with our lives.
And doing that meant not doing things your way.
Fine! I'm back now.
That doesn't mean that we can go back.
And you do not have the right to come back here
and question everyone's choices.
Just let me know if there's any change in her condition.
Hey, how's it going?
What's that for?
My life has been really complicated lately,
so I-- I just need something simple.
So...
This seat taken?
It's a free country.
Apparently.
The first time that we went after Zytle,
I told you that this was my crusade.
Doesn't seem to be the case anymore.
You're right. It isn't.
Diggle, I get that I was gone for--
No, you weren't gone-- you were dead.
And all of us, including me,
we were ready to hang it up.
Why didn't you?
Because I realized we weren't just fighting for you;
we were fighting for ourselves, too.
And that includes Roy.
And, yes, that includes Laurel.
She's not a soldier.
Neither were you.
That's not the same thing, and you know that.
What I know, Oliver, is that you started something.
Something strong enough to live on past you.
The question is,
can you live with what it's become?
Oliver.
Are you all right?
I told them you were on the ferry.
I'm sorry.
They tortured you.
I sold you out.
No, you didn't.
Because we were never going to Shanghai.
I lied.
A precaution just in case you were captured.
Then how'd they find you?
They didn't. When I found out you'd been taken,
I came back.
You're an idiot.
Maybe.
But I will not let you face Waller alone for my actions.
So now we're both going to get tortured, or worse.
Great plan.
I must speak with Agent Waller.
Hey! Why did you--
How are you feeling?
When Zytle hit me with Vertigo, I...
I saw Sara.
She was alive.
And she was calling me a fraud.
I was crazy to think that I was fit to wear Sara's jacket.
Much less follow in her footsteps.
You're right.
I hope I'm not out of line here,
but...
I think Sara wore her mask just as much to hide her demons
as she did to help people.
And I don't see that with you.
You have a light inside of you that Sara never had.
So...
Maybe you should stop trying to be Sara...
and just be yourself.
Thank you.
What's that?
One of the chemical drums Zytle stole tonight just sent out a GPS signal.
Why?
Cause he just opened it.
I dig your place.
I'm sorry I interrupted the tour.
Pretty sure you saw everything you needed to.
You want a drink?
Sure.
This was nice.
I almost took it personally when you said I was simple.
Well, I never said that you were simple.
What?
Nothing. It...
It's just something my father once said.
We were sitting in this little taberna in Corto Maltese,
drinking this amazing Carmnre,
and he said that for centuries,
noblemen have been using the rich aroma of red wine
to cover up a very different scent.
Cyanide.
Tell me who you are and what the hell you think you're doing here!
Serving my master, Ra's Al Ghul.
Please!
Don't struggle. I can do this so you won't feel a thing.
Get away from her.
If you beg forgiveness for trying to harm my daughter,
I'll grant you a quick death.
I'd never give you the satisfaction, Al Sa-Her.
You're unarmed and you have nowhere to run.
But there's some place I can go where you won't dare to follow.
Daggett Pharmaceuticals. 5th and Kingsley.
Looks like Zytle found a place to change those chemicals
into some new Vertigo... and he's got hostages.
Where's Roy?
I can't reach him.
Laurel.
Oliver.
There isn't anything that you can say to me
that I don't already know.
Actually, there is.
I must once again thank you
for letting us use your laboratory this evening.
And my sincerest apologies to your colleague here.
But mistakes will not be tolerated.
Werner Zytle...
This ends now.
As you wish!
May I suggest a grand finale--
chlorine triflouride.
Oliver, I'm registering an enormous spike in thermal activity.
Oliver, the whole place is going to blow.
You have to get out of there!
Not yet.
Go! Run! Now!
Please! Help!
I'm surprised.
Usually women don't return
for a second go.
Hi, sis.
You're not her. You're...
You're not real.
Oh, I'm quite real.
You lied to me, Laurel!
Straight to my face, my own daughter!
Sara was my daughter, I deserved to know! I had a right!
To grieve, to mourn!
Who do you think you are to take that away from me?
Who do you think you are?!
I'm--I'm sorry!
I know you are.
She says she's sorry, but she'll do it again.
You keep my own daughter's death a secret
because you think I'm too weak for the truth?!
You think you can wear my mask?
You think you can be me?!
No.
And I'm done trying to be.
Oliver, are you there?
It's over.
No, it's not. You have to get home.
It's Thea.
See? All good.
Is everything ok?
Oh, yeah, just the usual insurance policy
search and seizure.
Seems like I'm a high risk case.
I wonder what gave them that idea.
What's a matter? You OK?
There's...
There's something that I have to tell you.
And I didn't tell you--
I didn't tell you before,
because I was worried about your health.
But... I realize that...
that you deserve to know.
I already know it.
Sara's off God knows where, and yet there's another blonde
in a mask running around tuning up the bad guys,
and it's you, isn't it?
Sweetheart, come on.
It's all right. It's OK.
It's OK, honey.
I mean, look, I am pissed as hell.
But, you know, we'll figure it out. We figure out everything.
No. No, no, daddy, that--
that isn't what I was going to tell you.
What I was going to tell you
is about Sara.
No.
Dad...
- No. - Dad...
Daddy, I'm sorry.
Not my baby, not again.
Oh, God.
Thea?
It's OK. You're OK.
I thought that I was stronger.
I thought that I could keep myself safe.
Who was he?
One of Ra's agents.
Roy...
could you give us a minute?
Really hope you're not expecting a thank you.
No parent needs gratitude for saving their child.
I didn't ask to be a part of this.
I didn't ask for any of this.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe we can't do this without him.
But I am never going to forget the things you've done.
Or the person that you are.
Understood.
But before we can begin,
there's something that only the two of you can do.
Ra's Al Ghul preys upon the fears of his enemies.
Conquer your own fear,
and you eliminate that critical advantage.
For you, there is only one place
on earth uniquely suited to doing that.
So you're leaving again?
She's got a point, man. You just got back.
It's just for a few days.
Ordinarily, I wouldn't do this.
But it's for Thea.
And if you've shown me anything,
it's that the city is more than safe in your hands.
All of your hands.
Thank you.
Ollie told you we're heading out for a bit?
You cool with it all?
After the whole chase thing,
I think it's going to be a little while
before I'm cool with anything.
What was that for?
Take your pick. Saving my life,
or standing up to Oliver about Malcolm.
I should get going.
Come on, Speedy, we have four more miles
to make before night fall.
God.
I get that Malcolm wants to whip us into shape
so we can face the League, but don't you think
it's a little bit excessive?
We've been here for two hours. Are you complaining already?
I--I started thinking it after the first ten minutes.
Well, give it time.
Eventually this place will feel like home.
It does not look like home.
It was for me. For other people,
this is Purgatory.
You're not dead, if that's what you're wondering.
Once again, you have the good fortune
of being uniquely qualified to help me.
Me? Why?
Chien Na Wei has left Hong Kong. We've tracked here here.
Here? Where are we...
Welcome home, Mr. Queen.