Previously, on "Arrow"...
These waters' powers,
they have permitted me to live way beyond my time.
I want you to take my place.
I want you to become the next Ra's Al Ghul.
If you insist on pursuing this path of resistance,
there will be consequences.
Is that a threat?
I am the demon's head.
And very soon, your brother.
He will never take your place.
He will.
Thea?
Thea?!
Oh, my God, Thea!
I... couldn't... stop him.
I need an ambulance to 455 Merced, unit 10.
Please hurry.
Ok, you're going to be ok.
You're going to be ok.
No, Thea, stay awake! Come on! Up!
Hang on, we're almost there.
How long was she like this?
Uh, 20 minutes, 40,
I don't know, I just found her.
- You need to stay here. - I'm not going to leave her!
You need to let us work.
- Get me a set of vitals. - Lift.
Charge up to 200 joules.
Clear.
Draw up one milligram epi, charge to 200.
Start CPR.
Come on.
Come on, stay with us.
We did the best we could under the circumstances,
but her injuries were extensive.
Even if she were to regain consciousness,
we can prolong her life for as long as you wish.
But...it might be best to consider other options.
I am truly sorry, Mr. Queen.
May I see her?
Sorry.
Oliver...
Thea.
What are they doing?
They're unloading the truck,
and, um,
having dinner.
General Shrieve is there.
The alpha, the Omega, he's combining them.
- The bio weapon is armed. - What happens now?
Now he'll take it somewhere to be released.
Somewhere densely populated where it will have the most impact.
We need to stop that truck.
Where's Oliver?
Come on!
You stole a car?
I borrowed it. Come on.
Oh, my God. Oliver!
Oliver, we came as soon as we could.
What happened?
Oliver.
They just left her there.
To die.
Oliver, is--is she?
It's bad.
What is it?
Smoke.
The League?
Screw 'em. At least until we get our bearings, Oliver.
- Come up with a plan. - He's won.
There is no plan.
Stay here with Thea.
Did you do this?
Did you do this?!
You could still save her, Oliver.
I don't understand.
Take your rightful place as heir to the demon...
And Ra's Al Ghul will bring your sister back.
Oliver, what's going on?
- Oliver, where are you going? - Away.
You can't just leave like this.
You have to tell us what's happening.
There's a way for me to save her.
Thea?
Come on, Oliver, that's not possible.
Yes, it is.
There are waters in Nanda Parbat.
They've permitted Ra's to live for over a hundred years.
And in rare instances,
told in legend, those waters have been used to restore
the dead to life.
He offered to use the Lazarus pit on Thea, didn't he?
Lazarus, as in from the Bible, Lazarus?
The pit's real. I've seen it.
- It can save Thea. - Right.
But only if you become the new Ra's.
Ok. Well, even if a magic hot tub
were not crazy talk,
we're not going to let you go
and join the league of psychotic murderers,
Even if it is to save Thea.
Which this wouldn't.
The waters change a person.
In the soul.
Even if they work, the Thea you get back
will not be the one you lost.
The one we lost because of you.
- Oliver... - I'd prefer that we didn't do our usual
"Please don't go" dance.
We're not going to.
Because I'm coming with you. Assuming that this works,
someone's going to need to bring Thea back home.
We need a way to get to Nanda Parbat.
Sorry to interrupt.
Everything all right?
Cause you got that crease between your eyebrows
that tells me things most definitely are not.
Something awful has happened.
And I-I need a favor.
A really big favor.
Last time you asked me for a big favor,
I had to loan you my helicopter.
Don't need your helicopter.
I need your jet.
Well, Oliver does, but both of us.
It's not what you think.
Well, if you're going to fly away with him,
then...it's exactly what I think.
Ray...
Last night was a bit of an eye-opener.
Insofar as realizing something
I should have realized a long time ago...
can be considered eye-opening.
Last night, when you were saying good-bye to Roy,
you and Oliver...
You still have feelings for him.
When I...told you that I loved you at the hospital,
you responded with jell-o.
Seeing you two together last night,
I realized...
you don't love me because you're in love with him.
I'm sorry.
You're the last person I ever meant to hurt.
Take the jet.
I hope the something awful
stops being awful.
What did Felicity say to Dr. Vaca?
She thinks Thea's being moved to Central City.
You know, they do amazing things at S.T.A.R. Labs.
We might think about paying them a visit
before putting Thea on a long flight to Nanda Parbat.
S.T.A.R. Labs can't save her.
Only the Lazarus pit can.
Oliver!
Look, I know what I have done
doesn't seem like the actions of a loving father,
but I do love her.
She's the only child I have left.
Having said that,
I would rather lose her forever
than-- than subject her to the pit.
Get on the plane, Malcolm.
You look chilly.
Thanks for letting me be here for you.
You're welcome.
I didn't have much of a choice, though, did I?
No.
I wanted to make you think
you had grown a little as a person.
I know that I've only told you a little
about the five years that I was away.
Well, if by "Little," You mean hardly anything.
I came back to Starling City
before they found me on the island.
I don't understand.
It was complicated.
I saw Thea.
She didn't see me.
She had a drug problem.
So I... confronted her dealer.
And I broke his neck.
And I did it because I was angry, sure.
But I also did it because I felt like I was protecting her.
All I've ever wanted to do was protect her.
Malcolm told me.
He warned me what Ra's might do.
But I never thought...
I failed.
Incoming!
Maseo, take the wheel.
You look like you can use a hand.
It's not in here.
What is that?
It's the League.
Welcome home, Al Sah-him.
I must prepare for the ritual.
I will treat her as my own family.
I hope you find the accommodations acceptable.
Such luxury is a small glimpse of the life that awaits Oliver.
You trying to reassure me or yourself?
I don't know what you mean.
You're Oliver's friend.
Maseo, right?
I am Sarab.
Call yourself whatever you want.
If you gave a damn about Oliver,
you wouldn't be working for
the man who practically killed his sister.
Oliver will be spared grief
in a manner that was denied to me,
and he'll receive an honor greater than you can imagine.
League of Assassins.
You're feared for your bravery
and power.
Well, all I see are a bunch of weak men
running from their lives, trying to escape.
That's not powerful, Maseo.
Or brave. That's cowardly.
Do not presume to know me
until you've held your dying child in your arms.
Until you've told him everything would be ok
so that the last words he ever hears
are a lie.
You know nothing.
I'm sorry.
What was your child's name?
Akio.
You think Akio would be proud of his father right now?
Thea!
I've fulfilled my end of our arrangement.
I suggest you begin to make peace with yours.
It's ok. You're ok.
I don't know you.
Thea, it's-- it's me.
It's Ollie.
Ollie's dead.
Dad?
I'm here, Thea. It-- it's me.
What's going on?
Where am I?
Some place safe.
You are safe.
Where's mom?
Your mother's not here.
Look--
just lie back, close your eyes and get some rest, OK?
I love you, dad.
Ra's told me that the confusion would pass.
You have no idea what you've done.
What I've done?
She's alive, Malcolm.
What I did saved her life.
- She thinks Moira's still alive. - She'll be fine.
- You don't know that. - Yes, I do.
Because you, Diggle and Felicity
are going to take her home and she will recover.
And what is that worth?
- Felicity... - No, this is wrong! It is just wrong!
I need to talk to you.
What is happening here is perverse!
What you are doing to Oliver.
What you are making him do; I am not going to let it happen.
You can leave us.
You have a great fire within you.
I can see now why Oliver loves you.
If you knew the first thing about love,
you would not be ripping Oliver away from his family.
I am merely helping him fulfill his destiny.
Yeah, I know all about the "Survive my sword" prophecy,
and I am here to tell you that I could really give a crap.
Me and John and, God help me, Malcolm,
are not going to let this happen, and we have friends,
and we have resources and we will go to war to get Oliver back.
You know, many lifetimes ago,
I loved a woman immeasurably.
And she loved me.
And we had a son and then a daughter,
and for many years,
I felt I was the most fortunate man in the world.
My life was bliss.
And one night, a man came to my door
and he gave me a horrible choice--
to leave without saying a word to them,
or to stand and watch them tortured and then killed.
And I left without a farewell.
And to spare them pain,
I endured an agony worse than death.
Sounds like you gave up too easily.
If there's one immutable truth about life...
it's often more cruel than it is fair,
and rarely provides an opportunity for any of us to find closure.
And all your posturing
and all your threats of war
will merely delay the inevitable,
causing you to forfeit the opportunity you have.
This was denied me.
You need to tell oliver good-bye.
Tell him how much you love him.
Tell him whatever it is your heart needs to express.
And do it now.
Before he is lost to you forever.
Yeah?
You OK?
I'm sorry, that's a stupid question. You...
you just saw your sister come back from being mostly dead
and you are about to give up everything you know and love,
So you're probably not.
I remember the first time that I thought
I'd never see Thea again.
When my father's boat went down.
But you did see her again.
And you'll see her again...
again.
This is different.
I've just been thinking about the... person I was.
The brother that I was.
And how he probably died when that boat went down.
All this time, I've been struggling with who I am...
And you think who you're supposed to be is...
the next Ra's Al Ghul?
Honestly?
I don't know.
The only thing that I can know for sure
is that everything that I've done;
every--everything that happened,
it lead me right here,
to this moment.
And Felicity, if that's true,
then...I don't know what it was all for.
I do.
I wish that I could change your mind about staying here,
but I know I can't.
Just like I know how leaving you here is going to destroy me.
I don't regret a single moment.
And you shouldn't, either.
You have done so much.
You have saved so many people's lives.
And you have changed so many for the better.
Including mine.
Knowing you has changed my life.
You...opened up my heart
in a way I didn't even know was possible.
I love you.
We searched the whole truck. There's nothing in there.
Where is the bio weapon?
Don't make me ask again.
Food cart. It's in the food cart.
Where is the food cart?
We should split up to cover more ground.
What's wrong?
I know you don't think we should be doing this.
You decided we should set an example for our son.
And for ourselves.
We can't just let people die.
If we do, we are just a shell.
Not really alive at all.
So...that happened.
I'm glad it did.
Me, too.
What's this?
If there's any kind of God,
something...
alcoholic.
There's not much to toast to up here, is there?
There's us.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
Look, I know there's no way of avoiding this,
of--of getting out of here,
going some place where Ra's can't find us, but I...
Felicity...
Felicity.
What did you--
I can't lose you.
I won't.
I stole some of that powder
that that creepy priest lady used on Thea.
Wasn't sure exactly what I was going to do with it when I got it,
but I...
Yeah, how did you know
you were going to completely lose your mind?
Or commit suicide.
Was your plan to sneak Ra's prize out
unconscious without getting us all killed?
No, it's an insane idea, but I couldn't do it.
I couldn't leave him.
We have to get him out of here.
Felicity, this place is like a fortress.
There's no way we're getting Oliver out of here
without Ra's knowing.
We can't. You can.
If we get caught, he'll kill all of us.
Then we can't get caught.
I have seen enough movies to know
that the scary fortress always has a secret exit.
You were Ra's right hand stooge for years.
If there is anyone that knows the way out of this hellhole,
it's you, so don't even try to play games with me.
The catacombs.
It's rough terrain. It is not going to be easy.
How do we get there?
Through the temple.
Go get Thea and meet us back here in five minutes.
Go!
Which way?
Temple's this way, come on!
There's not much time. Hurry.
Why are you helping us?
Because if I don't, then I am just a shell.
You reminded me of that.
30 meters down. The path forks.
- Take the left passage. - Come on.
These tunnels are centuries old. Stay close.
Need to stop and rest for a minute?
No, no, no.
Maseo says stay left.
Thea?
- We have to move, now! - Too late.
Believe me, we do not want to be taken alive.
Hold!
I am Al Sah-Him.
Wahreeth Al Ghul.
Heir to the demon. And you will obey.
Put your weapons down.
Now!
Tell Ra's I will return shortly.
Oliver, please!
Thank you for trying.
I love you all the more for it.
But this only ends one way.
This is as far as I go.
Oliver, the jet's less than a mile away.
Where are we going to fly to?
Ollie, I don't understand.
Malcolm is going to take you home.
Aren't you coming with?
Not now.
You go on, I'll catch up.
I love you, Thea.
Don't ever forget that, ok?
Oliver...
Oliver, I don't know what to say.
I do.
John, you're the best man I've ever known.
And whatever happens,
you're my brother.
I am afraid I will never forgive myself for leaving you here.
You told me once that...
life is precious.
And that you wanted more from it than I could offer you.
Don't give up on that.
The only way that I'm going to survive this...
is if I know that you're out there living your life, happy.
We're always saying good-bye to each other.
You'd think I'd be good at it by now.
Well, let's not say good-bye this time.
What's-- what's going on?
Everything's fine, Thea, you're-- you're ok.
If you're here, then I'm not.
Well, at least you're feeling a little more like yourself again.
What do you want?
Where's Ollie?
Thea, do you remember anything about the past few days?
I...
I was here.
And-- and Ra's, he--
he attacked me.
No, Thea.
He nearly killed you.
Where is my brother?
That is-- that is what I'm trying to explain.
To save you, Oliver had to join the league.
He-- he traded his life for yours.
No.
I'm so sorry.
I know you hate me, and you have every right,
But I am going to make up for that, for everything.
- That is not possible! - Yes, it is!
The league isn't after us anymore; I am free!
I could go anywhere in there world,
But... this is where I want to be. Here.
With my daughter.
You took care of me when I was injured. Now, please, Thea,
Please. Let me take care of you.
Sorry to interrupt.
Is everything all right?
No.
It's not.
Felicity...
Oliver's...
He's gone.
What are you talking about?
He joined the league.
He's not coming back.
Blood has been shed.
League blood.
And that is a transgression
punishable by death.
And yet you allowed your friends safe passage home.
You tell me why I should not hunt these people down
and stain my blade with their blood.
Because I stayed.
I'm honoring our agreement.
Now no one close to me will ever be harmed again.
And your allies would not
have been able to escape through the catacombs
without assistance, so you tell me who aided you,
Who this traitor is.
- I don't know. - Me.
I struck down three of our number.
For my betrayal...
I offer you my life.
You did not betray me tonight, Sarab.
Maseo Yamashiro did.
For a moment,
your old life took hold.
But by coming here and kneeling before me,
you have proven your loyalty,
And I will not spill Sarab's blood
for Maseo's actions. Stand up.
Your service will be vital in the coming weeks.
Oliver will need you for his transformation.
And like Sarab...
vestiges of your old identity still remain.
Oliver Queen must be extinguished from memory.
Stop!
Give me the vial.
The word "Assassin" has fallen victim
to many abuses of language.
Its real meaning hidden beneath the sediment
of lies and falsehoods.
In truth,
"Assassin" comes from Hashishiyya,
which means, "Those who stand apart from society."
Now, every man and woman in here
have renounced their past life
and forfeited their identity in the name of something new.
And it is a cleansing
only achieved by fire.
Embrace the pain,
for it is your soul finally being unburdened.
Oliver Queen is dead.
Eventually to be reborn as Ra's Al Ghul.
But for now, only the arrow,
Al Sah-Him, shall remain.
Al Sah-Him.
Heir to the demon.