[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微軟正黑體,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,1,2,5,5,15,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.32,0:07:49.89,Default,,0,0,0,,{\shad5\fad(0,600)\bord0\move(189,190,189,114,0,3424)\fs150\t(0,3400,\fs40)}{t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)}綠   箭   俠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.32,0:07:49.89,Default,,0,0,0,,{\shad5\fad(0,600)\bord0\fs60\t(0,3400,\fs16)\move(223,224,242,188,0,3341)}{t(0,0,\\c&H000001&\t(500,4000,\c&H4D4E4F&)}第二季 第四集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.38,0:00:02.95,Default,,0,0,0,,我的名字叫奧利弗•奎恩\N{\b0\fs12}My name is Oliver Queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.27,0:00:05.79,Default,,0,0,0,,五年裡  我被困在地獄一般的小島上\N{\b0\fs12}After five years on a hellish island,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.48,0:00:08.89,Default,,0,0,0,,我回來只有一個目標\N{\b0\fs12}I have come home with only one goal--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.35,0:00:11.16,Default,,0,0,0,,拯救我的城市\N{\b0\fs12}to save my city.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.64,0:00:15.09,Default,,0,0,0,,但要達到目標  我不能像過去一樣成為兇手\N{\b0\fs12}But to do so, I can't be the killer I once was.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.86,0:00:18.78,Default,,0,0,0,,為了紀念我的朋友\N{\b0\fs12}To honor my friend's memory,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.89,0:00:20.67,Default,,0,0,0,,我只能偽裝成另一個人\N{\b0\fs12}I must be someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.05,0:00:21.24,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}深切懷念托馬斯•梅林\N孝子
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.75,0:00:24.45,Default,,0,0,0,,成為另一個存在\N{\b0\fs12}I must be something else.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.45,0:00:28.10,Default,,0,0,0,,《綠箭俠》前情回顧\N{\b0\fs12}Previously on "Arrow"...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.14,0:00:30.37,Default,,0,0,0,,-誰是布拉德  -出身貧民區\N{\b0\fs12}- Who's Blood? - An alderman from the glades
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.37,0:00:31.51,Default,,0,0,0,,想拯救城市的一個議員\N{\b0\fs12}trying to save the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.51,0:00:32.66,Default,,0,0,0,,我很驚訝你居然會想見我\N{\b0\fs12}I'm surprised that you wanted to meet.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.66,0:00:34.40,Default,,0,0,0,,-我不是你的敵人  -你也不是朋友\N{\b0\fs12}- I'm not your enemy. - You're not a friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.40,0:00:35.84,Default,,0,0,0,,但我希望能證明自己\N{\b0\fs12}I'm hoping to prove otherwise.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.84,0:00:37.26,Default,,0,0,0,,他叫我離開貧民區\N{\b0\fs12}He told me to stay out of the Glades.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.27,0:00:38.82,Default,,0,0,0,,他讓我退出創新聯合會\N{\b0\fs12}He told me to get out of CNRI.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.83,0:00:41.42,Default,,0,0,0,,就因為我太固執  湯米才出現在那裡的\N{\b0\fs12}Tommy was only there because I was too stubborn.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.42,0:00:44.09,Default,,0,0,0,,你說得對  我責怪綠箭俠是因為\N{\b0\fs12}You were right. I was blaming the arrow because
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.09,0:00:46.80,Default,,0,0,0,,都是我的錯  爸  湯米死了\N{\b0\fs12}it's all my fault, dad! It's all my fault
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.80,0:00:48.12,Default,,0,0,0,,都是我的錯\N{\b0\fs12}that Tommy died.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.51,0:00:50.92,Default,,0,0,0,,這個女人是怎麼回事\N{\b0\fs12}What's going on with this woman?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.09,0:00:52.58,Default,,0,0,0,,她一直跟著你  幫助你\N{\b0\fs12}She keeps following you around, helping you out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.58,0:00:53.49,Default,,0,0,0,,我們得找到她\N{\b0\fs12}We've got to find her.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.49,0:00:55.06,Default,,0,0,0,,為了阻止她  還是給她一封感謝信\N{\b0\fs12}To stop her, or to send her a thank you note?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.07,0:00:56.60,Default,,0,0,0,,-那得看情況  -什麼情況\N{\b0\fs12}- That depends. - On what?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.61,0:00:59.01,Default,,0,0,0,,她站在哪邊\N{\b0\fs12}What side she's on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.82,0:01:09.09,Default,,0,0,0,,奎恩先生要遲到了  他非常抱歉\N{\b0\fs12}Mr. Queen's going to be late. He's extremely sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.09,0:01:11.27,Default,,0,0,0,,-事出突然  -他在哪\N{\b0\fs12}- It couldn't be helped. - Where is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.23,0:01:20.28,Default,,0,0,0,,-在那邊  -在哪啊\N{\b0\fs12}- Over there! - Where, man?!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.35,0:01:21.57,Default,,0,0,0,,小心\N{\b0\fs12}Watch out, man!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.05,0:01:23.15,Default,,0,0,0,,他被拖住了\N{\b0\fs12}Just got a little held up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.57,0:01:25.94,Default,,0,0,0,,處理一些枝節問題\N{\b0\fs12}You know, tying up some loose ends.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.18,0:01:33.56,Default,,0,0,0,,我現在已經和他聯繫上了\N{\b0\fs12}I'm actually in direct contact with him now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.56,0:01:35.13,Default,,0,0,0,,我來問問他\N{\b0\fs12}Let me--let me check.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.16,0:01:43.84,Default,,0,0,0,,你從哪弄到槍的\N{\b0\fs12}Where are you getting the guns?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.35,0:01:45.40,Default,,0,0,0,,你會殺了我嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Are you going to kill me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.19,0:01:47.47,Default,,0,0,0,,趕緊動手吧\N{\b0\fs12}Get it over with.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.19,0:01:52.14,Default,,0,0,0,,狄格\N{\b0\fs12}Dig.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.96,0:01:54.59,Default,,0,0,0,,又搞定了兩名青少年犯罪團夥成員\N{\b0\fs12}Took down two more gangbangers.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.59,0:01:57.36,Default,,0,0,0,,他們帶著全自動M4A1沖鋒槍\N{\b0\fs12}They were armed with fully automatic M4A1 assault rifles.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.36,0:01:59.99,Default,,0,0,0,,M4A1是軍用武器\N{\b0\fs12}M4A1s are military grade weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.99,0:02:01.64,Default,,0,0,0,,很可能是偷來的\N{\b0\fs12}Stolen, most likely.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.64,0:02:02.78,Default,,0,0,0,,從哪偷來的\N{\b0\fs12}Stolen from where?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.78,0:02:04.90,Default,,0,0,0,,我們可以在你派對結束後進行調查\N{\b0\fs12}Well, we can look into that after your party.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.10,0:02:06.24,Default,,0,0,0,,什麼派對\N{\b0\fs12}What party?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.31,0:02:08.22,Default,,0,0,0,,他來了\N{\b0\fs12}He's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.24,0:02:10.39,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉我遲到了\N{\b0\fs12}Sorry I'm late.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.79,0:02:13.17,Default,,0,0,0,,這次派對的目的是為你的破產公司\N{\b0\fs12}This party is to attract investors
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.17,0:02:14.58,Default,,0,0,0,,吸引投資者\N{\b0\fs12}for your failing company.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.89,0:02:17.41,Default,,0,0,0,,時髦地遲到可能在夜店挺吃香\N{\b0\fs12}Being fashionably late might do well for the club circuit,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.41,0:02:18.95,Default,,0,0,0,,但這樣沒法在華爾街\N{\b0\fs12}but it does not inspire
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.95,0:02:20.63,Default,,0,0,0,,鼓舞信心\N{\b0\fs12}confidence in Wall Street.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.63,0:02:22.54,Default,,0,0,0,,你臉上是血嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Is that blood on your face?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.90,0:02:24.88,Default,,0,0,0,,別擔心  不是他的血\N{\b0\fs12}Don't worry, it's not his blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.88,0:02:26.47,Default,,0,0,0,,我是說  這當然是他的血啦\N{\b0\fs12}I mean, of course it's his blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.47,0:02:28.73,Default,,0,0,0,,他臉上怎麼會有別人的血呢\N{\b0\fs12}Why would he have somebody else's blood on his face?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.79,0:02:31.23,Default,,0,0,0,,誰教你刮鬍子的  先生\N{\b0\fs12}Who taught you to shave? Mister.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.52,0:02:33.63,Default,,0,0,0,,什麼事耽誤了\N{\b0\fs12}What kept you?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.12,0:02:35.77,Default,,0,0,0,,是不是戴面具的金髮女人拿著那架重型武器\N{\b0\fs12}Was it our masked blonde that carries that giant staff
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.77,0:02:37.23,Default,,0,0,0,,把襲擊者打得落花流水\N{\b0\fs12}to beat the sauce out of attackers?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.23,0:02:38.76,Default,,0,0,0,,-這次是槍  -槍\N{\b0\fs12}- This time it was guns. - Guns?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.76,0:02:41.17,Default,,0,0,0,,我們剛聊到槍\N{\b0\fs12}We were just talking about guns.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.17,0:02:43.18,Default,,0,0,0,,奧利弗\N{\b0\fs12}Hey. Oliver.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.25,0:02:46.29,Default,,0,0,0,,你對槍感興趣嗎  奎恩先生\N{\b0\fs12}What's your interest in guns, Mr. Queen?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.71,0:02:48.16,Default,,0,0,0,,我自己沒碰過\N{\b0\fs12}Never touched them myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.16,0:02:49.17,Default,,0,0,0,,貧民區盛行槍支\N{\b0\fs12}The gun epidemic in the Glades
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.17,0:02:50.49,Default,,0,0,0,,已經越來越失控了\N{\b0\fs12}has gotten increasingly out of control.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.49,0:02:52.29,Default,,0,0,0,,所以地檢辦已經下決心\N{\b0\fs12}Which is why the DA's office has committed
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.29,0:02:53.37,Default,,0,0,0,,終止槍支暴力\N{\b0\fs12}to ending gun violence.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.37,0:02:54.22,Default,,0,0,0,,我敢肯定員警\N{\b0\fs12}Well, I'm sure the police
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.23,0:02:55.24,Default,,0,0,0,,正盡力而為\N{\b0\fs12}are doing whatever they can
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.24,0:02:57.69,Default,,0,0,0,,抓捕把槍支帶入這座城市的人\N{\b0\fs12}to catch whoever's bring the weapons into the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.11,0:03:02.55,Default,,0,0,0,,我說了什麼好笑的話嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Did I say something funny?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.48,0:03:06.30,Default,,0,0,0,,他們知道是誰在為幫派提供槍支  奧利弗\N{\b0\fs12}They know who's been arming the gangs, Oliver.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.35,0:03:08.35,Default,,0,0,0,,市長\N{\b0\fs12}The Mayor.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.90,0:03:09.77,Default,,0,0,0,,市...\N{\b0\fs12}The...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.12,0:03:12.93,Default,,0,0,0,,冒牌兜帽男不是殺了市長嗎\N{\b0\fs12}I thought the hood copycats killed the Mayor.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.00,0:03:14.52,Default,,0,0,0,,不是真正的市長\N{\b0\fs12}Well, not the actual Mayor.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.51,0:03:17.96,Default,,0,0,0,,一個當地黑幫老大自稱為市長\N{\b0\fs12}A local gang lord calls himself the Mayor.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.96,0:03:19.36,Default,,0,0,0,,他認為自己是拯救我們城市的人\N{\b0\fs12}Think he's the man to save our city.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.36,0:03:22.32,Default,,0,0,0,,但那個位置已經有人占了  對吧\N{\b0\fs12}But that position has already been filled, hasn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.08,0:03:25.94,Default,,0,0,0,,這位市長只有一個目標\N{\b0\fs12}Now this Mayor has only one goal--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.10,0:03:27.35,Default,,0,0,0,,製造混亂\N{\b0\fs12}to create chaos
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.49,0:03:29.66,Default,,0,0,0,,這樣他就能用槍桿子來控制貧民區了\N{\b0\fs12}so he can rule the Glades with the barrel of a gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.65,0:03:45.11,Default,,0,0,0,,你沒攜帶武器啊  孩子\N{\b0\fs12}You are noticeably unarmed, son.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.52,0:03:46.61,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉  市長先生\N{\b0\fs12}Sorry, Mr. Mayor.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.61,0:03:48.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我們碰上了治安維持者\N{\b0\fs12}Um, we ran into the vigilante,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.24,0:03:50.91,Default,,0,0,0,,他搶走了我們的武器\N{\b0\fs12}and, um, he ganked our weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.91,0:03:53.02,Default,,0,0,0,,在地震之前你知道我是誰嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Do you know who I was before the quake?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.18,0:03:56.71,Default,,0,0,0,,我是無名小卒\N{\b0\fs12}I was no one. I had no name.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.71,0:03:57.67,Default,,0,0,0,,反正那也不重要\N{\b0\fs12}None that mattered, anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.67,0:04:00.13,Default,,0,0,0,,我只是另一個軟弱的人\N{\b0\fs12}I was just another weak man
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.13,0:04:03.49,Default,,0,0,0,,等著被炒魷魚  被驅逐或是被殺\N{\b0\fs12}waiting to get fired or evicted or killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.35,0:04:06.88,Default,,0,0,0,,但是地震發生了  現在我很重要\N{\b0\fs12}But then the ground shook, and now I matter,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.89,0:04:09.56,Default,,0,0,0,,因為我知道拳頭大的就是老大\N{\b0\fs12}because I know the guy with the biggest gun wins,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.56,0:04:11.86,Default,,0,0,0,,所以我將統治貧民區\N{\b0\fs12}and that's why I will rule the Glades.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.86,0:04:13.25,Default,,0,0,0,,但我可容不下\N{\b0\fs12}But there's no room at my table
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.25,0:04:15.16,Default,,0,0,0,,-你這種膽小如鼠的人  -別這樣\N{\b0\fs12}- for weak ass punks like you. - Come on, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:17.68,Default,,0,0,0,,市長先生  我想請你寬容一點\N{\b0\fs12}Mr. Mayor. I want to ask for leniency.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.76,0:04:20.77,Default,,0,0,0,,他是我表弟  我帶他入夥的\N{\b0\fs12}The kid's my cousin. I brought him in.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.19,0:04:22.29,Default,,0,0,0,,是嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Oh, you did?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.61,0:04:33.23,Default,,0,0,0,,但願你比他更能成為家族的驕傲\N{\b0\fs12}Now let's hope you do your family prouder than he did.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.60,0:04:35.59,Default,,0,0,0,,天啊\N{\b0\fs12}Oh, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.74,0:04:46.94,Default,,0,0,0,,求你別問我好不好\N{\b0\fs12}Please do not ask me if I'm ok,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.95,0:04:49.38,Default,,0,0,0,,因為每個人都這樣問我  我都快煩死了\N{\b0\fs12}because I am sick to death of everyone asking me that!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.38,0:04:51.38,Default,,0,0,0,,-我不會問的  -很好\N{\b0\fs12}- I would never do that. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.67,0:04:52.61,Default,,0,0,0,,你還好嗎\N{\b0\fs12}You ok?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.38,0:05:01.31,Default,,0,0,0,,娃娃製作者只是你普通的\N{\b0\fs12}The Doll Maker was just your garden variety
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.31,0:05:02.64,Default,,0,0,0,,慘痛經歷\N{\b0\fs12}traumatic experience.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.60,0:05:05.62,Default,,0,0,0,,地震和湯米的事過去後\N{\b0\fs12}After the quake and Tommy,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.25,0:05:07.61,Default,,0,0,0,,我應該已經習慣了\N{\b0\fs12}I should be used to that by now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.61,0:05:08.98,Default,,0,0,0,,我也經歷過這種事\N{\b0\fs12}I've had a few of those.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.27,0:05:11.74,Default,,0,0,0,,永遠沒辦法習慣\N{\b0\fs12}You never get used to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.30,0:05:16.44,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉  奧利弗  我能和你聊聊嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Excuse me, Oliver, may I talk to you for a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.44,0:05:17.79,Default,,0,0,0,,-是急事  -好\N{\b0\fs12}- It's urgent. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.78,0:05:20.10,Default,,0,0,0,,我們一會就說完了\N{\b0\fs12}You can have him back in a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.59,0:05:22.78,Default,,0,0,0,,失陪了\N{\b0\fs12}Excuse us.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.27,0:05:27.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我剛剛想明白了\N{\b0\fs12}I just realized something.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.46,0:05:28.89,Default,,0,0,0,,戴面具的那個人\N{\b0\fs12}What if our masked friend
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.89,0:05:30.48,Default,,0,0,0,,你走到哪她跟到哪的那個  記得吧\N{\b0\fs12}that keeps showing up everywhere you go, you know her?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.48,0:05:31.58,Default,,0,0,0,,怎麼了\N{\b0\fs12}What about her?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.59,0:05:33.68,Default,,0,0,0,,有沒有可能我們一直都想錯了\N{\b0\fs12}What if we've been going about this the wrong way?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.81,0:05:34.99,Default,,0,0,0,,我們認為她對你很感興趣\N{\b0\fs12}We thought she was obsessed with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.99,0:05:37.37,Default,,0,0,0,,你去地檢辦的時候  她出現了\N{\b0\fs12}I mean, she showed up in the D.A.'s office when you were there...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.77,0:05:42.03,Default,,0,0,0,,在娃娃製造者的化學工廠她也出現了\N{\b0\fs12}and in the chemical plant where the Doll Maker was holed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.80,0:05:46.29,Default,,0,0,0,,但是還有誰也出現在這兩個地方\N{\b0\fs12}But who else was at both those places?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.19,0:05:49.65,Default,,0,0,0,,有沒有可能那個人不是在跟蹤你\N{\b0\fs12}What if our masked friend isn't following you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.08,0:05:52.49,Default,,0,0,0,,她是在跟蹤勞蕾爾\N{\b0\fs12}She's following Laurel.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.69,0:06:41.97,Default,,0,0,0,,能再大點聲嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Can it get any louder?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.85,0:06:45.71,Default,,0,0,0,,你為什麼跟蹤勞蕾爾•蘭斯\N{\b0\fs12}Why are you following Laurel Lance?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.72,0:06:47.55,Default,,0,0,0,,我也想問你這個問題\N{\b0\fs12}I could ask the same thing of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.85,0:06:49.72,Default,,0,0,0,,看來有些事永遠不會變\N{\b0\fs12}I guess some things never change.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.58,0:06:53.10,Default,,0,0,0,,你和她  永不分離\N{\b0\fs12}You and her, always and forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.06,0:06:56.16,Default,,0,0,0,,你是誰\N{\b0\fs12}Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.86,0:06:58.93,Default,,0,0,0,,你一旦知道了  你的生活就要變樣了\N{\b0\fs12}Once you know, your life will never be the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.93,0:07:00.02,Default,,0,0,0,,我接受的了\N{\b0\fs12}I could take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.03,0:07:01.18,Default,,0,0,0,,這次不行\N{\b0\fs12}Not this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.98,0:07:03.09,Default,,0,0,0,,奧利\N{\b0\fs12}Ollie.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.74,0:07:21.19,Default,,0,0,0,,勞蕾爾會殺了我的\N{\b0\fs12}Oh, Laurel's going to kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.06,0:07:28.22,Default,,0,0,0,,莎拉\N{\b0\fs12}Sarah?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.18,0:07:30.36,Default,,0,0,0,,莎拉\N{\b0\fs12}Sarah?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.52,0:07:34.25,Default,,0,0,0,,我給你點時間慢慢消化吧\N{\b0\fs12}I'll give you some time to let it sink in.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.53,0:07:59.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}當地女孩隨"金牌奎恩"號失蹤
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.27,0:07:59.46,Default,,0,0,0,,莎拉•蘭斯\N{\b0\fs12}Sarah Lance?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.81,0:08:02.71,Default,,0,0,0,,勞蕾爾的妹妹  那個警探的小女兒\N{\b0\fs12}Laurel's sister? The detective's other daughter,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.71,0:08:04.76,Default,,0,0,0,,你帶上"金牌奎恩"號的那個\N{\b0\fs12}the one that you took on "The Gambit" with you
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.76,0:08:05.98,Default,,0,0,0,,盡管那時你在和勞蕾爾戀愛\N{\b0\fs12}even though you were dating Laurel at the time,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.98,0:08:07.64,Default,,0,0,0,,-我們從沒談過這事  -費利西蒂\N{\b0\fs12}- which we never talked about-- - Felicity.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.91,0:08:09.12,Default,,0,0,0,,很抱歉  只是\N{\b0\fs12}I'm sorry, it's just...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.48,0:08:12.76,Default,,0,0,0,,她  她不是死了嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Isn't she--isn't she dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.76,0:08:14.88,Default,,0,0,0,,你說在"金牌奎恩"號沉沒時她死了\N{\b0\fs12}You told everyone that she died when "The Gambit" went down,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.88,0:08:16.09,Default,,0,0,0,,被淹死了\N{\b0\fs12}that she drowned.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.38,0:08:19.57,Default,,0,0,0,,你說謊了\N{\b0\fs12}You lied.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.45,0:08:23.37,Default,,0,0,0,,"金牌奎恩"號翻船時\N{\b0\fs12}When "The Gambit" capsized, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.88,0:08:27.31,Default,,0,0,0,,莎拉也沉了下去\N{\b0\fs12}Sarah was pulled under.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.77,0:08:30.53,Default,,0,0,0,,當時又黑又冷\N{\b0\fs12}It was so dark and cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.04,0:08:32.98,Default,,0,0,0,,所以我以為她被淹死了\N{\b0\fs12}And I thought she drowned.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.14,0:08:37.00,Default,,0,0,0,,大約一年之後  我看見了她\N{\b0\fs12}About year later, I saw her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.78,0:08:39.26,Default,,0,0,0,,在哪看見的  島上嗎\N{\b0\fs12}You saw where, on the island?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.26,0:08:40.78,Default,,0,0,0,,她也漂到了島上\N{\b0\fs12}She drifted to the island, too?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.93,0:08:42.10,Default,,0,0,0,,不是\N{\b0\fs12}Not exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.19,0:08:44.86,Default,,0,0,0,,你為什麼不告訴她的家人她沒死\N{\b0\fs12}Why didn't you tell the Lances that she didn't die in that boat?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.24,0:08:47.07,Default,,0,0,0,,勞蕾爾和蘭斯先生他們都很責怪你\N{\b0\fs12}Laurel and Mr. Lance, they blame you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.07,0:08:48.31,Default,,0,0,0,,畢竟是我的錯\N{\b0\fs12}Yeah, well, it was my fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.27,0:08:52.55,Default,,0,0,0,,一切都是我的錯\N{\b0\fs12}What happened was my fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.55,0:08:54.21,Default,,0,0,0,,她這些年去哪了  奧利弗\N{\b0\fs12}Well, where has she been all these years, Oliver?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.21,0:08:55.45,Default,,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\b0\fs12}I don't know!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.84,0:09:00.49,Default,,0,0,0,,狄格爾  我發誓真不知道\N{\b0\fs12}Diggle, I swear to God.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.83,0:09:05.16,Default,,0,0,0,,我真的以為她死了\N{\b0\fs12}I was sure she was dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.01,0:09:07.51,Default,,0,0,0,,你有什麼不悲情的故事嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Do you have any happy stories?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.52,0:09:10.44,Default,,0,0,0,,好吧  我再來理一下\N{\b0\fs12}All right, so just to make sure I understand this correctly,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.36,0:09:13.58,Default,,0,0,0,,"金牌奎恩"號沉沒時莎拉沒有淹死\N{\b0\fs12}after not drowning when "The Gambit" went down,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.58,0:09:17.08,Default,,0,0,0,,她不是和你一起登上的島\N{\b0\fs12}Sarah didn't exactly make it to the island with you,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.08,0:09:20.12,Default,,0,0,0,,但是你在島上又一次看到她死了\N{\b0\fs12}where you would see her die yet again.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.45,0:09:22.23,Default,,0,0,0,,-沒什麼要補充的嗎  -現在不想說\N{\b0\fs12}- Feel free to fill in the blanks. - Not right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.23,0:09:23.74,Default,,0,0,0,,你是永遠都不想  對吧  奧利弗\N{\b0\fs12}You mean not ever, don't you, Oliver?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.74,0:09:25.48,Default,,0,0,0,,難道你不覺得她的家人有權利知道\N{\b0\fs12}Don't you think her family had a right to know
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.48,0:09:26.91,Default,,0,0,0,,她也登上了那座島嗎\N{\b0\fs12}that she made it to the island, too?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.91,0:09:28.87,Default,,0,0,0,,那可是五年啊\N{\b0\fs12}These were five years!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.34,0:09:30.65,Default,,0,0,0,,五年啊\N{\b0\fs12}Five years...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.85,0:09:33.92,Default,,0,0,0,,那段時間就沒有好事\N{\b0\fs12}where nothing good happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.24,0:09:40.55,Default,,0,0,0,,他們不知道比知道要好\N{\b0\fs12}And they were better off not knowing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.01,0:09:42.56,Default,,0,0,0,,那他們現在可以知道了嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Do they deserve to know now?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.98,0:09:51.39,Default,,0,0,0,,我要去辦公室處理一下生意的事\N{\b0\fs12}I need to take care of some business at the office.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.15,0:09:53.38,Default,,0,0,0,,市長的事查的怎麼樣了\N{\b0\fs12}Where are we with the Mayor?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.38,0:09:56.84,Default,,0,0,0,,我跟部隊裡的朋友聯繫過\N{\b0\fs12}I'm in contact with some of my military sources.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.91,0:09:58.12,Default,,0,0,0,,想要弄明白\N{\b0\fs12}Trying to get a line on
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.12,0:10:00.45,Default,,0,0,0,,他是如何獲得這些非法軍隊武器裝備的\N{\b0\fs12}how he's getting his illegal army weaponry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.45,0:10:01.81,Default,,0,0,0,,有消息我會通知你\N{\b0\fs12}I'll keep you updated.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.72,0:10:05.85,Default,,0,0,0,,奧利弗  有人告訴過我\N{\b0\fs12}You know, Oliver, somebody once told me that...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.25,0:10:08.60,Default,,0,0,0,,秘密也有重量\N{\b0\fs12}secrets have weight.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.08,0:10:11.12,Default,,0,0,0,,你的秘密越多  你就越難前行\N{\b0\fs12}The more you keep, the harder it is to keep moving.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.90,0:10:16.58,Default,,0,0,0,,你知道我在努力處理\N{\b0\fs12}You see how hard I work out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.41,0:10:33.87,Default,,0,0,0,,你殺了我兩個手下\N{\b0\fs12}You kill two of my crew.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.43,0:10:37.34,Default,,0,0,0,,跟你一起在島上的還有多少人\N{\b0\fs12}How many others are with you on the island?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.56,0:10:40.45,Default,,0,0,0,,你們的武器怎麼樣\N{\b0\fs12}What are your weapon capabilities?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.26,0:10:44.63,Default,,0,0,0,,你們找到墓地了嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Did you find the graves?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.68,0:10:48.91,Default,,0,0,0,,你有兩個選擇\N{\b0\fs12}Two things will happen--
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.09,0:10:51.30,Default,,0,0,0,,告訴我我想知道的事\N{\b0\fs12}You will tell me everything I want to know,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.62,0:10:52.95,Default,,0,0,0,,然後我殺了你\N{\b0\fs12}then I will kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.72,0:10:54.95,Default,,0,0,0,,或者我對你大刑伺候\N{\b0\fs12}Or I will torture you
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.95,0:10:56.89,Default,,0,0,0,,直到你開口\N{\b0\fs12}until you tell me everything I want to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.89,0:10:58.53,Default,,0,0,0,,然後我再殺了你\N{\b0\fs12}and then I will kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.50,0:11:15.70,Default,,0,0,0,,下地獄去吧\N{\b0\fs12}Go to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.94,0:11:17.02,Default,,0,0,0,,去不了\N{\b0\fs12}Can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.85,0:11:19.28,Default,,0,0,0,,我們已經在地獄裡了\N{\b0\fs12}We're already there.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.29,0:11:42.27,Default,,0,0,0,,跟你說了\N{\b0\fs12}Told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.27,0:11:43.82,Default,,0,0,0,,第五大道和布魯街上的帕蒂小屋\N{\b0\fs12}The Patty Shack on 5th and Berwer,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.82,0:11:45.07,Default,,0,0,0,,做的漢堡最好吃\N{\b0\fs12}best burgers in town.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.07,0:11:47.19,Default,,0,0,0,,帕蒂小屋在市長的地盤上\N{\b0\fs12}Well, Patty Shack's in the Mayor's territory,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.19,0:11:51.66,Default,,0,0,0,,所以我得冒著槍林彈雨去買早餐\N{\b0\fs12}so I'll take a sub par breakfast over a bullet.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.20,0:11:58.33,Default,,0,0,0,,怎麼了\N{\b0\fs12}What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.52,0:12:02.14,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道我很瘦  但是我能吃下兩個  真的\N{\b0\fs12}Look, I know I'm skinny, but I can eat two of these, and I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.93,0:12:05.63,Default,,0,0,0,,遇到了前男友\N{\b0\fs12}Just ran into an old boyfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.88,0:12:11.09,Default,,0,0,0,,我\N{\b0\fs12}I'm just...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.95,0:12:15.23,Default,,0,0,0,,擔心他會告訴我的家人我回來了\N{\b0\fs12}worried that he might tell my family I'm back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.24,0:12:16.76,Default,,0,0,0,,你在星城還有家人\N{\b0\fs12}You have family in Starling?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.80,0:12:17.78,Default,,0,0,0,,是的\N{\b0\fs12}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.12,0:12:21.66,Default,,0,0,0,,我父親  他是個員警\N{\b0\fs12}My father, he's a-- he's a policeman.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.54,0:12:24.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我姐姐  是個律師\N{\b0\fs12}And my sister, she's a lawyer.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.23,0:12:27.42,Default,,0,0,0,,他們一定會為你這個蒙面罪犯"驕傲"的\N{\b0\fs12}Well, they must be real proud of their masked delinquent.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.05,0:12:33.59,Default,,0,0,0,,他們以為我死了\N{\b0\fs12}Yeah, they think I'm dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.96,0:12:35.18,Default,,0,0,0,,好啊\N{\b0\fs12}Oh, cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.07,0:12:37.26,Default,,0,0,0,,我的家人也以為我死了\N{\b0\fs12}My folks think I'm dead, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.26,0:12:39.99,Default,,0,0,0,,或者他們希望沒生下我\N{\b0\fs12}that, or they wish I'd never been born.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.30,0:12:41.38,Default,,0,0,0,,就這兩個可能\N{\b0\fs12}One of those.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.21,0:12:44.92,Default,,0,0,0,,為什麼  你不想讓他們\N{\b0\fs12}Why...don't you want them
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.92,0:12:46.47,Default,,0,0,0,,知道你還活著\N{\b0\fs12}to know that you're still alive?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.19,0:12:50.68,Default,,0,0,0,,因為我已經不是以前的我了\N{\b0\fs12}'Cause I'm not what they remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.59,0:12:54.04,Default,,0,0,0,,爸爸的好女兒\N{\b0\fs12}Good little daddy's girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.63,0:12:55.94,Default,,0,0,0,,絕對不是\N{\b0\fs12}Actually far from it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.44,0:12:58.69,Default,,0,0,0,,我以前很像你\N{\b0\fs12}I was a lot like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.90,0:13:01.98,Default,,0,0,0,,所以\N{\b0\fs12}Is that...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.55,0:13:04.68,Default,,0,0,0,,那晚你從那些人手裡把我救下\N{\b0\fs12}why you saved me from those guys that night?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.03,0:13:10.17,Default,,0,0,0,,所有女人都不該在男人手中被折磨\N{\b0\fs12}No woman should ever suffer at the hands of men.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.94,0:13:16.59,Default,,0,0,0,,我們不能再這麼見面了\N{\b0\fs12}We've got to stop meeting like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.87,0:13:18.52,Default,,0,0,0,,你女朋友會怎麼想啊  約翰\N{\b0\fs12}What would your girlfriend think, Johnny?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.34,0:13:20.49,Default,,0,0,0,,萊拉  你沒見我這些日子\N{\b0\fs12}Lyla, I am checking the box
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.49,0:13:21.85,Default,,0,0,0,,身上貼著"單身"標簽麼\N{\b0\fs12}marked "Single" these days.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.01,0:13:24.43,Default,,0,0,0,,真遺憾  發生了什麼\N{\b0\fs12}Sorry to hear it. What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.43,0:13:26.29,Default,,0,0,0,,另一個男人"插足"了\N{\b0\fs12}Well, another man came between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.34,0:13:28.38,Default,,0,0,0,,死亡射手\N{\b0\fs12}Deadshot.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.32,0:13:30.40,Default,,0,0,0,,他真是一而再再而三的\N{\b0\fs12}You're getting in the bad habit
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.40,0:13:31.53,Default,,0,0,0,,破壞你的生活啊\N{\b0\fs12}of letting him ruin your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.53,0:13:33.15,Default,,0,0,0,,這話我也一而再再而三的聽到了\N{\b0\fs12}So I've been repeatedly told.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.72,0:13:35.65,Default,,0,0,0,,被盜竊的軍火有什麼消息嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Anything on those stolen army weapons?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.73,0:13:37.26,Default,,0,0,0,,兩個月前卡比軍營丟失了\N{\b0\fs12}A crate of 12 M4A1s went missing
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.26,0:13:38.92,Default,,0,0,0,,一箱12毫米M4A1步槍\N{\b0\fs12}from Camp Kirby two month age.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.92,0:13:40.28,Default,,0,0,0,,我想我知道這些槍的去向\N{\b0\fs12}Yeah, I think I know where they went.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.28,0:13:41.93,Default,,0,0,0,,箱子上都裝有定位系統\N{\b0\fs12}Every crate was fitted with a GPS system
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.93,0:13:43.37,Default,,0,0,0,,應該可以被遠程追蹤\N{\b0\fs12}so they could be remote tracked.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.52,0:13:45.48,Default,,0,0,0,,我試過  但是沒反應\N{\b0\fs12}I tried pulling it up but it's not receiving.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.49,0:13:46.92,Default,,0,0,0,,肯定是被人弄失效了\N{\b0\fs12}Must have been deactivated.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.37,0:13:48.01,Default,,0,0,0,,謝謝  萊拉\N{\b0\fs12}Thanks, Lyla.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.01,0:13:49.46,Default,,0,0,0,,你為什麼會對這個感興趣呢\N{\b0\fs12}And your interest in this is what?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.70,0:13:53.79,Default,,0,0,0,,萊拉  你和我去阿富汗斯坦是想\N{\b0\fs12}Lyla, you and I went to Afghanistan to try to
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.79,0:13:55.38,Default,,0,0,0,,是想給那個被戰爭販子用武器肆虐的國家\N{\b0\fs12}bring law and order to a country overrun
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.38,0:13:57.16,Default,,0,0,0,,帶去法律與秩序  對嗎\N{\b0\fs12}by war lords with weapons, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.27,0:14:00.06,Default,,0,0,0,,那我們對自己的城市不是應該更加關心嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Should we do any less for our own cities?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.98,0:14:03.13,Default,,0,0,0,,再次感謝\N{\b0\fs12}Thanks again.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.56,0:14:05.96,Default,,0,0,0,,-約翰  -怎麼\N{\b0\fs12}- Hey, Johnny. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.96,0:14:08.74,Default,,0,0,0,,目前我身上也貼著"單身"標簽\N{\b0\fs12}These days, I check the box marked single, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.45,0:14:18.54,Default,,0,0,0,,布拉德先生  看來你見過羅切夫小姐了\N{\b0\fs12}Mr. Blood. I see you've met Miss Rochev.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.60,0:14:20.18,Default,,0,0,0,,-她是我的  -上級\N{\b0\fs12}- She's my-- - Superior.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.18,0:14:21.69,Default,,0,0,0,,-合作者  -名義上的\N{\b0\fs12}- Partner. - On paper.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.40,0:14:24.12,Default,,0,0,0,,這就是你叫我過來的原因  奎恩先生\N{\b0\fs12}Is that why you asked me to come down here, Mr. Queen,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.12,0:14:25.46,Default,,0,0,0,,來調解你的工作頭銜嗎\N{\b0\fs12}to mediate your job title?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.46,0:14:27.81,Default,,0,0,0,,你和我之間總是一開始就不順利\N{\b0\fs12}You and I have gotten off on the wrong foot repeatedly.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.13,0:14:29.84,Default,,0,0,0,,這簡直成你的超能力了吧\N{\b0\fs12}Seems to be your super power.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.88,0:14:33.62,Default,,0,0,0,,你那晚關於貧民區槍支暴力的言論\N{\b0\fs12}I was inspired by what you said the other night
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.62,0:14:35.21,Default,,0,0,0,,使我很受啟發\N{\b0\fs12}about gun violence in the Glades.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.05,0:14:37.39,Default,,0,0,0,,我有個主意也許能幫上忙\N{\b0\fs12}And I had an idea that might help.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.39,0:14:39.96,Default,,0,0,0,,是嗎  在你的深宅大院再來一場派對嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Really? Another party at your stately manor?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.96,0:14:42.53,Default,,0,0,0,,不  我想贊助一次"槍支換現金"活動\N{\b0\fs12}No. I wanted to sponsor a cash for guns event.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.53,0:14:44.58,Default,,0,0,0,,我給你錢  你讓你的居民們\N{\b0\fs12}I give you the money and you get your constituents
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.58,0:14:47.34,Default,,0,0,0,,放下手中的武器  大家都高興\N{\b0\fs12}to lay down their arms. Everybody wins.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.10,0:14:50.32,Default,,0,0,0,,特別是你\N{\b0\fs12}Especially you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.09,0:14:53.39,Default,,0,0,0,,通過解除貧民區的武器\N{\b0\fs12}Trying to repair your family's tainted name
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.63,0:14:55.28,Default,,0,0,0,,來洗刷你們家族的汙名\N{\b0\fs12}by ridding the Glades of guns.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.42,0:14:57.00,Default,,0,0,0,,你把錢拿好就行  布拉德先生\N{\b0\fs12}You just get the money, Mr. Blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.00,0:14:59.91,Default,,0,0,0,,我不希望我的家族之名被提及\N{\b0\fs12}I don't want my family's name involved.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.91,0:15:02.76,Default,,0,0,0,,奎恩先生  我能跟你說幾句嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Mr. Queen, may I have a word with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.62,0:15:05.12,Default,,0,0,0,,讓我考慮考慮\N{\b0\fs12}Let me think it over.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.10,0:15:13.72,Default,,0,0,0,,我們不會贊助那個活動\N{\b0\fs12}We are not sponsoring that event.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.72,0:15:14.66,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\b0\fs12}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.30,0:15:16.23,Default,,0,0,0,,是我贊助\N{\b0\fs12}I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.23,0:15:17.67,Default,,0,0,0,,用什麼錢\N{\b0\fs12}With what money?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.10,0:15:20.18,Default,,0,0,0,,你的投資派對花掉了公司五萬美元\N{\b0\fs12}Your investment party cost QC 50 grand,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.18,0:15:22.03,Default,,0,0,0,,卻沒有任何人投資一分錢\N{\b0\fs12}and no one invested a dime.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.22,0:15:24.33,Default,,0,0,0,,我不會再繼續批準公司撥款\N{\b0\fs12}I will not continue to authorize corporate funds
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.33,0:15:28.27,Default,,0,0,0,,好讓你假裝自己還是總裁\N{\b0\fs12}just so you can keep pretending that you are the CEO.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.26,0:15:30.46,Default,,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\b0\fs12}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.65,0:15:32.49,Default,,0,0,0,,我自己掏錢\N{\b0\fs12}I'll pay for it myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.80,0:15:33.83,Default,,0,0,0,,你大概還沒注意到\N{\b0\fs12}Maybe you haven't noticed,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.83,0:15:35.96,Default,,0,0,0,,你的個人信用已經今非昔比\N{\b0\fs12}but your personal trust isn't exactly what it used to be,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.96,0:15:38.47,Default,,0,0,0,,這家公司也一樣\N{\b0\fs12}and this company isn't, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.90,0:15:41.29,Default,,0,0,0,,雖然我也想讓這個城市變得更安全\N{\b0\fs12}As much as I would love to make this city safer,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.29,0:15:44.94,Default,,0,0,0,,但我的首要職責是奎恩聯合企業\N{\b0\fs12}my first obligation is to Gueen Consolidated.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.48,0:15:47.10,Default,,0,0,0,,你也一樣\N{\b0\fs12}And yours is, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.57,0:16:07.01,Default,,0,0,0,,我正準備訂外賣  你要嗎\N{\b0\fs12}I was going to order some takeout, you want in?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.01,0:16:08.91,Default,,0,0,0,,謝謝你的好意  亞當  但是\N{\b0\fs12}I appreciate the offer, Adam, but--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.91,0:16:10.52,Default,,0,0,0,,這周每天晚上我都吃得外賣\N{\b0\fs12}I've eaten takeout every night this week,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.52,0:16:12.27,Default,,0,0,0,,我需要下一次正經館子了\N{\b0\fs12}I need a meal served on an actual plate.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.27,0:16:13.56,Default,,0,0,0,,你也是\N{\b0\fs12}So do you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.57,0:16:15.67,Default,,0,0,0,,我明白了\N{\b0\fs12}I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.98,0:16:18.63,Default,,0,0,0,,工作很容易就會占滿生活\N{\b0\fs12}It's easy to let the job become your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.66,0:16:20.84,Default,,0,0,0,,我一直提醒自己要去健身房\N{\b0\fs12}I keep having to remind myself to go to the gym,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.84,0:16:23.30,Default,,0,0,0,,去看電影  去吃大餐\N{\b0\fs12}see a movie, eat a good meal.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.73,0:16:27.78,Default,,0,0,0,,聽起來非常像是有生活情趣了\N{\b0\fs12}That sounds dangerously like having a life.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.39,0:16:31.02,Default,,0,0,0,,那你呢  你不可能只有工作吧\N{\b0\fs12}What about you? You can't be all about work.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.64,0:16:34.86,Default,,0,0,0,,我工作時候狀態是最好的\N{\b0\fs12}I'm the best me when I am working.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.86,0:16:36.60,Default,,0,0,0,,那你什麼時候狀態不好呢\N{\b0\fs12}And when you're not?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.91,0:16:38.74,Default,,0,0,0,,你不會想看到的\N{\b0\fs12}You don't want to meet her.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.98,0:16:40.77,Default,,0,0,0,,那樣的我可不太友善\N{\b0\fs12}She's not good company.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.87,0:16:43.76,Default,,0,0,0,,我願意冒這個險\N{\b0\fs12}I'd be willing to risk it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.17,0:16:49.39,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉\N{\b0\fs12}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.89,0:16:51.11,Default,,0,0,0,,我剛想起來\N{\b0\fs12}I just remembered.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.11,0:16:52.33,Default,,0,0,0,,我得走了\N{\b0\fs12}I have to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.33,0:16:53.98,Default,,0,0,0,,很抱歉  我不是故意要\N{\b0\fs12}I'm sorry. I didn't mean to--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.98,0:16:55.78,Default,,0,0,0,,不  沒事\N{\b0\fs12}No, it's ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.78,0:16:57.04,Default,,0,0,0,,沒關係\N{\b0\fs12}It's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.43,0:16:58.84,Default,,0,0,0,,我只是該走了\N{\b0\fs12}I just have to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.90,0:17:03.08,Default,,0,0,0,,晚安\N{\b0\fs12}Good night.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.16,0:17:04.32,Default,,0,0,0,,晚安\N{\b0\fs12}Good night.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.66,0:17:25.20,Default,,0,0,0,,糟了\N{\b0\fs12}Crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.20,0:17:30.02,Default,,0,0,0,,駕照和行駛證\N{\b0\fs12}License and registration?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.55,0:17:32.03,Default,,0,0,0,,有什麼問題嗎  警官\N{\b0\fs12}Is there a problem, officer?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.03,0:17:34.11,Default,,0,0,0,,你今晚是不是喝酒了  女士\N{\b0\fs12}Have you had anything to drink tonight, ma'am?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.46,0:17:39.30,Default,,0,0,0,,我是勞蕾爾•蘭斯\N{\b0\fs12}I'm Laurel Lance.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.61,0:17:41.28,Default,,0,0,0,,我是地區助理檢察官\N{\b0\fs12}I'm an Assistant District Attorney.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.28,0:17:42.12,Default,,0,0,0,,抱歉  蘭斯小姐\N{\b0\fs12}I'm sorry, Miss Lance,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.12,0:17:44.81,Default,,0,0,0,,恐怕我得讓你從車裡出來\N{\b0\fs12}but I'm going to have to ask you to step out of the car, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.19,0:17:49.90,Default,,0,0,0,,我需要一些好消息\N{\b0\fs12}I need some good news.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.39,0:17:52.07,Default,,0,0,0,,先說壞消息吧\N{\b0\fs12}The bad news first.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.07,0:17:53.58,Default,,0,0,0,,市長的確跟一箱\N{\b0\fs12}Somehow the Mayor did get his hands
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.59,0:17:57.32,Default,,0,0,0,,來自科比軍營的軍用武器有關\N{\b0\fs12}on a crate of military-grade weapons from Camp Kirby.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.68,0:17:59.10,Default,,0,0,0,,好消息呢\N{\b0\fs12}The good news?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.19,0:18:00.12,Default,,0,0,0,,如果他拿著箱子\N{\b0\fs12}If he kept the crate,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.12,0:18:02.05,Default,,0,0,0,,也許能找到他的藏身之所\N{\b0\fs12}might be able to find where he's hiding.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.15,0:18:04.20,Default,,0,0,0,,這個追蹤系統跟軍方裝在所有武器箱上的\N{\b0\fs12}This is the same make and model of a tracking system
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.20,0:18:06.28,Default,,0,0,0,,系統用了同樣的工藝和模型\N{\b0\fs12}the army installs on all of its weapons crates.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.28,0:18:08.92,Default,,0,0,0,,如果他們丟了武器箱  就會發射一個\N{\b0\fs12}If they lose a crate, they send out
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.92,0:18:10.12,Default,,0,0,0,,遠程信號來啟動示警\N{\b0\fs12}a remote signal that activates the beacon.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.12,0:18:11.05,Default,,0,0,0,,市長很聰明\N{\b0\fs12}The Mayor's clever.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.05,0:18:12.35,Default,,0,0,0,,他讓他的示警失效了\N{\b0\fs12}He deactivated his beacon.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.35,0:18:14.13,Default,,0,0,0,,發送信號  沒有任何反應\N{\b0\fs12}Send a signal, nothing comes back.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.13,0:18:17.00,Default,,0,0,0,,你們倆都需要改進一下對好消息的定義了\N{\b0\fs12}You both need to work on your definition of good news.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.00,0:18:18.99,Default,,0,0,0,,好吧  那這個怎麼樣\N{\b0\fs12}Ok. How's this--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.99,0:18:22.05,Default,,0,0,0,,猜猜是哪個公司設計了這個軍用追蹤系統\N{\b0\fs12}Guess which company designed the tracking system the army uses?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.05,0:18:25.81,Default,,0,0,0,,給你個提示  你的總裁  總是晚一步\N{\b0\fs12}I'll give you a hint -- your CEO? Always late.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.84,0:18:27.11,Default,,0,0,0,,很好\N{\b0\fs12}Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.70,0:18:30.13,Default,,0,0,0,,我進入了奎恩聯合企業主機的初始平面圖\N{\b0\fs12}I pulled up the original plans from the QC mainframe.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.13,0:18:31.64,Default,,0,0,0,,發現裡面有個設計瑕疵\N{\b0\fs12}Turns out there's a design flaw.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.64,0:18:34.20,Default,,0,0,0,,警報器依然對子信號波很敏感\N{\b0\fs12}The beacon is still susceptible to a subform wave
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.20,0:18:35.51,Default,,0,0,0,,即使它已被暫停\N{\b0\fs12}even if it's been deactivated.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.51,0:18:36.86,Default,,0,0,0,,市長把它關了  奧利弗\N{\b0\fs12}The Mayor turned it off, Oliver.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.86,0:18:38.40,Default,,0,0,0,,我們可以把它再打開\N{\b0\fs12}We can turn it back on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.34,0:18:45.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}檢測到警報器
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.42,0:18:48.06,Default,,0,0,0,,失竊武器是您訂購的吧  奎恩先生\N{\b0\fs12}I believe you ordered the crate of stolen military weapons, Mr. Queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.58,0:19:00.92,Default,,0,0,0,,不是叫你們把追蹤器關掉嗎\N{\b0\fs12}I thought you deactivated the tracker!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.78,0:19:11.90,Default,,0,0,0,,快撤\N{\b0\fs12}Go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.32,0:19:19.41,Default,,0,0,0,,掩護\N{\b0\fs12}Cover!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.32,0:19:34.53,Default,,0,0,0,,武器都還在\N{\b0\fs12}Weapons are secure.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.53,0:19:36.00,Default,,0,0,0,,市長呢\N{\b0\fs12}And the Mayor?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.43,0:19:39.10,Default,,0,0,0,,還沒抓到\N{\b0\fs12}Still in office.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.70,0:19:48.84,Default,,0,0,0,,多謝你告訴我  戴利警官\N{\b0\fs12}Thanks for the heads up, Officer Daily.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.84,0:19:50.62,Default,,0,0,0,,順便說一下\N{\b0\fs12}Just FYI--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.90,0:19:53.37,Default,,0,0,0,,她的酒精測試比標準高出0.6\N{\b0\fs12}She blew 0.6 past the legal limit.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.76,0:19:55.87,Default,,0,0,0,,謝謝\N{\b0\fs12}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.48,0:20:00.37,Default,,0,0,0,,他沒必要給你打電話的\N{\b0\fs12}He didn't need to call you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.90,0:20:02.07,Default,,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\b0\fs12}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.25,0:20:04.17,Default,,0,0,0,,但幸虧他給我打了\N{\b0\fs12}But you're lucky he did.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.81,0:20:05.74,Default,,0,0,0,,你可能會丟掉工作\N{\b0\fs12}You could have lost your job.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.74,0:20:06.63,Default,,0,0,0,,可能喪命\N{\b0\fs12}You could have lost your life,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.63,0:20:08.71,Default,,0,0,0,,還可能撞死別人\N{\b0\fs12}and you could have killed somebody!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.78,0:20:11.67,Default,,0,0,0,,我晚餐的時候多喝了幾杯\N{\b0\fs12}I had a few too many glasses of wine at dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.67,0:20:12.78,Default,,0,0,0,,這只是意外\N{\b0\fs12}It was an accident!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.78,0:20:15.42,Default,,0,0,0,,意外  那些意外就是這麼發生的\N{\b0\fs12}An accident. Well, I guess those happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.42,0:20:17.80,Default,,0,0,0,,你這是什麼語氣啊\N{\b0\fs12}Was I not supposed to notice that tone?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.05,0:20:20.21,Default,,0,0,0,,我們倆\N{\b0\fs12}The two of us...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.21,0:20:22.20,Default,,0,0,0,,你很多地方都隨我  勞蕾爾\N{\b0\fs12}You got a lot from me, Laurel.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.28,0:20:24.04,Default,,0,0,0,,也許嗜酒也隨了我\N{\b0\fs12}Maybe you got this, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.04,0:20:27.62,Default,,0,0,0,,你怎麼把我的小失誤跟你的嗜酒相提並論\N{\b0\fs12}You can hardly compare my one mistake to your drinking problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.63,0:20:30.08,Default,,0,0,0,,現在只是一個小失誤\N{\b0\fs12}So long as it is only one mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.78,0:20:32.91,Default,,0,0,0,,我不知道你有沒有注意到\N{\b0\fs12}I don't know if you've noticed...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.47,0:20:36.28,Default,,0,0,0,,我最近過得不太好\N{\b0\fs12}but I've had a little bit of a hard time lately.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.10,0:20:39.81,Default,,0,0,0,,被綁架  差點被一個瘋子殺了\N{\b0\fs12}I was kidnapped, nearly murdered by a psychopath,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.81,0:20:41.62,Default,,0,0,0,,而且男朋友也死了\N{\b0\fs12}and my boyfriend died.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.81,0:20:43.40,Default,,0,0,0,,我不知道  可以的話...\N{\b0\fs12}So, I don't know, maybe...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.94,0:20:45.14,Default,,0,0,0,,放我一馬吧\N{\b0\fs12}cut me some slack.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.14,0:20:46.73,Default,,0,0,0,,當我在困難的時期\N{\b0\fs12}You know, when I started having a hard time,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.73,0:20:49.62,Default,,0,0,0,,希望的是別人沒有放我一馬\N{\b0\fs12}I wish people had not cut me slack.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.65,0:20:52.24,Default,,0,0,0,,把你的車停在這兒  我載你回家\N{\b0\fs12}Leave your car here, I'm driving you home.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.24,0:20:54.25,Default,,0,0,0,,-我打車  -勞蕾爾\N{\b0\fs12}- I'll take a cab.  - Laurel...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.63,0:20:55.81,Default,,0,0,0,,勞蕾爾\N{\b0\fs12}Laurel!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.20,0:21:05.49,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}威登酒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.32,0:21:38.30,Default,,0,0,0,,你有沒有告訴我家人我還活著\N{\b0\fs12}Did you tell my family that I'm alive?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.30,0:21:39.45,Default,,0,0,0,,沒有\N{\b0\fs12}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.48,0:21:45.65,Default,,0,0,0,,莎拉\N{\b0\fs12}Sara.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.12,0:21:49.60,Default,,0,0,0,,我親眼看到你死了\N{\b0\fs12}I saw you die.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.60,0:21:52.47,Default,,0,0,0,,這不是第一次了  對嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Not the first time that's happened, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.47,0:21:54.45,Default,,0,0,0,,我也以為你死了\N{\b0\fs12}And I thought you were dead, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.45,0:21:57.16,Default,,0,0,0,,斯萊德怎麼樣了\N{\b0\fs12}What happened to Slade?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.17,0:21:59.67,Default,,0,0,0,,你去哪裡了\N{\b0\fs12}Where have you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.04,0:22:00.92,Default,,0,0,0,,哪裡都去了\N{\b0\fs12}Everywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.92,0:22:02.10,Default,,0,0,0,,這不是問題的答案\N{\b0\fs12}That's not an answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.11,0:22:03.99,Default,,0,0,0,,這就是我給你的答案\N{\b0\fs12}Well, it's the one you're getting.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.89,0:22:10.61,Default,,0,0,0,,大約一年之前\N{\b0\fs12}About a year ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.28,0:22:12.91,Default,,0,0,0,,我開始聽說\N{\b0\fs12}I started hearing tales
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.91,0:22:15.67,Default,,0,0,0,,星城治安維持者的故事\N{\b0\fs12}of the Starling City vigilante.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.97,0:22:18.96,Default,,0,0,0,,戴著綠兜帽的男人\N{\b0\fs12}The man in the green hood.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.08,0:22:20.57,Default,,0,0,0,,我就知道是你\N{\b0\fs12}I knew it was you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.77,0:22:22.90,Default,,0,0,0,,我不知道你竟變成了一個打手\N{\b0\fs12}I had never known you as much of a fighter.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.90,0:22:24.23,Default,,0,0,0,,你從哪裡練得這一手\N{\b0\fs12}Where did you pick that up?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.23,0:22:26.17,Default,,0,0,0,,我遇上了一些高人\N{\b0\fs12}I met some rough people.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.27,0:22:28.60,Default,,0,0,0,,-覺得自己也應該成為高人  -莎拉\N{\b0\fs12}- Thought I should get rougher, too.  - Sara.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.66,0:22:31.92,Default,,0,0,0,,你為什麼要回來\N{\b0\fs12}Why did you come back?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.40,0:22:37.12,Default,,0,0,0,,因為地震\N{\b0\fs12}The earthquake.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.62,0:22:40.31,Default,,0,0,0,,你想確認家裡人是否都安好\N{\b0\fs12}Because you wanted to make sure your family was safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.95,0:22:43.06,Default,,0,0,0,,但你還留在這兒\N{\b0\fs12}But now you're still here,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.06,0:22:44.54,Default,,0,0,0,,看著他們\N{\b0\fs12}watching over them.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.57,0:22:48.03,Default,,0,0,0,,保護他們\N{\b0\fs12}Protecting them.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.26,0:22:53.26,Default,,0,0,0,,你來這裡就是為了確認我沒有告訴他們嗎\N{\b0\fs12}So, did you come here to make sure I didn't tell them?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.33,0:22:56.61,Default,,0,0,0,,還是你其實希望我已經告訴了他們\N{\b0\fs12}Or because you were hoping I had?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.04,0:23:03.40,Default,,0,0,0,,我去處理一下\N{\b0\fs12}I'll get rid of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.37,0:23:12.71,Default,,0,0,0,,蘭斯先生\N{\b0\fs12}Mr. Lance?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.25,0:23:19.11,Default,,0,0,0,,有什麼能幫您的嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Something I can help you with?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.18,0:23:22.79,Default,,0,0,0,,我是為我女兒來的\N{\b0\fs12}I'm here about my daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.06,0:23:27.39,Default,,0,0,0,,勞蕾爾\N{\b0\fs12}Laurel.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.69,0:23:28.37,Default,,0,0,0,,她還好嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Is she ok?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.37,0:23:31.23,Default,,0,0,0,,其實  她不好\N{\b0\fs12}Yeah. Well, no, she's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.23,0:23:33.77,Default,,0,0,0,,她昨晚酒後駕車被員警攔下了\N{\b0\fs12}She got pulled over for a DUI last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.15,0:23:36.27,Default,,0,0,0,,我想試著跟她談一談  但是...\N{\b0\fs12}I tried talking to her about it, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.44,0:23:38.19,Default,,0,0,0,,她不聽\N{\b0\fs12}she wasn't hearing me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.47,0:23:41.40,Default,,0,0,0,,我前幾天晚上看到她了  她...\N{\b0\fs12}I--I saw her the other night. She...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.20,0:23:43.85,Default,,0,0,0,,看起來不像原來的她了\N{\b0\fs12}didn't seem like herself.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.85,0:23:46.34,Default,,0,0,0,,對  我知道  她看起來像我\N{\b0\fs12}No, I know. She seems like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.56,0:23:51.03,Default,,0,0,0,,不知你是否知道\N{\b0\fs12}I don't know if you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.03,0:23:54.79,Default,,0,0,0,,你和莎拉失蹤以後\N{\b0\fs12}but when you and Sara disappeared,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.62,0:23:57.46,Default,,0,0,0,,我成天都在酗酒\N{\b0\fs12}I hit the bottle pretty hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.55,0:23:59.63,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道你們是朋友\N{\b0\fs12}I know the two of you are friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.98,0:24:02.94,Default,,0,0,0,,她需要朋友\N{\b0\fs12}And she needs a friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.65,0:24:07.15,Default,,0,0,0,,跟她聊聊吧\N{\b0\fs12}Maybe talk to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.83,0:24:09.03,Default,,0,0,0,,好的\N{\b0\fs12}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.31,0:24:13.53,Default,,0,0,0,,就這樣吧\N{\b0\fs12}Anyhow.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.56,0:24:16.29,Default,,0,0,0,,-蘭斯先生  -什麼事\N{\b0\fs12}- Mr. Lance.  - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.36,0:24:25.60,Default,,0,0,0,,我很樂意跟勞蕾爾聊聊\N{\b0\fs12}I'd be happy to talk to Laurel.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.30,0:24:51.23,Default,,0,0,0,,為什麼\N{\b0\fs12}Why...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.25,0:24:53.04,Default,,0,0,0,,為什麼\N{\b0\fs12}why...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.04,0:24:56.06,Default,,0,0,0,,為什麼要這麼對我\N{\b0\fs12}Why'd they do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.47,0:24:58.73,Default,,0,0,0,,所有人都要經歷的\N{\b0\fs12}They make all of us do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.28,0:25:02.75,Default,,0,0,0,,應該是顯示實力\N{\b0\fs12}Supposed to show "prochnost".
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.71,0:25:07.11,Default,,0,0,0,,這是俄語\N{\b0\fs12}It's Russian.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.67,0:25:09.12,Default,,0,0,0,,實力\N{\b0\fs12}For strength.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.25,0:25:15.45,Default,,0,0,0,,他們這麼做就是為了看我強不強壯\N{\b0\fs12}They--they did it to see if I'm strong?!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.45,0:25:18.58,Default,,0,0,0,,他們是想看你能不能熬過來\N{\b0\fs12}They're doing this to see if you survive.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.63,0:25:19.96,Default,,0,0,0,,弱者\N{\b0\fs12}Living...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.44,0:25:24.41,Default,,0,0,0,,是活不下去的\N{\b0\fs12}is not for the weak.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.75,0:26:15.91,Default,,0,0,0,,奧利弗\N{\b0\fs12}Oliver.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.71,0:26:19.13,Default,,0,0,0,,你怎麼會在這裡  出什麼事了嗎\N{\b0\fs12}What are you doing here? Is everything ok?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.13,0:26:21.59,Default,,0,0,0,,我也不知道  出什麼事了嗎\N{\b0\fs12}I don't know. Is everything ok?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.47,0:26:24.98,Default,,0,0,0,,開玩笑呢吧\N{\b0\fs12}You've got to be kidding me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.98,0:26:26.79,Default,,0,0,0,,我爸居然去找你了\N{\b0\fs12}My dad went to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.85,0:26:28.75,Default,,0,0,0,,他過去六年都在詛咒你\N{\b0\fs12}He spent the last six years cursing your name,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.75,0:26:31.09,Default,,0,0,0,,-現在你卻成了他的閨蜜  -勞蕾爾\N{\b0\fs12}- and now you're what, gossip buddies? - Laurel.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.09,0:26:32.96,Default,,0,0,0,,他很擔心你\N{\b0\fs12}He's worried about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.11,0:26:34.52,Default,,0,0,0,,棒極了\N{\b0\fs12}Perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.01,0:26:38.24,Default,,0,0,0,,你曾經是酒鬼  還是狂歡公子\N{\b0\fs12}A recovering alcoholic and recovering party boy
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.24,0:26:40.20,Default,,0,0,0,,竟然對我的生活指手畫腳\N{\b0\fs12}trying to tell me how to live my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.20,0:26:41.78,Default,,0,0,0,,你不覺得這很假嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Don't you see the hypocrisy there?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.78,0:26:45.68,Default,,0,0,0,,我只知道一個我們倆都關心的人\N{\b0\fs12}What I see is somebody that both of us care for
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.82,0:26:47.74,Default,,0,0,0,,現在過得很不順\N{\b0\fs12}having a rough go of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.30,0:26:51.78,Default,,0,0,0,,你知道我多少次把我爸從酒吧裡拖出來\N{\b0\fs12}Do you know how many times I've had to pull my dad out of a bar?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.78,0:26:53.73,Default,,0,0,0,,多少個夜晚我得開車送他回家\N{\b0\fs12}Or how many nights I've had to drive him home
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.73,0:26:56.00,Default,,0,0,0,,而他在我車後座就這麼睡著了\N{\b0\fs12}where he's passed out in my backseat?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.29,0:26:58.22,Default,,0,0,0,,有問題的是他\N{\b0\fs12}He's the one with the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.35,0:27:00.62,Default,,0,0,0,,不是我\N{\b0\fs12}Not me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.23,0:27:02.95,Default,,0,0,0,,他接受不了失去莎拉這一事實\N{\b0\fs12}Just because he can't cope with losing Sara
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.95,0:27:05.30,Default,,0,0,0,,不代表我過不好自己的生活\N{\b0\fs12}doesn't mean I can't handle my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.66,0:27:09.25,Default,,0,0,0,,下次你們閨中密話的時候記得告訴他\N{\b0\fs12}Feel free to tell him that during the next chit chat.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.37,0:27:29.70,Default,,0,0,0,,看來你縫紉技術不怎麼樣\N{\b0\fs12}Sewing is not your strong suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.23,0:27:37.96,Default,,0,0,0,,現在我們可以談了\N{\b0\fs12}Now we can talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.90,0:27:41.45,Default,,0,0,0,,兩年來\N{\b0\fs12}For two years...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.48,0:27:45.35,Default,,0,0,0,,我和我的手下一直在找墓地\N{\b0\fs12}my crew and I have been looking for grave site.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.34,0:27:50.37,Default,,0,0,0,,你找到墓地了嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Did you find the graves?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.21,0:27:55.01,Default,,0,0,0,,屍體是不是\N{\b0\fs12}Were the bodies...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.02,0:27:56.28,Default,,0,0,0,,很奇怪\N{\b0\fs12}odd?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.34,0:28:00.39,Default,,0,0,0,,屍骨是不是都畸形了\N{\b0\fs12}The bones misshapen?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.83,0:28:12.72,Default,,0,0,0,,我們找對島了\N{\b0\fs12}This is the right island.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.95,0:28:22.40,Default,,0,0,0,,一把柯爾特1911自動手槍\N{\b0\fs12}Looks like we got a colt 1911,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.91,0:28:24.97,Default,,0,0,0,,32毫米口徑傑寧斯手槍\N{\b0\fs12}Jennings .32,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.15,0:28:28.04,Default,,0,0,0,,還有一把K架構左輪手槍\N{\b0\fs12}and a k-frame revolver.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.55,0:28:32.10,Default,,0,0,0,,一共兩百五十塊\N{\b0\fs12}We'll give you 250 for the lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.11,0:28:33.32,Default,,0,0,0,,留著吧\N{\b0\fs12}Keep it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.14,0:28:36.52,Default,,0,0,0,,我都不想知道你從哪兒弄來這些槍的\N{\b0\fs12}Do I even want to know where you got those guns?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.52,0:28:39.23,Default,,0,0,0,,都是以前的事  我告訴過你\N{\b0\fs12}They're from the old days. I told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.23,0:28:40.87,Default,,0,0,0,,我再也不會犯罪了\N{\b0\fs12}Look, no more being a criminal.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.87,0:28:43.25,Default,,0,0,0,,再也不逞英雄  只做好羅伊•哈珀\N{\b0\fs12}No more being a hero. Just Roy Harper.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.25,0:28:45.48,Default,,0,0,0,,打雜工  當男朋友\N{\b0\fs12}Bus boy and boyfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.63,0:28:47.45,Default,,0,0,0,,小屁孩\N{\b0\fs12}Yo, abercrombie.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.75,0:28:52.13,Default,,0,0,0,,怎麼不講禮貌了\N{\b0\fs12}Where's your manners?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.13,0:28:53.43,Default,,0,0,0,,辛\N{\b0\fs12}Sin.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.68,0:28:56.26,Default,,0,0,0,,這是西婭  西婭  這是辛\N{\b0\fs12}This is Thea. Thea, this is sin.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.26,0:28:57.73,Default,,0,0,0,,西婭•奎恩\N{\b0\fs12}Thea Queen?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.73,0:29:00.21,Default,,0,0,0,,瞧瞧  你已經和上層社會混到一起了\N{\b0\fs12}Look at you, rolling with royalty.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.21,0:29:02.47,Default,,0,0,0,,提醒一句  吃沙拉用的叉子要小一號\N{\b0\fs12}By the way, the salad fork's the small one.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.47,0:29:04.16,Default,,0,0,0,,很高興再見到你\N{\b0\fs12}It was good to see you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.44,0:29:10.56,Default,,0,0,0,,她不知道你在給治安維持者打工  對嗎\N{\b0\fs12}She doesn't know you're the vigilante's delivery boy, does she?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.57,0:29:14.20,Default,,0,0,0,,很高興見到你  殿下\N{\b0\fs12}Nice to meet you, your highness.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.20,0:29:15.49,Default,,0,0,0,,我也是\N{\b0\fs12}You, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.07,0:29:18.64,Default,,0,0,0,,你怎麼認識她的\N{\b0\fs12}So how do you know her?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.64,0:29:20.04,Default,,0,0,0,,就那麼認識的\N{\b0\fs12}From around.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.40,0:29:25.56,Default,,0,0,0,,你說會出現的時候你不出現\N{\b0\fs12}You don't show up when you say you will,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.01,0:29:28.70,Default,,0,0,0,,你說不會出現的時候  卻又出現了\N{\b0\fs12}and when you promise not to, here you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.08,0:29:31.20,Default,,0,0,0,,一切順利嗎\N{\b0\fs12}It's going well?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.20,0:29:31.83,Default,,0,0,0,,據我所知\N{\b0\fs12}Last check,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.83,0:29:34.98,Default,,0,0,0,,我們在三個小時裡收繳了超過兩百把槍支\N{\b0\fs12}we've taken in over 200 guns in only 3 hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.67,0:29:38.62,Default,,0,0,0,,別表現得太高興了\N{\b0\fs12}Try not to look so happy about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.62,0:29:40.83,Default,,0,0,0,,我還有其他事  議員先生\N{\b0\fs12}A lot on my mind, alderman.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.62,0:29:47.04,Default,,0,0,0,,我的工作是解決這裡市民的一切問題\N{\b0\fs12}My job is to help the people in this city with their problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.82,0:29:55.01,Default,,0,0,0,,兩個對我來說非常重要的人\N{\b0\fs12}Two people that are very important to me are...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.62,0:29:57.27,Default,,0,0,0,,現在過得都很不順\N{\b0\fs12}having a tough time.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.27,0:29:59.23,Default,,0,0,0,,算是姐妹吧\N{\b0\fs12}Sisters, actually.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.23,0:30:02.95,Default,,0,0,0,,而這兩人都不願意讓我幫她們\N{\b0\fs12}And neither one of them is making it very easy for me to help them.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.13,0:30:06.30,Default,,0,0,0,,我們總會歷經一次磨難\N{\b0\fs12}Sooner or later, we all go through a crucible.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.85,0:30:09.41,Default,,0,0,0,,對你來說是在島上的那段時間\N{\b0\fs12}I'm guessing yours was that island.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.88,0:30:13.55,Default,,0,0,0,,一般來說  經歷磨難後\N{\b0\fs12}Most believe there are two types of people
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.55,0:30:14.87,Default,,0,0,0,,只有兩種結局\N{\b0\fs12}who go into a crucible--
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.37,0:30:18.51,Default,,0,0,0,,一種是從磨難中成長\N{\b0\fs12}The ones who grow stronger from the experience
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.22,0:30:20.09,Default,,0,0,0,,最終戰勝它\N{\b0\fs12}and survive it,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.05,0:30:22.12,Default,,0,0,0,,另外一種就是在磨難中死去\N{\b0\fs12}and the ones who die.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.89,0:30:25.32,Default,,0,0,0,,但其實還有第三種\N{\b0\fs12}But there's a third type.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.73,0:30:27.54,Default,,0,0,0,,擁抱黑暗\N{\b0\fs12}The ones who learn to love the fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.97,0:30:29.24,Default,,0,0,0,,他們決定不走出來\N{\b0\fs12}They choose to stay in their crucible
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.24,0:30:30.76,Default,,0,0,0,,因為當一個人只剩下痛苦\N{\b0\fs12}because it's easier to embrace the pain
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.76,0:30:32.11,Default,,0,0,0,,反而會更好接受\N{\b0\fs12}when it's all you know anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.96,0:30:36.00,Default,,0,0,0,,所以我才這麼急於幫助這座城市\N{\b0\fs12}That's why I'm on the clock to help this city.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.25,0:30:39.29,Default,,0,0,0,,為了不讓它習慣於這樣的生活\N{\b0\fs12}Before it becomes used to living like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.47,0:30:40.96,Default,,0,0,0,,弱者無法生存\N{\b0\fs12}Living is not for the weak.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.45,0:30:45.29,Default,,0,0,0,,有個老朋友這麼跟我說過\N{\b0\fs12}Old friend of mine once told me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.36,0:30:46.47,Default,,0,0,0,,你朋友很聰明\N{\b0\fs12}That's a wise friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.53,0:30:49.03,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}警戒線  不得跨越
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.10,0:30:58.83,Default,,0,0,0,,聽好了  現在是你們的市長在講話\N{\b0\fs12}Listen up, people. This is your mayor speaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.87,0:31:03.07,Default,,0,0,0,,我不記得我有批準過這裡的行動\N{\b0\fs12}Now I don't recall this here event being sanctioned.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.07,0:31:05.57,Default,,0,0,0,,貧民區的所有事\N{\b0\fs12}What happens in the glades
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.57,0:31:08.12,Default,,0,0,0,,都是我說了算\N{\b0\fs12}only happens if I allow it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.13,0:31:10.05,Default,,0,0,0,,你不是這裡的領導\N{\b0\fs12}You're not the leader of this community!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.23,0:31:13.04,Default,,0,0,0,,你代表不了這些人民\N{\b0\fs12}You don't speak for these people!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.80,0:31:16.28,Default,,0,0,0,,你也代表不了  至少現在不行\N{\b0\fs12}And neither do you. Not anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.61,0:31:41.08,Default,,0,0,0,,-你還好嗎  受傷了嗎  -沒有\N{\b0\fs12}- Hey! Are you ok? Are you hit? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.17,0:31:44.21,Default,,0,0,0,,辛  你還好吧\N{\b0\fs12}Sin, you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.27,0:31:46.21,Default,,0,0,0,,還好\N{\b0\fs12}All's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.53,0:31:52.37,Default,,0,0,0,,去找人幫忙\N{\b0\fs12}Go get help!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.97,0:31:53.84,Default,,0,0,0,,快去\N{\b0\fs12}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.83,0:32:02.05,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}威登酒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.81,0:32:01.75,Default,,0,0,0,,槍擊案的指使者\N{\b0\fs12}The shooting was committed
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.75,0:32:04.49,Default,,0,0,0,,是一個叫作"市長"的黑幫首腦\N{\b0\fs12}by the gang leader kown only as "The Mayor,"
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.49,0:32:06.96,Default,,0,0,0,,在此之前  他從未在公共場合現過身\N{\b0\fs12}who, until now, has never been seen in public.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.96,0:32:08.53,Default,,0,0,0,,我們希望警告各位觀眾\N{\b0\fs12}We do want to warn our audience
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.53,0:32:10.50,Default,,0,0,0,,其中有一些非常觸目驚心的畫面\N{\b0\fs12}that some of these images are graphic.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.15,0:32:15.10,Default,,0,0,0,,這個膽小鬼終於露出真面目了\N{\b0\fs12}The coward finally decided to show his face.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.36,0:32:17.70,Default,,0,0,0,,自負會讓他付出代價\N{\b0\fs12}Vanity is going to cost him.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.70,0:32:20.50,Default,,0,0,0,,我"借用"了聯調局的面部識別軟件\N{\b0\fs12}I borrowed the FBI's facial recognition software.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.75,0:32:23.51,Default,,0,0,0,,找到匹配的了\N{\b0\fs12}Got a match.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.09,0:32:25.22,Default,,0,0,0,,賽維爾•裡德\N{\b0\fs12}Xavier Reed.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.23,0:32:26.91,Default,,0,0,0,,他參過軍嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Did Mr. Reed serve in the military?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.01,0:32:29.08,Default,,0,0,0,,沒有\N{\b0\fs12}No military history.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.08,0:32:29.98,Default,,0,0,0,,家庭成員呢\N{\b0\fs12}Family members?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.47,0:32:32.76,Default,,0,0,0,,裡德一直都生活在各個寄養家庭\N{\b0\fs12}Reed was in and out of foster care his whole life.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.98,0:32:33.90,Default,,0,0,0,,等等\N{\b0\fs12}Wait, hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.89,0:32:37.23,Default,,0,0,0,,1996年起  裡德在寄養家庭裡\N{\b0\fs12}In 1996, Reed spent three years with
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.23,0:32:39.83,Default,,0,0,0,,和一個叫艾澤拉•巴恩斯的孩子待了三年\N{\b0\fs12}a foster family and their son, Ezra Barnes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.14,0:32:43.48,Default,,0,0,0,,他去伊拉克參戰了三次  目前在美國本土\N{\b0\fs12}He served three tours in Iraq. He's stateside now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.48,0:32:45.38,Default,,0,0,0,,我打賭他現在駐紮在科爾比營區\N{\b0\fs12}20 bucks says he was stationed at camp Kirby.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.55,0:32:47.76,Default,,0,0,0,,沒錯  市長的寄養家兄弟\N{\b0\fs12}Pay the man. The Mayor's foster brother
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.76,0:32:49.76,Default,,0,0,0,,被分配到一輛運載\N{\b0\fs12}is assigned to a weapons convoy
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.76,0:32:51.38,Default,,0,0,0,,SCAR 16S的卡車上\N{\b0\fs12}that carries SCAR 16S by truck.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.38,0:32:54.02,Default,,0,0,0,,車隊今晚會穿過星城\N{\b0\fs12}The convoy's scheduled to come through Starling City tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.23,0:32:56.32,Default,,0,0,0,,SCAR 16S是軍用攻擊武器\N{\b0\fs12}fn scar 16s are military assault weapons
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.32,0:32:57.85,Default,,0,0,0,,加裝榴彈發射器\N{\b0\fs12}with grenade launchers.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.31,0:32:59.85,Default,,0,0,0,,如果那個人得到這些  奧利弗\N{\b0\fs12}The man gets a hold of these, Oliver,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.69,0:33:01.66,Default,,0,0,0,,一切就結束了\N{\b0\fs12}it's game over.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.40,0:33:04.37,Default,,0,0,0,,他拿不到\N{\b0\fs12}He won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.27,0:33:11.95,Default,,0,0,0,,子彈射入她的前腹部\N{\b0\fs12}Bullet penetrated her anterior abdomen.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.95,0:33:13.87,Default,,0,0,0,,我們可以取出絕大多數碎片\N{\b0\fs12}We were able to remove most of the fragments.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.04,0:33:15.52,Default,,0,0,0,,先觀察幾個小時\N{\b0\fs12}We'll know more in a few hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.45,0:33:32.05,Default,,0,0,0,,我要在這等著  以防她隨時醒過來\N{\b0\fs12}I'm going to stick around, in case she wakes up.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.13,0:33:34.99,Default,,0,0,0,,我和你一起等著可以嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Is it ok if I stick around with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.98,0:33:39.88,Default,,0,0,0,,你救了她的命  羅伊\N{\b0\fs12}I mean, you saved her life, Roy.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.14,0:33:44.34,Default,,0,0,0,,我想你停不下當英雄的腳步了  對吧\N{\b0\fs12}I guess you can't stop being a hero, can you?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.79,0:34:02.09,Default,,0,0,0,,我想看看你在真正的打鬥中做得怎麼樣\N{\b0\fs12}I want to see how you do in a real fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.54,0:34:04.35,Default,,0,0,0,,很好\N{\b0\fs12}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.97,0:34:06.45,Default,,0,0,0,,我正在找打架的機會呢\N{\b0\fs12}I was looking for a fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.06,0:34:30.99,Default,,0,0,0,,他們是和我一起的\N{\b0\fs12}They're with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.84,0:34:34.74,Default,,0,0,0,,他不是\N{\b0\fs12}He wasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.05,0:34:41.72,Default,,0,0,0,,你做到了你能做的一切\N{\b0\fs12}You're done being all you can be.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.43,0:34:48.62,Default,,0,0,0,,你我二人將擁有這座城市\N{\b0\fs12}You and I are going to own this town.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.50,0:34:51.86,Default,,0,0,0,,讓我們來看看這個傢伙有什麼能耐\N{\b0\fs12}Now let's see what this bad boy can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.27,0:34:58.29,Default,,0,0,0,,放下武器  馬上\N{\b0\fs12}Drop the weapon, now!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.35,0:35:20.31,Default,,0,0,0,,小心後面\N{\b0\fs12}Behind you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.65,0:35:22.73,Default,,0,0,0,,傳統武器  向你們致敬\N{\b0\fs12}Old school weapon. Respect.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.95,0:35:24.33,Default,,0,0,0,,不過你的弓箭能做到這樣嗎\N{\b0\fs12}But can your arrows do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.06,0:35:45.95,Default,,0,0,0,,來啊  你們在哪呢\N{\b0\fs12}Come on, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.34,0:35:53.45,Default,,0,0,0,,你傷了我的一個朋友\N{\b0\fs12}You hurt a friend of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.45,0:35:54.16,Default,,0,0,0,,放開他\N{\b0\fs12}Let him go.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.96,0:35:57.10,Default,,0,0,0,,懷著寬仁之心可救不了這座城市\N{\b0\fs12}You can't save a city with forgiveness.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.10,0:35:58.61,Default,,0,0,0,,你不需要寬恕他\N{\b0\fs12}You don't have to forgive him.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.55,0:36:02.08,Default,,0,0,0,,但是你必須讓他活著\N{\b0\fs12}But you do have to let him live.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.98,0:36:07.21,Default,,0,0,0,,賤貨  我知道你沒有寬容心\N{\b0\fs12}Bitch. I knew you didn't have it in you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.98,0:36:13.39,Default,,0,0,0,,我不喜歡那個詞\N{\b0\fs12}I really don't like that word.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.84,0:36:22.76,Default,,0,0,0,,針對星城實驗室的\N{\b0\fs12}Demonstrations opposing the construction
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.76,0:36:24.75,Default,,0,0,0,,粒子加速器建造工作的示威遊行\N{\b0\fs12}of the new Star Lab's particle accelerator
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.75,0:36:26.42,Default,,0,0,0,,達到了狂熱的程度\N{\b0\fs12}have reached a fever pitch
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.42,0:36:28.75,Default,,0,0,0,,又有五名抗議者被逮捕\N{\b0\fs12}with five more protestors being arrested.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.00,0:36:29.74,Default,,0,0,0,,另一則消息\N{\b0\fs12}In other news,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.74,0:36:31.96,Default,,0,0,0,,近日在貧民區廢墟進行的以槍換錢的活動\N{\b0\fs12}the recent cash for guns event held in the glades
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.96,0:36:35.28,Default,,0,0,0,,已從街上回收了超過800支槍支\N{\b0\fs12}is credited for getting over 800 weapons off the streets.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.44,0:36:37.89,Default,,0,0,0,,謎團依然未解  為這次活動慷慨解囊的\N{\b0\fs12}Still a mystery-- the anonymous donor
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.90,0:36:40.78,Default,,0,0,0,,匿名捐助者  身份依然神秘\N{\b0\fs12}whose generous donation funded the event.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.43,0:36:43.90,Default,,0,0,0,,我想他們說得對\N{\b0\fs12}I guess it's true what they say--
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.10,0:36:45.54,Default,,0,0,0,,一己之力可以改變世界\N{\b0\fs12}One man can change the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.59,0:36:47.60,Default,,0,0,0,,我把改變世界的機會留給你  議員\N{\b0\fs12}I'll leave changing the world to you, Alderman.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.94,0:36:49.43,Default,,0,0,0,,多虧了你我還能活著\N{\b0\fs12}I'm only in the world because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.15,0:36:50.81,Default,,0,0,0,,謝謝你\N{\b0\fs12}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.56,0:36:54.23,Default,,0,0,0,,我只不過是在憑直覺行動\N{\b0\fs12}I was just acting on instinct.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.59,0:36:56.98,Default,,0,0,0,,那不是直覺  那是力量\N{\b0\fs12}It wasn't instinct. It was strength.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.36,0:37:01.01,Default,,0,0,0,,我看到了標記和塗鴉\N{\b0\fs12}I see the signs and the graffiti.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.32,0:37:02.69,Default,,0,0,0,,"市長血債血償"\N{\b0\fs12}"Blood for Mayor."
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.15,0:37:06.00,Default,,0,0,0,,現在那個"市長"進監獄了\N{\b0\fs12}Now that the "Mayor" is in jail,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.03,0:37:07.12,Default,,0,0,0,,你該走馬上任了\N{\b0\fs12}maybe you should run.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.04,0:37:09.94,Default,,0,0,0,,拯救城市的辦法不止一個\N{\b0\fs12}There is more than one way to save a city.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.93,0:37:18.78,Default,,0,0,0,,哈珀先生\N{\b0\fs12}Mr. Harper?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.76,0:37:20.81,Default,,0,0,0,,出什麼事了  她還好嗎\N{\b0\fs12}What's wrong, is she ok?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.42,0:37:32.39,Default,,0,0,0,,你救了我的命\N{\b0\fs12}You saved my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.63,0:37:36.49,Default,,0,0,0,,我想我應該保守你的秘密了吧\N{\b0\fs12}I guess I have to keep your secret now, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.30,0:37:41.12,Default,,0,0,0,,你知道你在和一個白癡約會吧\N{\b0\fs12}You know you're dating a moron, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.16,0:37:44.35,Default,,0,0,0,,我每天睜眼閉眼都這麼想\N{\b0\fs12}It's my first and last thought of every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.03,0:37:45.80,Default,,0,0,0,,糟糕\N{\b0\fs12}Crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.97,0:37:47.76,Default,,0,0,0,,我喜歡她\N{\b0\fs12}I like her.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.02,0:38:07.86,Default,,0,0,0,,你的朋友\N{\b0\fs12}Your friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.93,0:38:10.93,Default,,0,0,0,,我幫她付了醫療費\N{\b0\fs12}I took care of her medical expenses.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.91,0:38:12.72,Default,,0,0,0,,謝謝\N{\b0\fs12}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.32,0:38:15.60,Default,,0,0,0,,聽著  我不想讓西婭看到我\N{\b0\fs12}Look, I don't want Thea to see me--
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.60,0:38:17.09,Default,,0,0,0,,你有什麼計劃  莎拉\N{\b0\fs12}What's your plan, Sarah?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.83,0:38:21.32,Default,,0,0,0,,因為現在  你...\N{\b0\fs12}Because right now, you just...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.02,0:38:23.15,Default,,0,0,0,,你在屋頂穿梭\N{\b0\fs12}Well, you're whipping across rooftops
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.15,0:38:25.15,Default,,0,0,0,,像一個幽靈一樣\N{\b0\fs12}and keeping watch over your family
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.64,0:38:26.93,Default,,0,0,0,,照看你的家人\N{\b0\fs12}like some sort of ghost.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.93,0:38:27.97,Default,,0,0,0,,我們都是幽靈\N{\b0\fs12}We're both ghosts.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.26,0:38:31.30,Default,,0,0,0,,我們都死在了那座島上\N{\b0\fs12}We died on that island.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.30,0:38:32.10,Default,,0,0,0,,但我們沒有\N{\b0\fs12}But we didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.53,0:38:34.65,Default,,0,0,0,,我們都活下來了\N{\b0\fs12}We both lived.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.27,0:38:37.07,Default,,0,0,0,,而且\N{\b0\fs12}And...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.51,0:38:43.02,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道你承受了很長時間的痛苦\N{\b0\fs12}I get that you have been in pain so long
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.37,0:38:45.93,Default,,0,0,0,,也許到現在才恢復正常\N{\b0\fs12}that it probably just feels normal now.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.93,0:38:48.70,Default,,0,0,0,,但你可以忘掉那些然後回家\N{\b0\fs12}But you can let it go and come home.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.73,0:38:52.70,Default,,0,0,0,,我知道那場地震讓你回到這裡\N{\b0\fs12}I mean, I know that the earthquake brought you here,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.70,0:38:54.62,Default,,0,0,0,,但是  是你的家庭讓你留下\N{\b0\fs12}but your family kept you here.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.00,0:38:57.07,Default,,0,0,0,,你應該告訴他們  莎拉\N{\b0\fs12}You have to tell them, Sarah.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.70,0:39:02.56,Default,,0,0,0,,他們需要你\N{\b0\fs12}They need you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.38,0:39:07.49,Default,,0,0,0,,你告訴過他們我死在"金牌奎恩"號上\N{\b0\fs12}You told them that I died on "The gambit."
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.24,0:39:09.06,Default,,0,0,0,,如果他們知道真相\N{\b0\fs12}If they know the truth...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.06,0:39:10.29,Default,,0,0,0,,他們永遠\N{\b0\fs12}They would never--
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.27,0:39:12.88,Default,,0,0,0,,他們永遠都不會再理我了\N{\b0\fs12}They would never talk to me again.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.53,0:39:17.10,Default,,0,0,0,,沒有人會\N{\b0\fs12}Not one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.33,0:39:22.12,Default,,0,0,0,,但那也值得\N{\b0\fs12}But it'd be worth it.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.51,0:39:27.58,Default,,0,0,0,,我的女兒有麻煩了\N{\b0\fs12}My daughter's in trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.71,0:39:31.76,Default,,0,0,0,,她  她經歷了一些很糟糕的事\N{\b0\fs12}She's, uh, she's been through some really terrible things.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.60,0:39:33.54,Default,,0,0,0,,而且\N{\b0\fs12}And...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.86,0:39:37.99,Default,,0,0,0,,比起勇敢面對  她選擇了逃避\N{\b0\fs12}instead of facing up to them, she's running away from them.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.16,0:39:40.76,Default,,0,0,0,,她在她的工作中迷失了自己\N{\b0\fs12}She's losing herself in her work,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.57,0:39:43.71,Default,,0,0,0,,也許更糟\N{\b0\fs12}and maybe even worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.76,0:39:47.86,Default,,0,0,0,,她是我的女兒  我只想讓她安全\N{\b0\fs12}She's my daughter, I just want her safe,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.87,0:39:48.88,Default,,0,0,0,,我想要保護她\N{\b0\fs12}I want to protect her.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.50,0:39:58.04,Default,,0,0,0,,但是就像我們說過的\N{\b0\fs12}But I guess like we say in our meetings,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.04,0:39:59.01,Default,,0,0,0,,會有更多的問題浮現出來\N{\b0\fs12}more will be revealed.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.20,0:40:22.89,Default,,0,0,0,,你的苦日子才剛剛開始\N{\b0\fs12}Your days of screaming are just beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.66,0:40:55.80,Default,,0,0,0,,搞什麼\N{\b0\fs12}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.29,0:41:01.32,Default,,0,0,0,,這他媽的是什麼意思\N{\b0\fs12}What the hell is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.87,0:41:04.12,Default,,0,0,0,,這裡不是警察局\N{\b0\fs12}This ain't the police station.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.44,0:41:08.41,Default,,0,0,0,,你好  兄弟\N{\b0\fs12}Hello, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.06,0:41:10.47,Default,,0,0,0,,你準備為我效力了嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Are you ready to serve?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.60,0:41:11.85,Default,,0,0,0,,你為什麼要帶著那個面具\N{\b0\fs12}Why are you wearing that mask?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.76,0:41:15.20,Default,,0,0,0,,這座城市戴著鐐銬\N{\b0\fs12}This city is in chains,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.20,0:41:16.86,Default,,0,0,0,,我要解放它\N{\b0\fs12}and I'm going to free it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.37,0:41:19.44,Default,,0,0,0,,為了達到目的  我需要一支軍隊\N{\b0\fs12}But to do that, I need an army.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.78,0:41:20.99,Default,,0,0,0,,一支強勁的軍隊\N{\b0\fs12}An army used strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.00,0:41:22.31,Default,,0,0,0,,那是什麼東西\N{\b0\fs12}Whoa, what's in that thing?!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.50,0:41:23.68,Default,,0,0,0,,一個奇跡\N{\b0\fs12}A miracle.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.26,0:41:25.27,Default,,0,0,0,,把它拿開\N{\b0\fs12}Get that off me!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.22,0:41:27.58,Default,,0,0,0,,把這破玩意拿開\N{\b0\fs12}Get that crap away from me!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.90,0:41:29.92,Default,,0,0,0,,你準備為我效力了嗎\N{\b0\fs12}Are you ready to serve?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.25,0:41:54.24,Default,,0,0,0,,再帶一個人過來\N{\b0\fs12}Bring me another.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.93,0:41:57.89,Default,,0,0,0,,是  布拉德\N{\b0\fs12}Yes, brother Blood.
