My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home with only one goal--
to save my city.
Now others have joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
To the rest of Starling City, I am someone else.
I am...something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
If you want to go out there, I can't stop you.
But I don't have to help you.
Who the hell are you?
I'm the justice you can't run from.
It's Danny Brickwell. His street name's Brick.
You are all part of my crew now.
Together, we are going to take over the Glades.
Oliver.
I asked her to come here...
So she could bring you back to life.
This is a duel...
Oliver, with one of the most dangerous men
that has ever walked the earth.
I wouldn't be doing it if I didn't think I could win.
I don't worry that you can beat him.
I am terrified you won't kill him.
That's not who you are anymore.
And I'm afraid that Ra's is going
to use your humanity against you.
You're right.
- I'll stay. - Really?
Are you sure?
I'm sure of one thing--
I love you.
Oliver.
Drink this.
More herbs?
Penicillin. For the infection.
You saved my life.
The snow and cold helped.
And your will to live.
You should be dead.
Did you know Maseo would bring me here?
He was the one who told me to meet you at this cabin.
I didn't realize that the...two of you
were still in contact.
We are not.
Maseo...
You're in no condition to stand.
Then help me.
I'm glad you stayed.
Then you'll be disappointed.
When the storm passes,
I'll return to Nanda Parbat.
Maseo...
if Ra's finds out that you saved me,
betrayed him...
he's going to kill you.
Don't waste your breath for worries on me.
Your concern should be for your home,
and what has become of it in your absence.
Help!
You picked the wrong alley.
See, this one cuts off here at Carlisle.
You pick the next one,
and you're free and clear to Reimer Avenue.
Now, you want to do this the hard way...
or the harder way?
Run.
I heard rumors about a mask who protects girls around here.
I guess you ain't her.
This is Brick's town now.
I think we should talk.
This is going to hurt a little.
Just one more.
Sorry, I warned you it was going to hurt.
You said a little.
Yeah, well. Dig taught us how to suture.
I guess Felicity got the hang of it quicker than I did.
- Where is Felicity? - Let's talk about you.
What the hell do you think you were doing out there?
Same thing as you.
I've had training from Oliver
and years on the streets.
You have a law degree.
Look...
I get it.
This?
This isn't how you deal with grief, Laurel.
This is how you get yourself killed.
Laurel, what the hell?
I'm fine.
You are certifiable if you think
you can wear your sister's mask.
Yeah, yeah, you're right.
But Oliver, the Arrow...
He's gone now.
And like it or not, the Canary sends the same message.
- They fear her. - No, Laurel.
They fear your sister.
Yeah.
She's not here anymore.
What are you doing here so early?
The meeting's not for another three hours.
Yeah, well, I convinced Mayor Castle
it might be a good idea to move it up.
What, with a murderous killer running amuck in the city.
Isn't that what the police are for?
Well, she wanted to speak to city leaders.
And I'll help in whatever way I can.
And by help, you mean money and counsel,
not a suit powered by...
Dwarf star alloy that fires lasers at people?
Well, they aren't lasers. That would be ridiculous.
They're compressed hard light beams.
And they don't actually fire, because I can't
get anyone, specifically you,
to help me fix the nanite chip.
Well, I already told you, Ray, I am not interested
in helping you with your suicide mission.
There is nothing that you can say
or do that is going to change my mind.
Are you ready to go?
Hey. What are you doing here?
Oh, with that Brick guy running around the Glades,
I figured I shouldn't leave my gear any place he might find it.
What are you doing here?
This neighborhood isn't exactly
a safe place to be hanging out right now.
Well, I'm not hanging out, I'm just doing my job.
Are we cool? It just seems like
you've been avoiding me, you know,
ever since we had that moment.
Moment? You have a very high opinion on your kissing skills.
Judging from how you responded,
I think you've got a pretty high opinion of them, too.
Unless you need a reminder.
No, not right now.
But, I'll see you later?
- What are you doing here? - I went by your apartment
to see how your packing is going,
only to discover that it's not.
I can't leave.
Not without knowing where Oliver is.
I thought it made it clear that leaving was not optional.
No, actually, you didn't make anything clear.
You just ordered me to uproot my life
and didn't even give me a reason why.
All you need to know is that we're in danger,
and every day we remain in Starling,
the danger grows greater. Now get in the car, Thea.
No.
Not until you tell me the truth.
You're not ready for the truth.
Then I guess I'm not ready to leave Starling City.
Yeah, I know, yeah. OK, I'm on it.
- I’m sorry I'm late. - You're not late.
Castle's still hashing things out with her people.
You heard from your sister?
No. Why?
Well, she's, back in town.
A girl came into the precinct a few hours ago.
Claimed a blonde in a mask
and a black leather jacket saved her life.
All right, thank you, everyone,
for coming, please take your seats.
As you know, over the last week,
a criminal organization headed by Danny Brickwell
has been on a crime spree unlike anything since Al Capone.
Which begs the question-- why aren't you arresting him?
We sent in an ESU team to do just that.
Most of those men are in the hospital now.
Now we got no clue where he's holed up.
Maybe if we had more men,
but that means more money.
I've got a few bucks.
Sorry. In fact, Palmer Technology
has just made a large donation to the SCPD,
but it'll take time for that personal equipment to do any good.
We need to consider calling in the National Guard.
Always wanted to meet the mayor.
Bring the mayor and the aldermen.
Kill the rest.
Laurel!
See? That's why I need a technosuit.
Is Mayor Castle secure?
Yeah.
But what about the aldermen?
Brick's got them.
Your penicillin tea tastes like penicillin.
We can't let him go back to the League.
It's not our choice.
Maybe we could have changed Maseo's mind,
but not his.
Not Sarab's.
Sarab is just a name that Ra's Al Ghul calls him.
He's still your husband.
Thank you.
Maseo blames himself for what happened.
Yeah. It wasn't his fault.
The line between grief and guilt
is a thin one.
Sometimes, death is preferable to the agony of life.
Tracker's in there.
Looks like a VIP area.
Probably where they're holding Tatsu.
There's a lot of muscle in front of that door.
This club is a Triad front.
It will be heavily guarded.
But will you do anything to get her back?
Yes, I would.
I told you it would be heavily guarded.
You're late.
- That's funny. - I wasn't talking to you.
Was addressing your partner.
What?
Did you bring the item?
What is she talking about?!
I want to see my wife.
I said I want to see my wife.
Once I know she's alive,
then you can have the Alpha.
Sorry, Oliver.
Maseo!
What are you doing?
How's your heart?
Still beating. You OK?
Listen, I couldn't help but notice that nobody in a green hood
showed up to save the day.
That's because he's gone.
What do you mean, gone?
It means we're on our own.
But that doesn't make sense, what,
the Arrow's gone, but Sara's back?
Wait, Sara's back?
What are you talking about?
Yeah, she's been taking out Brick's men solo.
I've been getting reports down at the precinct.
Blonde, mask, bo-staff. You didn't know?
I've sort of been living under a rock these days.
Ask him to give me a call.
Yeah.
Will do.
Jim huffman.
34, eight arrests,
no convictions.
Grand theft auto, B&E, drugs.
You did pretty well flying solo.
What made you decide to start working for Brick?
I'm not telling you anything.
Are you sure about that? I still have another heel.
Kidding.
You don't want to talk about Brick, that's fine.
Then let's talk about something else.
Why would you murder Julio Salazar?
Salazar?
Head of Los Halcones?
I had nothing to do with him getting popped.
Well, that's not what your file says.
See?
What kind of game is this?
You just wrote that down!
You're making this stuff up!
Actually, I can charge you with whatever crime that I want.
Of course, then they'd have to keep you in custody
until the trial.
Good news--
Belle Reve, it's a lot more comfortable than Iron Heights.
Belle Reve's where the Los Halcones are locked up.
They think I offed Salazar.
I won't last two seconds in there!
Tell me where I can find Danny Brickwell
and you won't have to.
They'll kill me.
Charges filed by Dinah Laurel Lance, Assistant District Att--
Hey, stop. Stop!
I'll tell you where you can find Brick.
If you're looking for Thea,
she's not here.
I know. I came to see you.
Following me, Mr. Harper?
You need to stay away from her.
I don't know why you want her to leave Starling City,
but I'm not letting her go anywhere with you.
Well, thank you for that.
I was in need of some humor.
I wasn't joking.
You are poison.
You put her in Ra's Al Ghul's gunsights.
You had her kill Sara.
Thea knows nothing about Sara.
And she never will.
That's where you're wrong.
I know her.
She'll get to the truth no matter how well you think you're hiding it.
And when she does find out that you've been lying to her,
you're going to lose her forever.
Trust me; I know from experience.
This is a family matter, Mr. Harper.
And you are not family.
- Sit. - Ok.
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Armed gunmen attacking you.
That had to have brought back a few bad memories.
Yeah.
When it started,
all I could think about was the night Anna died.
But when that gunman charged us,
all I could think about was
saving you.
You were right.
I've been going about this all wrong.
When I started the atom project,
it was all about avenging Anna.
But what it has become about
is... protecting the people I care for.
You mean the city?
No.
I mean you.
You sure you still want to use that thing?
We have plenty of other weapons here.
- It was Sara's. - Roy!
I thought we were on the same page with this.
That was before Brick kidnapped three aldermen.
Laurel said she knows where they are.
We put their location through Felicity's surveillance program
but Brick keeps moving them.
We can still track them,
take them out en route, but the window's closing.
Fine. Laurel, monitor us from here.
- Talk me and Roy in. - No.
That's not how this is going to work.
Are you trying to get yourself killed?
Laurel, you're not your sister!
You think I don't know that?
You lost a brother. If there's anyone
who I thought would understand, it would be you.
Stay close to her.
We should have got the Mayor. That was a loss.
Let's go.
Laurel... Laurel, Laurel, watch your six!
Lucky for you, I don't like hitting women.
Go, go, go!
Bad choice!
This one's on you.
Danny Brickwell is still at large tonight
after abducting three aldermen from City Hall
earlier this evening.
Though he's managed to evade SCPD thus far--
- Dad. - Cell phone video shows two vigilantes...
- Hey. You OK? - Yeah.
associated with the Arrow,
the Red Arrow and the woman in black, in pursuit.
Reports now trickling in suggest a confrontation...
Your sister did her best.
Channel 52's running cell phone footage of her
and the Arrow's partner, the guy in the red hood.
Did Sara talk to you?
What? No.
She hasn't, not yet.
You know, she must know we're seeing this stuff.
Madame Mayor, there's a call for you on line one.
- Take a message. - It's Danny Brickwell.
Mr. Brickwell.
How is your evening going, Madame Mayor?
Mine's not going too well.
Because your city's "Vigilante problem"
became mine earlier tonight. And it's forced my hand--
Look, if you have demands to make, just get on with it.
No demands, just Shakespeare.
"Julius Caesar,"
Act Five, Scene Two.
"They stand and would have parley."
The war stops and together they converse.
I would have parley with you.
That isn't what we're doing right now.
In person, Brockton Point, one hour.
I don't negotiate with terrorists.
And I certainly don't do it in person.
You are already going to one funeral, Madame Mayor.
If you want to make it a hat trick,
well, that's your prerogative.
Me? I'll be at Brockton Point.
If you came to see how packing is going,
it's not.
No.
I came to apologize.
I don't want to lose you, Thea.
But at the same time,
sharing the truth with you is sometimes difficult for me.
Well, maybe you'll get better with practice.
Who are we running from?
His name is Ra's al Ghul.
And why does he want to kill you?
Ra's has a particular code of honor
he feels I've violated.
And he's marked me and my family for death.
I fell in with Ra's because I was consumed by the death of my wife.
And I was marked for death because of the undertaking
that killed my son.
You're all I have left, Thea.
Keeping you safe is all that matters.
Please let me.
Alderman Richard Ford was in his second term at city hall.
He leaves behind a wife and two children.
The city asks the family's privacy
be respected during this trying time.
No official statement...
Laurel...
I'm sorry. I can come back.
No, it's ok. Is...
Is everything ok?
I came to ask you the same thing...
Canary.
I guess you came here to talk some sense into me.
Seems like you could use some.
Not sure you're going to have to bother.
Brick, he...
he killed someone tonight.
In front of me.
I thought that being--
being Sara would make it hurt less.
But instead, it just...
it caused more pain.
Not just for me.
So you don't have to worry.
I'm not going to be putting on that mask again.
I'm not strong enough to fight for Sara.
Maybe you're not supposed to.
Maybe it's not about Sara,
or Oliver, or anyone else that we care about, who we lost.
Maybe what we've been doing...
we've been doing it because there are people we care about
that are still... alive.
Maybe we're doing it for them.
I thought you quit.
He's confident.
Meeting out here in the open
where any police sniper could take him out.
Yeah, well, that's 'cause he's got men
that could take the hostages out, check mate.
Madame Mayor.
All this for me?
I'm impressed.
What are you doing here, Palmer?
Just want to make yourself look important?
Good luck with that.
Star City.
Seems more like Brick City to me.
Night is young.
Tough talk.
Too bad all you got is money to back it up.
But you can't fix this with money, Palmer.
I don't know. I got a lot of money.
Say what you came here to say.
We can all end this farce.
Ok.
I've still got two of your men.
If you want them back, it's simple.
Get out of the Glades.
The city servicemen, especially the police--
evacuate.
You're out of your mind!
And you've got until midnight tomorrow.
If I even see a hint of a blue,
your city yes-men, they will be buried.
We won't abandon an entire district.
They did in L.A. In '92, didn't they?
Besides, you don't want every news station
in the country showing graphic footage
of the murders of the aldermen, do you?
You have 23 hours, 59 minutes.
I suggest you move your sweet ass!
Brick wants every cop out of the Glades
or he's going to kill his hostages.
We need help, we need it now.
Look, I know you said the Arrow is gone.
Are you sure about that?
Yes, I am.
But I think I know where to find the Canary.
The storm has passed.
Maseo...
You don't have to leave.
You can still have a life.
Why do you assume I want one?
Because I know you and this isn't who you are.
I love you.
No matter who you think you've become.
Maseo?
They found you.
Sarab. What are you doing here?
Ra's al Ghul wants Oliver Queen's remains.
I found no body, only tracks.
Which led here.
Queen is still alive.
But there is no one here.
I was just about to go.
Brothers...
we should go.
Traitor!
She's the mother of my son. You do not get to judge me.
Too late.
This concludes our business.
Only... if the serum is genuine.
It's genuine.
Then you should have no problem with me testing it.
It's a fake. Kill them all.
Go, go, go!
That alderman died because of the decision that I made.
and there was no Mirakuru to blame this time.
Don't take that on yourself, man.
That was Brick.
What's that?
Sometimes, me and Oliver will come down here after,
you know, tough nights.
He would pour this,
look up and say...
"Prochnost."
What does that mean?
I have no earthly idea.
To Oliver.
We can't do this without Oliver, can we?
Felicity was right.
Actually, I was wrong,
and I'm not wrong a lot.
He said the mayor is going to cave
and cede control over the Glades.
They're going to evacuate the police force.
So it's up to us to stop Brick.
"Us?" What, are you and Laurel a team now?
I was wrong when I said Oliver's mission was over,
because it's not
just Oliver's mission anymore, it is ours.
It's our home that is under attack.
For all we know, Oliver could be dead
and Sara certainly is.
But there are people that are still alive.
People who need us.
OK.
First we have to find out where those aldermen are.
- It's a bad idea. - So you've said...
repeatedly. But it's my decision,
so do as I tell you and give the order!
You give it. You want to pull my men out the Glades,
fine, that's your funeral. But I don't want any part of it.
Excuse me.
Hello?
Hi, Daddy.
Sara.
Sara, where you been?
I've been worried sick about you.
I'm sorry.
I'm here.
Are you OK?
Well, yeah, I mean, I've been better.
I'm sure you have been, too.
Listen, why didn't you call me sooner, honey?
It's complicated.
How is she doing this?
I fed recordings of Sara's voice
through a symbolic algorithm.
Daddy, I'm sorry that I've been away,
but I don't want you to worry about me.
I'm fine.
And I'm here to help.
OK.
What do you need from me?
I need you to tell me everything you know about the hostages.
No matter how seemingly insignificant.
Well, I don't know how knowing their favorite color's
going to help find them, honey.
There has to be something.
Some sort of intel that you couldn't move on
because of the mayor's orders.
I wish.
The clock's running down on these guys, too.
I just found out one of them's got a heart condition.
If his pacemaker isn't recharged soon,
we're going to lose another alderman.
Daddy, that actually helps.
But, I have to go now.
Wait, just listen to me. Be careful out there, OK?
Because I don't know what I'd do if anything happened to you.
I'll be careful.
I love you, sweetheart.
I love you, too, daddy.
One of the aldermen has a pacemaker.
If it's remote programmable...
It'll have a GPS.
It's going to take me a few minutes to log on to the pacemaker.
Gear up.
This one breakthrough, is all we need, is one--
Yeah. One second.
Sorry to interrupt.
What's going on?
I need the keys to your helicopter.
How would you even fly it?
I got that covered.
Can you please just give me the keys now? I...
promise, promise, I will not crash it.
I've got to be honest,
I'd feel a little more confident
in your aeronautic abilities if you knew,
for instance, that helicopters don't actually have keys.
They don't have keys?
No.
Is it on the roof?
Yeah, it's on the roof.
Thank you!
I'm going to hold you to the no crash promise.
You do realize it's been five years since
I've flown one of these things, right?
It's like riding a bicycle, I hope.
Do you have Brick's location?
According to the last signal from the pacemaker,
Brick has the aldermen in a warehouse at 16th and Kent.
Not for long, he doesn't.
We got a chopper outside. Check it out.
Roger that. Checking it now.
I guess we're even now.
Follow the hallway 20 yards.
Turn left.
Aldermen!
Come on! Don't worry!
We're going to get you out of here.
Let's go. Go. Go!
Dig, I'm going to need you to find me a way out of here.
Copy that.
I still don't like hitting women.
But I could make an exception for you.
I will keep this city safe.
By killing anyone that doesn't do what you say?
Something like that.
Warmer...
We're not going to let you--
Well, it's-- it's done.
Bodies will not be found.
Ok, Maseo, I get you wanting to go back before,
but that was before.
When Ra's finds out that you betrayed the League...
Maseo!
Why the hell did you do that?!
I didn't. You did.
In a successful attempt to escape.
Or you could just come back to Starling City with me.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
If you're going to bluff with a fake virus sample,
let me in on it.
- I wasn't bluffing. - What does that mean?
That-- that the Alpha we stole from the military was a fake?
That Amanda Waller knew I would try something like this.
She must have switched out the vial before I took it.
Maseo! You were willing to risk letting hundreds,
maybe thousands of people die?
For my wife...yes.
There's nothing I wouldn't do for my family.
Thank you.
You saved my life.
Dad?
Both aldermen are back with their families.
Nice job. For all the good it did.
What does that mean?
Mayor Castle caved.
She's pulling SCPD out of the Glades.
But why? Brick doesn't have the aldermen anymore.
No, but what he does have is the home address
of every city council member and their family,
and the means to hurt them.
Played that card 15 minutes ago.
Hey, sweetie, sweetheart, hey,
how about we, uh, cry over each other's shoulders?
Over dinner, at the Chinese place you love.
I can't. I'm sorry.
What's going on with you, sweetheart?
Why are you trying to avoid me?
I'll explain everything.
Just... not tonight.
You ok?
I'm fine, daddy. I'm fine.
Are you ready to leave?
No.
I'm not leaving.
Is this supposed to make up for me missing your adolescence,
this routine of listening and then disobeying me?
Just hear me out.
You told me that we were in danger.
You even told me who was after us.
But what you didn't tell me is why.
Yes, I did.
Because Ra's al Ghul wants us dead.
That's pretty much the case anywhere we go.
So why run?
Why not stay and fight?
Seven months ago, I asked you to teach me.
To teach me how to not be afraid and how to not get hurt.
So why are you asking me to be afraid now?
I am not asking you. I am telling you.
You should be very afraid.
Well, I'm not. 'Cause my father taught me not to be.
You taught me how to stand my ground
and how to not give an inch in a battle.
I'm not afraid of this man and you shouldn't be, either.
He should be afraid of us.
Then we'll stay.
Your helicopter
is back on the roof.
I didn't crash it.
Turns out...
It actually had keys.
And this.
The reason you couldn't get the Nanite chip to function
is because what you actually need...
is a quantum processor.
The design is elegant.
Thought you weren't going to help me on my suicide mission.
Well, that's the thing.
With my help, you might not end up dead.
I thought you knew about this whole neighborhood
turning into a scene from "The Purge."
We didn't even open tonight.
I forgot my music files here and I've got another gig.
Cheating on me with another club manager.
Well, I heard a rumor you were leaving town.
Happy to say that those rumors are false.
That's good news. For both of us.
Don't get so ahead of yourself.
My hard drive's up there.
Take your time.