This season, on "Arrow"...
I was told once that a man
cannot live by two names.
I thought that I could be me and the arrow,
but I can't.
I see it in your eyes--
The struggle you have with your dual identity.
I am the demon's head. I want you to take my place.
I want you to become the next Ra's Al Ghul.
Oliver queen is the Arrow.
I got you now, you son of a bitch.
There is no more Arrow.
Ra's took that from you.
Take your rightful place as heir to the demon,
and Ra's Al Ghul will bring your sister back.
All this time, I've been struggling with who I am.
Do you recognize this?
The Alpha and Omega bioweapon.
You will unleash this on Starling City.
My son was killed by the virus
Ra's intends to use on your city.
Oliver...
You asked us to trust you and we trusted you!
No, Oliver!
You were asleep.
I was dreaming.
Ibn Sirin once wrote there are three types of dreams--
there are ones about truth;
there are ones about desire,
and there are ones about temptation.
What did you dream of?
Rebirth...
As Ra's Al Ghul.
There is no greater burden
than the one you're about to take on--
the annihilation of one's home.
It is necessary to complete my ascension.
And I will be there to steady your hand when the time comes.
I appreciate your assistance.
Soon you will wear this.
And you will command a multitude,
and I shall call you Ra's.
Something's wrong.
Not that I'm complaining,
but shouldn't we be dead by now?
Oliver tried to kill us.
Ra's tried.
Oliver was forced to let him appear to be successful.
So now we're back to trust Oliver,
and while we're at it, trust you, too?
Yeah, because the last time I checked,
you tried to make a deal with Ra's to save yourself.
In order for our plan to work,
Ra's trust in Oliver had to be complete.
And after that plane fiasco, it wasn't.
Oliver needed to demonstrate
one more time his loyalty to Ra's.
Which I guess brings us back to...
why aren't we dead?
Not that I'm complaining.
Oliver...
was vaccinated against the Alpha Omega virus five years ago.
An associate was able to draw a version of the vaccine
from his blood.
A synthetic skin graft.
Upon our incarceration,
I was able to vaccinate
each one of you cutaneously.
I saved your lives.
I believe the words you're searching for
are "Thank" and "You."
Ok.
Assuming this is all some part
of a brilliant double double cross
or triple cross-- I'm losing count--
your master plan still has one major flaw,
since we're still chained in a dungeon.
Patience, Miss Smoak.
All we have to do is wait.
Wait for what?
The thunder.
Keep walking.
It's time.
All right.
You guys have a hot tub?
Nice.
Hi, you guys!
I mean, this is like a real dungeon!
Barry!
Thank you, Felicity.
You just outed my secret identity to a super villain.
No offense.
None taken.
Now get us out of here!
All right, uh, stand back.
Excellent.
How many assassins, do you figure?
Uh, none. They're all taking a little nappy time.
Thank you. And not to be greedy,
but we could really use your help
on this whole Starling City super virus thing.
And you know I would, but I am overdue
for a very pointed conversation with Harrison Wells.
I'm sure Oliver's got this.
I wouldn't count on it.
Oliver hasn't been very forthcoming
with his plans lately.
Well, I don't know
what's been going on with him lately,
apart from a recent wardrobe change,
but one thing that hasn't changed is,
he needs you guys.
Even if he doesn't think so.
Good luck.
I'll never get used to that.
Well, there goes our ride home. John?
The plane we came in is still secure,
but we need to get to it quickly.
Come on.
Tatsu. Let's go, we're leaving.
I left a life of solitude because Oliver asked it of me.
It's time to return to it.
I'm wired.
In direct communication with my men outside.
I'm going to count to five.
One...
What's happening?
Two engines are down.
We're trying to compensate, but they've been tampered with.
Sabotage?
You!
This is all your doing.
Don't!
Nyssa had nothing to do with this.
You were delivered by the prophecy.
You wed my daughter.
Your name is Al Sah-Him
and you are Wareeth Al Ghul!
My name...
is Oliver Queen!
Oliver Queen is dead.
And soon, you will be, too!
I handed you my crusade!
My only mission!
I already have one.
Survive this,
and I will come for you again and again
until your end of days!
But first, your city will perish!
It's the only parachute.
Stay strapped in and do exactly as I say.
All right, we've lost hydraulics.
Is there a red lever by your right leg?
Yes!
Ok, on my go,
you'll pull it up, you'll turn it clockwise,
push it back down. You understand?
Yes!
3, 2, 1. Now!
Now back down!
This is going to hurt.
Oh, no.
I couldn't.
He loved you.
You were his friend.
Excuse me.
My people will be looking for me.
It's just a matter of time till they find me.
Do it.
Do you remember Amanda Walle?
She's the reason that I'm in Hong Kong.
She thought I had a special talent.
She taught me things.
Let me show you.
We don't have much time.
For what?
I thought you said Oliver had a plan.
Yeah, and in the event that it doesn't work,
He has a back-up
us.
John, let's determine
the status of our arsenal.
Laurel, go to your father; start mobilizing the police.
Mr. Palmer, I need you to find something that will neutralize
an airborne contagion.
Miss Smoak, let's find out
where our League of Assassin friends might be.
I'm sorry. Did I mumble?
We follow his lead.
For now.
Ah, guys, I set up a proximity alarm
to detect an unauthorized entry to this level.
It's going off like crazy.
Nyssa.
- John-- - You son of a bitch!
Maybe we should give these guys the room.
Nyssa looks happy.
You two on your honeymoon?
What the hell's going on, Oliver?
Start talking!
The reason that I have
kept Malcolm close for the past several months
is because he had critical intel on our enemy.
He knows Ra's. He knows the league.
And he knew that if I was appointed his successor,
that meant Starling City was marked for death.
The only way that we were going to defeat the league
was from the inside.
I had to get close enough to Ra's to find out how he was
going to destroy the city...
and stop him.
You trusted malcolm Merlyn
more than you did the two people closest to you!
John, it wasn't about trust!
It was about making sure that you and you were safe.
I had to keep the circle as small as possible.
How did you expect to repair all this once you got back?
I didn't.
I flew with Ra's and the virus to Starling
and I sabotaged the plane.
The plan...
was to kill ra's and destroy the virus.
It didn't work.
How did you expect to survive the plane crash?
You didn't.
You never expected to have this conversation.
You were planning on dying.
So that was your big plan?
Sacrificing yourself to take out Ra's?
It was the only way.
At least now that it didn't work,
I get a chance to tell both of you
how sorry I am.
Sorry won't cut it, Oliver.
Not this time.
But we have bigger problems
than hurt feelings
and broken trust.
Laurel needs to contact her father.
Ray needs to find a way to counteract the virus.
I'm sure Malcolm told you...
we don't have a lot of time.
Oliver!
What have you done?
He failed this city.
And I'm giving him the justice he deserves.
This isn't justice!
It's... wrong.
He's still alive.
Just passed out from the pain.
What'd you find?
My father isn't using any of the league's
ordinary redoubts in the city.
If Ra's is here with the virus,
why hasn't he used it yet?
Where are we?
Nowhere. Ra's is old school.
Every way I have of finding him is new school.
Oliver, maybe we need to change the way we're looking for him.
If we're trying to find a sub that's gone dark,
we should look for what's out of the ordinary in the water.
So we look for what's unusual
and maybe that points us
to how or where Ra's plans to release the virus.
Traffic lights were down for 20 minutes at Adams and O'Neil.
All computers at Starling National Bank are offline.
The entire top floor of the Essex Hotel is closed.
There's an electrical spike at 52nd and Robson.
Wait, go back. The top floor of the Essex is closed.
My father doesn't frequent hotels.
According to internal emails,
the floor was shut down for a Damien Darhk.
A name like that has to be an alias.
Damien Darhk is in Starling city.
My father's most bitter enemy.
That's why Ra's hasn't released the virus.
He wants to use it to kill Damien Darhk.
This was never just about my ascension.
Ra's wants to take out his nemesis.
Looks like you weren't the only one with a hidden agenda.
This can work for us.
Ra's wants Damien.
So we give him Damien.
We trade Damien for the virus.
That is remarkably ruthless and cold-blooded.
I approve.
Count two on the roof,
One on the penthouse floor.
I got two guarding the elevators,
another three going in and out of the service entrance.
And a patrol in the stairwell.
Same for the northwest corridor.
Keep Darhk's men from joining the party.
Getting into position.
Damien Darhk.
You know, the hotel's going to bill me for that window.
Turn around!
This is bold,
Even for Ra's.
Ra's Al Ghul wants you dead.
He's planning a bioweapon to take you out.
Well, that's a considerable amount of work to go to.
Ra's certainly must want Mr. Darhk off the board.
Oh, you seem surprised.
Mr. Darhk left Starling the moment he learned
of Ra's' intention.
It's amusing the demon's head
thinks he can catch my employer unawares.
It's just my phone.
Hello, Al Sah-him.
Apparently both our plans did not go as we'd hoped.
I'm going to find you.
It was a bold gambit, hoping to leverage Mr. Darhk,
but one which had done you no good.
I set in motion the death of your city
10 minutes ago.
The Alpha Omega shall be disseminated by means of four vessels.
Four instruments of death.
And I doubt that you and your friends
will have time to stop all of them.
Unlike you, Oliver Queen,
I'm a man of my word.
And I swore that you would see your city perish.
I told you I needed the dd-fives for the Andreyko case on my desk,
and unless I recently went blind, they're not here!
Now what...
I got to put you on hold for a second.
Won't be long.
I thought you and I agreed to give ourselves some space.
Not when the city's in danger.
I don't have time for this.
Wait. Do you remember that chemical spill
in Hong Kong five years ago?
It turns out, it was a biological attack
- and that bioweapon... - Let me guess.
This is coming from your buddy Queen, right?
The city's under attack? Must be may?
What do...
You still keep it in the middle drawer?
- What? - The bottle?
I'm going to bet that it's scotch.
It's not what you think it is.
Don't.
If you want to drink, then drink.
But don't just stand there and lie to me right to my face.
Doesn't feel good, does it?
It makes you thirsty.
I love you.
No matter what happens between us, that'll never change.
You can hate me for lying,
you can blame Oliver for Sara,
you can even blame me.
But falling off the wagon, that's on you.
I got it under control, all right?
It's two drinks a day and that's it.
We're alcoholics, dad! Drunks!
There's no such thing as two drinks a day.
And now you have a choice.
You can keep drinking
and keep being angry at me and Oliver or the rest of the world, if you want.
Or you can make both of your daughters proud
and throw away the bottle and help save the city.
John, Malcolm, and Nyssa are on their way back.
- What happened with Darhk? - He was gone.
Man that I found was a cut-out.
Ra's plans to release the virus at four points across the city.
I worked out a containment system that can safely neutralize the virus,
if we can get our hands on it.
Well, we need four of them,
and a way to spread the inoculant if this gets out of control.
I scrubbed through all the information that Malcolm gave us
on the Hong Kong attack five years ago.
The Alpha Omega virus gave off a low level
mission from its R.N.A., almost like radiation.
If you can hack the Keyhole Hexagon satellite,
you can tune the quadband to search for it...
which you've been doing for the last five minutes.
We need probable locations
where he would release the virus
as soon as you can get them.
Maseo!
Where you going?
I don't know.
All I know...
is I wasn't strong enough
to save my son.
Or to do what Oliver did.
What oliver did was horrible.
He allowed himself to become a monster.
No more of a monster than I am.
I am...
without a soul, Tatsu.
Only if you abandon your wife when she needs you the most.
Every time...
I look in your eyes...
I see my son's.
I see my failure.
I love you.
I'm not worthy of that love.
Where's he going?
Somewhere we cannot follow.
I know I said I would never, ever bring you coffee again,
but the city facing
a bioweapon attack
seemed like a valid exception.
So your plan to take out Ra's by dying...
We should talk about that.
Every night since the mountain,
I've had the same dream.
You are pleading with me not to go face Ra's,
and I listen to you.
Sometimes the dream still ends badly;
I end up with this sword in my chest.
But most of the time,
we escape.
And we're just driving.
And all this seems...
it seems so far away,
because it's just...
it's the two of us.
I know you think that that's not possible,
that you dead and Ra's
dead is the only realistic best case scenario.
Felicity...
I can't defeat Ra's Al Ghul.
Oliver Queen can't.
The Arrow can't.
Both those men tried and both those men failed.
You remember what you said to me during our night together
in Nanda Parbat?
You're no longer either of those men.
You've become...
someone else.
Become something else.
This...
is different now.
Because despite your best efforts,
you've allowed yourself to feel something.
I know you think that that's a weakness; it's not.
It's your key
to beating Ra's.
Don't fight to die.
Fight to live.
Satellite trace is back. I've got four locations.
OK, let's go.
Felicity...
thank you.
All right, yeah, got 'em.
I don't know, we'll talk about that later.
I need all units. I need E.S.U., all squad cars
converging on these four locations.
We got a potential bioweapons attack.
I'm onsite.
Onsite.
I'm onsite,
But I have no idea what I should be looking for around here.
Do you see anyone in a League of Assassins outfit?
That would be a dead giveaway.
I have no weapons.
And I have no virus.
Ra's Al Ghul awaits you on the Starling City dam.
He wishes to be in your presence
as your city dies.
And what makes him think that I won't just stay focused
on saving my city?
Because he knows of your deluded belief
that you can defeat him in battle.
And you know that as long as the demon's head lives,
he will continue to threaten your home.
Ok, I got a runner carrying a metal briefcase.
The bioweapon is going to be in the briefcase.
OK, I'm scrubbing footage from traffic
and surveillance cameras at the remaining three locations.
Don't... move.
- Nice threads. - Thanks.
Felicity, the briefcase is empty.
It's empty!
Where's the virus?
Where's the virus?!
He is the weapon.
Ra's is using his own men to disperse the virus!
And we will not be stopped.
The will of Ra's Al Ghul is our own!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I knew you couldn't resist.
The man who survives the sword of Ra's Al Ghul
shall become Ra's Al Ghul.
So you brought me here to kill you?
Either way, I am victorious.
You either ascend to Ra's as I have designed,
or you will die. And the last thing
you will ever see is your beloved city
succumbing to disease and death.
Look out! Go! Go, go, go, go, go, go!
Get back! Go! Go, run!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Get back, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Everybody get back!
You got to get out of here!
No, Malcolm inoculated me. Oh, my god.
Starling city appears to be in the throes of a biological attack.
Outbreak at Nelson Plaza. It's bad.
It looks the virus spreads
when infected blood is exposed to open air.
Even if we find Ra's men, how are we supposed
to stop them from spreading the virus?
Really bad temporary solution--
get them off the streets in a secured place as possible
and do not let them cut themselves.
Wait. You're not inoculated.
This is my father's doing.
I will see it undone.
You choose a sword that has already defeated you in battle.
Miss Smoak, I've taken out one of Ra's' men.
Don't take chances. Put that body some place airtight,
and try not to kill anyone else, while you're at it!
The virus is spreading. Can you replicate the inoculant?
That is the easy part.
The hard part is disseminating it over a three block radius.
Your nanotech.
Can you make them airborne?
That is what I'm trying to do.
I have been a most excellent trainer.
We need to get this guy somewhere he can't infect anyone.
What the hell's going on here?
We're in the middle of a city-wide crisis.
I don't have time for this.
We've got two suspects up on the dam.
Don't know why they're fighting each other,
but the chief says they're responsible for what's happening.
He's ordered me to take them out as soon as I have a clean shot.
Something has changed within you, boy.
Your will to live burns brighter,
and yet you rejected my offer of eternal life.
What you were offering wasn't living!
Power serves you no interest.
You'd rather love.
A man who condemns his daughter to death wouldn't understand.
Detective, Captain?
We got a problem.
You're going to have to be a lot more specific.
I'm pretty sure your boy is at the Starling City dam,
and I got officers not listening to me
getting ready to shoot him.
Now, despite what I think about your guy,
I don't want to see him killed
while I think he is trying to save the city.
But unless you order up a miracle pretty quick,
that's exactly what's going to happen.
- Got number four. - Hold on a second, John.
We have a new problem.
Hey, you have to get to Starling City dam. You have to fly.
I'm still uploading the operating code to the nanotech.
And I'm still rewriting on the fly.
I--I can't leave the station. Why?
Oliver's in trouble. He needs your help.
Felicity, if I can't get
the nanotech to disperse the inoculant,
thousands of people in this city will die.
What? No! Ray, Oliver!
It's one life against the city's.
What would Oliver do?
Unlike you,
thousands of honorable men will mourn my death
when I leave this earth.
No.
They will kneel
before the next Ra's Al Ghul.
I knew I chose well with you, boy.
If I could figure out how
to get this thing off, I would be kissing you right now.
The casualty count would have been much higher
if not for an airborne inoculant
that rumors credit Palmer Technologies with developing.
You killed my father.
I had to.
I wanted to be the one.
You're lucky you're still alive.
You wouldn't be had you not been wearing League armor.
I like to think I had
a little something to do with that.
When I started this,
I wanted to keep you as far away from it as possible,
because that has always been my instinct--
to go it alone.
But the truth is that we won tonight
because I wasn't alone.
I thought that this crusade would only end with my death.
But even if I had died tonight,
it would live on, because of you...
and you.
Oh, and you.
It's true.
This city isn't lacking masks.
Heroes.
Which is why I no longer need to be one.
What are you saying?
Ra's took the Arrow identity from me.
I couldn't be that person even if I wanted to be.
And I don't want to be.
I told you that...
I couldn't be the Arrow and be with you.
I want to be with you.
You told me that I have become someone else,
and I would like to...
maybe discover a little more about that person.
If you'll come with me.
With you where?
Some place far away from here.
Even without me,
Starling still has heroes to watch over it.
John...
I'll talk to him.
- Wow. - Yeah.
That's the word I've been saying over and over in my head.
So, does that mean I'm going to have to find
a new vice president?
I think so.
I hope that you find someone who makes you happy, Ray.
You deserve that.
- John? - I'm happy for you, Oliver.
Despite our issues,
you deserve to be happy. You and Felicity.
And you're right, the city's in good hands.
- Including yours. - I'm no superhero.
You're a hero.
For three years, you've been a rock.
The city's rock, my rock.
For three years, you have been the person i can count on.
I'm still counting on you.
Oliver, I don't know if I can get past
what happened between the two of us.
I'm not asking you to.
I'll think on it.
Ok.
John.
If you're going to keep going,
you may want to find a way to conceal your identity
when you're out there.
I'll think on that, too.
- You be well, Oliver. - You, too.
Where will you go?
Kumamoto.
There's a monastery there
near my childhood home.
I had always hoped to show it to Akio
when we returned to Japan as a family.
I'm so very sorry, Tatsu.
And where will you go?
Back to Starling City?
No, I...
I tortured Shrieve for hours.
I don't want that darkness around my mother or my sister.
What of your father?
You told me about his message.
His hope that you would save your city.
I'm not the man my father thinks I am.
Even if I was, I...
I should be alone.
I need to be alone.
Be well, Tatsu.
He's upstairs,
packing.
I'll be leaving Starling as well.
Try to imagine my profound disappointment.
Thea, I love you.
I know my actions always haven't shown that.
But I am your father.
and whatever you need,
I will always be there for you.
Yeah, well, don't wait by the phone.
But, a year ago,
you told me that you could teach me to be strong.
You've made good by that promise.
God, are you sure you really want to do this?
As sure as I was the last five times you asked me.
Be safe out there, ok?
As safe as anybody with a mask on can be.
But, actually, I was thinking, um,
maybe I'll call myself the Red Arrow?
I think I already told everyone to call you speedy.
As we agreed.
We've come a long way, you and I.
I've always looked at you as a son, Oliver.
And I'm glad we got to work together
to trust as we did.
I will never forgive you
for what you did to Sara.
And my sister.
Ever.
Does that mean we're enemies once more?
That depends on what you do with your end of the bargain.
Open new file.
"Atom project update gamma."
Had an interesting breakthrough
while repurposing nanotechnology
for anti-viral dissemination.
With the proper modifications,
the nanotech can be applied
to the miniaturization of key components
of the suit.
This will be miniaturization test number one.
Why can't anything ever work the first try?
At least admit this was your goal all along.
My only aspiration was to free myself of your father's grasp.
A feat we both managed to achieve.
I don't see how it was possible in your case.
When I was your father's captive three months ago,
he tortured me with his blade.
And you survived because my father chose to release you.
Funny thing, prophecies.
Fate and my father have shown you mercy.
I will not.
You took Sara from me, and I will have justice.
You are welcome to try.
Until then...
kneel before Ra's Al Ghul.
My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I returned home with only one goal--
to save my city.
And I did.
I became a hero who helped people.
But now it is time for me to be someone else.
It is time for me to be... something else.
So, where are we going?
I'm thinking a state that can annul a Nanda Parbat marriage.
Can I say something strange?
I'm happy.