YYeTs.com
My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home with only one goal,
to save my city.
Now others have joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
To the rest of Starling City,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
My sister. She was murdered.
And I can't tell anyone.
See, before, Laurel, you were swinging at your sister's killer.
Don't train for that. All right, train for yourself.
The serum that you were exposed to,
it changes your body but it also warps your mind.
You're not moving very quickly this morning.
I just didn't sleep much last night.
What are you doing here?
Roy!
Where'd you go?
Sorry.
Get your head in the game.
We're in position.
So is the Culebra Cartel and their gazillion pounds of heroin.
They all showed up about 30 minutes ago
and they haven't moved from your location.
Copy that.
No sentries outside.
If we're going to do this, we need to do it now.
I've got north entrance, Dig's got south.
- Roy. - East.
The roof.
You're on over watch.
The Culebras get their weapons from the Bratva.
All military grade.
I've got your backs.
Let's do this.
South is clear.
Nobody's home.
Roof's clear.
North is empty, too.
That doesn't make sense. They all showed up
half an hour ago and never left.
They are in there somewhere.
Looks like somebody beat us here.
There's at least a few million dollars worth of heroin.
He took Paco.
Whoever did this ignored the drugs,
took a gang member.
This was personal.
Yeah, more than that.
Whoever did this was trying to send a message.
I think I know what it is.
Guilty. Well, yeah.
The Culebras are the bloodiest gang in Starling.
Who's the second bloodiest?
Culebras have a long standing rivalry with the Los Halcones.
Thought you said this was personal, not business.
And Paco?
There are only 86,000 Pacos in Starling,
give or take 5,000 for a few nicknames.
Something tells me that the Culebra's
long standing rivals will narrow that down for us.
You know, when we find Paco, he'll be too dead to say anything.
I'm not looking for him. I'm looking for whoever did this.
I will handle this.
Take the rest of the night.
I'll back you up.
Not dead on your feet, you won't.
I'm sorry. I know I've been a little out of it recently.
Don't be sorry. Be rested.
I wouldn't be much of a teacher
if I let you get killed because your reaction time is slow, ok?
Dig.
There are a lot of Halcones members in Starling City.
How about I take the ones north of Tenth Street.
You know, we've been waiting here an hour.
After walking around the block five times.
We need to work on your patience.
Where is this guy? And more importantly,
how is he going to help us find out what this
China white person is--
- Chien Na Wei. - Whatever!
How is he going to help
us find out what she's doing in Hong Kong?
Waller hasn't been able to locate Chien Na Wei
because she avoids using any traceable forms of communication.
So he's the target now?
He's her delivery guy.
Her courier. But he's not a target.
Waller doesn't want you to kill him.
That's refreshing.
They'll use a dead drop.
Leave behind information for Chien's network.
Information Waller intercepts.
I see him.
Stay on bluetooth.
I'll be right behind you.
What was that?
Did he make you?
Yeah, I think he did.
He's gone. Where is it?
- Where's what? - The envelope.
The message. We need it!
He must have stashed it somewhere
while you were chasing him.
I didn't see him stash anything!
Yes, you did.
You just don't know it yet.
That's not bad.
Yeah. It's better than not bad.
What the hell was that?!
Today's lesson.
Fighting's about being surprised and not getting rattled.
You look rattled.
Try angry.
Another lesson, then.
It's not about you getting knocked to the mat.
It's if you get up.
Okay, fine.
Then let's go again.
Not tonight. All right?
I got to close up shop.
And you need to get some rest.
Let those muscles recover.
Make sure you get some protein within the hour, all right?
Yeah, egg whites. They're my new bff.
Oh, that's disgusting.
No, no, no, two blocks from here--
Korean tacos.
- Korean tacos? - Trust me.
They're heaven. Come on, I'm buying.
Can I ask you a question?
You just did.
Kidding. What?
You know how to do a blood test, right?
I know just enough to make me dangerous.
And, well, me holding a syringe,
well, that makes me more dangerous.
Why?
I need you to test my blood.
For what? And don't say STDS,
because that would be crossing a line.
For Mirakuru.
I don't need to check you for traces of Mirakuru.
You were cured.
I know, I--
If this is about your sleep problems,
Mirakuru makes people crazy strong
and crazy crazy. It doesn't make it hard for them to get 8 hours.
Could you just...
Are you ok?
I mean, besides the whole not sleeping thing.
Totally. I'm fine.
I'm just looking for reasons to help me sleep, you know?
Ok.
I'm looking for a crew member named Paco.
- Emilio? - Paco!
That's what they call him, ese!
- Paco's his street name! - Who?!
Emilio.
Emilio Ortega.
Thank you.
Felicity, I have a name.
Emilio Ortega.
Pinging his cell's GPS.
He's in the Glades. Ninth and Hasen.
Why'd you kill all those men?
What the hell are you talking about?
What are you doing?!
Get out of here.
Oh, my God.
Now, Laurel!
No!
Ted didn't do this. Ted's been with me
for the past two hours. He trained with me,
and then we went for dinner.
And that...
He wasn't here when we left.
Ok, that is ten minutes of my life I am never getting back.
I'm clean?
Your cholesterol is a little high for someone of your age,
but absolutely zero Mirakuru serum.
Congratulations.
Thank God.
Ok, you're acting like I just told you
that the biopsy came back negative.
What is going on?
It's--it's stupid.
You just had me test your blood
for a serum you were cured of six months ago.
I already knew it was stupid.
The reason I haven't been sleeping
is 'cause I've been having dreams,
and not normal ones.
It was like I was remembering the time I was out, you know?
When Slade oded me on the Mirakuru.
What do you remember?
Nothing much. Just a feeling.
A feeling of being...
not me.
And being strong and out of control,
but here's the thing,
In those dreams...
I killed Sara.
This really had you worried?
Because the dreams, they didn't feel like dreams, Felicity.
They felt like memories.
I actually remembered throwing arrows into her.
Crazy, right?
Yeah.
Crazy.
So that's it?
I was with him the whole time.
You can put me on the box if you'd like.
If I wanted to give my daughter a polygraph,
I'd have done it back when you discovered beer.
So listen, what's the story
with you and this guy, anyway?
He's just my trainer.
- Who you went to dinner with? - As friends.
But I know him, and he would never do something like this.
Well, we've got to hold him here
till the coroner's official findings come back,
and then if they're consistent with his story,
we'll cut him loose.
It's like I said.
He didn't do it.
Why would a mass murderer string up a body in his gym?
Ted caters to a pretty rough clientele.
A lot of career criminals,
gangbangers.
He runs afoul of one every now and again.
He thinks someone was trying to send him a message.
- Who? - He says he doesn't know.
I want to talk to him.
About this case, or me?
Two weeks ago, I said I wouldn't train you to fight.
Now you have a trainer.
Who's training me to box, to let off some steam.
I think I have a pretty good reason to have some.
Keep your eyes open with this guy.
He didn't do this.
Just the same.
Why are you sitting like that?
I'm concentrating.
Why?
- Because I need to remember something. - Why?
Try this.
Pay attention.
Remember where the matching one is?
See, your memory's fine.
He needs your help.
You need my help.
You know I don't like your friend.
This gaijin, he is trouble.
Well, I need him to remember what he saw.
When we capture Chien Na Wei, my debt is paid.
All I care about
is us getting home.
Then help me.
I love you.
You know that, right?
Oh, come on, you must be cheating.
I'm just better at this than you.
Akio.
We were just playing a game.
Mr. Queen.
I will house you, feed you, and clothe you.
But my son is off limits.
Fine.
Stay!
What are you doing?
I'm helping you.
Now...
Do exactly as I say.
You ever heard of this Ted Grant?
Yeah, I saw his title fight a few years back on pay per view.
They call him Wild Cat. He's the real deal.
Body in his gym was strung up the same way
that the bodies in the warehouse were.
Like punching bags.
What if Laurel vouches for him?
I don't think that Laurel is seeing clearly on this one.
If Grant's our doer, he's more than boxer.
I hacked CSU's files on the warehouse murders.
The Culebras were armed to the teeth,
but the killer, the psycho mass murder guy,
Never fired a shot.
They were beaten to death by brass knuckles.
It's a pretty specific M.O.
It matches one murder from six years ago.
Same as tonight, Culebra drug dealer.
Blunt force trauma, consistent with brass knuckles
worn by a left-handed assailant.
Let me guess-- Ted "Wild Cat" Grant's a lefty.
They called him the Starling southpaw.
Well, SCPD never put that together,
because Ted was never arrested.
He's moving.
You dinged him with a tracer?
Just because Laurel trusts him doesn't mean I have to.
Talk me in.
Second time I've found you with a body!
I've never killed anybody. I'm being set up.
Why should I believe you?!
Because I used to be a vigilante.
I used to be you.
The city has been hurt long before you showed up.
I've never heard of another vigilante in Starling.
It was six years ago.
I wasn't news-- I stuck to the Glades.
And these are supposed to convince me?
Masks are also useful for serial killers.
Says a guy currently wearing one.
Who's that?
I don't know. I've never seen him before in my life.
But this was hung around the body
that was found in my gym.
The key is to the storage locker.
He's leaving me a trail to follow.
Who is?
Whoever's setting me up.
Look, I've never killed anyone.
Except for that drug dealer that you beat to death six years ago.
That was a mistake.
I may have avoided jail, but I have lived
with the guilt of that man's death
every single day of my life.
I gave it all up after that.
I locked this place up and I swore I'd never open it again.
Who else knows about the locker?
No one.
This is where I kept my supplies.
A safe place separate from my day job.
I'm sure you've got one just like it.
Mine's bigger.
Look, we're both trying to find out
who the hell's doing this.
We could help each other.
His name is Albert Mancini.
No criminal record,
aside from a few unpaid parking tickets.
Grant says he doesn't know who this guy is.
- Oh, and now you believe him? - I haven't decided yet!
Do you know that you're training with a vigilante?
Former, apparently.
And no, I didn't.
I didn't!
So you also didn't know
that six years ago, he beat someone to death?
How many more reasons
am I going to have to give you
before you stay away from this guy?
Ok, you know what,
are you guys just about finished with your little private chat?
The guy from your storage unit,
he has no criminal record.
He was a magician.
Magician's assistant, more accurately.
He worked with a local act before getting cut loose.
Mancini hasn't worked since.
Culebra Cartel, magician's assistant.
What's the connection?
Their act was at the Sansa Bar.
The Sansa Bar's where's the drug dealer was murdered.
You mean the person you beat to death?
I told you--
whoever's doing this
is leaving me a trail to follow.
Then we follow it.
We need another minute.
How do you two know each other?
We used to date.
You cannot be serious.
I am not on your team.
I don't work for you.
Exactly. You're untrained.
Oh, who's fault is that?
Does he know?
What's driving you?
I told him...
that Sara's gone.
But does he know
that you want to follow in her footsteps?
You're playing a very dangerous game, Laurel.
I can handle it.
No, you can't.
Because you haven't realized
that it's not actually a game.
Let's go.
What about Laurel?
She's not coming.
Oliver has a 20 on our killer.
I thought Oliver was tracking Grant.
Looks like things have changed.
Suit up, he wants us to provide back-up.
- Roy can't go. - What?
I need to talk to you about something important.
- It can wait. - No, it can't. John?
I'll take care of it.
What the hell is that about?
We need to talk.
Yeah, you made that pretty clear.
Before we buried Sara,
I scanned her body using portable magnetic resonance imaging.
Felicity, you're really starting to freak me out.
I basically created a virtual autopsy.
It's not as good as a regular autopsy,
but like when I can use it to determine things
an autopsy would,
like angle of tack, trajectory,
and the force of the arrows.
Felicity, what are you saying?
There were certain things about the forensics
that I couldn't reconcile with,
specifically,
the angle and the velocity of the arrows were not consistent
with a normal bow or archer of normal height.
But if the arrows were thrown with mirakuru force...
What if there was some residual mirakuru in your system?
It would explain the forensics.
The angle and the force of the arrows.
But you said that I tested negative for mirakuru.
There isn't any in your blood today,
but if one last mirakuru episode
burned down any remnants in your system...
"Episode?"
You mean...
me killing Sara.
I'm onsite.
Copy. Keep watching the perimeter.
How many partners do you have, anyway?
The Culebras.
The body in your gym,
the body in your storage locker.
Someone's gone to a lot of trouble to frame you for murders
and bring you here.
Why?
What does all this have to do with one killing six years ago?
Hello, Ted.
I see you got my messages.
Arrows.
Brass knuckles.
I never knew
why we couldn't just use a gun the way they did.
Because we're better than they are.
At least we're supposed to be.
That's almost ironic, coming from you.
I trusted you!
SCPD!
Ted Grant,
you are under arrest for multiple counts of homicide.
What are you talkin' about?
- I didn't do this. - Yeah?
Tell that to the stiff we found in your locker.
Let's go.
Sorry he got past me.
He knew an exit out of the building
that wasn't on any of the blueprints
that Felicity hooked me up with.
You had Ted Grant arrested?
Your father's men found him at a crime scene.
Another body was found at a storage locker that he owns,
along with evidence of past vigilantism.
- No. He's innocent. - I know.
I saw the person who's doing this.
Who is it?
He was wearing Ted's old gear. Full face mask.
Let's go.
Clearly Grant knows who's behind the mask.
Oliver.
Laurel. I...
What's up?
I have to--
Roy, don't. Let's just--
I need to tell you something.
Ok?
I...
I killed Sara.
That doesn't...
You're not making any sense.
Why would you kill Sara?
It was the Mirakuru.
Roy had no memory of the attack.
No real memory, at least. But he's been recalling
fragments of his Mirakuru exposure last year.
That, and suppressed memories often resurface in dreams.
This is insane.
Laurel, I am so sorry. I'm really--
Don't!
Wait, Roy, where do you think you're going?
Let him go.
I thought he was cured.
What we know about Mirakuru is vastly outweighed
by the things we don't know.
What does that even mean?
That Roy killed my sister and it's not his fault?
The arrows that killed Sara,
we pulled D.N.A. off of them, didn't we?
I tested it against the sample of Roy's blood.
It was the first thing I did.
And?
The results were inconclusive.
I can't process this right now.
Look at me.
Focus on what you can process.
Ted knows who we're coming after.
I need you to find out who it is.
I can't. I can't.
If Roy killed Sara, then--
If Roy killed Sara, then...
We will deal with it.
For right now, I need you to deal with Ted.
Ok?
Ok.
How sure are you?
There's other forensic evidence.
A virtual autopsy, in light of what Roy's described,
it sounds incriminating.
That, and his trouble
sleeping started right when Sara was killed.
My husband says you are having problems
remembering what you saw earlier today.
That's the problem.
I didn't see anything.
You see and hear far more than you think.
Hidden truths,
very deep in your sub-conscious.
You saw something, but your head is too busy.
You need to quiet it.
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath.
In through your nose, out through your mouth.
In...
and out.
And again.
You're floating, in nothingness.
All that exists is your breath.
Any thoughts you have are clouds.
They just drift away.
I remember.
16 murders.
17, counting the one from six years ago.
That's more than the son of Sam, less than Bundy.
Probably worth a mini-series, huh? Maybe a book?
You became a defense attorney?
Can I talk to him for a minute?
You sure can pick 'em.
You ok?
I'm not the one facing a lifetime in prison.
Who framed you?
I don't know.
I can't help you if you're going to keep lying to me.
The arrow saw you with him. He knows you know who it is.
If the D.A.'s office refuses to seek an indictment,
the police have to release you.
But first...
I'm going to need you to be straight with me.
Who was the man behind the mask?
His name's Isaac Stanzler.
Six years ago, the Culebras ran the Glades.
I thought it would be a good idea for families
to be able to live there
without worrying about their kids getting shot.
So I decided to do something about it.
You became a vigilante.
Just like your friend in the green hood--
without the green hood.
And what about Stanzler?
You know the guy the arrow's been running around with lately?
The one in red?
Stanzler was my guy in red.
I guess you can call him my apprentice.
And one night, we decided to go after
this drug dealer that was pushing crank near the school.
We tracked him all the way to this nightclub.
And what happened?
That drug dealer...
Isaac got to him first.
That murder from six years ago...
That wasn't you, that was him.
I hung it up after that.
What about Stanzler?
What happened to Isaac Stanzler?
I told him to get the hell out of Starling.
That I never wanted to see his face ever again.
I cut him loose.
That's why I've been lying to you this whole time, Laurel.
Everything that's happening is my fault.
No word from Laurel?
Not yet.
But according to SCPD email traffic,
which I may or may not have hacked into,
they are dropping the charges against Ted Grant.
Oliver, let me go after Roy.
If he's experiencing Mirakuru side effects,
we can't leave him running around.
So you bring him in.
Then what?
Oliver, this crusade of ours,
it's supposed to be about justice, right?
So if that's supposed to mean something,
we can't have two sets of rules--
one for the bad guys and one for us.
I'm the one who brought Roy into this crusade.
And maybe it's time for you to cut him loose.
Are you telling me to abandon him?
Yes, Oliver.
If that's what it takes to find justice for Sara.
So what do you think Stanzler's next move is?
Well, framing me didn't work.
I'm almost afraid to think of
what he might try to do next.
What I should have done from the start.
After you abandoned me, the Culebra family,
they wanted payback for the man they lost.
They tortured me for months before I escaped.
Isaac, I'm so sorry.
I didn't know.
But come on, let's talk about this.
Oh, don't worry, we will.
There's so much I have to say before I kill you.
Where are we going?
Just drive!
Your beef is with me.
Ok, you got me.
Let her go.
Taking innocent people hostage?
Man, I taught you better than that.
They're not people, they're criminals.
Albert Mancini wasn't.
You still strung him up in that nightclub.
You taught me that there are no innocents
when you abandoned me to the Culebras.
You gave me direction, purpose.
And then when things got tough,
when I really needed you,
you weren't there.
It's Laurel.
Put her on speaker.
I hated you so much for that.
That voice, that's him.
I was just a kid,OK?
You were supposed to know better.
Call's coming from Laurel's cell.
Moving fast, 45 miles an hour.
They're in her car.
They're headed north on Route 17.
Keep that line open.
Isaac, I'm sorry.
I had no idea!
Eyes on the road!
Don't stop!
Who was that?
- Who was that?! - I don't know.
The only friend I ever had was you.
Another vigilante.
Looks like we started a movement.
Go, go, go!
Get Grant!
Get Laurel.
Don't you get it? He's using you!
You're not a human being, man.
You were just another weapon in his arsenal.
And the second you do something wrong,
he'll turn his back on you.
He will abandon you!
I'm not you.
Don't abandon me.
Never.
You planning on hiding in the shadows all night?
That's a good trick.
Used it once or twice myself back in the day.
Thank you.
You can thank me by doing something for me.
Name it.
Stay away from Laurel Lance.
She's in a vulnerable place
and I don't want her getting hurt.
Did you bother asking what she wants?
Cause that's her choice.
If she stops coming, that's fine.
She'll stop coming.
You know, you did me a solid,
so let me repay you with a little hard won advice.
Learn from my mistake--
What I did, what you do...
this playing judge and jury,
it messes with people's heads.
It messed with Isaac's;
I just waited till it was too late to cut him loose.
Don't make the same mistake
with the kid you're running around with.
Ted, your mistake wasn't cutting him loose...
it was losing faith in him.
How are you feeling?
The worst part about sobriety
is having to pass on the pain meds.
Right.
I thought maybe you could use a ride home.
And an "I told you so?"
I don't think that I owe you one of those.
When I said I wouldn't train you,
I was trying to protect you.
But a homicidal former vigilante apprentice
was not what I had in mind.
I know you're trying to protect me, Ollie,
but I'm not helpless.
I've never seen you that way.
But Laurel, I'm always going to watch out for you.
It's not because I think you're helpless.
It's because I care about you.
And what about Roy?
Do you trust me?
I'm going to miss this.
I feel like I was just starting to get good at it.
You are getting good at it.
That guy?
He said I was just another weapon in your arsenal.
Well, maybe that's what we should call you, then.
Arsenal.
I don't know why you would ever let me suit up
after what I did.
Doesn't matter anyway, because...
I'm going to be turning myself in.
OK.
There's something you need to know, Roy.
Something that your mind has been trying to tell you.
And I think it best
if you help me let it.
With a candle?
With meditation.
Clear your thoughts.
Find hidden truths.
This is weird.
You're hurting.
But it's not for the reasons that you think.
And I've been afraid
that if I just came out and told you,
it would only make the hurt worse.
Do you trust me?
Always.
Good. Close your eyes.
Now focus on your breathing.
In through your nose,
out through your mouth.
In...
Out.
Floating along, weightless.
And the only thing that exists
is your breath.
Now your thoughts are like clouds.
They just drift away.
No!
Let go.
I killed him.
The police officer. Why didn't you tell me?
Because you were overdosed on Mirakuru,
you didn't remember,
and I was hoping that you never would.
But then Felicity told me you had the dream
that you killed Sara, and I realized...
It was a memory.
I think because of the way Sara was murdered,
the fact they used arrows...
brought it to the surface.
So I didn't kill Sara.
No.
But I am a murderer.
- Roy... - No, I just need to be alone for a while.
This is it.
This is the dead drop.
What kind of a message is this?
Have you ever heard of steganography?
Is that the dinosaur with the plates on its back?
It's the art of concealing a message
within another message. In this case,
within an image.
Li Kuan Hui.
- Who's that? - I do not know.
But if Chien Na Wei's interested in him,
so are we.
It worked. Thank you.
I don't want your gratitude.
There's only one thing I want from you.
Name it.
Get out of our lives as soon as possible.
Sign says "closed." Learn to read.
I thought you might make an exception.
Yeah? And why would I do that?
Because I just made sure your past vigilantism
fell under the statute of limitations.
No new charges will be filed.
Much obliged.
But you still shouldn't be here.
No, this is exactly where I should be.
Last night when Isaac had me at gunpoint
and when he was shooting at my friends,
I should have been so scared.
Rattled.
But I wasn't.
I saw what needed to be done, and I did it.
Because you taught me.
I've just been teaching you how to throw a proper jab.
And your pal Robin Hood doesn't want me even doing that.
I want you to give me the tools
to avenge my sister's death.
I want you to teach me to get justice outside of a courtroom.
I took on an apprentice once.
That didn't work out so good.
Well, it's like you said--
It's not about how you get knocked down to the mat.
It's about whether you get up.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Cupid, stupid.