[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.00,0:00:03.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《绿箭》前情回顾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Previously on "Arrow"...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.48,0:00:05.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿纳托利说过你有个好计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Anatoly said that you had a plan
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.37,0:00:07.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能拿下这座城市\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to take control of this city.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.78,0:00:09.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉你好像要开除守望者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's like you were firing Overwatch.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.41,0:00:10.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须阻止迪亚兹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I need to stop Diaz,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.60,0:00:12.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了能够阻止他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And in order to do that,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.33,0:00:15.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能本末倒置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I need to bring the mission back to basics.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.21,0:00:17.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弹劾只是一个小前奏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The impeachment was just the latest step.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.31,0:00:18.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你下一步要做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And what's the next one?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.22,0:00:22.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星城现在百无禁忌了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Star city, it's open for business.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.83,0:00:29.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}赞迪亚孤儿院\N星城
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.04,0:00:32.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}三十二年前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.51,0:00:33.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爬起来  爱哭鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get your ass out of bed, chillon.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.21,0:00:37.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爱怎么看那张照片就怎么看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You can look at that picture all you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.83,0:00:39.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你爸爸不会回来了  迪亚兹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Your father ain't never coming back, Diaz.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.50,0:00:44.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃早饭  我回来时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Getting breakfast. When I come back,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.67,0:00:46.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地方最好已经干净得可以检查了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}this place better be clean for inspection.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.99,0:00:48.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,床上一道褶皱也不准有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No wrinkles on the bed-- seriously--
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.99,0:00:49.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Or...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.00,0:00:54.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就需要另一个纪念品来长点记性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get another souvenir to help remind you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.35,0:01:00.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再那么做  我就告诉赫勒修女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you do it again, I'll tell sister Heller.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.30,0:01:02.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为他们会相信你这爱哭鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You think they'll believe someone like you, chillon?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.39,0:01:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  你想打我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What? You want to take a shot at me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.32,0:01:11.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啊  我就在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Go ahead. I'm right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.51,0:01:16.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还回来  那是我唯一一张照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Give it back. That's my only one!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.34,0:01:21.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有家庭会收留你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No family's gonna want to take you in.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.25,0:01:23.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们为什么要收养你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why would they?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.55,0:01:25.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么也不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.60,0:01:27.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个失败者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're a loser.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.10,0:01:38.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要这个提醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You need that reminder now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.53,0:01:48.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}布鲁德海文\N现在
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.53,0:01:48.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他们邀请我们过来的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know that they invited us here, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.84,0:01:51.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破门而入有点不礼貌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Breaking and entering is a bit disrespectful,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.90,0:01:52.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}don't you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.92,0:01:54.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等不下去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm tired of waiting.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.23,0:01:57.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己要跟过来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're the one that wanted to tag along.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.15,0:01:59.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了看你怎么操作  看你的大事业\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To see how you operate, to see your big job.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.90,0:02:02.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到现在我们做的只是开三小时车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So far, all we've done is drive in the car for 3 hours
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.49,0:02:04.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后在外面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and wait outside...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.73,0:02:06.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再等两小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}for two more.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.37,0:02:09.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耐心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Patience.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.81,0:02:11.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一个人能有的最重要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}it's one of the most important virtues
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.23,0:02:13.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,品质之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}a person can have.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.80,0:02:16.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Meaning?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.62,0:02:19.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你只考虑眼下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you think short-term,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.94,0:02:21.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无非是从上一刻漫无目的到下一刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you're gonna drift moment to moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.50,0:02:23.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要点更大的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want something big,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.14,0:02:25.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正惊人的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}something truly remarkable,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.43,0:02:27.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得着眼于长期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you got to think long-term.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.67,0:02:31.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这等的够长的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We've been waiting out here long-term.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.41,0:02:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说清楚点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let me put it in perspective.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.07,0:02:38.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经为一件事努力了五年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've been working on something for 5 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.87,0:02:40.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等两小时算什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}what's waiting two hours?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.90,0:02:42.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一记耳光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A slap in the face.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.04,0:02:45.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相对于被引见给四分体来说不值一提\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Small price to pay for an introduction to the Quadrant.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.48,0:02:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为他们是都市传说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I thought they were an urban legend.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.61,0:02:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们非常真实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They're very real.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.26,0:02:52.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们掌握着整个国家的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They control all criminal enterprises
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.85,0:02:54.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,犯罪组织\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}across the entire country.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.38,0:02:56.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四个角\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}4 corners.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.34,0:03:00.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四分体  我懂了  很聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. Quadrant. I get it. Very clever.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.04,0:03:02.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有耐心他们得不到这种权力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They didn't get that type of power without patience.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.92,0:03:03.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是他们真这么厉害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, if they're so powerful,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.91,0:03:05.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你怎么一个后援也不带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}then why didn't you come with any backup?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.96,0:03:09.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是没带  我带了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not. I got you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.56,0:03:20.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来早了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're early.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.90,0:03:25.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲来不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My father couldn't make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.29,0:03:26.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不介意对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You don't mind, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.65,0:03:27.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let's get started.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.63,0:03:30.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有很多要讨论的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We have a lot to discuss.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.22,0:03:31.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Indeed we do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.08,0:03:41.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey. You made it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.86,0:03:46.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. Um...I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.24,0:03:48.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很好  我很高兴你来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, that's great. I'm glad you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.93,0:03:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.17,0:03:52.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我们有一阵没有作为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, it's just been a while since we've done
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.88,0:03:54.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"螺旋"活动了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}any Helix dynamics stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.20,0:03:55.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我们都忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. Well, we've been busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.97,0:03:57.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直在争斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We've been fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.63,0:03:59.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是你和我  我们的队伍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not you and me. I mean, our teams, yeah,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.25,0:04:00.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这对我不是问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but that's not an issue for me anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.87,0:04:02.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴你没有问题  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Glad it's not for you, but,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.04,0:04:03.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷内还在医院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you know, Rene's still in the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.84,0:04:05.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在才要出院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's only now just getting out.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.97,0:04:08.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为我的队伍抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry about our teams. I'm...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.93,0:04:10.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.23,0:04:14.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很希望"螺旋"能运转\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'd really like Helix to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.55,0:04:18.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来你在试图稳定神经接口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Looks like you're trying to stabilize the neuro-interface.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.51,0:04:20.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  这有点棘手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. I mean, it's just still really twitchy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.12,0:04:23.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上我想过这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, actually, I had a thought about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.51,0:04:25.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为血清素接口是由\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I think the serotonin interface is a result
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.44,0:04:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,病理反应导致的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}of the pathogenic reaction.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.11,0:04:30.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星城现在百无禁忌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Star city's open for business.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.27,0:04:34.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们掌握了警局  港口  整个城市\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We have the police, the ports, the whole city.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.78,0:04:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们操纵它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We got it wired.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.69,0:04:38.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想买东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now, you want to run merchandise,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.17,0:04:41.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想运商品  洗钱  任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want to move product, launder money, anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.22,0:04:44.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星城都可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Star city's the place.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.73,0:04:46.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假设我们有兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Assuming we're interested--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.24,0:04:49.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说真的  只是假设\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}not saying that we are but assuming,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.36,0:04:53.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想开多高的价码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}how much you looking to charge?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.21,0:04:54.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免费\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's free.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.44,0:04:59.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世上没有免费的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nothing's ever free.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.63,0:05:02.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只希望有一席之地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I just want a seat at the table.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.56,0:05:04.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在四分体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Of the Quadrant?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.89,0:05:07.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得很合理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That seems reasonable to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.82,0:05:11.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs14\fsp2\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0}每人自带一个菜的家庭聚餐
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.82,0:05:11.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把四分体说得像百味餐一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, you make the Quadrant sound like it's a potluck,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.45,0:05:13.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像我们的桌子上总有个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}as if there's always room at our table
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.33,0:05:16.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给随便带点东西来的什么人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}for anyone with something to add,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.19,0:05:18.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but it's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.39,0:05:21.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是个家族\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're a family.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.24,0:05:25.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们其实不太欢迎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're not really that welcoming
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.98,0:05:28.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外来者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to outsiders
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.47,0:05:33.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起码在我们知道你能跟上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}At least not before we know--
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.93,0:05:36.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们玩牌的水平之前不欢迎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that you can operate at our level.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.63,0:05:40.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚开出了一整个城市的价码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I just offered you a whole city.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.09,0:05:43.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你看不出来里面的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now, if you can't see the opportunity in that,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.94,0:05:46.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如让我跟你父亲谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}why don't I talk to your father?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.53,0:05:47.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He sent me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.66,0:05:53.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是想要一点额外的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're just looking for a little something extra.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.15,0:05:56.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以视之为建立你的信用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Call it establishing your bona fides.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.90,0:05:58.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What'd you have in mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.31,0:06:02.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是罗伯特·贝勒  我们的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is Robert Baylor, one of our guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.95,0:06:04.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联调局逮捕了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The FBI pinched him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.60,0:06:06.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这可不太好  -对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- That's not ideal. - Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.33,0:06:09.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得知道联邦警察把贝勒关在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We need to know where the federal marshals
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.88,0:06:12.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好让我们可以把他弄出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}are holding Baylor so we can get him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.13,0:06:14.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想测试他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want him to audition.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.03,0:06:17.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说可不太好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, that's not a very productive way of putting it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.56,0:06:18.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.46,0:06:20.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这对我不值一提\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It'll be nothing for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.50,0:06:21.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's not a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.92,0:06:24.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为达成交易不惜代价  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Whatever it takes to get the deal done, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.46,0:06:26.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赢家的思路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Champion mind-set.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.98,0:06:28.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这里有厕所吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You got a john in this place?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.04,0:06:30.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's right over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.37,0:07:08.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}绿箭\N第六季  第十九集
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.51,0:07:14.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm at the location now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.27,0:07:15.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你告诉我地址\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thanks for the address.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.40,0:07:18.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了欠你一个人情  而你欠我二十个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'd say I owe you one, but you owe me 20.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.88,0:07:24.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才是阿曼德在联调局的线人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Armand's contact at the FBI.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.52,0:07:26.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以还得继续等咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So more waiting, then.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.44,0:07:28.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得拍到那个人的照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Have to get a picture of the guy--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.61,0:07:30.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,证明他活着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Proof of life.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.22,0:07:34.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们把你当走狗  让你追球你就去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They tell you to fetch, you fetch.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.07,0:07:36.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那以后呢  让你打滚你也滚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So what's next-- roll over?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.17,0:07:40.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  你已经是条忠犬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, that's right. You've already done that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.03,0:07:42.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我对这群人太过忍让了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You think I'm giving in to these people too much?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.34,0:07:44.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我觉得  事实就是如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't think it. I know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.74,0:07:49.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过是生意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's just business.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.39,0:07:50.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能忍气吞声吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're ok with all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.49,0:07:52.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人跟你说话的语气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How that guy talked to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.81,0:07:54.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡地亚不算什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Cartier's nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.68,0:07:56.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是块垫脚石\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's a steppingstone.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.60,0:08:00.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要考虑长远利益  记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Long-term thinking. Remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.72,0:08:01.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, I remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.66,0:08:05.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么想心里好受点了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How's that working out for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.99,0:08:10.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出来抽烟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Smoke break.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.81,0:08:20.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去追  打滚  坐  真乖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fetch. Roll over, sit. Good boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.08,0:08:24.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  四分体是世上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know that the Quadrant's the most powerful
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.55,0:08:26.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最强大的犯罪组织\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}criminal organization on the continent?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.75,0:08:29.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和凯登·詹姆斯联手  我得到了一座城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When I joined up with Cayden James, I gained a city.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.77,0:08:33.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入四分体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When I join the Quadrant,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.72,0:08:36.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能获得一个帝国\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm gonna have an empire.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.75,0:08:47.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  试试看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ok. Try it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.93,0:08:52.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-行了  -太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Success. - Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.39,0:08:54.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,病理反应完全稳定了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Pathogenic reaction's completely stabilized.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.21,0:08:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.92,0:08:57.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真是优秀的团队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Damn, we make a good team!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.88,0:09:00.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说到团队  -别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Well, speaking of team-- - No. Don't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.41,0:09:02.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是干嘛  我们本来都很开心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why would you do that? We're having such a good time.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.11,0:09:03.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前不是说  对于你而言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, earlier, you said the
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.03,0:09:04.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,团队已经不再是问题所在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}team thing wasn't an issue for you anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.43,0:09:06.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我这么说了  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Did I say that? - Yeah, you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.21,0:09:07.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但为什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The question is why.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.38,0:09:10.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥利弗好像把我给炒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oliver sort of fired me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.97,0:09:12.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然他说他没有炒我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, he--he's saying that he didn't,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.59,0:09:15.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但感觉就是的  你懂的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but--heh--it sure feels like he did, you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.69,0:09:17.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是好像炒了  就是炒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not sort of fired. He fired me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.33,0:09:21.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会儿  发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait, wait. I'm sorry. What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.10,0:09:22.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长话短说  奥利弗不小心中招了迷魂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Long story short-- Oliver had a run-in with Vertigo--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.98,0:09:24.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是毒品  不是指人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The pharmaceutical, not the person--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.64,0:09:26.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,药效过去之后他突然顿悟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And he came out of it with this epiphany
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.28,0:09:28.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了阻止迪亚兹  他不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that to stop Diaz he has to
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.67,0:09:29.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"本末倒置"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"go back to basics."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.97,0:09:32.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-意思是  -他要一个人单干\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Meaning? - Meaning he's a lone wolf.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.08,0:09:34.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以绿箭队不复存在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So no more Team Arrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.94,0:09:36.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他也炒了约翰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So did he also fire John?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.49,0:09:41.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  约翰一周前主动请辞了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No. Uh, John left about a week before.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.63,0:09:45.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我得强忍着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ok. Uh, well, I'm gonna have to try
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.11,0:09:46.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不幸灾乐祸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}not to take satisfaction out of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.45,0:09:47.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加把劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Try really hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.98,0:09:50.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以本来只剩下你和奥利弗了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ok. So it was down to you and Oliver.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.41,0:09:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在就只剩下奥利弗了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now it's just Oliver.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.20,0:09:54.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.58,0:09:56.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How are you doing with all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.04,0:09:57.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挺好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.84,0:09:59.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一点都不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're not fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.68,0:10:00.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.43,0:10:03.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们谁都找不到他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So none of your people could find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.84,0:10:06.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我找到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.63,0:10:12.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让他们开始雕刻纪念碑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll tell them to start carving the monument.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.70,0:10:14.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们带你的人出来抽烟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They brought your boy out for a smoke.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.75,0:10:17.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来他更像个客人  而不是囚犯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Looked more like a guest than a prisoner.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.31,0:10:19.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  悠着点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}H-honey, ease up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.86,0:10:22.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是30年的单麦芽威士忌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's a 30-year-old single malt.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.16,0:10:26.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再叫我声"亲爱的"试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Call me "Honey" again,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.21,0:10:29.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打断你的腿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I might only break your legs.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.46,0:10:43.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I like this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.70,0:10:47.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我实现了我的承诺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So I held up my part of the bargain.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.47,0:10:50.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该轮到你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Time for you to deliver yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.92,0:10:54.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这位漂亮的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, uh, your pretty little friend makes
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.20,0:10:56.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提到了不幸的一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}an inconvenient point.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.53,0:10:59.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去贝勒先生话有点太多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It seems that Mr. Baylor's gotten a little chatty.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.71,0:11:01.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-所以呢  -所以我父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- So what? - So my father's going to
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.91,0:11:03.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得审问他  你懂的  看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}have to debrief him, you know, to find out
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.77,0:11:05.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都跟司法部门说了些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}what he told the Justice Department.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.16,0:11:08.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想让我去  -抓他回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- You want me to-- - Fetch him?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.32,0:11:12.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不就是未来的生意伙伴互相帮帮小忙嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's a little favor between future business partners?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.98,0:11:14.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以然后呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So what's next?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.98,0:11:16.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我原地打滚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want me to roll over,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.71,0:11:18.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我装死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want me to play dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.30,0:11:20.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得没错  当我没问\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're absolutely right. Forget I asked.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.01,0:11:22.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你帮我们找到贝勒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thanks for tracking down Baylor for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.20,0:11:24.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面交给我们来办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We'll take it from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.20,0:11:27.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一开始就该告诉我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You should have asked me from the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.80,0:11:30.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在浪费我的时间吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You wasting my time?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.68,0:11:35.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢别人浪费我时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't react well when people waste my time.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.75,0:11:41.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我不知道贝勒会和联调局合作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I--I had no idea that Baylor would be cooperating with the frisbees.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.97,0:11:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把贝勒弄来给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm gonna deliver Baylor to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.23,0:11:48.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那之后  我要见你父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Afterwards, I meet your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.30,0:11:52.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你帮我们解决这个小问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You solve this little problem for us,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.26,0:11:55.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父亲会求着见你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and my dad will be asking to sit down with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.63,0:11:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓到贝勒后给我个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Call me when you've got Baylor.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.79,0:11:59.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会派辆车去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll send over a car.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.80,0:12:03.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你手怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What happened to your hand?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.30,0:12:04.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人让我生气了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I got angry at someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.41,0:12:15.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四分体给你设了这么多难关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The Quadrant's making you jump through a lot of hoops.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.91,0:12:17.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望最后值得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I hope it's worth it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.87,0:12:19.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去敲门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why don't I knock on the door?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.76,0:12:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello, boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.47,0:13:27.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.29,0:13:28.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.93,0:13:29.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要杀我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You gonna kill me?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.21,0:13:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是继续提问就会杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you keep asking me questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.43,0:13:33.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}On your feet.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.63,0:13:36.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,派车来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Send the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.65,0:13:38.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Move.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.76,0:13:40.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Move!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.38,0:13:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡地亚家族会罩着自己人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Cartiers take care of their own.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.14,0:13:51.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入之后你就是家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Once you're in, you're family.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.16,0:13:52.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我预期如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's my expectation.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.75,0:13:54.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就说他们会派人来救我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All's I'm saying is I knew they'd send for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.67,0:13:57.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对不会告密\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I would never snitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.25,0:13:58.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当然不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sure you wouldn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.67,0:14:00.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我就不会冒这个风险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I wouldn't take the chance, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.18,0:14:02.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该庆幸你不是我的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're lucky you don't work for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.48,0:14:11.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝勒  兄弟  联调局对你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Baylor, buddy! Feds treat you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.51,0:14:14.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都没说  对上帝发誓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Whoa. I didn't say nothing, I swear to god.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.75,0:14:16.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟上帝说去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Tell him in person.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.55,0:14:34.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They're gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.16,0:14:40.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That packs a punch.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.66,0:14:43.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们冲你的脑袋开枪怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And what would you have done if they shot you in the head?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.00,0:14:48.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就死了呗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'd be dead probably.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.08,0:14:55.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没料到会挨枪子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Getting shot... wasn't part of my plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.05,0:14:57.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,年度最保守的说法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Understatement of the year.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.96,0:15:01.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现如今谁都不能相信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You just can't trust anyone these days.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.47,0:15:05.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.20,0:15:07.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,办成了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is it done?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.83,0:15:10.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝勒除掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Baylor's off the board.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.08,0:15:11.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪亚兹呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And Diaz?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.51,0:15:12.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也没料到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Never saw it coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.24,0:15:14.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个傻子还真以为他有机会呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Idiot really thought he had a shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.52,0:15:17.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的相信我们会分他那种恶棍一杯羹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}As if we'd share space with a thug like him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.95,0:15:20.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天我们会派人去星城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Tomorrow, we'll send a crew to Star City
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.16,0:15:22.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿下迪亚兹的手下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and lean on Diaz's networks,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.61,0:15:27.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把他的城市占为己有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And we'll make his city...ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.96,0:15:34.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}霍根小巷酒吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.36,0:15:49.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的计划似乎变得有些困难了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So this whole plan of yours has gotten a little complicated.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.38,0:15:51.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何值得拥有的都不容易取得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Anything worth wanting shouldn't be simple.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.55,0:15:53.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我的理念不合\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not my philosophy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.81,0:15:56.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划就像男人们一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Plans are like men.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.26,0:15:58.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离那些难懂的越远越好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's best to avoid the complicated ones.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.75,0:16:00.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Aw, shucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.39,0:16:03.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我很浅显\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You think I'm not complicated.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.66,0:16:08.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你意识到你今晚想要讨好的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You do realize that the guys that you wanted to impress tonight
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.17,0:16:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和刚才想杀你的人是一伙的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}are the same guys that just tried to kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.63,0:16:12.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我有备无患\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I was prepared.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.61,0:16:29.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这依然解释不了为什么我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It still doesn't explain what we're doing back here
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.16,0:16:32.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在回星城的路上而是在他们的地盘上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}at their place when we should be on our way back to star city.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.98,0:16:34.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能这就是我们之间的不同之处吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe that's the difference between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.09,0:16:38.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被击倒后就放弃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When you get knocked down, you give up.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.40,0:16:42.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-而我会站起来  -我也站起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- I get up. - I get up!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.22,0:16:44.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但同时智商在线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I just don't get stupid, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.16,0:16:50.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,长得漂亮就是好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Must be nice being pretty.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.38,0:16:53.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只用撅噘嘴  眨眨眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You pout your lips, you bat your eyes,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.54,0:16:55.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要的就都触手可得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}everybody gives you what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.01,0:16:59.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我需要自己争取\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Everything I wanted I had to take.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.76,0:17:10.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒吧打烊了  散了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Bar's closed! Everybody move!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.38,0:17:13.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都散了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Move!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.27,0:17:24.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活见鬼了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.37,0:17:27.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你热忱于除掉你的人时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In your enthusiasm to take out your man...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.21,0:17:31.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘了我还站在他旁边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you forgot I was standing next to him
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.80,0:17:33.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就开枪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}when you started shooting.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.63,0:17:36.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也因此感到很抱歉  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But you're sorry about that, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.49,0:17:38.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有针对你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It wasn't anything personal.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.51,0:17:40.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,子弹和你说的可不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Bullets make things personal.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.05,0:17:44.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能问你个问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}May I ask you something?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.40,0:17:48.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有为了填饱肚子而打架吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did you ever have to fight for a meal?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.22,0:17:56.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有过  从来没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not once. Not one time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.73,0:17:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,富家少爷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Mr. Silver spoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.85,0:18:04.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候吃的残羹剩饭都要自己去争\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I had to fight for every scrap of food I ate as a kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.45,0:18:08.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没体会过饥饿的感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You don't know what it's like to be hungry,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.53,0:18:12.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如此迫切地想要折什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to want something so bad
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.06,0:18:15.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪怕要去杀人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you'd kill for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.14,0:18:19.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我杀过很多人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've killed plenty.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.37,0:18:21.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但可不是为了生存\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not--not for survival.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.64,0:18:24.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有一次是在你的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now when the outcome of your life
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.91,0:18:27.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还安危未定的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}hangs in the balance.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.43,0:18:30.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这么说挺有意思的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's funny you should put it that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.06,0:18:37.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真该告诉你手下的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You really got to tell your guys,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.60,0:18:40.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脚步轻点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}creep a little quieter.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.47,0:18:42.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就我右边那俩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's two to my right,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.64,0:18:46.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有后面的三个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}three more behind me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.34,0:18:52.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为一个人力悬殊的恶棍你还真淡定啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's pretty confident for a thug who's outnumbered.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.84,0:18:57.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你见识过她的本事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You wouldn't think I was outnumbered
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.25,0:19:00.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不会说我人力悬殊了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}if you knew what she can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.91,0:19:08.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真该补充一下冰箱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We really need to restock the fridge.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.83,0:19:10.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得苏打水会过期吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Do you think soda can go bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.93,0:19:12.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能已经知道答案了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I should probably already know the answer to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.30,0:19:15.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,费利西蒂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Felicity?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.88,0:19:20.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有效的  记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's working, remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.56,0:19:22.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们击过掌  -但也不代表不能改进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- We high-fived. -Yeah. Doesn't mean it can't be improved.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.91,0:19:25.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  要不明天再弄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sure. Uh, so maybe improve it tomorrow
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.32,0:19:26.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待你睡过觉吃点饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}when you've had some sleep and some food
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.45,0:19:27.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝过保质期内的苏打之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and some non-expired soda.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.68,0:19:30.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想调节几个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. I just want to make a couple adjustments here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.21,0:19:32.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这比聊你丈夫要轻松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because that's easier than talking about your husband?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.64,0:19:35.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不能"本末倒置"  我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey. He's going back to basics, so, so am I.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.68,0:19:37.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是把这形容成被解雇的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're the one who described it as getting fired.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.58,0:19:40.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说"就像"  也只是长话短说起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I said, "kind of," and that was just shorthand.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.31,0:19:42.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我爱当绿箭团队里的一员那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}As much as I love being a part of team arrow--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.29,0:19:44.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管团队越来越小\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}as downsized as it may have become--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.69,0:19:46.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但它有点让我们本末倒置了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was taking us away from our real work, Helix.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.84,0:19:47.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"螺旋"才是正事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is where it's at.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.82,0:19:49.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一点也不担心他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And you're not worried about him?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.08,0:19:50.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他能照顾好自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nope. He can take care of himself,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.26,0:19:52.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经干这行五年了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I have been doing this for 5 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.08,0:19:54.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在地堡里和电脑作伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. In the bunker with computers
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.62,0:19:56.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有随身相机和GPS\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and body cams and GPS
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.33,0:19:57.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你之前知道他在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}so you knew where he was
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.43,0:19:58.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and what he was doing
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.62,0:20:01.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他好不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and if he was OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.05,0:20:03.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,柯蒂斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Curtis.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.27,0:20:05.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来觉得只要忙起来就不会想他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. I thought throwing myself into work would work,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.82,0:20:06.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but it's not working.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.47,0:20:07.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  我不知道他去哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, I don't know where he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.43,0:20:08.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不再告诉我他去哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He doesn't tell me where he is anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.56,0:20:10.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要知道他好不好  我担心得要死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I need to know if he's ok. I'm dying here!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.14,0:20:13.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.94,0:20:15.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新闻推送  贫民区枪战  奥利弗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}News alert: shootout in the glades. Oliver?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.24,0:20:20.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人目睹绿箭侠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The Green Arrow was last seen in the center
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.60,0:20:26.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}重大新闻  贫民区失火
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.22,0:20:22.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在爆炸发生前一刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}of an altercation moments before the explosion
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.88,0:20:24.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾和人有过争执\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}overtook the area.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.43,0:20:26.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,星城警局还未发出声明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}SCPD has yet to issue a statement.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.83,0:20:28.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们将跟进情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We will keep you updated.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.92,0:20:35.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在玩弄他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're toying with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.83,0:20:38.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样  未来的事业伙伴之间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, come on. What's a little fun
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.45,0:20:41.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找点乐子又能怎样呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}between future business partners?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.16,0:20:44.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可不想让他觉得我们在浪费他的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, we wouldn't want him to think that we're wasting his time
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.59,0:20:47.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是让他做一些愚蠢的差事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}by sending him on some fool's errand.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.65,0:20:49.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换谁都会生气的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. That would make anyone furious.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.99,0:21:03.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸把这地方买下给你的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Your daddy buy you this place?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.05,0:21:07.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为了忙真正的事业给你的这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not-so-shiny toy to distract you
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.29,0:21:12.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转移你注意力的玩具可不怎么光鲜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}while he's running the real business.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.86,0:21:17.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来没从我家得到任何东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I never got anything from my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.73,0:21:21.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我是个孤儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know I'm an orphan?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.83,0:21:25.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没骗你  我在名副其实的孤儿院长大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's true. I grew up in a real-deal orphanage--
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.37,0:21:30.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有修女  应有尽有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nuns and... and everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.22,0:21:32.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全套的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The full package.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.53,0:21:44.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时有个比我大的男生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There was this older boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.52,0:21:47.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫杰西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}His name was Jesse.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.73,0:21:54.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰西觉得他比我强\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Jesse thought he was better than me,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.81,0:21:57.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I believed him,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.99,0:22:00.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我很怕他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I was afraid of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.36,0:22:05.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每晚都会哭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'd cry every night.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.54,0:22:11.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些年以来  他一直拿我当无名小卒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}For years, he-- he treated me like a worm,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.09,0:22:13.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我一文不值\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}like I was worthless...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.64,0:22:17.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他之下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}like I was beneath him.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.03,0:22:19.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得为他整理床铺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'd make his bed,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.77,0:22:21.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扫房间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'd clean our room.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.56,0:22:28.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他拿我当他的仆人一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He treated me like I was his damn servant.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.91,0:22:38.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.25,0:22:42.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我谁的仆人也不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm nobody's servant now.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.10,0:22:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是划伤我  我爸什么都不会给你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you cut me, my father will never give you what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.80,0:22:52.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是以后的事  是未来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's prospective, the future.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.34,0:22:55.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对过去发生的事更感兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm more interested in the past.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.12,0:22:58.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么想杀了他  埃里克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why'd you try and kill him, Eric?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.13,0:23:02.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-因为我愿意  -这回答可不够好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Because I could. - That's not good enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.74,0:23:15.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.50,0:23:18.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我爸的主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was my father's idea!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.47,0:23:21.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要夺取星城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We were gonna take Star City,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.95,0:23:23.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收编你的关系网\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}co-opt your networks.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.66,0:23:26.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,窃取我的心血吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Take credit for my sweat equity?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.05,0:23:27.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太不体贴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That is so inconsiderate.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.02,0:23:29.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你宝贝的四分体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sounds like your precious little Quadrant
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.94,0:23:32.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是群自私的混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is a bunch of selfish jerks.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.51,0:23:33.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不知情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They didn't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.30,0:23:36.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没和他们提起过你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We never told them about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.50,0:23:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.02,0:23:40.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸和我  我们根本没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My father and I, we never brought
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.84,0:23:43.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你的提议告诉四分体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}your proposal to the Quadrant.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.42,0:23:46.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个无名小辈  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're a nobody, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.79,0:24:09.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满足了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Satisfied yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.24,0:24:10.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.87,0:24:12.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在还活着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're alive now.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.89,0:24:14.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想保持这种状态吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want to stay that way?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.19,0:24:18.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我四分体的会议时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Tell me when the Quadrant's meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.65,0:24:19.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.54,0:24:22.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太方便了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, isn't that convenient?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.47,0:24:24.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要再告诉我一些细节吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You gonna give me all the details?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.79,0:24:27.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是不会接纳你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They're not just gonna let you in.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.38,0:24:32.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没打算好声好气地请求\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not planning on knocking.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.50,0:24:42.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知怎么的  我们越过了复杂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Somehow, we moved past complicated
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.30,0:24:44.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接跳到了疯狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and straight into crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.31,0:24:47.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对凯登·詹姆斯的所作所为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What I did to Cayden James,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.80,0:24:49.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得那很疯狂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you think that's crazy?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.11,0:24:51.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫男子气概\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is manning up.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.53,0:24:55.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男子气概  我讨厌这个词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Manning up. I hate that phrase.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.13,0:24:57.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们把计划过一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ok. Let's talk this through.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.21,0:25:00.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果四分体像你说的那样强大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If the Quadrant is as powerful as you say,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.42,0:25:03.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道他们有什么军火\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}who knows what kind of firepower they have in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.02,0:25:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你低估自己了  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're selling yourself short, kiddo.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.44,0:25:08.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一人能顶得上十个男的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're better than 10 men.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.14,0:25:09.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们不止十个人呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And if there's more than 10?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.40,0:25:10.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.72,0:25:13.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我很欣赏你的自信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}While I appreciate your self-confidence,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.59,0:25:18.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你可能有一点点高估了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you could be overestimating your powers of persuasion
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.17,0:25:20.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己说服别人的功力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}by just a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.38,0:25:22.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你八成不会受他们的欢迎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You might not be their favorite person in the world
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.84,0:25:26.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑到你刚刚对发胶王子的所作所为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}considering what we've just done to the prince of hair gel.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.36,0:25:29.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了  相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I said, trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.28,0:25:32.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能告诉我  加入这个独家俱乐部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I would find it a whole lot easier to do so
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.59,0:25:33.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么对你如此重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}if you could just tell me
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.51,0:25:37.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我可能会更容易相信你些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}why it is so important for you to be a part of this exclusive club.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.51,0:25:40.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以用其他的方式建立你的王国\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There are other ways you can build your empire.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.34,0:25:44.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和建立王国无关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's not about empire building.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.29,0:25:45.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是在于尊重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's about respect.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.66,0:25:47.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  这就是你想要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Right, which you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.84,0:25:49.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你为了得到他们的尊重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and you're willing to disrespect yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.80,0:25:51.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甘愿自取其辱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in order to get it from them.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.11,0:25:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是这么回事  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- That's not how it is. - Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.84,0:25:55.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为看上去就是这么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because that's how it looks like it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.16,0:25:58.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在酒吧那里  你谈论杰瑞的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Back at that bar, you were talking about Jerry
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.51,0:25:59.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我觉得你依旧深受其扰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}like he still haunted you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.93,0:26:04.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰西  他叫杰西  而且确实如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Jesse. It's Jesse, and he does.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.48,0:26:08.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个小混蛋说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Little bastard was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.37,0:26:10.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是个失败者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, a loser.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.80,0:26:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.17,0:26:18.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果  你是国王  把他忘了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now you're a king. Forget about him.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.57,0:26:21.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘不掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.85,0:26:29.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我害怕杰西害怕了太长时间...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I was afraid of Jesse for so long
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.28,0:26:31.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以至于我所拥有的只有恐惧...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that all I had was my fear...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.43,0:26:35.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So I--
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.20,0:26:41.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我将这种恐惧取名为恶龙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I named that fear The Dragon.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.57,0:26:42.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.98,0:26:45.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和恶龙一起生活了很长时间...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I lived with The Dragon for so long...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.25,0:26:48.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它就是我的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's all I had...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.39,0:26:53.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在我加入四分体之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But now being a part of the Quadrant,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.14,0:26:55.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就会拥有其他东西了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm gonna have something else...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.99,0:27:00.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种让我不再是无名小辈的力量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The type of power where I'll never be nothing again.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.75,0:27:05.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我想起了把我带过来的那个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You remind me of the guy that brought me here...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.97,0:27:09.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带来这个地球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To this earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.70,0:27:14.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他...他内心充满了仇恨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He...he had so much hate inside of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.95,0:27:18.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仇恨控制了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Took control over him.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.60,0:27:20.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我控制恶龙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I control The Dragon.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.17,0:27:25.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而不是它控制我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It doesn't control me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.84,0:27:31.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}百年大宅
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.55,0:27:40.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.07,0:27:43.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来不来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You coming or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.69,0:28:01.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴你决定来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Glad you decided to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.65,0:28:05.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总得有人确保你不被杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Someone's got to make sure you don't get yourself killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.27,0:28:08.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我很高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's why I'm glad.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.65,0:28:17.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如四分体真像你描述的那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If the Quadrant's everything you say they are,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.48,0:28:18.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们绝对预见到了这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}they're gonna see this coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.90,0:28:22.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧  但亲情使人盲目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe. Family can be blinding.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.30,0:28:40.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他们预见到了这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You think they saw that coming?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.65,0:29:02.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人入侵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We got incoming!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.88,0:29:05.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着不止他说的11个人啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sounds like a little bit more than the 11 guys he said there were.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.47,0:29:07.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得把入口弄开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Had to soften the beach.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.57,0:29:10.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,C4炸药传达了信息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}C4 sends a message.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.97,0:29:14.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不如再去传达一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why don't you send another one?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.74,0:29:27.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,入口打开了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now the beach is soft.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.19,0:30:02.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我费了很大劲才来到这个会议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I went through a lot of trouble to get to this meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.18,0:30:06.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是本不用如此的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It didn't have to be, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.30,0:30:09.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了我儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You killed my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.02,0:30:11.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了你儿子的是C4炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}C4 killed your son.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.26,0:30:17.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底知不知道我是谁  我们是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Do you have any idea who I am, who we are?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.23,0:30:18.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.77,0:30:21.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才想和你们见一面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's why I wanted to meet.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.99,0:30:23.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你知道我们是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you know who we are,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.44,0:30:25.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就知道我不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you know I'm not going to kill you
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.12,0:30:26.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你对我儿子的所作所为而要杀你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}for what you did to my boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.84,0:30:28.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,松了口气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, that's a relief.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.50,0:30:31.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把你送到一个离这里很远的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm going to send you someplace far away from here,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.90,0:30:33.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送到我的一间医院里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to a hospital I own.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.84,0:30:38.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们知道如何在把一个人凌迟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They know every way there is to keep a man alive
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.51,0:30:41.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却让他不死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}as other men carve pieces out of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.84,0:30:46.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  你当然可以这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sure. Sure you could go that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.21,0:30:49.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以试试...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You could try...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.33,0:30:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你真这么做了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But if you do,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.33,0:30:57.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每年得花上几十亿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}it'll cost you billions annually.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.96,0:31:01.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿下他  但确保抓活的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Take him, but make sure he doesn't die.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.22,0:31:02.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.81,0:31:05.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他杀了我儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He killed my boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.21,0:31:08.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话  我很惊讶你那白痴儿子能活这么久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Frankly, I'm surprised your idiot son made it this far.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.79,0:31:12.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好好说  这事关你的性命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Talk as if your life depended upon it
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.42,0:31:13.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}because it does.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.20,0:31:18.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚说过了...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Like I said...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.57,0:31:23.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本不必如此的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}it wasn't supposed to be this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.46,0:31:27.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡地亚先生的儿子...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Mr. Cartier's son...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.00,0:31:35.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本应该安排这次会议  而不必引发血战\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}was supposed to arrange this meeting without bloodshed,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.05,0:31:40.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但卡地亚老爹  他却想走另一条路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But Cartier senior, he wanted to go another way.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.35,0:31:43.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你不配和我们共处一室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because you're not fit to be in the same room as us.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.43,0:31:44.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是个街头混混\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're a street thug,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.36,0:31:47.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至不配在我们手下工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}not even qualified to work on one of our crews.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.22,0:31:49.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来和你们会面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I came to this meeting
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.69,0:31:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为我有个生意上的提议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}because I have a business proposition.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.10,0:31:58.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道星城如今的情况吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know what's happening in Star City, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.47,0:32:00.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到它正在分崩离析\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I see it's falling apart.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.18,0:32:02.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到了混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've seen chaos.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.45,0:32:04.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.37,0:32:06.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控制下的混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Controlled chaos.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.86,0:32:10.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你视其为故障\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What you see as dysfunction,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.28,0:32:16.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我视其为一台全速运转的机器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I see a machine running on full efficiency.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.66,0:32:20.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控制警局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I control the PD,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.32,0:32:24.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,市政厅  码头  铁路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}city hall, the ports, the rails.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.13,0:32:30.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都在我的掌控之中  这都可以是你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I control everything, and it could all be yours,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.63,0:32:34.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个条件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All of it in exchange for one thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.84,0:32:37.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个条件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}one thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.27,0:32:42.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个位置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A seat...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.99,0:32:46.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个桌子上的一个位置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}At this table.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.54,0:32:51.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可看不到有空位子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't see an empty chair.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.79,0:32:53.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便有  我也不愿意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Even if there was one, I would never sit
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.75,0:32:55.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐在杀死我的亲人的凶手旁边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}beside the man who killed my own blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.67,0:32:57.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他逼我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He pushed me to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.64,0:33:02.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一直逼我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And he pushed, and he pushed,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.10,0:33:05.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直逼我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and he pushed.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.14,0:33:09.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人是有极限的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A man's got his limitations.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.59,0:33:11.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的极限\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And you are mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.26,0:33:15.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.95,0:33:18.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个街头混混\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A street thug
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.47,0:33:22.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至没能躲过监狱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}who couldn't even keep himself out of prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.44,0:33:24.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么也不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're nothing...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.97,0:33:28.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一个失败者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A loser.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.25,0:33:40.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look it here.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.79,0:33:44.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个空位子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's an empty seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.13,0:33:50.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能成功是因为我们深思熟虑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We are successful because we're deliberate,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.70,0:33:53.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有纪律  一丝不苟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}disciplined, and precise.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.57,0:33:56.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是为了一点食物就互相残杀的野兽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're not animals killing each other for scraps.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.82,0:33:58.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有文明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We are civilized.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.23,0:33:59.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这不能体现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is not.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.52,0:34:03.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我对你的提议感兴趣  迪亚兹先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But your proposal intrigues us, Mr. Diaz.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.52,0:34:06.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们想听你详细说说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We'd like to hear more.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.27,0:34:24.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let's get started.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.32,0:34:41.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  你达成了目的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's wrong? You got what you wanted,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.70,0:34:42.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不再是一个失败者了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you're not a loser anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.90,0:34:45.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是一个真正的黑帮老大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You are a legitimate crime lord,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.64,0:34:47.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而你依旧烦躁不安\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and yet you still seem on edge.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.79,0:34:49.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为一枚戒指和一个位置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You think a ring and a seat at the table
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.74,0:34:51.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能改变我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}changes things for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.55,0:34:55.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们受到攻击是因为你认为这会改变你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I think we ran a gauntlet because you thought it would.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.76,0:34:58.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有结束\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's not over yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.32,0:35:02.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有最后一件事需要解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's still one last thing I have to take care of.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.80,0:35:51.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Can I help you?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.00,0:35:55.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥利弗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oliver?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.75,0:36:04.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爆炸中没有幸存者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There are no survivors in the explosion
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.53,0:36:05.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早贫民区里的爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that consumed a city block
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.89,0:36:07.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吞噬了整个街区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in the Glades earlier this evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.77,0:36:11.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑到爆炸威力  专家认为需要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Given the power of the blast, experts say that forensics
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.13,0:36:14.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,法医确定绿箭侠的生死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}may be required to determine the fate of the Green Arrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.34,0:36:16.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh. Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.34,0:36:16.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}绿箭侠下落不明
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.48,0:36:18.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}寻找中
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.41,0:36:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fs18\fsp2\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\blur0\shad0\fad(0,0)}寻找失败
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.10,0:36:19.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.60,0:36:22.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  -你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Hh, my God! - You ok?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.04,0:36:25.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, my god!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.12,0:36:28.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在新闻里看到了爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, I saw the explosion on the news,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.76,0:36:30.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就在爆炸当中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and you were right in the middle of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.31,0:36:32.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  不  我射了一发抓钩箭...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. No. I fired a grappling arrow, and I flew...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.90,0:36:34.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你  -飞了出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- You-- - backwards right out of there.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.63,0:36:35.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm f--I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.03,0:36:38.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我可不好  -好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Well, I'm--I'm not! - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.22,0:36:39.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里担心你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Worrying about you out here is--
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.03,0:36:41.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和在地堡里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, it's completely
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.64,0:36:43.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心你的感觉完全不同\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}different from worrying about you in the bunker.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.47,0:36:44.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果你在地堡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Right, because when you're in the bunker,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.41,0:36:47.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会觉得你能发挥作用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you feel like you can make a difference.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.04,0:36:50.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能  我能发挥作用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can. I can make a difference.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.11,0:36:53.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以提供支援\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can--I can deploy backup.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.29,0:36:54.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能  我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can do--I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.90,0:36:57.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能做些什么  在这里  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can do something. Out here, I c--
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.91,0:37:01.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我束手无策  很无用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm helpless out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.05,0:37:04.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天生你才必有用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You aren't helpless anywhere ever,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.05,0:37:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然我也有用  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I'm not helpless either, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.55,0:37:14.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和小家伙约定好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Made a promise to that guy in there
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.32,0:37:17.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定会回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I would always come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.25,0:37:19.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, William made an excellent point
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.76,0:37:21.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说你回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}when he said you coming back
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.64,0:37:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不总是你自己的选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is not always gonna be your decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.97,0:37:25.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,威廉说得没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}William does make excellent points,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.88,0:37:31.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是许诺了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but I made the promise anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.96,0:37:34.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也要向你许诺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm making the same promise to you
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.52,0:37:37.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此时此地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}right here and right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.24,0:37:40.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,费利西蒂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Felicity...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.46,0:37:43.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定会回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I will always come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.89,0:38:03.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我等了一个小时了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've been waiting an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.71,0:38:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走上来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get up the stairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.63,0:38:13.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你讨厌等待\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know you hate waiting.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.05,0:38:16.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.47,0:38:20.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要解决的最后一个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That last thing I have to take care of.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.96,0:38:23.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've got kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.77,0:38:26.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们需要我  不要伤害我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They need me. Please, please don't hurt me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.37,0:38:28.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论你想要什么  我都能给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Whatever you want, I can give it to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.39,0:38:33.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有钱的好日子才算幸运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're lucky if you got two dimes to rub together on a good day.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.95,0:38:37.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How do you know me?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.10,0:38:39.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.65,0:38:43.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.40,0:38:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么知道你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How do I know you?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.56,0:38:52.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've known you
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.53,0:38:56.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都知道你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}my whole life.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.37,0:38:58.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.94,0:39:04.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劳蕾尔  这是杰西·弗雷德里科\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Laurel, meet Jesse Fredericco.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.98,0:39:09.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰西  这是劳蕾尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Jesse... meet laurel.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.34,0:39:11.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为人们应该不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't think people are supposed to know
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.91,0:39:14.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,劳蕾尔在和黑帮老大合作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that laurel's working with a crime lord.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.01,0:39:20.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑帮老大  黑帮老大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Crime lord. Crime lord."
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.88,0:39:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这个词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I love the sound of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.16,0:39:28.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的不记得我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You really don't remember me?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.12,0:39:34.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起伦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Chillón?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.63,0:39:39.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪亚兹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Diaz?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.43,0:39:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真让我失望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That is really disappointing.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.10,0:39:49.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为我会留下更深的印象\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I thought I made a bigger impression.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.95,0:39:51.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}On your knees.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.25,0:40:05.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.21,0:40:08.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以牙还牙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Getting my payback.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.64,0:40:15.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这已经不只是以牙还牙了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I think that this is a little bit more than payback.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.05,0:40:27.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}See that?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.82,0:40:33.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从火里拿出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I took this from the fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.27,0:40:42.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把手伸进了火里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I stuck my hand right in.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.76,0:40:46.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手上都是水疱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I had blisters.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.96,0:40:51.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都掉皮了  都裂开了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I had raw, cracked skin!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.65,0:40:55.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好几周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}For weeks!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.83,0:40:59.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, Jesse.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.47,0:41:07.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还喜欢火吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You still like fire?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.36,0:41:17.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里卡多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ricardo.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.53,0:41:20.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我暗自发誓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I promised myself...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.60,0:41:24.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等时机成熟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}when the time was right...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.68,0:41:29.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我不再是失败者了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that I'd get my payback...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.84,0:41:33.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就会报复你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}when I wasn't a loser.

