My name is Oliver Queen.
After five years in hell,
I have come home with only one goal--
to save my city.
Now others have joined my crusade.
To them, I am Oliver Queen.
But to the rest of Starling City,
I am someone else.
I am something else.
Previously, on "Arrow"...
My name is Amanda Waller, Mr. Queen.
Welcome to Hong Kong.
Amanda Waller wants you working for her.
She will have her way.
You're Felicity Smoak.
I know a guy who might be interested
in hiring someone with your expertise.
Apparently there's another bidder for the company.
- Who? - Ray Palmer.
What are you doing here?
No! No! Sara!
Sara!
No! No!
Felicity, all I'm trying to do is make things easier on you.
By having me completely
reconfigure our phone system?
Do you even know how difficult it is
to ping a clone off a hacked transband multiplex?
No, but only because you weren't speaking English just now.
Sara?
I didn't know where else to take her.
Oh, my God!
- What happened? - I couldn't...
I couldn't leave her.
We have to call... we can...
take her to the hospital!
Ollie, it's not fair!
We just got her back, it's not fair!
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry.
We'll take our position here.
Who's your target?
I don't have a target.
- You do. - What?
Might have escaped your notice,
But Amanda Waller doesn't have a sense of humor.
Oh, really?
Then why'd she drag me off of Lian Yu
and bring me all the way to Hong Kong
- To become her hit man? - To become her operative.
Obviously she needs you for something
or she wouldn't be threatening my family
to assure your compliance.
The target will be entering our line any moment.
The target will walk 10 paces through the roof garden
and arrive at his hotel suite.
That's your window.
I see it.
Now.
Tommy?
You know, Sara used to have a stuffed animal.
It was this old, worn out shark
that she got from the Starling Aquarium.
Every time something awful would happen to her,
I would always find her holding that stupid little shark
close to her chest.
And now that my sister's dead,
Again the only thing that I can think about
is finding that dumb stuffed animal
and putting it in her arms.
I'm sorry.
You have nothing to apologize for.
Hey, whoever did this,
I'm going to find them.
We're going to.
When I thought that Sara died on "The Gambit,"
the only thing that I could do
was scream at the ocean.
I had so much anger and rage,
and I didn't know what to do with it.
But I do now.
And I'm going to help you catch
whoever it is that did this.
You're already helping.
Laurel...
you told us where to look.
I'm just supposed to sit here and wait?
No. Now you take care of yourself and your family.
Your father is going to need you.
Telling him now, it would kill him.
At least now if we wait until we catch whoever did this,
it'll be easier on him.
Ok.
Where are you going?
I don't know. I don't know anything anymore.
But I know that a bar is the last place I should be.
Come on, pick up.
You've reached Thea. Leave a message.
Thea, it's Oliver.
I know you're still traveling, but I just, I could really...
I'd really like to hear your voice.
So please call me back.
What'd we get off the cameras?
Place is a drug haven.
They've all either been disabled
or paint-balled by local dealers.
Where are you going?
Where it happened.
Felicity told me.
You OK?
Killer stood there,
loose gravel on the rooftop.
- Oliver... - Sara was here.
Scuff marks back to the edge.
You don't have to do this right now, man.
It's the only thing that I can do.
Listen, I get it. Military training.
Stay on task.
Your friend gets shot, you just keep fighting.
- But Oliver... - I'm fine.
Well, I'm here for you just the same.
Listen, Sara was my friend, too.
And if you think you're going after the person who did this solo,
You couldn't possibly be more wrong.
- Yeah? - Detective Lance called, he says it's important.
Do you think he knows about Sara?
What is it, detective?
You ok?
You look like someone peed in your cornflakes.
That kind of day, huh?
What's going on?
Another archer in town.
Dropping bodies.
- Seen this guy's work before? - I might have.
You know where SCPD's finest might find him?
- Who's the victim? - John Burke.
Some corporate financier from Qurac.
Seems like he wandered into the wrong part of town
Tonight looking for a little local "Entertainment."
He ended up with an arrow to the chest.
You watch your back, all right? Whoever this guy is...
He's a killer.
Her hands are so small.
I never noticed before.
She was always so strong and brave.
I always envisioned her as this sort of
amazonian warrior.
Invincible.
Something I could never be.
I was so jealous.
Hi. I know I was supposed to come into work today.
I--the--I'm sorry.
There's been a death in the family.
Thank you.
You have any idea what other archer could have done this?
There aren't that many of us.
Maybe 10 that I know of,
and most of them are in the League of Assassins.
Oliver, you don't think...
No. No.
They don't target their own.
- What'd you find out? - He hit again.
An abandoned warehouse on the corner of Third and Lemire.
Ninth floor. The victim was a construction foreman, Tim Kauffman.
Security cameras can't get an angle.
- Who's that? - Just some low level dealers
that set up shop in abandoned warehouses.
Doesn't look like much of an archer to me.
- He might be a witness.  - Where do you want me?
Will Lyla give you access to A.R.G.U.S.'s database?
To find out who did this, Lyla will give us access to A.R.G.U.S.
I need a list of everyone on their
radar--assassins and mercenaries who use a bow.
I'm on it.
What?
Uh, Thea hasn't called back yet.
You didn't eliminate the target!
That's not a target, that's my best friend!
Why am I pointing a gun at my best friend?
Is this some sort of test?
Yes. One you failed!
Good. Flunk me.
You think it's a coincidence your friend just happened
to show up in Hong Kong?
- He's here looking for you! - What?
When you logged into your email, it set off an account alert.
Dead men don't check their email, Oliver.
Oh, so this is my fault?
Waller needs you. She can't let you be compromised
by some rich kid flashing your picture all over Hong Kong.
Whether you're the one who pulls the trigger or not,
she wants Tommy Merlyn off the board.
That is a cobalt encrypted workstation.
You better not be using it to tweet.
I was--I was, um, actually just...
Accessing an FBI database? What...
Roy, why are you looking for Thea?
Because I don't think she is where she says she is.
Why would she lie?
Roy, Oliver needs to see this.
No. This is my fault. He's going to kill me.
- What if she's in trouble? - What if she's not?
What if she just needs space?
She's had five months
and thousands of miles of space.
Oliver needs to see this.
You need to show it to him.
You have got to be kidding me.
What--where are you going?
There's someone I need to kill.
Did you do it to make a point?
Because I get it. Loud and clear.
You are rich. You are impulsive.
And frankly, you are the creepiest form of stalker
that I have ever had to deal with,
and believe me when I'm telling you that that is saying a lot,
and--what are you doing to our old offices?
Hi. I'll be right back.
You like it? Yeah, I'm just trying
to liven up the place a bit.
I'm hosting an event tonight.
A pledge drive of sorts.
Got to make an impression, right?
Now, what can I do for you?
You can stop. You can stop sending me flowers,
And you can stop texting me and calling me and emailing me,
because I spam them, anyway.
Oh, is "spam" a verb now?
Because I am never, ever, ever going to work for you.
Actually, you already do.
Only because you bought the store that I work at!
- No, I didn't. - Yes, you did!
My boss just called and told me that you did.
Well, he's wrong--kind of.
I bought the holding company which owns and operates
all 20,000 tech village stores.
But I guess either way,
yes, I am your boss now.
So you can either work for me here
in a big office with a big salary,
or... you can work for me there,
in that awful uniform.
Or... I can quit.
Which is what I just did.
You know, most girls would be flattered
that I spent $1.2 billion to hire them.
Even if I do have a fairly genius plan
for revamping the stores.
In case you haven't noticed, I am not most girls.
And I don't need this.
Or you.
Or any of this.
Felicity, I--I piss people off on a daily basis.
It's part of business, and, well,
being the smartest guy in any given room.
I own that.
So I have enough experience with people being angry with me
to know when they're really angry at something else.
You right now are not angry at me.
What's your something else?
Oh, money won't fix this problem.
Money won't solve most problems.
Not the ones that matter.
But talking helps.
I know we barely know each other...
I'm going to leave now.
Listen, whatever happened,
I'm sorry.
It helps to remember that... it gets better.
Someone was murdered here.
Tell me what you saw.
I saw nothing.
There was a black face mask,
like a--like a hockey mask.
Now, please, man--
Diggle, are you at A.R.G.U.S.?
I've got something.
Yeah, I'm here.
I got a list of archers 20-long, man.
How many of them wear masks?
Only one.
Simon Lacroix. Mercenary.
Goes by "Komodo."
Send Felicity everything.
Yep.
Oliver, I'm opening up the file now.
Is that him?
Simon Lacroix. Born in Sainte-Sophie, Quebec.
Raised by a single mom. Terrible credit score.
And wanted for murder in seven countries.
- I need his location. - One minute.
Put him on speaker.
Ok, indexing all active burner cell phones within the city limits.
There's got to be 10,000 phones.
Yes, but how many are making calls to dear old mom
in Saint-Sophie, Quebec?
I got him. He's on the move.
I found Lacroix.
I need to see what's happening.
Ok.
Blowing up street camera feed.
Oliver, what's happening?
Come on, Ollie.
- Get up. - Oliver? Are you OK?
Oliver?
Oliver? Are you OK?
He got away.
I had him, Diggle.
The way you look, he almost had you.
Where's Roy?
He's out canvassing.
Tell me about the driver of the car.
His name is Erlich Kelso.
He just got out of Starling General--
And where are we with Lacroix?
He ditched his burner.
I'm searching the city for any calls made to Quebec.
We used that to track him once;
he's not going to let it happen again.
All right, so why don't we stop searching for Lacroix
and start searching for his target?
Because there must be a connection with his victims.
Already on it.
I mean, what if we just-- we go to a local morgue
and we find a body that looks like Tommy's?
At the Hong Kong morgue?
You've got a better chance of winning the lottery
and trying to pay Waller off.
I am not going to assassinate my best friend,
do you understand? There has to be another way.
There is.
But it involves Amanda Waller
finding someone else to execute your friend.
No no, not you, dad.
Look, I'm already in Hong Kong.
No! No, I didn't tell you I was taking the jet
because I knew you would freak out like this.
No, I don't know how long, OK? It doesn't matter.
Listen, if Oliver is still alive,
if he is still here--
Look, why don't you just go back to banging your Pilates instructor, OK?
I'll just be here searching for my best friend.
I'm sorry, miss. You can't go in there.
Laurel Lance. I'm with the district attorney's office.
Erlich Kelso is a witness of my ongoing investigation.
Mr. Kelso's under protective custody.
Not from me. And if you have a problem with that,
you can call your captain.
Tell him his daughter says hello.
Who are you?
I work in the D.A's office.
I already told the police, I don't know anything.
I still have to ask you a few questions.
- Why isn't this working? - It is.
It's running an N.S.A. algorithm aggregating
the victims' personal information using
every government database known, and unknown.
Well, it's taking too long. Sara's killer is still out there,
which means that every minute that we waste down here--
I know! You don't need to tell me,
as if I don't already know.
You're right.
And I apologize. I just need your A game right now, Felicity.
I don't have it!
My friend--our friend--
Was shot with arrows and fell off of a rooftop.
Her body is upstairs right above us in a freezer
Because we don't know what to do with it--
with her.
So I am so sorry, Oliver,
if I have feelings, but maybe if you did, too, we...
Sorry.
That was mean. But this is Sara we're talking about.
Your Sara.
How can you stand there being so cold
and rational?
'Cause I don't have the luxury of falling to pieces.
Everyone's looking to me to handle things,
to make the right decisions.
Everyone is looking to me...
to lead.
If I grieve,
nobody else gets to.
You're still a human being, Oliver.
You're allowed to have feelings.
I know sometimes that it's easier
to live under that hood.
I'm not.
Earlier today, I was looking at Sara,
I realized something.
One of these days it's going to be me.
And this...
this life that I've chosen...
it only ends one way.
So that's it?
You're just going to spend your life
hiding down here in this cave,
waiting to die? I'm sorry.
I'm not going to wait with you,
because if there's one thing that today has taught me,
is that life is precious.
And I want so much more in mine than this.
Let's start with the obvious.
Why would someone want to kill you?
I have no idea.
This whole thing, it's insane.
Mr. Kelso, despite what you may have heard,
homicides at the hands of a stranger
are incredibly rare.
Imagine how rare homicides by bow and arrow are.
Yeah, the guy was a sicko.
And you're a liar.
- I'm the victim here. - You're also a witness--
My witness. And you better give me something useful,
otherwise you're going to be facing an obstruction charge.
You know, I think I want to talk to your boss,
because you can't treat people like this.
Oh, really, you want to talk to my boss?
How's your arm feeling?!
What are you doing?!
John Burke and Tim Kaufman,
they were also shot by with arrows.
And they're too dead to tell me why.
Can't.
Burke and Kaufman!
What do the two of them have to do with you?
We were all working on a deal!
But nobody was supposed to know about it.
What kind of deal?
To build an oil pipe line,
for AmerTek. It's--
You've reached Thea. Leave a message.
Hey, Thea, it's me. Again.
And I don't know if you're getting these messages,
but I would really like to talk to you.
So please, just...
call me back.
Bye.
Lyla has multiple teams trying to get an angle on Lacroix.
Where's Felicity?
She needed some air.
And what do you need, Oliver?
I just need Thea to call me back.
That's not going to happen.
Why? What do you mean?
It was during the siege.
We were going to run away together,
but I couldn't leave without helping you fight.
And when I came back, she was gone.
I didn't say anything because this is my fault.
She knew I was lying to her the entire time.
I'm sorry I didn't say anything about the letter.
I know that I should have.
OK.
Felicity, I really need to talk to you,
so please, can you...
call me back as soon as you get this.
Laurel! Baby, are you all right?
- Are you hurt? - I'm fine.
Baby, a guy just got skewered right in front of you.
I hope you're not fine.
And what the hell were you doing here in the first place?
The District Attorney's office--
Did not send you.
You lied to my officers and now what,
you're just going to stand there
and you're going to lie to me?
I needed to talk to him. It was important.
Look, sweetie, I know you want to help,
but you don't need to take these kind of risks,
You understand? Pretty sure your sister's
got that covered for the both of you.
Yeah.
Go home. We got this.
Ok?
I've got something. Meet me at Verdant.
AmerTek Industries.
It's an oil company based in Starling City.
Ok. Now that I've consolidated
all of Lacroix's victim's records,
I can run the algorithm, scan the data
and see who received money from AmerTek.
- How long does that take? - Not long.
Three to Kelso, one more to Burke,
two more to Kaufman.
All from a subsidiary from AmerTek in Qurac,
which just happens to be
the largest untapped oil field on the planet.
Yeah. Looks like AmerTek was trying to strike an oil deal.
And some paid Lacroix to stop it.
None of this explains how Sara was involved.
Sara once told me she worked in Qurac.
And by "worked," I mean she killed people for the League.
You're saying she might have brought her work home with her.
Who authorized the payments?
A board member of AmerTek called Tom Westin.
He's Lacroix's next target.
What's his location?
You will not believe where he's headed.
Where do you think you're going?
- I'm coming with you. - Absolutely not.
Oliver, the only reason
why you know where to find him is because--
You were reckless. And Lacroix almost put an arrow in you.
Let me handle this.
Don't you dare tell me to stay put and think that I'll listen!
You know me better than that.
Sara was trained by some
of the greatest killers in human history.
Lacroix put her down.
So what do you think he's going to do to you?
I don't care about anything except for getting him.
- And I will. - You couldn't before!
I won't let him escape again.
I promise.
Ray Palmer.
Good evening.
Nice to see you.
Ladies and gentleman, Mr. Ray Palmer.
Thank you.
Thank you all for coming out tonight.
Given all that has befallen this city,
it's easy for us to lose hope--
to hide in our castles and
be thankful that our ledges are in the black.
Well, we, the city's most affluent businessmen and women
hold its future in our hands.
Tonight, I'm making a pledge.
I will give away half of my net worth
to the benefit of our home.
And this will be my salary for the year.
So tonight, I invite you all to join me in this investment.
Not just with your money,
but with your ingenuity,
and most importantly, your time.
The city is my home, but it's yours, too.
So help make Star City our future.
Let go of the arrow.
I thought you'd be taller.
It's over.
Lower your bow and live.
We both know that's not going to happen.
- Who hired you?! - Who's she?
You don't want to do this.
Yes, I do!
Killing him won't bring her back.
I know it won't bring her back, she's dead!
I have stood where you are right now;
where you're so consumed with rage you can hardly breathe,
and you think that taking revenge will make it better,
but Laurel... it won't.
It only makes it worse.
No, he murdered Sara!
Who's Sara?
My sister, you son of a bitch!
Two nights ago,
you put an arrow in her chest.
Two nights ago
I was drunk in Bludhaven.
You're lying.
I'm proud of my work.
I wouldn't deny it.
Even with a gun in your face?
Laurel, you need to stop and listen to him.
No.
No, he killed my sister.
Laurel, Sara wouldn't want--
Don't you dare tell me
that this isn't what Sara would have wanted!
Don't you tell me to think of her,
because I am thinking of her!
Laurel, if you pull that trigger--
You took the bullets out of the gun!
We have to go.
Lacroix's alibi checks out.
Two murders in Bludhaven,
same MO.
Same night Sara was killed.
I almost killed Lacroix.
The only thing that matters is you didn't.
Laurel...
The trail's run cold.
I'm going to find whoever did this.
I will.
But I don't know when.
Your father deserves to know.
I don't know. Yeah. It looks pretty good, it looks pretty good.
Lacroix, with an "X." Yeah.
I don't know, the guy's French
or something, why you asking--
Oh, hold on, hold on. I got to call you back.
Laurel, baby, what's wrong?
Hold on.
What is it?
Just tell me. Tell me, what is it?
It's about last night.
At the hospital.
I lied to you.
And you deserve to know the truth, and--
Sorry, sweetheart.
Damn thing goes off every hour if I don't take my pills.
Laurel, what do you know?
You looked like you were in the middle of telling me something.
I just wanted to say that...
that I'm really sorry.
I know that I should have told you the truth,
I just...
I just got to--
Hey, I'm your dad.
I forgive you.
Come here.
I always forgive you.
It's all right.
She can rest now.
She's home.
It's a Jewish custom.
I know she wasn't,
but it feels right.
Laurel.
No, this isn't right.
This isn't-- it--
she doesn't even get a fresh grave?
It's so perverse.
She deserves a proper burial.
She's earned it.
No, it's not fair.
No one will ever really know who she was.
Oliver, it's not fair.
It's not fair!
Laurel, we'll know.
I know this doesn't count for much,
but me and Lyla, we're naming the baby Sara.
We will never forget.
Thank you.
How did I--
What the hell is going on here?
Where am I?
Please, please don't-- please don't hurt me.
Just--just let me go, please.
I promise, I--I won't tell anybody about this.
Would a fisherman throw his prized catch back into the sea?
What are you talking about?
Look, whoever you are,
you really don't want to do this.
Do you have any idea who I am? Who my father is?!
You're Thomas Merlyn.
You've been looking for Oliver Queen.
How--how do you-- how do you know that?
A simple hack of a missing billionaire's email account.
I knew somebody would come looking for him,
but I thought it would be his...
mother.
His sister.
But you, the son of the CEO of Merlyn Global.
Jackpot.
My friend, you are going to make me
a very rich man.
So Oliver didn't...
He isn't...
Oliver Queen is dead.
He's rotting at the bottom of the ocean.
And you will, too,
if your father doesn't pay that ransom.
I'm in here, please help! Help!
Police! Hong Kong police!
- It's OK. - Thank you!
You're going home. You're safe now.
I'm going to catch whoever killed her.
I know you are.
And until you do, I'm back on the team.
What about your family?
Sara is family, Oliver.
Just like you, man.
So now what?
Now I got to go get Thea.
It's long past time she came home.
John.
I don't want to die down here.
So don't, Oliver.
You changed your mind?
I just decided I want more out of life.
Well done.
Thanks, Dad.