You think there's a kid
in Kenny's crew
that's over the age of 17?
More like 15.
Yo, we got eyes
on our boys on the block,
if y'all are ready.
Copy. Shutting down now.
- This one mine.
- What's up, Malik?
What's up, girl? Looking fine,
as usual.
You know she's with me, right?
Yeah, for now, son. For now.
All right, all right.
All right, so what you all need?
The usual?
Actually, we need
a little extra today.
We have friends up in Lakeview
that had a taste
of the good stuff,
want a little more.
How much extra weight
we talking?
100 grams.
I don't usually carry
that much product on me,
so I'ma need to do
a little wheelin' and dealin'.
We talking straight packed
or powder?
Packed up for sure.
Okay, I can make that happen.
Meet me at Division Street,
One Stop parking lot,
at 400 p.m.
- All right.
- We can make that happen.
And look, feel free
to come solo, baby.
Hey, I heard that.
Yeah, it was meant
for you to hear.
Watch yourself.
We'll see you later.
All right, kid took the bait.
Downside to using child labor
Inexperienced.
It's 500.
For a dealer, being an hour late
is actually considered early.
You guys got anything?
Nothing so far.
Should've had Upton
do the deal alone.
Kid's got eyes for her.
Units in 21,
we're getting multiple calls
of shots fired
at 3852 South on Wells.
Jay, did you hear that?
We just got a call
over the zone.
Shots fired two blocks away.
We're gonna take it.
This is the site here.
How we look, Ruz?
We're good. We're good.
Body.
Hold on. Call it in!
5021 Ida. Roll an ambulance.
Hang on, bro. Okay?
Hang on. Help is coming.
Malik. Malik!
Malik!
Ain't got a pulse. He's gone.
Just a dumb kid, man.
Kid took two to the chest.
Found two nine-millimeter
rounds right next to the body.
Signs of a struggle?
No, just took two and dropped
right where he stood.
- Weapon?
- Nothing recovered so far.
Been doing surveillance
on this block for weeks.
This is a known re-up spot
for Kenny's corner boys.
DOA was actually a kid
we were supposed
to meet up with tonight.
All right, so the kid
asks for more weight.
Kenny gets spooked that
he might be snitching,
so he shoots him.
We have two witnesses
that saw a boy
running away from
the construction site
moments after the shots
were fired.
And the physical description
matches Nathan,
Malik's sidekick.
Well, maybe he's the shooter.
Or he's a friend
that saw the shooter
and he ran like hell.
Well, either way,
he's our only lead,
so let's find him fast.
Nathan Hawkins, 15 years old.
Dropped out of school a year ago
to start slinging dope
for Kenny Armstrong.
Yeah, he has one arrest
on his record.
It's for a delivery charge
three months ago.
Any idea where he might
be hanging out?
His last known address was
his mom's apartment in Austin.
But she OD'd a year ago around
the time he started dealing.
Okay, father?
Been behind bars
for the last decade.
Who bailed him out
when he got busted?
That would be Sarah Washington,
- Nathan's aunt.
- All right,
so find an address.
Check it out.
Hey, Dr. Appelbaum.
Thanks for getting back to me
so quickly.
Look, I was hoping
you could call me in a refill.
I ran out, and my shoulder's
still killing me.
What?
Eight days?
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not gonna work.
I need more tonight.
How you doing, ma'am?
I'm Officer Atwater.
This is Officer Ruzek.
Are you Sarah Washington?
What y'all boys need?
We're looking for your nephew,
Nathan Hawkins.
Does he live here?
He does, but he's not home.
When was the last time
you saw him?
This morning.
Okay, would you mind if we
took a look around his room?
Y'all got five minutes.
Yes, ma'am.
Down the hall.
In the back.
Man, dude.
Look at this place.
No wonder kids like Nathan
end up working for guys
like Kenny.
Mom's dead, dad locked up.
Working those corners
is probably
the most stable thing
in that boy's life.
There's a POD camera
across the street.
Maybe something from that, yeah?
Okay, there's Nathan.
All right, so that's
time-stamped 545,
45 minutes after
Malik was killed.
- Let's keep going.
- Okay.
Freeze right there.
There's Nathan right there.
Passenger side window.
Yeah. Who's she?
Where's she going?
Okay, bro, let's see if we can
get facial rec on the driver.
- Check around back?
- Yeah.
Back the hell up now!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Yo, we're CPD.
- We're CPD.
- Put that gun down.
Let me see your badge.
Okay, I'll show you the badge,
but I need you to put
that gun down.
I will when you show me
your badge.
There it is right there.
You see that?
We are cops, okay?
Put the gun down.
Now, you leave that gun inside.
You meet us out front.
All right? Right now.
Yeah.
Get your hands
out of your pockets
and come here.
Come right here.
Keep 'em up.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Pull a gun on the cops?
Well, how the hell
was I supposed to know?
It's not like you sent
a résumé ahead of time.
All I saw was two dudes
walking up on my house.
Is this necessary?
Yeah, you just
pulled a gun on us.
All right?
Is it registered?
It sure is, and I can
show you the permit.
Okay. Do you know anybody
by the name of Nathan Hawkins?
Yeah.
When was the last time
you saw him?
I don't know.
Two, three weeks ago.
Wrong answer.
Next wrong answer,
we're gonna bring you in,
and we're gonna start
writing up paper.
Last chance, Laila.
Why the hell
do you know my name?
Because you are a suspect
in a murder investigation.
That's why we know your name.
What the hell are you
talking about?
We're talking about
how we have a video
of you and Nathan Hawkins
riding in your car...
This carthis afternoon.
No, I think you got
the wrong person.
I think we should bring her in.
Why? What'd I do?
What'd you do?
You helped your friend
Kenny Armstrong
kill Nathan Hawkins.
You think I'd kill Nathan?
Then prove us wrong, Laila.
Where is he?
He's right here.
- Nathan.
- You guys got it
all wrong, all right?
Laila's not trying
to kill me, all right?
She's trying to help me.
Man, I ain't saying nothing
to y'all.
Not gonna say anything?
Come on, man, what happened?
You and Malik,
you get into an argument?
He steal from you?
He screw your girlfriend?
- What?
- Man, not even close.
Okay? Malik was my boy.
All right? We were tight.
I'd never hurt him, man. Never.
Okay, you didn't do it.
Who did, Nathan?
Don't know.
Look, we all know what's
going on here, okay?
We know that Malik asked Kenny
for some more weight.
So Kenny thought that Malik
was snitching,
so he killed him.
He thinks you are too.
Right? Thinks you're snitching?
But I'm not.
Malik wouldn't either.
Doesn't matter,
if Kenny thinks you are.
Kenny thinks you are,
he's gonna kill you too.
Look, Nathan.
Look at me for a second.
That's why you went
to Laila's, right?
That's why you went to Laila's.
You were looking
for a place to hide out.
Look, bro, we just need
your help.
Okay, we don't care
that you sell drugs.
We don't care, bro. Not at all.
We just need to know if you saw
who did the murder.
- That's all.
- I didn't.
- Don't lie to me.
- Man, I'm not.
Did Nathan see who shot Malik?
No, but he knows it was Kenny.
Hell, my five-year-old niece
knows it's Kenny.
Okay, so let me
get this straight.
You run with Kenny Armstrong,
but at the same time,
you protect kids
from getting shot by him?
I don't run with Kenny
or anybody else.
Now, we used to be a thing,
but I've been out the game
for nine years.
I haven't gotten as much
as a parking ticket.
So don't lump me up with Kenny
or any other punk-ass
gangbanger I grew up with.
Why the change?
I grew up. That's why.
We all make mistakes
when we're young.
Even you, Detective.
She's a tough chick.
Yeah. Smart too.
Nathan's lucky to have her
in his life.
Yeah, we'll see about that.
Come on, Kev. You and me.
- You and me what?
- Come on.
All right, Ms. Davis.
You're free to go.
Okay, good.
Now, what about Nathan?
Can I take him home too?
We're charging him
with heroin distribution.
What? Heroin distribution
for slinging dime bags
on the corner?
Well, if he agrees to
cooperate in the murder case,
we might be able
to cut him a break.
But he didn't see anything.
Well, that doesn't mean
he can't wear a wire.
That boy has a target
on his back
the size of Soldier Field
and you want him
to wear a wire?
Kenny will kill his ass
in ten seconds flat.
Well, God doesn't give
with both hands.
Nathan is a good boy.
He is a scared-ass little kid
with no place to go,
and it is your job to help him.
Listen, it's my job to arrest.
Malik's killer, Kenny Armstrong,
your ex-boyfriend.
Right now, Nathan is my
best shot at doing that.
Introduce me to Kenny.
Right?
We know his crew
meets at his crib.
Find a way to get me in there.
So I can plant the wire.
Okay, then you gotta promise me
that you're gonna get Nathan
out of Chicago fast.
Deal.
I got you, man.
All right.
You ain't gonna be here
too long.
Long as it takes for us
to find somebody
to take you in.
You got anybody we can
reach out to outside the state?
Anywhere you wanna go?
No, I'm not interested
in leaving.
Hey, come on, man. I dig it.
Listen, man, I get it.
Moving is rough, but you might
actually like a new city.
My little brother
had to relocate to Texas.
He wasn't feeling it at first.
Digs it now.
My cousin.
He's older. He lives in Atlanta.
I ain't seen him in a while,
but he's always been nice to me.
Okay.
Track cuz down.
- All right.
- Thanks.
Yo, you leavin'?
Yeah, man, I gotta get
to a birthday party.
But you're all set.
We got a police officer
at the door.
They got you.
You're good.
How you feel?
- I'm cool.
- Cool? Good.
So what's this, a first date?
First date?
To a 60-year-old's
birthday party?
No, I don't think so.
Okay, a few months, then.
Make it look real, right?
- Surprise.
Laila, good to see you, baby.
So glad you're here
to help me celebrate.
Look at you, girl.
Damn, just as beautiful as ever.
Hey, Kenny.
- Thanks for coming.
- Yeah.
You know Mama always
liked you more than me.
Yeah. Hey, y'all.
This is my friend Keith.
Hey, what's good, man?
Nothing much.
Make sure y'all go and get
some of that pork, you know?
I brought it in from St. Louis.
I actually like
how that cobbler looks.
Best peach cobbler in the city.
You kidding.
Better get inside
before it's all gone.
Okay, I can do that.
You need anything?
All right.
Happy birthday, Mama.
Thank you, baby.
How's it going in there?
Pretty good.
Found Kenny's man cave.
Seems like a good place
to do some talking.
Okay.
Wait. I'll be right back.
- Cool.
- All right.
Hey.
It's been a while, Laila.
Thought you were trying
to avoid me.
Just been busy,
you know, down at the center.
Yeah, I heard about that.
Yeah, you working
with the kids, right?
You know, I got a lot
of respect for that.
How 'bout I make a donation
to the cause, you know?
No. No, I'm cool.
No offense.
I just wanna keep
this thing legit.
Yeah, the choice is yours.
But thanks for offering.
- Hey, yo, Marlo.
- Yo.
Yo, keep these fools
out of my basement.
Yeah, all right.
Mama, I'm gonna grab a drink.
Can I get you something?
- I'm good, sweetie.
- Okay.
Okay, let me know
when you got a visual.
We've got eyes.
Who the hell are you?
Hey...
let's not get worked up, okay?
What you doing down here?
- I got lost.
- You got lost?
Let me get back to the party.
All right. Come on, fellas.
There's no need to play
with guns, okay?
I said, what you doing
down here?
I told you, I was looking
around and I got lost, okay?
Nah, bro.
You see, I just met you.
And the way I see things, man,
that just don't feel right.
- We gotta get in there now.
- Okay, wait. Give him a sec.
He still hasn't used
the safe word.
I understand that, Kenny. Okay?
I should have asked
your permission first.
I didn't mean
no disrespect, man.
Yeah, you should've.
So I'ma ask you one more time.
Why you down here, Keith?
Laila told me about
your '96 ball, man.
'96 Bulls, come on, that's
my favorite team of all time.
- I had...
- Baby, that you?
- Yeah.
- Where the hell you been?
Down here talking to Kenny.
That's all.
What's going on?
Why's he got a gun in his hand?
We're here chatting
with your new man.
Put the gun away
before you hurt someone.
- Hey, listen. It's okay, baby.
- Hey.
It was just a
misunderstanding, that's all.
I should have asked
for permission first.
Permission to do what?
Check out his '96 ball.
You left a party
to come look at that crap?
You crazy?
I knew I shouldn't have
told you about this ball.
Come on, let's go get...
No, no, no, no, not yet.
What you mean, "not yet"?
You ain't never
been down here before.
And I just got that ball
last week.
Which means the two of y'all
are lying about something.
How you know about this, Laila?
How you think?
Your mama.
She always joking about
how stupid you are
spending all your money
on this nonsense.
Go ask her.
Come on, let's go ask her.
Let's go ruin her party...
No, no.
About this crap.
Not yet. Not yet.
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
It's just a big
misunderstanding, you know?
Hey, go on. Get out of here.
Go enjoy the party.
Hey.
You're good to go.
Thank you, and appreciate you
for helping me out back there.
It means a lot.
- Sure thing.
- No, seriously.
If that charity thing
doesn't work out for you,
you should think about
a future here.
Let's not get carried away.
Okay, I understand.
But real quick.
We were rapping with Nathan's
cousin down in Atlanta,
and he's got two kids.
He's a little worried
that Nathan's problems
are gonna follow him down there.
So do you know of any other
family that Nathan has
outside of Chicago
we can send that boy to?
Um...
he's got a grandma
down in New Orleans.
Grandma in New Orleans.
We will track her down.
We're gonna do everything
in our power to make sure
that Nathan gets out of here,
okay?
You got my word on that.
If you say so.
What?
You don'tyou don't trust me?
I don't trust anybody,
let alone a smooth-talking cop.
Well, you obviously
don't know me too well.
You're right. I don't.
So why don't you buy me a drink
and let me know
who you really are?
Okay, here we go.
Glass of water.
Shot of Hennessy.
I see you into that hard stuff?
I'm not wasting calories
on that fruity crap.
- Or a Heineken.
- What?
Straight up, you've been
around them white boys too long.
Don't do that,
Ms. West Side.
That is just like a cop.
Always gotta put a label
on somebody.
Well, obviously sometimes
those labels fit.
Sometimes they don't.
So tell me, Kevin.
How does a good-looking
brother like you
raise his hand and say,
"I wanna be a cop"...
And in Chicago, no less?
My pops got locked up early.
And I didn't wanna go out
like that.
So in order to make
a difference,
I decided to do some good
in my community.
I like that.
Yeah, that's not too corny
for you?
No, that's corny as hell.
But it's honest.
What's that?
It's, aspirin.
These all-nighters are tough.
Yeah.
I'm getting a headache
staring at this monitor.
Guess I'm not as young
as I used to be.
Well, this isn't gonna help.
Decaf. All they had left.
Decaf at 300 a.m.?
What's the point?
I know, right?
Finally.
Hey, anybody put eyes on Nathan?
No, not yet.
Well, y'all put a tap
on the wire,
get it out to his peeps.
If anybody knows something
or anything,
you bring his ass down
to the EP, all right?
You get that?
What'd he say, "EP"?
- That's what I heard too.
- Yeah.
Let's get a warrant.
- Hey.
- Hey there.
Yeah, I can dig waking up
to this face.
Well, look, Kevin.
I had fun and all, but...
But what?
I'm just playing.
You play too damn rough for me.
Well, so do you.
I gotta go.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Sort of.
Listen, let's rain check
round two.
See? Yeah, you have been
with those white boys too long.
Well, I could come to your place
a little bit later,
finish what we started.
That's better.
And the answer is yes.
Chicago PD!
Listen up, we have a warrant
to search this establishment.
Hey, hands in the air.
Get 'em where I can see you.
Get 'em up.
Warrant? Based on what?
Based on we have a warrant.
Now, everyone get up.
Move with your hands up
against that wall.
- Come on, now.
- Let's go, let's go, let's go.
Come on.
Well, well, well, well,
well, well, well, well.
27 firearms, Kenny?
We had to put a rush order
in to ballistics
to go through 'em.
If it's too much trouble...
Your boys can give them back
to the streets.
Yeah, I'm guessing
there's a good chance
one of them nines is gonna
come back with a body on it...
maybe even Malik's.
Don't know anybody named Malik.
Yeah, you do.
That's the kid you shot
for snitching.
Doesn't ring a bell.
I'm sorry.
And like I said...
those guns are not mine.
Then how did they
wind up in your bar?
Not my bar, neither.
You know...
if you guys are gonna trump up
some fake-ass charges,
go ahead.
Or can I go now?
You're free to go.
Just don't go too far.
- Yo, Maury.
- What?
Tell me you got something good.
I do.
- On the nines, right?
- No, those are clean,
all of them, but I found
a print on a Beretta 32
that was used in a cold-case
homicide ten years ago.
The handle was wiped clean,
but the magazine wasn't.
I got two partial matches and
then one solid 12-point match.
12 points, nice. You get a hit?
Yeah.
She's pretty for a killer?
You're late.
It's almost 1000.
Didn't think you were coming.
Did something happen?
Is it Nathan? Is he okay?
Nathan's fine.
We're still trying to track down
his grandma in New Orleans.
All right, then what's up?
You seem preoccupied.
We found a bag of guns
in Kenny's bar.
One of those guns
was used to kill
a convenience store clerk
ten years ago.
- Your prints are on it.
- I...
I can explain.
Listen...
I'm a cop.
You talk to me, that's evidence.
Well, I didn't shoot nobody.
Okay? I swear to God.
Cop or not cop, I'm gonna
tell you what happened,
and you can do what you want.
I was in the car with Kenny.
We were just hanging out,
chilling.
And then he just pulls over
in front of a convenience store
and says that a guy who works
inside owes him some money.
So he hops out and then
he runs into the store.
Two minutes later,
I hear "pop, pop," and then
he hops back in the car,
and we drive off.
I was in the car the whole time.
I never even stepped foot
in that store.
How did your prints
get on the magazine?
'Cause Kenny told me
to load the damn thing,
so I did it.
I didn't even think about it.
Look, it sounds stupid, okay?
I know.
But I was 17.
I had no idea he was gonna
shoot that guy.
Doesn't matter what you think.
You were there.
You were a part of a crime
that resulted in a man's death.
Thinking or not, naive or not,
that's felony murder.
I've had a smile on my face
all day
'cause I knew you were
coming here tonight,
and we're sitting here
talking about murder
and fingerprints and Kenny.
- It's just like...
- Laila...
I'm in a bad dream or something.
Laila, this is the last thing
that I want to be
talking about, okay?
Trust me.
But I don't have a choice.
So now what?
Are you going to arrest me?
Come on.
- So it's like that?
- Like what?
Like as soon as things
get tough,
you hide behind your badge?
Don't do that.
Don't put this on me.
I didn't ask for this.
But it came your way,
nonetheless.
So the question is,
what are you gonna do about it?
I'm not perfect. I'm not.
Okay? I made mistakes.
I know that.
But for the past nine years,
I have been a good person.
A very good person.
I've been at
the community center every day,
helping our young people
make good decisions.
The way that I see it... okay,
me being out here
is a good thing.
I'm keeping young brothers
from selling drugs
and joining gangs
and robbing people.
I'm saving lives.
So why arrest me for something
that I did stupid
when I was a kid?
She was dating Kenny.
Doing what he told her to do.
She stayed right there
in the car.
Said she had no clue
he was gonna pop that dude.
We got nothing linking
Kenny to Malik's murder.
We gotta use the print.
Force Laila to wear a wire,
get Kenny talking about
how he killed that clerk.
Felony murder?
She'd have to do some time.
I know, but...
we gotta get Kenny
off the street.
- Sarge...
- Let me say something.
The clerk who took two
in the chest,
did he get a free pass?
- That was ten years ago.
- Yeah.
Ten years of hell
for the victim's family.
Waking up every day
thinking about
what happened to their father.
Their husband. Their son.
Is there something else I need
to know about you and Laila?
Yeah.
We got together the other night.
Then you gotta walk away
from this, Kev.
Now.
Understand?
No more communication
of any kind.
Okay.
Help us get Kenny to confess
to murdering that clerk,
agree to testify
to that effect in court,
and you may not do any time.
Are y'all crazy?
Kenny's not stupid.
I can't just walk up
to the man and say,
"Hey, remember the night
you murdered that clerk?"
Laila, I'm trying
to help you, okay?
But to do that,
you gotta help us.
Come on, help us get Kenny
off the street
once and for all.
Y'all, this is wrong.
And Mr. Undercover too.
He knows this is wrong.
He's just too afraid
to do anything about it.
Where is he anyway?
Is he hiding in the bathroom
like a little punk-ass bitch?
Officer Atwater's
been assigned to another case.
Of course he has.
'Cause there's nothing left
to do, right?
He got me to help.
Got me into his bed.
And then he buries me for
something I didn't even do.
I saved this punk's life,
and he does this.
For real?
I should have let Kenny know
he was a cop...
And let him kill his ass.
Got it?
Hey, can I get a minute?
Yeah, we got some equipment
to load.
There's really nothing
I can say,
other than I'm sorry.
I didn't want
for this to happen.
But you didn't do anything
to stop it, either.
It's not that easy, Laila.
You're right.
It required you
to have some courage.
You don't understand...
No, sure, I do.
You one of those brothers
that like to straddle the line.
You pick and choose
when to be black
and when to be blue.
What about Nathan?
You gonna screw him over too?
Is that your thing?
Is that what you do?
You screw over your own kind?
Yo, Nathan. Come on, man.
Found your grandma.
She can't wait to see you.
Let's get up out of here.
Come on.
No, man. I ain't leaving.
We already talked about this.
Can't go. I need to stay here.
Help my aunt.
What are you talking about?
Kenny's people broke into
my aunt's house last night.
Tore it apart, wrote all kinds
of nasty things on the walls.
Okay, well, I'll send
somebody over there
to check on her,
but you gotta get
your ass up out of here, man.
Man, wherever I go,
Kenny's gonna track me down.
Okay, so I might as well
just stay here.
You're a boy. All right?
That means that you can
go to another city
and start all over.
I can take care of myself.
Look, dude,
I'm not going nowhere.
All right? So you might as well
justjust lock me up
or just let me go.
If that's what you want.
Hey, all right, look at me.
The distress word is "Voight."
If anything goes bad,
just say the word,
and we'll bust in.
I got it.
All you gotta do is get Kenny
to incriminate himself, okay?
Just get him talking
about the robberies...
I said I got it.
Okay, you good?
All right. Go, go, go, go, go.
Hey, you. Where Kenny?
Hey, girl. Don't know.
Check the back office.
Just play it cool.
Kenny, you in there?
God.
Voight! Voight!
- Voight!
- Laila.
Police.
Put your hands on the bar.
Don't move.
Laila.
It's all right. What happened?
I don't know what happened.
He was like that
when I walked in.
All right. It's okay.
It's okay.
He's cold.
Come on.
Yo, Laila okay?
Yeah, she's all right.
Tech said Kenny's been dead
for three hours.
Bartender claims
he didn't see anything.
We know who did it?
No, but I'm guessing
there's a lot of contenders.
Any evidence?
Just two nine-millimeter
shell casings on the floor.
That's about it.
That's not our problem.
Homicide's taking the case,
so pack up any loose ends.
Let's get out of here.
Copy that.
Wait, Kev.
Hang on a sec.
What's up?
Excuse me?
You gotta be kidding me.
What? No.
Listen, there is always
something you can do about it.
Let me tell you something,
next time you need a favor,
don't bother asking me.
Yeah. I gotta go.
Kevin...
it's the ASA...
Look, with Kenny dead,
there is no trial.
The ASA is not willing
to be as...
as lenient.
What does that mean?
It's gonna be three years.
Said that's the best
they can do.
I'm sorry.
Jenna.
Kenny's dead.
He killed Malik for no reason.
And he was gonna
kill me too, so...
So I did what I had to do.
Give me the gun.
So what,
you gonna arrest me now?