All right, should we run through it one more time?
All right. The targets are the Becerra Brothers,
Enrique and Hector.
Latin Players.
Bought from these guys three times,
so it should be nice and easy.
Nine grand gets us that eighth.
We'll make the exchange, give you guys the positive,
and then take 'em down, book 'em before lunch.
Yeah, one problem.
- You look like Paul Bunyan. - That's what I was going for.
Paul Bunyan was a handsome giant, so thank you.
Cool seeing Makayla at the park the other day.
Good to see her laugh.
Yeah. She's the strongest person I know, Kev.
You? Well, you brought her in.
That's a big challenge.
Yeah, I love it. I really do.
- I love it. - And?
And, um, I can barely crawl into bed at the end of the day
and that's when everything goes perfect.
Probably wouldn't hurt to have another pair of hands,
would it?
Thought about wrapping Ruz into this?
- Yeah, I have. - And?
- Yo, looks good. - Here we go.
- Here we go. - What's up, fellas?
How do? What's up, bro?
- Living the dream over here. - Ain't we all?
A'ight, check it out. That's 9 large.
You can count it if you got to.
All good. I'll get your package.
Right on.
Y'all need a taste of the product?
Nah, man. We're good, we're good.
One of our boys called us,
said he was in the shoulder with this stuff last time.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, we got that good stuff, man.
Right on.
Come on. We don't play around.
I know.
It's the same recipe as last time, right?
- Tried and true. - Purity, homey.
It's why the crystals are so big.
Oh, I know. That's what I'm talking about.
All right, let's do this.
Jay, get down!
Let's go.
5021 Eddie, 10-1, 10-1! Shots fired at the police!
We're at the 4200 block of South Justine.
We got undercover officers taking fire.
Eddie, are there officers hit?
Unknown. Approaching now.
All again, we have a 10-1 being called.
Jay, Adam!
Guys, we're okay! We're good!
Shooter's in a silver pickup fleeing southbound.
5021 David, officers are not hit.
I repeat, officers are not hit.
Offenders fled southbound on Justine in a silver pickup.
What the hell just happened?
All right. So where are we?
I got a partial from the shooter's vehicle that fled southbound.
CPIC's running it down.
A newer-model Silverado.
- Any shell casings? - 19 so far.
That'll do.
Assault rifle. Green tip .223s.
All right.
Have Forensic bag, tag, hand-deliver 'em to Ballistics.
Well, we know these two victims
are gang-affiliated meth dealers,
so hit the streets.
Look for beefs, anniversary shootings, all of it.
Get me PODs, ShotSpotters.
Hey, whoever did this damn near took out two of our own.
Don't forget that.
Closest ShotSpotter to the shooting.
Looks like someone else got there first.
It's from 2300 hours.
That's the night before it went down.
Well, tells the shooting was calculated, planned.
- What else you got? - Nothing actionable.
I talked to some of the victims' people.
They say they don't know what's going on or who did this.
Okay. Anything on the shooter's car?
CPIC pieced together the plate from the hot sheet.
Vehicle was stolen three days ago.
We lodged BOLOs, but--
No, vehicle's torched to the rims by now.
We're circling the drain here.
Actually, maybe not, Sarge.
OCD busted into two burners
found at the Becerra Brothers' place.
These are the texts on their phones.
"You sell, you die." "I warned you."
"Muerte." Dead.
There's dozens of 'em.
Someone threatened to kill the Becerra Brothers
if they didn't get out of the meth game
and then they made good on it.
- Okay, can we trace the texts? - Not to a person.
Texts were sent burner-to-burner.
But to a neighborhood? Yes.
OCD puts them in and around Garfield Park.
Yeah, one of my best CIs, Tommy Lane,
he's a meth guy in Garfield Park.
- Pay him a visit. - All right.
You gotta be kidding me.
Course.
- Is that him? - Yeah, that's him.
Why are you busting my chops?
This is what I always do.
Calm down. I'm asking, not accusing.
Okay, this is me calm when you come to my home
for the crime of having a good time
and then call me a thief while you're at it.
Only thing I ever stole was my old lady's heart.
God, Tommy.
They should take you to jail for being a stupid sap.
I'm guilty, my queen. I am guilty of love.
I love you. Okay?
- Stop it. - Tommy.
- Ruz, what's up, bro? - How you doing?
Guys, speak to you privately real quick?
Yeah. Please take care.
- You stay there. - Where am I going?
- We ain't done with you. - My house, my home.
- Tommy. - What?
We got business with this guy.
- With this nitwit? - Yeah, I know.
It seems improbable.
But, uh, you wanna tell us what's going on?
What's the problem?
Look, your boy's having a birthday party for his kid.
The adults got a little wasted, all right?
Neighbors called in a noise complaint.
- That's it? - No, that ain't it.
We got reason to believe your boy stole this bouncy house.
All right.
Look, guys. Do us a favor.
Walk away, I promise you
we'll get this nitwit to shut things down, okay?
Promise.
Take the tap off that keg?
Yes.
We ain't walking away a second time.
Fair enough.
And hey, listen.
Expect to find something bottled, brown,
and moderately expensive in your lockers, okay?
I really appreciate it.
Thank you, thank you.
We'll be fine.
Ruz.
Are you literally out of your mind, bro?
Where you been all my life, bro?
Still letting you pick your own partners these days, huh?
Sometimes.
- Feel a chill. - Nah, she warms up.
Don't worry about it. Come on.
Isabel!
Come party, man. Get a couple of shots!
- Thanks, little man. - You're welcome.
All right, come on.
Dad will be back out in a minute.
- Okay. - Thanks, Isabel.
Really steal the bouncy house?
Course I stole the bouncy house.
Neighbor's a prick. Finn's having a good time.
God would rather you be a thief than a prick any day.
- So. - So.
What's up?
I need you back in play.
- Come on. - Look, bro.
We got a real bad person or persons
causing a lot of serious trouble.
How serious?
Well, we got two men, brothers.
Glass dealers in New City.
They were both shot and killed yesterday
and we're trying to figure out
who's trying to muscle in on their turf
before more people get killed.
Come on, man. I'm doing this now, you know?
- Birthday cakes, bouncy houses. - I know, I know, I get it.
No, you can't bro. My wife, Isabel, trust me.
Lot of ladies would've left by now.
I pushed things far as I can go, all right?
I'm trying to get clean, get off the pipe, you know?
Got out of that whole scene.
I got nothing but respect for that.
So check it:
I can get you 5 grand
and the state's attorney's gonna seal your record.
That means you don't have to disclose anything
to any potential employers.
You can do this whole thing right.
You can get a real job, raise your family.
All right, but yo, I gotta talk to Isabel first.
Well, she's already on board. Called her before we came over.
He's conniving, ain't he?
Eh. Let's call it persuasive.
All right, the person you really want is Logan.
- Who? - Logan Teague.
Me and him used to run around the block a few times.
Like I said, I'm out of the game,
but Logan's a player.
Knows everyone out there. He'll--
he'll take us where we need to go.
- Okay. - Nice.
All right.
Hitting him up now.
Hey, you ready? You clean?
As a whistle.
How did a whistle become the thing we use
to measure being clean?
Got people's saliva all up in there.
Who uses a whistle, huh?
- Gym teachers? Cops? - All right, yo.
Hey, we gotta be serious now, okay?
This is real.
Yeah, literally not real.
And they said irony was dead.
Wait, what's your name supposed to be again
when we get over there?
- It's Mike, bro. - Mike.
I rest my case.
Tommy, you're gonna remember that, right?
Adam's got himself a live one.
Indeed.
Mike rhymes with bike. Mike, bike, Mike, bike.
Yeah, right. When we get in there,
you don't gotta take it too far.
You don't gotta front like you're back in the game.
Right, right.
You're just making introductions.
Felt like a meet would be good for me, Logan Teague,
you get a little taste, and then after that,
you gotta do what you're not so good at.
Shut the hell up and let me do the talking, all right?
Kay. Mum's the word, Mikey.
All right, so then I'll lay groundwork for a buy.
Cool, cool.
- This it right here? - Yep.
Here we go.
- Hey, Logan. - Tommy, hey.
What's up, man?
My boy Mike I was telling you about.
Contact confirmed with Logan Teague.
Copy.
- Is that for me? - Yeah.
Smoke on up while we're hanging out.
- For real? - Yeah, customer loyalty, eh?
Oh, dude.
How long we been running together?
I ever tell you I love you, man?
- Never enough. - I love you.
This.
Sweet, sweet Jesus. Sweet, sweet Jesus.
Jay, be advised our CI is using.
This could crap out at any second.
I understand you're in a bit of a pickle.
What do you mean?
What, Tommy didn't tell you he called me and...
gave me a heads-up on your issues?
- He did not, no. - Tommy.
You gotta tell people when you're, you know,
sharing their business.
Oh, yeah, sorry. That's right.
This guy, eh?
Yeah, this guy.
Yeah, no, no. I told Logan how, you know you and me,
we're all in this new thing together.
Partners, you know?
Moving product up from the suburbs.
Ah, that's right.
This is what's up, man. I also told him...
about our little supply problem, you know,
how the Mexicans, the Players, you know,
are scared as hell after getting shot up the other day.
And look, man, we don't need to know what's up, all right?
It's above our pay grade.
But we do need to know what's down
as in we need a new supplier.
I mean, that's about the long and short of it, man.
You talking about the Becerra Brothers?
Over New City way?
- Yeah. - That's them.
Yesterday's news, literally.
There's a new sheriff in town. Indiana boy.
Monahan.
- Monahan. - Monahan.
He's got beaucoup product to move.
- Made in the USA, too. - Oh, all right.
Well, shoot, that sounds like a guy we should know.
Sounds exactly like a guy we should know.
How much product do you two think you can move
out in the suburbs?
- Half a pound a day, easy. - Pound a day.
Sky's the limit if the glass is clean, bro.
I'm telling you we got something here.
We got the funnel, we got the funnel.
Okay.
That's some real weight.
It's a serious situation, baby.
I'll get in touch with Monahan,
see if I can get the ball rolling.
That's what we wanted to hear, man.
That's what I came to you for.
All right, I will leave you be, man.
Have a good one, man. Great seeing you, bro.
See you, Tommy.
- So now you two partners? - What?
Me and Ruz, we're buds.
You better hope so, 'cause now you're on my wing
to the bitter end of this thing.
You guys are a barrel of laughs.
You told Adam you were clean, like, 20 minutes ago.
Yeah, I was clean.
20 minutes ago.
It's like a pack-a-day smoker. Quits every 20 minutes, right?
All right, look. When I'm not using, my head don't work right.
I can't think fast enough, okay?
And that's fine if I'm farting around at home or whatnot,
but in this line of work?
Gotta electric slide, baby, you know?
That's it.
Crystal meth isn't exactly known
to bring out the best in people, Tommy.
I highly disagree.
Look, we got what we wanted.
What is everyone so glum about?
- Tommy. - What?
If you want your money, you want your record scrubbed,
there's no more dope.
Fine.
- Come here, come here. - What's their problem?
Just go home to your family.
Remember why you're doing this, all right?
Hey, where you going? How am I supposed to get there?
Oh, you take a walk.
Take a walk and clear your stupid head.
- What's up, Sarge? - What do you got?
Indiana State Police confirmed the ID of the man
we believe killed the Becerra Brothers.
His name's Keith Monahan. Heavy hitter.
Sold mountains of crystal meth in Muncie.
He's here now.
Indiana's intel says he's here to stay.
They're pretty happy he's our problem now.
They've linked this guy to ten murders,
but Monahan is smart and he's calculated.
Probably knows where to hide the bodies,
so he's one step ahead of them all the time.
They got him on two gun charges which are both misdemeanors,
so he's got virtually no record.
So we're nowhere on the murders?
All right, let's keep chasing the drug angle.
We'll get this son of a bitch off the street that way.
Then we'll make the murders.
So?
So Logan Teague made contact with Monahan.
We fronted like we wanted to move some real weight,
so Monahan's pretty interested.
I got a dry meet on the books with Tommy, my CI,
Logan, myself.
Logan wants to see money,
he wants to know that we're capable,
he wants to set rules and prices,
then he'll make the meet with Monahan.
Okay, let's do it.
I understand you ran into a little trouble with your CI.
Yeah, a bit.
He kind of took one for the team, boss.
And we got what we wanted.
Well, we can't go into a meeting like this
with a CI high on meth.
Just bring him in, put him in the box,
we'll keep him clean until the dry meet.
- Oh, boss, I just don't know - Just bring him in.
All right.
- Wanna go in? - Yeah, I'll be right back.
Tommy ain't here.
He's gone, Ruz.
- Gone where? - I never know.
He's into something.
Well, what does that mean?
Usually, it means he'll be back in a few days,
smell like death, get on his knees,
beg me for forgiveness, sleep 48 hours straight,
then promise me he'll never do it again.
Okay.
I'm gonna find him for you. I'm gonna find him, yeah?
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
- What, here? - Yeah.
Homan between 15th and 16th.
Son of a bitch.
Keep it together. You don't wanna burn him.
- He's a CI. - I know, I know.
I'm gonna kill him with my bare hands.
You're good.
Oh, crap.
- You ripped me off. - No.
There's a guy selling the same sneakers for far less
over in Independence Park!
Sir, I'll be with you in a minute.
- I'm just handling a customer. - Yeah?
- So dude, yeah, take - Why don't you get the hell out of here?
I'm trying to buy these shoes.
You're trying to buy these shoes?
That's a very nice choice.
- Get the hell out of here! - Okay.
- What are you doing? - You owe me 100 bucks for those, man.
100 bucks? I got 5 grand coming your way, man.
You know what the resale value is
- on Carolina blues, dude? - What's wrong with you?
Look, I'm keeping clean like you want.
I am, okay?
I am and it hurts and it sucks, but I'm doing it.
But I gotta make a living, man.
This is how I put food on my table.
I mean, what are you even doing, man?
You can't just disappear right before a meet.
The two of you! Just get in the car.
How you feeling, bro?
It's freezing in here.
I'm sorry to tell you it's not.
All right, well, hang in there.
I'll go get you a blanket, all right?
Okay.
All right, we are trying to take down a smart, violent dealer.
Guy puts people in the ground they blink the wrong way.
So I gotta know: can we do it with this guy?
- Yeah. - No.
No.
I'm not saying we surrender.
I'm just saying we cut Tommy lose.
We find another way to get to Monahan.
All right, look. I get it, I do.
All right? I do.
It's just you do not know this guy like I do.
I know that you guys go way back.
He's put in good work for you. You're friends.
But this guy is a mess, Adam. He's a storm of bad news.
Just got a call about another double play.
Looks like it's connected to Monahan.
Have Trudy keep an eye on that guy.
Yeah.
What's the story?
Unfortunately, it's a familiar one.
DOA is Ramon Santiago. He's 25.
Let me guess.
Hispanic, documented gang banger, crystal meth dealer?
Yes, sir. Shot and killed by automatic rifle fire
from a vehicle that rolled up on him.
Shell casings are .223s. Green tips.
Same rounds that killed the Becerra Brothers.
- This other victim? - Innocent, this time.
Ramon's girlfriend. Wendy Garcia, 22.
Has a-- had a three-year-old son.
All right, have Ballistics confirm these rounds were fired
from the same weapon used on the Becerra Brothers.
See if that DOA got any threatening text messages
from the same burner.
I mean, we already know but
let's do the work to connect the two crimes.
Body count's up to four now.
Monahan's doing this as loud and public as possible.
Yeah.
Boss.
Look, I know Tommy's a mess.
He's a liar, he's a cheat, he's a junkie.
That's a hell of a sales pitch.
He's also the best CI I ever had
and I think we can work through this.
At this point,
I don't know if we got a lot of choice in the matter.
We cut him loose now, think we're dead in the water.
Yeah, well, unfortunately, I think you're right.
- Let's get it done. - Yes, sir.
After this thing's over, we're gonna get you some help.
Just worry about getting me my money.
You're sick, Tommy. No way to live.
Yeah? Well, maybe.
There's a chance I get better.
And however that turns out,
you'll still be an unattractive, Irish prick from Canaryville.
Tommy's got enough strength to talk smack.
I'd say that's something.
He's gonna need more than that.
All right, so we were thinking,
you know, two pounds to start.
You get that done?
That's what I do. Generate business.
Price'll be 20 per.
20? Damn. I mean, that's pretty steep, man.
With Monahan, I'd encourage you not think of it as a negotiation.
Look, if I can get this thing set up, you gotta understand.
- If you're five minutes late with this guy, he walks. - All right.
You try to change the location on him, he walks.
Who's he, the chosen one? We gotta kiss his ring, too?
Pull the plug, you don't like it.
- What's his problem? - Ah, he's having a rough day.
Don't worry about him.
My brokerage fee is 10%.
Okay, so then we split that with Monahan?
No. No, that's all on you.
Just pay the man so we can get the hell out of here, man.
All right, Logan, look.
First time out, you need it up front?
We can do it up front.
- Are you dry? - I'm good, bro.
Just step off me, man.
Here, knock yourself out.
Knock yourself out.
Damn.
I'm good, man. Not here to get high.
Let's just finish this, all right?
- You're dry, Tommy. - Logan.
Leave him alone. Let's get this done.
Go on.
Why don't you smoke up, too, Mike?
I sell it. I don't smoke it.
I said smoke up, Mike.
He's made. Let's go get him.
He wants to let it play, so we let it play.
What are you doing? I mean, come on.
We all stand to make a hell of a lot of money here.
- What are you doing? - Yeah, that's the idea, yeah.
And you're gonna pull a piece on me?
I gotta protect myself.
There's a lot of sketchy people in this business.
You're starting to make me nervous.
You're making a very big mistake, Logan.
Am I?
Go!
Stop fighting, Logan. Stop fighting, man.
Stop!
Chicago PD! Chicago PD!
What else you got?
There's crystal in his place back there.
We should get him checked on, make sure he's okay.
Yeah.
- You wanted to see me? - Yeah.
What the hell happened out there?
Tommy was a mess. It went south.
No kidding.
I had to arrest the broker, so I got him in the box.
I'm thinking we flip him, we can get to Monahan that way.
Shut the door.
What's going on?
I got a call from an old buddy of mine,
that sergeant in the 13th.
You happen to recall seeing some crummy liquor store
where all this went down?
I mean, we parked right outside of one.
Well, turns out the owner of that store's got a camera in the alley.
Says he's got you on film.
"Police brutality" are the words being tossed around.
You gotta be kidding me. I pinned the guy's carotid.
I'd do the exact same thing next time.
Boss, I know the new rules.
I know the limitations when we're out there.
But if I say that my life was in danger, which it was,
I mean, we're good.
I'm telling you, boss, no. This was a violent situation.
- Adam. - I didn't do anything wrong.
I know you didn't do anything wrong.
That's just not the math anymore, you understand?
Bro, in this new world order,
what matters is that some jerk is shopping around
the perception that you did something wrong.
That alone is enough to ruin your career,
you understand?
Yeah.
All right.
How's the throat? Mine's a little sore.
We got you dead to rights here, Logan.
Calculated drug conspiracy. That's a Class X felony.
You're looking at six to 30.
That's a long time.
We're not actually finished.
You already got a felony on your record,
so mandatory extension under sentencing guidelines,
you're looking at, I don't know,
let's be generous--50 years?
I ain't flipping on Keith Monahan.
That's a death sentence. I'd rather be in the joint.
Three squares a day,
couple special friends in the shower.
I didn't ask about your sex life
and I didn't ask you to flip.
So what do you want?
Your phone.
Give me the password,
tell me where you meet Monahan when you do business,
and I will get you a good deal.
I pulled a piece on a cop. Game over.
I know. You pulled a piece on this cop.
Well, maybe I don't remember it that way.
What?
Let me worry about the details.
Things go well for us, be out of here before you know it.
So.
All right, come on, man. Come on.
- Adam. - Yeah.
What are you doing?
Setting up a buy with Monahan posing as Logan Teague
just like we learned in UC school.
You give Logan a slap on the wrist,
the first thing that he does when he gets out,
he pops Tommy.
- No, that's not gonna happen. - It is gonna happen.
No, look, I'm gonna hold Logan for 24 hours
then I'll send him downstate.
By the time he gets out, he's looking for Tommy,
What are you talking about?
he's gonna have to search in nursing homes.
You can bend the truth in there, Adam,
but I heard you give that man your word.
- I don't-- - You promised him something.
Hold on, hold on.
He pulled a gun on a cop, all right?
I mean, like he said. Game over.
Good Lord.
If this too messy for you, look away, please,
'cause I will sleep fine tonight.
Here we go.
Okay.
Game on. 3:00 p.m.
And now he's expecting you and your partner.
Yeah, well, that's what he's gonna get.
You kidding me?
Tommy couldn't make it through that last meeting
- without blowing it up. - I'm gonna check on him.
- Adam, listen. - I will make sure he's okay.
It's gonna be fine, I promise.
I never seen it so bad, Adam.
He can't keep food down; he can't keep water down.
I want him sober, obviously.
Things were just getting good for us.
But I swear to Christ, I'm afraid he's gonna die
before he makes it to the other side.
I--
I'm sorry.
Tommy, stop. Tommy, stop scratching.
I can't, Steve.
Whatever your name is supposed to be.
It's Mike.
Remember. Mike, bike, Mike.
Mike.
Drug dealer. Suburbs.
Come here. Let's sit you up.
There you go, all right.
Just, uh, maybe the next time we do this,
you pick a name that matches your personality more.
Like Elizabeth.
Or Amanda.
You sit tight. I'm gonna clean you up.
Gonna clean you up, all right?
All right, buddy. Come here, bud.
I want you to bite down on this, all right?
Just real slow. Wet your whistle a little. Here.
Here you go, man.
Yeah. That's nice.
God.
Now, we're close.
I'm not gonna make it.
- Not like this. - No.
There's only one way to the promised land.
You know what that is.
No.
Yeah.
- No, Tommy. - Yes.
- No. - Yes.
Yes.
You said it's off Pulaski, right?
Yeah, just a... just a little further.
Here. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Here, yeah. Just dump me off right here.
Okay, okay.
All right. Go, man.
No.
Bro, you can't be serious right now.
If it makes you feel any better,
you can just look at it as payment back
for those sneakers you owe me.
Isn't gonna make me feel better about this.
How much you need to make it through the night,
turn on that magic?
Two grams, maybe. 60 a pop.
Good man, good man.
Everything's gonna be okay, all right?
It's all gonna be worth it in the end.
- Yeah. - Okay.
Adam and Tommy are on their way.
Everybody listen up.
We surveilled the site, we all know our jobs,
but we didn't pick this spot.
There's a lot we don't know
including how much resistance to expect.
Don't forget Ruzek's in there naked.
He's got no weapon.
Let's make sure everyone goes home tonight.
We got security.
Two guys armed to the teeth.
Heads up. Coming at us.
All right, here we go.
They're greeting our party now.
- Spread. - Yes, sir.
That's a hell of a tricked-out piece, man.
Folding stock, little muzzle suppressor.
What, it can cook you breakfast, too?
What's that thing spit?
Green tip .223s, bro.
You get the street mod, make it a chopper?
No need. Came with a selector.
- Fully auto, then go home. - Amen to that.
- .223s. Green tip, fully auto. - Probably the murder weapon.
Count it.
We got a positive on Monahan.
I don't mean to give the impression
that I need to be friends, 'cause I don't.
Fair enough.
But I am in the midst of a...
significant business expansion.
- Looking to move product. - All right.
Not looking to create competition for myself.
Logan said you two plan to distribute in the suburbs.
That's right.
Tell me more about that.
Yeah, man. We're an open book.
You know, tell us what you wanna know.
- We'll answer any questions you-- - You ever see those birds
that sit on top of them water buffalos?
White suckers. Know the ones?
I used to think,
"What are you doing on top of that buffalo, birdy?"
Turns out he's having a snack. Yeah.
It's true. I saw it on TV.
Yeah, the bird eats the ticks that make the buffalo sick.
It's a win-win for everyone.
Buffalo gets a clean bill of health,
bird gets to have a feast.
Is Tommy geeking out?
He is.
So am I the buffalo? Am I the bird?
You're...
whoever, man.
Dealer's choice.
Eh? See what I did there?
But point is we ain't competitors.
We'd be fools, all right?
We want to be partners.
What does that look like to you?
- Trust. - Trust.
Right?
So I'm gonna tell you what our secret sauce is.
We're gonna take your product, mix it with X, make super X.
Kids love it.
That's why we're hitting up the suburbs.
For the colleges.
Prairie, Wheaton, State.
I got ins all over the place. What do you think's up there?
Listen to that kid.
So bunch of kids,
bored, with a buttload of money,
just waiting.
Waiting for us.
- Super ecstasy? - Yeah.
Yeah, he came up with it.
Yeah, this guy's funny.
Let's keep it simple.
We do this deal today.
Let's let this sit for a minute, simmer.
All right.
Positive. I repeat, we have a positive.
Move, move.
What do you say? Meet back here in a week?
We explore all this other stuff together?
- Done. - Yeah, hell yeah, man.
We'll be here.
You're good, you're good.
What the hell's going on? What the hell is this?
Get out of here, Tommy.
Go now. Go.
Talk to me, Burgess!
- Good, Burgess? - I'm good, I'm good!
5021 George. Shots fired.
Be advised, unarmed UC in the middle of it.
- I don't have a shot. - Copy that.
Cover me, cover me!
- Hey! - Chicago PD!
On your knees.
Hands behind your head.
I got this--you guys go. I'll wait for patrol.
Police, stop!
Chicago PD! Turn around!
Turn around, Monahan! Stop moving!
Put the gun down.
Yeah, I don't think I will.
Put the gun down, Monahan.
This thing's over. There's nowhere to go.
Put it down.
Is it over?
Monahan, you don't stop pointing that gun at my friend,
I swear to God, I will drop you!
Put it down!
Put it down.
You ain't gonna shoot me.
Put it--
God!
Ruz, Ruz.
Tommy, Tommy.
Listen, man. I need you to take your hands,
I need you to put 'em right there, okay?
- Hold down, all right? - Sure...
- We'll get you all covered up. - Tommy!
Sarge, we found him at the east end!
Shots fired, offender down! Ruz is okay!
All right? Just keep your eyes open.
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry. - Copy that.
Stop saying, "I'm sorry."
You did good. Not your fault.
There you go, there you go.
I got him.
- Thank you. - Yeah.
I need you to keep your eyes open, eh?
I need you to keep talking to me, all right?
Hey, keep your eyes open.
5021 David, we got a man down, GSW to the chest.
You gotta keep your eyes open
for Isabel and your family, right?
You gotta go home to 'em now,
enjoy the fruits of your labor.
Yeah? Tommy.
Hey, what's-- hey, what's my undercover name?
Elizabeth.
Yeah, that's right. Elizabeth it is.
You keep those eyes open.
You did good, bro. You did good.
You stay with me, Tommy. Tommy, you stay with me.
I screwed up.
Hesitated.
I just had all these voices in my head.
You know, rules and...
not right or wrong, the perception of right or wrong,
and all that crap and I don't have my piece.
Carrying a rifle that's used to murder four people.
This guy's not pointing the gun at me,
he's pointing a gun at Tommy.
And so what the hell do I know?
What do I know?
Can't trust my instincts anymore.
And I think I had a lawful shoot out there.
- You did. - I know.
I know.
Yet I hesitated and I...
didn't pull the trigger until after he shot my friend.
Look, Adam.
Adam.
I mean, we're running point on a whole new thing here.
You're taking all these new rules they're writing in here,
taking them into the chaos out there.
It's not gonna be easy.
Not when you got, what, half a second to decide
whether to take one guy's life in order to save another?
Tell you one thing, right...
I mean, right is still right, Adam.
I think we're all gonna be
groping around in the dark for a while.
Yeah.
You know?
Least we'll be doing it together, man.