.
- All right, all right.
Half soy, half coffee.
I kid.
I know you like it black.
- [laughs]
Thank you.
- You know what the greatest
part about this situation is?
- What's that?
- It's only 8:00
in the morning.
- What about the coffee?
- Screw the coffee.
[phone buzzing]
- No, no, no.
[groans]
Stop.
- Ow.
- Oh, come on.
You gotta be kidding me.
Come on.
Every time she's supposed
to do something,
she drops the ball.
It's incredible.
My sister's supposed to pick
my dad up
and bring him to the doctor,
and she bailed again.
- Yeah, I get it.
I don't do yelling,
and I don't do slamming.
Not even a little bit.
- Yeah, Dad...
Hey, listen...I'm, uh,
I'm sorry about before.
All right?
I want you to know to know
I'm not a yeller or a slammer.
I just..you know, family stuff
makes me crazy.
- I get it.
- Thank you.
- We're good?
- Yeah.
But you've been warned.
Hey, listen, uh, when we get
closer to the district,
drop me off a few blocks away.
- Really? We're just driving
into work together.
- People who aren't
sleeping together
don't drive to work together.
Not to mention,
the people we work with
are elite detectives, so...
- All right.
But look--
- I don't want this
getting out.
- Oh, ouch.
- I'm just being honest.
I don't wanna have to talk to
Voight about our relationship
or whatever this is--
fill out HR forms.
- I hear ya.
We're on the same page.
But, hey, listen, my cousin is
having a party this weekend.
There are no HR forms involved,
and it should be a good time.
What do you think?
- Let me think about it.
- All right.
- Units in the 21
and units on the citywide,
we have reports of a female
screaming for help
inside a residence at
1226 North State.
- Oh, yeah.
5021 Henry, Squad advise--
plain clothes officers
rolling on that.
We're three blocks out.
- Copy that, 5021 Henry.
- Hey. Over here!
Stop the car! Stop the car!
Stop! Stop!
Inside--just in here.
She was screaming.
She was screaming inside
the house.
- Okay, ma'am.
Get back in your house.
- She was screaming,
and I think she's in trouble.
- Get back in your house,
ma'am.
[tires squealing]
- I got a car fleeing
in the back!
[dramatic music]
♪
[brakes screech]
[car horns honking]
♪
- Chicago police.
Turn off the car.
Exit the vehicle.
5021 Ida. I got a blue Honda
trying to flee southbound
from the area of
a distress call.
Get out of the car.
Illinois plate, 79 Victor
Paul eight Zebra five.
Get out of the car
or I'll shoot.
Squad, he's backing up on me.
Stop!
[gunshots]
♪
Shots fired by the police.
That car just tried
to run me down.
It's fleeing down the alley,
northbound.
- Copy that, 5021 Ida.
Down the alley northbound.
- 5021 Henry--roll an ambo to
1226 North State Street.
- Copy that, 5021 Henry.
Ambo en route.
- Okay.
♪
- [moans]
- Ah, okay.
Stay with me.
I'm the police, okay?
Help is on the way.
- [wheezing]
- All right.
I'm right here.
Okay.
Just--help is on the way, okay?
We're gonna find the person
that did this to you, okay?
We're gonna find
the person that did this.
Stay with me, stay with me!
Stay with me.
- [wheezing]
- Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, okay.
Look at me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
No.
♪
- You all right?
Hailey, is the house clear?
Hailey, you all right?
Hailey!
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
- All right, stay with her.
I'm gonna clear the house.
- Yep.
♪
Victim's name is
Allison Collier.
Her husband is--
- Jason Collier.
Yeah, he's Alderman
for the 43rd Ward.
We crossed paths way back
when he was a prosecutor.
- Sarge, this looks like this
was a burglary.
The back door was pried open
with a crowbar.
- It was on the floor
near Allison's body.
I had Forensics send it
to the crime lab,
requested a rush order.
Hopefully, we can pull a print.
- Hey, man.
You okay?
- I guess.
The, uh, plates on
the blue Honda
came back to
a Lincoln Town Car.
- How nice.
So, the offender steals a plate
off a random Lincoln,
and he puts it on his Honda.
- I'll figure out where
the Town Car was parked,
see if I can get some
surveillance photos
out of the deal.
- Okay, good.
Meantime, run every blue Honda
in Chicago.
Let's see if one of the owners
has a sheet to match the M.O.
And start canvassing
the neighborhood
for witnesses, PODs,
surveillance cameras.
Hey.
The press is gonna be
all over this.
Not a word to anyone.
- Copy.
- You good?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I heard about Allison.
What the hell happened?
- Well, we're not sure.
Looks like a burglary gone bad.
- I was friends with her
and Jason for years.
Superintendent is close
with them, too.
She's a good woman.
- Wanna make the notification?
- I already did.
Jason's at
a conference in Boston.
Poor guy couldn't even talk.
I want bracelets on someone
by the end of the day.
Is that understood?
- Yes, ma'am.
- I was coming home from
pilates, checking my texts,
and I heard a woman screaming.
- Did you happen to see
anyone near the house?
Anyone who looks suspicious?
- Yeah.
Early this morning
there was this guy
near the gangway.
He was just walking around.
He seemed out of place.
I'm not saying he killed her.
I'm just saying I noticed him.
- Okay, can you describe
the guy?
- He was black--
I mean, African-American.
Um, average height.
Thin and young,
early 20s.
- Did you see
what he was wearing?
- He had a white hat
on his head.
That's all I remember.
But again, I'm not saying
this man is involved.
And it has nothing to do
with the fact
that he's African-American.
- Right, he just
looked suspicious.
Like he was casing the house
that he was about to rob,
right?
- Yeah, he looked suspicious.
Very suspicious.
And...he was holding something
in his right hand, too,
under his jacket.
- Crowbar?
- Maybe.
I couldn't tell.
- Jason, I'm so sorry
for your loss.
- Thank you, Sergeant.
What do we know?
- Looks like a home invasion.
Offender appears to be
a young African-American male.
That's about it right now.
But it's early.
Look, was there anything
going on we should know about?
Any jealous boyfriends,
girlfriends,
stalkers,
that kind of thing.
- No, nothing like that.
We were good.
- Well, if you think of
anything
that might be useful...
We are gonna find
this son of a bitch.
You have my word on that.
- Hey, boss.
- Yeah?
- Good news.
- Okay.
- So, the POD cameras near
Collier's house,
they were able to pick out
an image of the blue Honda.
You can't see the driver,
but I was able to find
a "Franklin's Plastics" decal.
It looks like an employee
parking decal
on the windshield.
- All right.
So, find out who works
there that drives a blue Honda.
- I did, it's a man
by the name of Jerome York.
He's got no priors.
- Good.
Grab Upton, track his ass down.
Oh, hey.
- Hmm?
- How is it that you and Upton
showed up at the crime scene
together this morning?
- Uh, her car's in the shop,
so I gave her a ride.
- Oh, oh.
Well, if her car keeps
having problems,
and you keep giving
her rides...
You should probably tell
your supervisor,
fill out the proper HR forms.
- I'm not the only person in
the city of Chicago
with a blue Honda.
- You're the only one with
a "Franklin Plastics"
decal on it.
- What's going on, Dad?
- Go back inside.
- I just wanted to know
if you're okay.
- Get back inside, now.
- What happened to your eye?
- Don't talk to my daughter.
- Let her answer the question.
- She plays soccer, okay?
She caught an elbow yesterday,
after school.
- Is that what happened?
Did that happen
at soccer practice?
- Yes.
Yesterday, after school.
- Kia, go to your room now.
[dramatic music]
You got some nerve
accusing me--
- I didn't accuse you
of anything.
I asked a question.
- Get off my property
or I'll file a complaint.
- I want the name of
that soccer coach.
- I want your badge number.
- 5-5-0-5-5--
- Whoa, hey, Detective Upton,
why don't I take it from here?
- No, we're all right.
- No, no, no.
I'm gonna take this.
I got it, Detective Upton.
♪
- She's got no right asking
me questions like that.
- Sir, I know you're upset...
- None, whatsoever.
- All I care about is the blue
Honda--most likely your car--
I saw fleeing the
scene of a murder this morning.
- Murder?
- Yes, murder.
That's why we're here, sir.
That's why we need to know
where you were this morning.
♪
- I was here at home,
working on my computer,
sending emails.
You could ask my wife
or check my laptop.
- We will.
- I got nothing to hide.
Who else has access to the car?
- A kid from the neighborhood,
Devin Williams.
I'm trying to help him out.
He runs errands for us.
I gave him the car last night.
He's a good kid.
He wouldn't do anything
like this.
- Well, did he return the car?
- No, he hasn't.
- Where does he live?
- With his grandma.
Corner of 10th and Bradley.
Tan house.
- All right, thank you.
I apologize.
♪
- What's going on with you?
What the hell was that?
- Kid had a black eye.
- Yeah, it sounds like she got
it at soccer practice.
You kept pushing.
We're chasing a murder here.
- I don't care
what we're chasing.
She's a kid.
She needs to be protected.
- That is not the point.
- I asked a simple question.
It's not a big deal.
- Hailey, look,
you outrank me in everything,
but if you're gonna
accuse a father
of smacking around his kid,
you gotta have
some evidence first.
- I did.
It's called a black eye.
♪
Don't ever undermine me
or dismiss me
from an interview
like that again.
♪
[train roaring]
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Hold up.
Bingo.
Blue Honda inside.
- All right, come on.
Hello, ma'am.
Chicago PD.
Is Devin Williams home?
We'd like to talk to him.
- What's this about?
Why y'all want to talk to him?
- The car he was driving
was spotted
near the scene of a murder.
- Murder?
Devin ain't involved in
no damn murder.
I can promise you that much.
- Yeah well, that's great.
Then we'll be in and out.
Two, three minutes.
- The truth is, ma'am, is that
we know Devin isn't involved.
We've heard really good things
about him.
But, you know, we gotta
check him off a list, so...
- Come on in.
Devin!
Can I get you all something
to drink?
Some water, some tea,
some coffee, or something?
Wait a--wait a minute!
- He's running your way.
- Devin, don't run.
Boy, get back here.
- Stop right there.
Stop, man. Stop!
Stop, stop!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Stay down.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
You're done, bro. You're done.
You're done. You're done.
Stay down.
- You're under arrest
for murder.
- No. No, no, no, no.
You got the wrong guy.
I got nothing to do
with that murder
on the North Side, I swear.
You got the wrong guy!
- Murder on the North Side?
What you talking about, pal?
- The one where
that lady got killed.
I--I didn't--I didn't do that,
I swear.
- Okay, we believe you, Devin.
We really do.
- Come on.
.
- The best thing you can do
is tell us
what really happened
at that house.
If you do that, we can talk to
the State's Attorney's Office
and try to work out
a good deal.
- Like I said,
I didn't kill her.
I haven't been to
the North Side in...weeks.
- Okay.
The problem is, Devin,
you keep talking about a murder
on the North Side...
Right?
- Mm-hmm.
- We never told you about that.
- What do you mean?
- You keep denying something
you shouldn't know about.
Means you're guilty.
- But I'm not.
- Then how do you know someone
from the North Side was
murdered?
- I...
just know...I guess.
- Where were you this morning
between 9:00 and 10:00?
- Humboldt Park.
Uh, I was, uh, smoking weed
near the chess tables.
- Hey, look at me.
You still high?
- Yeah, but only a little.
- Yeah. Were you alone,
with someone else?
- I was with someone else.
- Who?
- God.
- God?
- Yeah.
We were hanging out.
Talking to each other.
And it was really nice.
[tense music]
♪
- Is this guy bluffing?
Or is he really that clueless?
- I just talked to the lab.
- Yeah?
- Still no fingerprints
or DNA hits.
- We got the witness, though,
Sarge.
Neighbor said she got
a good look at the offender.
- That's right.
Well, get her down here
right away.
Just let us know if you see
the man you saw
standing outside of Allison's
house this morning.
Take a look.
See if anyone looks familiar.
♪
- I'm pretty sure
it's number three.
- Good.
Thank you.
- Why don't we step outside?
- I guess we got him, boss.
- Yeah, all right.
So, take a run at him.
Let's put this thing to bed.
- Copy that.
♪
'Sup, bro?
- 'Sup?
- Oh, let me
help you out with those.
- Oh, thanks.
- Hey, bro, hold on.
Let me help you with these.
- Okay.
- You want a sandwich or
something to go with those?
Just let me know.
- Yeah, that would be awesome.
- Yeah, man.
First thing's first.
Let's talk about what happened.
- Cool.
- I'm gonna keep it 100
with you, man.
No BS, no games.
- I appreciate that.
- A witness just...
picked you out of a lineup.
She said she saw you
outside the house
the morning of the murder.
We also got that getaway car,
the blue Honda--found that
parked at your granny's garage.
This is where it gets bad.
Your fingerprints are
all over the crowbar
that killed the female victim.
We know you did the murder.
But I think you're
a decent kid,
and I would love
to give you a deal.
I just need you
to help me understand
what really happened.
- I keep trying to tell
you guys, I didn't kill her.
I was in Humboldt Park.
Can I get one of them
sandwiches now?
- How's that sandwich?
Yeah, well, I were you,
I'd enjoy it.
'Cause the food
in prison sucks.
Well, I guess you
already know that.
You did two years
in Danville, right?
Well, honey...
I'm here to tell you,
life is different.
There's no light
at the end of the tunnel.
There's no calendar.
No girlfriend
to look forward to.
It's just you.
And your cell.
Forever.
That's why we're trying
to help you, Devin.
To give you that light
at the end of the tunnel.
- I'm really thirsty.
Can--can I get another soda?
[loud bang]
- You think I'm running
a restaurant?
- No, I'm--I'm just
really thirsty.
- We got a young woman
beaten to death,
and all you care about is pop?
- I'm sorry, sir.
I--I don't mean no disrespect.
- Let me tell you something,
that woman you killed?
Her husband is an alderman.
And that's about as close
as you get
to being a king in Chicago.
And when the wife
of an alderman
gets beaten to death
with a crowbar,
somebody is gonna pay.
You understand?
The only question is,
how much?
How long?
How painful?
♪
- I keep telling you guys,
I didn't do it.
I--I was in Humboldt Park.
Now, if it's okay, can I--can I
please get that soda?
.
- Kid is a trip.
- Yup.
- Can't figure out where
he's coming from.
- No, well, whatever he's
doing, it's working.
It's been seven hours; he
hasn't given up a damn thing.
- Yeah, he hasn't
lawyered up yet, though,
which is good, but it's odd.
I mean, I don't know why he's
still talking to us.
- He doesn't know any better.
- Lab says there's still
no forensics
tying Devin to the crowbar
and body,
the crime scene--nothing.
- Sarge, let me take
a run at him.
I've been going over his file.
I think I have
an angle to play.
- Give it a shot.
Oh--
Kid wants a pop.
- Ah.
I just wanted to check in
on you.
See how you're holding up.
Is it okay if I sit down?
How old were you
when they started?
- When what started?
- The beatings.
- I don't know.
Five.
Six.
- Your dad, he beat
your mom, too, right?
- Yeah.
That's why I had to move.
- When was it the worst?
Morning?
Night?
For me, it was worst
on the weekends.
My dad...
[tense music]
Would start drinking early.
Like, noon.
He'd just sit around...
getting more and more
pissed off.
My brothers and I,
we were just kids, you know?
We wanted to have fun.
♪
And it drove him crazy.
So he'd pick a fight
with my mom,
saying that we were
being too loud.
She'd defend us,
because she always did.
So he'd go after her.
And then he'd come after us...
with anything he could get
his hands on.
Belt...
extension cord.
- You ever think
about killing yourself?
♪
- Yeah.
But I didn't,
because I'm strong like you.
- Hailey's good.
This cop thing
doesn't work out,
she should think
about being an actor.
Damn.
- Sometimes I get
this...anger inside of me.
It's like a need for revenge,
you know?
Like I want someone else to
feel the pain that I felt.
Do you know
what I'm talking about?
- I do.
- Feels good to let it out,
doesn't it?
- Yeah.
[sniffs]
Until it's over.
And then you hate yourself
even more.
- You need to remember
that it's not your fault.
Your dad made you this way.
He made you violent.
♪
Everybody makes mistakes.
You didn't know that lady was
gonna be home.
When you saw her there,
you probably got scared.
She probably got scared.
- Yeah.
She got scared.
She hit me.
- So you hit her back.
- Yeah.
With the crowbar.
I wanted her to stop
screaming and crying.
♪
- Devin, were you alone?
Or was someone else with you?
- No, it was just me.
I'm s--I'm so sorry.
- I know.
- [sobbing]
I'm sorry.
- I know.
♪
Got him.
- Yeah, you sure did.
That was great work.
All right.
I'm gonna call the ASA.
- Ah, you...really
got that boy.
For real.
Like, for a second there,
I thought he was gonna confess
to shooting
Abraham Lincoln, too.
- [laughs]
Say what you need to, right?
- Good job.
- Thanks.
- Are you okay?
Those stories
that you just told...
- Were complete crap.
- Is that the truth?
- The truth is,
I played his ass,
and now he's going down
for murder.
- All right.
- Confessions are great.
But we still need to make sure
that they're admissible,
that they were made
voluntarily.
- Well, I can tell you Upton
did this right.
I was there.
- Great.
I'll look over the video,
and get back to you.
- Thanks.
Hailey...
I wanna tell you,
you were terrific.
I mean, you found
that kid's weakness,
made him vulnerable,
and you buried his ass.
- Hey, we finally got a DNA hit
inside the Collier house.
Strand of hair
in the living room.
- Good.
More evidence, the better.
- Yeah, the problem is,
it's not a match to Devin.
Belongs to a guy named
Nate Stevenson.
In and out of the joint
since he was 18.
- He connected to Devin?
- Not sure.
All we know is that they
live in the same neighborhood.
- Okay.
Get a search warrant.
- Yeah.
[dramatic music]
♪
- I got it.
- You got it.
♪
- Got me?
- We're good.
- Nate Stevenson.
Chicago PD.
Open up.
You there?
♪
All right, let's move.
- Yeah.
Clear.
- Go.
♪
Clear.
- Clear.
- Yeah, it's all clear.
- All right.
Well, we have a search warrant,
so let's search.
Pick a room, start tossing
the place.
[intense music]
♪
- Yo, check this out.
That's a Cartier.
Same as on the list of items
stolen from Collier's house,
right?
- Sure was.
- Okay.
- That looks like Allison's,
but I think the one
I bought her was thinner.
- Did you pay with
a credit card?
- I think so.
Let me go check.
Where did--where did you
find this?
- At a house belonging to a guy
named Nate Stevenson.
- Does that mean
a second person's involved?
- Could be.
We're still investigating.
You ever hear of this guy?
- No.
- You ever seen him before?
- Is this man in custody?
- Not yet.
We're still looking.
- Okay.
I'll get you what you need.
- Hey, put out a BOLO
on Nate Stevenson.
Get some boots
on the ground, too.
Let's find this prick.
- Hailey.
We gotta talk.
- What's going on?
- So, I just spoke to
the Manager of Operations
for Humboldt Park.
- Yeah, the one that was
looking into Devin's alibi.
- So, yeah.
He just sent me a video
that confirms that Devin was
telling the truth.
He was smoking weed
at the chess tables.
- What?
That's impossible.
- I don't think so.
Look, that's Devin for sure.
The timestamp says 9:32.
- The 911 call was at 9:25.
How can he be at the park
at 9:32?
- Because I don't think
he ever was
at Collier's house
in the first place.
- What the hell is going on?
Devin, you've got some
explaining to do, my friend.
- Oh, God.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Devin!
- Get an ambulance
down here, now!
- Devin, Devin.
- Hold on.
Hold him up.
- I got him.
I got him.
- Okay.
[grunts]
Okay, down. Down.
[heavy breathing]
- Devin?
Please, no.
No, Devin.
Don't you die, Devin.
- Hailey, come on.
- No, no.
No, no, no.
- He's dead.
Hailey, come on.
- Stop it.
- He's dead.
- No, no, no.
- Hailey, we're too late.
.
- He was telling the truth.
Kid was at Humboldt Park
the whole time.
I was so desperate to get
a confession,
I didn't even consider the fact
that he could be innocent.
I just kept poking
at his pain--his wounds.
- Hailey, you did what you were
supposed to do.
You had a suspect in the box
without a lawyer,
you got him talking,
and you exploited a weakness.
- I exploited a 20-year-old
kid's tragic past.
- All the evidence
pointed to Devin.
I would have done
the same thing.
- [sighs]
I know.
[doorbell rings]
[groans]
- Hey.
Are you all right?
I heard what happened.
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Hey, brother.
- Hey.
- Just having a tequila.
You want one?
- No, I'm okay.
I--I heard what happened.
I wanted to come
and check on Hailey.
- I'm okay.
- I'm glad to hear it.
- You sure
you don't want a drink?
- No, I don't wanna interrupt.
You guys should talk,
partner to partner.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I'm glad you're okay.
- Thanks.
- Good night.
See you tomorrow, Jay.
- Yeah.
- Uh, am I drunk?
Or was that pretty
uncomfortable?
- Um, maybe a little.
It's Adam though.
He's awkward.
- I hope he doesn't think
that you and I are...
- No, he knows I don't date
people I work with.
- Smart policy.
Nothing good comes
out of a workplace romance.
- I'm, uh--I'm actually
a little tired.
But thanks for coming by.
- Yeah.
You should get some rest.
- See you tomorrow?
- Okay.
- All right.
- Devin Williams confesses
to a crime he didn't do.
- Mm.
- And then hangs himself?
- Mm-hmm.
- Do you know for sure
he's innocent?
That he has no involvement
in this crime?
- No, we're still looking
into that,
but we do know he wasn't
at the crime scene,
and he didn't do the murder.
- Press is gonna be
all over this.
Another false confession.
- Okay, well, you address
this any way you want.
But Detective Upton did
nothing wrong.
I'll raise my right hand
to that.
We track down
Nate Stevenson yet?
- Trying but he's still
in the wind.
- I ran Devin's phone.
He got a series of
threatening texts yesterday.
- Saying what?
- "Snitches die.
Grandmas do too."
- Sounds like Nate and Devin
are connected.
- Yeah.
So Devin loans Nate
the blue Honda.
Nate puts the stolen Lincoln
plates on the car,
drives over to the Colliers',
robs the joint, kills Allison.
Gives the car back to Devin.
All right, ping the phone
sending those texts,
get a location.
- I just did--the address
is 2244 Adams Street.
- Tact up, hit it now.
[suspenseful music]
- Go.
♪
- Hey, we got something.
- Our DOA is Nate Stevenson,
the guy we think really
killed Allison Collier.
- I've been going through
Nate's phone.
He's been getting
a lot of texts
from an unknown number.
The most recent one says:
"Need to meet, bro.
Have cash and passport."
- Somebody's trying to help
Nate get out of the country.
- Or make Nate think he was
trying to help him
get out of the country,
so he could just
track him down and shoot him.
- I pinged the unknown number.
All the texts were made
downtown,
corner of Superior
and Michigan.
- Well, unless the killer's
name is Neiman Marcus,
that doesn't really help us.
- I found a surveillance camera
across the street
from the warehouse.
We got a man wearing a hoodie
entering the warehouse at
3:12 p.m. and leaving at 3:21.
- Okay, that makes sense.
The M.E. put the time of death
between 2:30 and 4:00.
- You got a visual?
- Of him, no.
His car, yes.
I'll pull up the plates
right now.
Oh, my God.
It's Alderman Collier.
.
- So, I've been digging into
Collier's finances.
For starters, he bought
a Cartier watch from Landsberg
Jewelers for 14 grand.
That's the same make that we
found at Nate's house.
- All right, so he did know
it was his wife's watch--that
means he was lying to us.
- He also made two $9,000
withdrawals
while his bro, Nate, made two
$9,000 deposits last week.
- All right, so Collier paid
Nate 18 grand
to whack his wife, and he
whacked Nate to tie things off.
The question is, why?
- I think I have the answer
to that.
Found an email Allison wrote
to one of her friends.
"Need to talk to you about
finding a good lawyer.
Lots to discuss.
None of it good."
- She seemed pretty desperate
to begin the process,
so I gave her the name of a few
divorce lawyers that I know.
- Okay, did she mention why
she wanted to split up?
- Yes.
But given what's happened,
there's probably no point
in talking about it.
- Well, there's
definitely a point.
- What do you mean?
- We think her husband's
involved.
♪
- Oh, my God.
It was Jason.
It all makes perfect sense.
- How?
- Jason Collier was
physically abusing Allison,
and she wanted a divorce.
So he had her killed.
- You're sure about this?
- Afraid so.
- Is he in custody?
- I went by his office,
his house...
He's in the wind.
- Let me reach out to him.
I'll tell him the person we
think is responsible
for Allison's death,
this Nate Stevenson guy,
was just found dead.
The case is officially closed.
- Let me know when and where.
- I had no idea
Jason was capable of this.
- Everyone is capable of this.
It's why we're so busy.
- I know you don't wanna
talk about it.
- That's a terrible way to
start a sentence.
- I wanna make sure
you're okay.
- I can't believe
he killed himself.
- I know.
I get it.
- Internal Affairs wants
to look into it now.
Apparently, they have concerns
about my interrogation tactics.
- Screw that.
You did it right.
- Maybe.
- No, definitely.
- There he is.
- Collier's on site.
He's heading east on
Randolph, toward his house.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Take him.
[motor revving]
- Go to the next block.
I got the alley.
♪
He's going through the yards.
Stop running!
Stop--police!
Chicago PD!
Don't move.
Get your hands in the air now!
Jason Collier,
you're under arrest for murder.
Hands in the air now.
- This whole damn thing
is her fault.
She made a big deal
over nothing.
Nothing!
I grabbed her arms a few times.
That doesn't mean she gets
to ruin my career.
My life.
- Get on your knees now.
- Screw that.
- Stay back.
Stay back!
Drop your weapon.
I will shoot you.
Drop your weapon!
Drop your weapon now!
I will shoot you!
Drop your weapon.
I'll--
- [groaning]
- I ordered the suspect
to get on his knees.
He refused to comply.
And then he reached
into his waistband
and pulled out a weapon.
- But you didn't engage.
- No.
- Okay, why not?
- I shot before she could,
boss.
- Well, I know that, Adam.
I'm trying to understand
why Hailey didn't fire
on the offender before you did.
- She had two pedestrians
in her line of fire.
She knew I was there.
She knew I had the shot,
so she let me take it.
- Is that what happened?
- Yeah.
- Okay, good.
Listen, Hailey...
I don't want you meeting
with IAD right now.
Just tell them--tell them you
need to see your FOP rep first.
- Okay.
- For someone who has had
a long week, you look great.
- And it's only Wednesday.
- [chuckles]
Hmm.
- So, this Halstead thing...
- Oh, don't worry about that.
He's your partner.
I get it.
- I do have to ask, though.
Why didn't you take the shot?
- I don't know.
I just froze.
I got a lot on my mind,
I guess.
- Yeah.
Yeah, I know.
I've noticed.
I don't wanna push you.
If you don't want to talk about
it, we don't have to.
But the stories that you told
about your father...
[solemn music]
♪
- Yeah.
Those were true.
He wasn't like that
all the time.
Sometimes he was funny.
And sweet.
It's a lot more complicated
than people think.
- Come over here.
.
[dramatic music]
♪
[wolf howling]