How we doing, Pops?
You know, like I got a week to figure out
the hell I'm gonna do with my days.
30 years, and my only hobby was bitching about my job.
Ah, that's the cop way.
- You'll figure it out. - Yeah.
Gentlemen.
- Bob! - Rizzy!
- Old man. - Hey, Bob.
You remember my boy, Adam.
With scruff on his face, I don't.
Hey, Duff.
We just wanted to stop by, see how you usually do it.
Yeah, we got these things down pretty good, I think.
Figure you don't need the whole place, right?
No, no. 15, 20 max.
Well, we'll get that area closed off,
set aside for you, put out some snacks.
Won't be too complicated.
Usually take a little deposit.
200 maybe?
- Seems fair. - Uh, yeah, yeah, hang on.
Hang on.
Dad, I got it.
Yeah?
You don't pay for your own retirement party.
Come on.
Bob Ruzek.
Finally putting you out to pasture.
Well, better than being taken behind the barn and shot, I guess.
That's right.
What does it say about the Chicago Police Department
that you turkeys serve up the best coffee in the building?
Nothing good, Sarge.
I saw the flyer downstairs about Disco Bob's party.
Yeah, this weekend. No obligation.
Are you nuts? I don't go to those things.
Years ago, when we were babies working at the 13th,
your dad would show up for his shift
reciting your stats from your game the night before.
"Adam went three for four last night
with a double and two RBIs."
Well, we should definitely keep doing that.
Adam went three for four last night
with a hoagie and two beers.
And a sacrifice pickle.
Heyo.
Something for your old man.
Thanks, boss. You didn't have to do that.
I know you had your issues with him over the years.
30 years of service to the city of Chicago
is 30 years of service-- end of story.
Appreciate it.
What are you hungry for for dinner?
Let's go to that place on Clybourn.
What do you call it? Platonic Pizza?
Platonic Pie.
Oh, 'cause that's so much snappier.
It's a skillset.
Swing by my dad's house quick.
All right.
I'll just run this inside,
and then we'll go pick up Makayla.
Okay?
Actually, you know what?
Why don't you come in, see the old man?
He'd be happy to see your face.
Come on.
- You sure? - Yeah, come on.
- Sure, sure? - Yeah.
Have you told him about...
All the times you broke my heart?
No. You're good.
Are you protecting me from his wrath?
No, I just figured if he was ever forced to make a choice,
he'd pick you over me.
I mean, that's the choice I would make.
Pops, I hope you're decent.
Coming in with the girl.
Dad?
Hey, Dad?
Bob?
Adam.
All right. I'm gonna call him.
Yeah.
All right. It's ringing.
What the hell is this?
Dad?
- More blood down here. - Yeah...
Dad!
That blood is fresh, Adam.
You got anything?
Uh, sort of.
I spoke to a neighbor.
She said she saw two men pull up to the back of the house.
White, possibly Hispanic. They entered.
Then they left about 20 minutes ago.
It's a start. Call it in.
What?
It's just, Kim, my dad, you know,
he's made some pretty crappy choices over the years.
I don't know what happened in here,
but there's a decent chance it was self-inflicted.
Maybe.
But you gotta call it in.
5021I
5021 Ida.
Go ahead, Ida.
I need you to roll a crime lab
to 221 North Oleander.
Possible home invasion, possible kidnapping.
Copy that. Crime lab en route.
What up, dog? You good?
I've been better.
I don't know what happened there, boys,
but it wasn't good, whatever it was.
Well, you know, whatever it is, we gonna figure it out.
We got you.
Appreciate it, fellas.
I told you to get that van out of here.
Copy, Sergeant.
All right. Everybody, listen to me.
The last thing Bob Ruzek needs
is his face on the evening news.
That's how people get hurt.
Send patrol away.
We're working this as a 99 Confidential.
Only OCD in the loop.
But that means this is all on us.
All right? Where are we?
Okay. We got a struggle inside the house.
There's blood in the kitchen
which leads to the backdoor.
Pretty clear my father left in a hurry
and it wasn't his idea to do so.
I mean, his car is here. The TV was on.
His keys, his wallet, service revolver,
his phone, which I just started going through.
Password was his badge number
'cause who would've thought of that?
Okay. Anything jump out?
No, it's all just normal stuff.
I mean, here I am texting him about the retirement party.
What?
Talk to me.
It says,
Tuesday, 6:13,
"You don't deliver, it's over."
It's a restricted number.
All right, any idea who might send something like that
to your old man?
No.
Tech said that the footprints
and the blood leading to the back door
were made by somebody wearing socks.
So if this is what it seems, somebody grabbed him.
Didn't even give him a chance to put his shoes on.
All right. Keep canvassing this block.
Find some cameras.
Scrape together enough to get a BOLO out on that car.
- Kim. - Yeah.
I want a full scrub of all of Bob Ruzek's cases,
top to bottom.
Something like this happened to one of us,
the first thing we'd think it's related to a case somehow.
- Right. - Revenge,
- somebody seeking information-- - Boss.
My pop spent the last 20 years directing traffic
at afternoon Sox games, not kicking in doors.
I mean, I don't think Kim's gonna find anything there.
Okay, he's still a police officer.
That man spent a lot of time on a lot of streets.
Do the work.
Now, I'm on it.
- Can I help you? - Gonna see Benny.
Hey. You can't go back there.
No. Nope.
- Nope. - Benny.
Adam.
Benny, we need to talk.
Everybody, out.
Adam, the hell is this?
There's no Adam here, Benny.
Not tonight.
There's just a cop up your ass.
- Where's my father, Benny? - What?
I know you texted him, told him to deliver.
- I didn't-- - Where is he, Benny?
- That wasn't me; I swear. - No, no, no, where is he?
- I--I don't-- - Benny.
Hey, hey. Did you hurt my dad?
No, no. I did not.
- Did you hurt my dad? - No, I did not.
Listen to me.
Now you just take a breath.
I will tell you exactly what happened,
and you are not gonna do anything bananas.
Deal?
Tell me what happened.
Your pops-- I am not gonna lie--was in trouble with me.
- Bad. - How bad?
Like real bad.
Truth is, you know it. I know it.
He's the worst gambler I ever knew.
Got into a hole and just kept digging deeper
until I finally cut him off.
Benny, just tell me how much.
80 grand.
80 grand?
Benny, how could you let it get that bad this time?
- I mean, if you said hey, I-- - Listen to me.
I did not lay a finger on your father.
And the reason is simple.
He paid. All of it.
What are you talking about?
- In cash. - No.
Walked in one night, dropped it,
walked out, I ain't seen him since.
- Yeah? When's this? - About a month ago.
Date's in the ledger book if you need it.
Sorry, Benny.
What, are you following me?
Yes. Yes.
Look, you were clearly lying to Voight
when you saw that text at your dad's house.
I wanted to make sure
you weren't doing something extracurricular,
just plain ol' stupid. Were you?
Yeah. That'd be fair to say.
And?
And, well, it turns out a few weeks ago,
my father paid down an 80 grand debt.
A few hours ago, he couldn't put down
a $200 deposit on a bar.
And now he's gone.
Okay. Okay.
You know how he got the 80 grand?
No, I don't.
I thought I knew what was going on.
I don't.
Hey. We're gonna figure it out.
Yeah.
It's the same restricted number.
It's a video.
- Hello, son. - Oh, my God.
I'm okay. I'm all right.
I just, um-- I'm in a bit of trouble here.
These guys--Los Tiranos--
I don't need to tell you who they are.
They got a problem.
A snitch.
Someone on the inside
that's giving them trouble.
So they need you-- I need you--
to find out who it is.
And then give them the name, okay?
Or I'm gone for good, son. I'm gone.
We'll be back in touch.
We got a Chicago cop missing 12 hours.
Tell me something good.
We looped in OCD?
We got trap-and-trace on Officer's Ruzek's phone,
but so far, nothing.
Okay. What's the latest on the scrub of his police work?
I'm into it, Sarge.
It's just not a lot of meat on the bone.
Okay, so, Sarge, this is the claim territory of Los Tiranos,
the Hispanic gang that's holding down Bob Ruzek.
So these guys are an umbrella gang,
- cartel-connected. - Okay.
They got hundreds of foot soldiers,
dozens of cliques, each one is a silo.
It's gonna take some time to put a face to this.
Right, so they occupy the Lower West Side,
the South Loop, Marshall Square,
but the heart of it happens right here in Pilsen.
So we got reason to believe
these guys know what they're talking about.
I mean, Los Tiranos was running unchecked for a long time,
but the last couple months,
they've taken some hits.
CPDs punched 'em in the face a few times.
Hit a couple of their stash houses
and a couple bank accounts.
We're thinking that there has to be an informant on the inside--
a snitch.
Just got the bloodwork back from the scene.
So some of the blood definitely belongs to Officer Ruzek.
But the good news is most of it belongs to someone else,
and we got a hit on CODIS.
This is Hector Alvaro Santiago,
date of birth 03/30/88.
He's in the gang database.
He's a known member of Los Tiranos.
He's got an LKA in Pilsen. 539 South Allport.
Nice work. Let's move.
Chicago PD!
Chicago PD. Hands up.
- You walk towards me. - What?
Hands in the air. Step towards me.
- No! - Get away from him.
Get up.
- No, no, no, no, no, no. - Where is Bob Ruzek?
- Who? - You know who--Bob Ruzek.
I don't know who that is.
Who else is in this house?
Hey. Where's Bob Ruzek?
I need you to hear me. Where is Bob Ruzek?
Tell me where he is.
Officer Bob Ruzek.
Your blood's all over his house.
We need to know why. Hey!
House is empty. He's not here.
Help him!
Don't you die on me.
Where's my dad?
Hector!
- Where's my father? - Adam.
No!
5021E
5021 Eddie.
Roll a crime lab and ambo to 539 South Allport.
Okay, Elena, you and Hector were together for a year.
That's a very long time, okay?
That's a long time.
But I need you to remember. I need you to think.
Do you ever remember Hector using the name Bob Ruzek?
You keep saying that name.
Who is that?
All right. Tell me this.
When's the last time you saw Hector before he got injured?
Yesterday morning.
It was a regular day.
Dropped him on my way to the clinic.
The clinic?
Arden Family Health. I'm a nurse.
Got home from work, and I found him bleeding.
Okay. You're a nurse.
And you didn't bring him to the hospital?
Help me understand that.
He told me it was going to be up to me to save his life or not.
I knew he was going to bleed out eventually.
Begged him to go to the hospital.
- He wouldn't go. - Elena.
You're a nurse. Your man's bleeding out,
and he won't go to the hospital.
That didn't strike you as odd?
It didn't bring up any questions in your mind?
Did you know that he was in a gang?
- What? - Yes.
Hector was in a gang.
That's why he didn't want to go to the hospital.
Because he knew that if he showed up at an ER
bleeding out, someone like him was gonna start
getting asked questions that he didn't wanna answer.
- You lie. - No, he lied.
Did you know anything about the man?
Can I get a sec?
- Did you ask any questions at all? - Adam.
Voight was right to do the scrub.
I tracked everything that your dad tried to access
in the computer database, every keystroke.
Something there.
Something bad.
Three days ago, at the end of his shift,
your dad logged in to the gang database
and accessed the list of documented members of Los Tiranos.
Your dad doesn't work with gangs.
He doesn't work major crimes.
There's no reason that he would need that information.
- Right. - But it doesn't end there.
Because once he has the names,
he uses them to pull the field reports
for the recent operations targeting the gang.
And?
And one of those reports mentions a CI,
goes by the codename Merlin.
All right, but he doesn't know this Merlin, right?
- He said in the video-- - Adam.
He doesn't know who he is,
but it's not for lack of trying.
He tried to get Merlin's real name.
But he's just...
He's a patrol cop, and he doesn't have security clearance.
All right. All right.
I'm just gonna take a look at this.
I wanna retrace his steps again.
Adam.
Time's up, son.
We gotta do this.
Or not.
- You have a minute? - Yeah.
They sent a second video.
They put a clock on it.
They want the name of the snitch that's giving them trouble,
and they want it by noon tomorrow.
So we work all night.
We'll do whatever we gotta do--
Boss, boss, there's more.
My father's been doing favors for this gang--
at least he's been trying.
I just retraced his steps.
He used the arrest database to find his way to the snitch,
codename Merlin, and then he tried
to find the snitch's real name.
Um, if that's true...
It's a complete betrayal of the badge, I know.
But, uh, just because he tried doesn't mean he succeeded.
Story of Disco Bob's life.
No, he thinks you can do what he couldn't--
figure out who this Merlin is.
Well, he's not wrong.
I mean, we have higher clearance than Patrol.
I already got past the wall that he ran into.
Merlin works for a DA task force
that investigates cartels including Los Tiranos.
I mean, this CI, he's indexed in over 30 cases.
He is very good at what he does, whoever he is.
Okay, so...
Say you're me, right?
What happens next?
We find Merlin's real name. We make the trade.
So we make the trade.
Your old man walks out alive.
I mean, that's-- that's the hope, right?
But Merlin's dead.
That's for sure.
We're talking about trading one life for another.
But one life is Merlin, who's a gang member.
He's a rat.
Boss, you don't get to the position that Merlin's in
by living some clean life.
Adam.
You don't get to the position your father's in
by leading a clean life.
Do you?
No, sir.
But he's my father.
I would make the same trade for you every time.
I'm gonna go to the task force.
You stay out of this part.
- I'm taking Hailey. - All right.
Adam, listen to me.
I'm gonna get that name
because it's our best chance to find your father
on our own before the deadline
without making that trade.
You understand?
We're not in the business of signing execution papers.
So these pricks want Merlin's name.
Yeah, if we don't give it to 'em, they're gonna kill him--
the Chicago cop--tomorrow.
Well, we got some real problems here.
Who's that?
That's Merlin.
What?
Now she climbs the Tiranos ladder, but she works for us.
She's a gold mine.
She gets killed, that's two years of work up in smoke.
We're talking cartel-connected gangs from here to St. Louis.
Look--we don't want that any more than you do.
But a cop's life's on the line here,
and we're hoping that you can meet us in the middle.
How about instead of Merlin's name,
you give us someone else's?
Who?
The person who wants Merlin dead.
Give us that name.
Then we'll use that information to find Bob Ruzek.
We'll bring him in and protect your source.
Merlin's work has made one man's life a living hell.
His name is Lucas Barela.
Date of birth: 11/08/71.
Barela's the juice man of the gang.
His arm of the business is to launder money
by issuing cash loans to desperate people
at high interest rates.
Like cops with gambling issues.
Yeah. Like that.
Okay, remember, Lucas Barela is also a desperate man.
His life's at stake here too.
Yeah, so it was Barela's money houses that were hit by the cops,
Barela's bank accounts that were frozen.
We can thank Merlin for that.
So the task force has wiretaps up,
and we know that Barela's bosses have given him one more chance
to get his house in order, or he's dead.
Sarge, the grand jury transcripts you had me pull for the scrub.
- The guy who died, Hector Santiago... - Right.
His cousin is Barela. Also, his muscle. They were tight.
Hold on.
Santiago's girlfriend told me
she used to drop him off at some warehouse for work
on her way to, uh, Arden Family Health.
Arden Family Health.
Arden Family Health is on Bishop and 21st in Pilsen.
So why don't we run all the warehouses
between the clinic and Santiago's house?
Yeah. 19th and Aberdeen.
Closed three years ago.
Barela liquidated.
Got it. Barela's parents owned it before it went under.
The name's still on the deed.
Strap up. Go hit it.
All right, Coop, get 'em high.
Get 'em high.
Right there.
There you go.
I got you there. You got me here.
Copy.
We're in.
Dad?
I found him alive. Roll an ambo. Park it a block away.
Unknown number of offenders in the building.
Copy that.
Dad?
Here. Let's get you warm.
Here you go. Let's get you warm.
You're all right.
I knew it. I knew you'd come.
Keep your voice down.
- You're all right. - Yeah. All right.
Just be quiet.
How many are there? How many are there?
I don't know. I don't know.
Is it Barela--is that the one that did this to you?
I'm not sure.
They didn't use names.
- You okay to move? - Yeah, I think so.
Get up. Let's go home.
Okay.
I got you.
Go ahead. I got you.
- I got movement, lower level. - Copy.
Lucas Barela, don't move!
He's running west through the building--cover those exits.
Copy. We're coming around!
Stop!
All right, all right. Move with me.
Let's go wide. Go wide.
We got motion right here.
Chicago PD! Barela, stop!
- Out of the way! - Come on, move.
- Out of the way! - Stop!
- Come on, keep it moving. - Get out of the car.
Get out of here. Get out the way!
Move. Help her!
Help her! Help her!
Barela going down 19th in a civilian vehicle!
- Hey, Joy. - Adam, hey.
How's he doing?
Two broken ribs, some hypothermia.
He went through hell, but he'll be fine.
All right. That's good.
He okay to put on some real clothes?
Mm, close enough. He'll be out of here soon.
Thank you, Joy.
Officer.
Pa.
Ah, there he is.
Thanks, son.
All right, Pops.
Truth time.
You gotta tell me everything so we can find Lucas Barela.
Oh, the guy who took me?
Yeah.
Lu--Lucas? Wh--
- What'd you say? Barela? - Stop what you're doing.
You know exactly who he is.
You arrested him 25 years ago.
He got a reduced sentence in exchange for information.
He worked for you.
So you know exactly who Lucas Barela is, Dad.
Talk to me.
You're good, kid.
Back then, I was the guy in charge.
Barela was a street rat.
And over the years, you know, things changed.
I stayed right where I was,
but Barela, he climbed to the top.
And that's how paid off your debt with Benny.
You went to Barela, right?
Yeah.
- 10% a week. - Oh, my God.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You couldn't pay that off in a million years.
- What are you thinking? - I know.
He knew--he knew when he gave me the loan.
He knew when I couldn't pay him back,
he had me over a barrel.
He had a cop over a barrel.
That's worth more than--
more than any money.
So that's when he, uh--
he demanded that I, um,
find out the name of the snitch.
- And I-- - Came up short. I know.
So time was up.
And, uh, Barela and his guy...
- Hector Santiago. - Yeah.
They came to the house.
I fought like hell.
I probably hurt that Santiago pretty bad too,
but I--I couldn't get to my piece.
And...
Barela put a gun to my head.
Then--
and then that was-- that was it for me. I...
He was ready, and I...
And what, Dad?
I wasn't.
And I broke.
I did the only thing I could think of
to save my life-- I sold out my own son.
I told him that you were a cop, that you were a real cop,
that you were a better cop than I ever was,
and that you could find the name of that snitch.
I should've just taken the bullet.
I need to find Barela.
Now.
No.
What, Dad? What? No.
The man almost killed you.
What the hell are you talking about?
- You gotta let him walk. - I'm not letting him walk.
Why--why would you even say that, man?
Adam,
I've been borrowing money from him for years--
drug money.
And then trying to get the name of the informant?
You bring Barela in, that all comes out.
That's the end of me.
They'll bring charges. That'll be the end of my pension.
Our name will be destroyed.
Our name.
How is he?
Yeah. He'll be fine.
It's all right. Leave it open.
Sarge, um,
you know, if we find Barela and we bring him in,
what would really be gained by that?
Is that a real question?
It's just...
All this crap comes out, it's ugly.
My father's career, his pension.
Adam.
You gotta stop covering for him.
You gotta start taking care of you.
I am.
The name Ruzek's gonna stain this department,
and I gotta lug that around long after my dad is gone.
All the people that matter,
they know who you are.
I'm asking.
The answer's no.
We've been down this road before
with your old man, haven't we?
- Done things we had to do. - Yeah, I know.
And this is how he repays the favor?
Gets in bed with a new drug dealer.
Now you want me to just walk away?
We gave it a shot? We're moving on?
Olinsky told me my dad and you had beef.
He was a dog cop!
You think I'm not hearing you because of some beef
I had with your old man 20 years ago?
No.
Let me tell you something.
You do this to a cop--
put a gun to his head, pull him from his home--
you're not doing that to Disco Bob;
you're doing it to the Chicago Police.
You understand?
And we--we're gonna find Lucas Barela.
You can participate or not.
And I will be watching to see what you choose.
All right. What did we hear from our CIs?
Buttoned up pretty tight, Sarge.
So we're nowhere.
Okay. The vehicle Barela stole?
Patrol found it. Torched.
Right. Safehouses, stash houses.
Barela's on the run. He's gotta be somewhere.
We've gone through every inch of intel.
- So we're nowhere. - Maybe not, Sarge.
This is the last piece from the scrub I did
- on Bob Ruzek's activity. - Okay.
This is the data from the chip from his squad car.
Now every single one of his patrol stops
can be justified as an on-duty call--
all except for this one.
2451 South May. It's in Pilsen.
- In the heart of Los Tiranos. - Exactly.
Bob Ruzek stopped there five times.
Never called it in. Always off the books.
Hold on, you guys. 2451 South May.
We've got Barela in that stolen civilian car on a traffic cam,
and he was a block away from there headed in that direction.
Let's move.
The cases we bent the rules on over the years.
The crooks we sent into the wind
because bringing 'em in was more trouble than it was worth,
but this one, we cling to like a dog on a bone.
The name Ruzek's gonna be a joke from here on out.
My dad's a jackass, but he's right about one thing.
Everybody'd be better off if Lucas Barela just...
went away.
We're four minutes out.
Move on the house but quiet till we're all there.
All right. Here we go.
On scene.
- I'll take the back. - Wait.
Hey. Back inside.
Get back inside now.
Adam!
What did you do?
5021I
5021 Ida.
Shots fired by the police. One offender down.
Roll the crime lab to our location.
Copy.
Street Deputy and IRT are on their way
to open the investigation.
All right. Good.
You wanna talk it through?
Yeah, sure.
Went to apprehend Barela.
He reached for his piece, so I put him down.
Shot three times, hit him three times.
Twice in the back.
It was a good shoot, boss.
IRT and COPA want to talk to me
about your state of mind.
I know I didn't see the shooting,
but they want my version.
Well, you didn't see it.
So what is there to say?
Right.
- It was a good shoot. - I hope so.
Yeah. What does that mean?
It means that I'm worried about you, okay?
I'm worried.
I have seen you going
through some stuff lately, and now this--
Kim, stop dancing around with me.
Say to me what you're really thinking.
Say it.
They got a video of the shoot.
Security camera, house next door.
Play it.
What's he saying to you?
He told me he knew who I was.
I wouldn't bring him in
because my father already promised to let him go,
and he'd ruin my father's career.
And that I was a little bitch like my old man.
I told him he was wrong.
He reached for his gun.
He was moving fast, and the first shot spun him around.
Second and third shots went through his back.
Good shoot.
That went down exactly like you said,
exactly as you reported to IRT.
- That's good work, Ruzek. - Thanks.
- Nice shoot. - Thanks.
Hey, Adam. How is he?
Oh, yeah. He's gonna be fine, Sarge.
He got out of the hospital yesterday, so.
- Thanks for asking, Sarge. - Yeah.
Hey, you know that stuff you said
about my old man coming into shift talking
about my little league games?
Yeah?
Total BS.
What?
Yeah. He made it up.
That was his shtick.
Couldn't be the real police.
Couldn't be the first guy through the door
because he was a family man.
Even if it hurt his career, he had to be home for dinner
and in the stands for my games.
He made it all up.
He was at the bar making bad bets.
I knew you weren't that good a hitter.
- Thanks, Sarge. - Yep.
Taking that over to the Deputy Supe?
Yeah, you know. Case like this, I gotta.
Yeah.
All it says is the truth.
Officer Ruzek was abducted
because the offender was under the mistaken belief
he knew the identity of a CI.
Anything else,
that'll die with Lucas Barela.
Boss.
I don't know what to say.
That's the best news I've had all day.
You must be damn proud, Adam.
Hell of a legacy to carry on.
Sure is.
Thanks, Duff.
We need to clear the air.
All right.
- Adam-- - When you ran up on me
after I shot Barela,
you could've asked me if I was okay,
if I was hurt-- that's not what you did.
- Adam, listen. - You said, "What did you do?"
Yeah, I did.
"What did you do?"
Kim,
one of the many reasons that I fell in love with you
is that I felt like you believed in me.
Like you believed in me
in a way that nobody in my entire life has.
I did.
- Even me. - I do.
I'm not so sure.
You have to see how what I said made sense in the moment.
You have to see that.
I don't.
After everything that you and I have been through,
there just should have been something that...
Held you back from the edge of assumption.
Some sort of guardrail
that kept you from going over that ledge.
I mean, if this situation is reversed--
I'm you; you're me--
and I run up on you.
You're standing over Barela holding the gun.
If I got close to the ledge, fine--I wouldn't go over.
Not ever.
I just...
'Cause I know your heart.
And I know that there's not a world in which
you'd kill a man in cold blood,
that you'd shoot him in the back as he's running away.
For what--revenge? For your family name?
Come on.
That's what you meant
when you said, "What did you do?"
And in that moment,
I'd have thought you'd know my heart.
You're supposed to know.
I do know your heart. I do.
And I am sorry.
- Just-- - I--
Thanks for stopping by.