Angela Nelson, she was
married to Marcus West.
The addict who got killed at County?
Jay still blames himself for that.
So Jay went to see Angela yesterday.
Hello?
[WOOD POPS]
We find her, we find Jay.
Marcus didn't kill those two kids.
- What?
- I'm a cop, I arrested him.
You deserve to die.
[GRUNTING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
BOTH: [GROANING]
[GUNSHOT FIRES]
[GASPING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
10-1. 10-1, officer down.
Jay, stay with me. Stay with me, Jay.
His vitals are dropping.
He's losing too much blood.
Set up an Officer Down detail to Med.
Get those cars here now.
[GASPS]
♪ ♪
[PANTING]
- You got it, doc.
- Hang in there, Jay.
Hey, move it. Clear out.
Clear. Come on.
♪ ♪
Hold on.
Let's move now.
Hey, hey. I need this escort clean.
You shut down every street along the way.
Go.
This is 5021. I need all available.
Notify Med.
We have a GSW to the chest en route.
He's one of our own.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
Here you go.
Oh, excuse me.
Hey, everybody.
I just talked to Dr. Marcel.
He said the bullet grazed an artery.
They're still trying to repair it.
Will?
Is he gonna be okay?
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
He's lost a lot of blood.
I got an update on Angela Nelson.
- Okay.
- Doctors removed the bullet.
She's gonna be fine.
Where is she?
Angela Nelson.
You're being charged
with the attempted murder
of a Chicago police officer.
He got what he deserved.
What did you say?
It's karma for what he did.
I don't know much about karma,
but I do know if Jay Halstead dies,
you're gonna wish you never lived.
You can't silence me.
People are gonna know what
that cop did to my husband.
This whole damn city's gonna know.
She doesn't talk to anybody.
You understand?
Nobody.
Nobody in or out, including you.
[PHONE BUZZES]
We need a plan to put someone
on the door we can trust.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
Crawford.
Hank, I'm sorry to pull you
away from your man, Halstead.
Our man.
How's he doing?
He's still in surgery,
so we don't know, sir.
- It's a hell of a thing.
- Mm-hmm.
I feel terrible, and
obviously, I wouldn't pull you
- away unless it was important.
- Mm.
Okay, so evidence suggests
a home invasion.
The whole house was tossed.
Multiple offenders,
they were here for a while.
We believe they took jewels
and valuables.
But...
The owner caught nine bullets
in his chest and torso.
And he took them
from a freaking machine gun.
Well, it sounds like
a straightforward robbery-homicide.
All due respect,
why did you call Intelligence?
Because of those casings.
Now, those come from
an MK-18 assault rifle.
Are you familiar?
I know you got to be
in the Army to have one.
That's right.
And a military train was robbed
at the rail yard last month,
and now we got 50 MK-18s on the streets.
We've already had
eight homicides on these guns.
And this was gang on gang, but
now look where you're standing.
This threat has moved to the Gold Coast.
Oh, so you mean now
white people are dying.
No, Hank, these weapons pose
a threat to all civilians,
black, white, and brown.
And look, I need some heavy hands
to find out who is moving these
guns before more bodies drop.
Okay?
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Okay. Any witnesses?
Yeah, a neighbor saw two offenders
sneaking out the back.
The scene is fresh. It's all yours.
Superintendent? Anybody notify the wife?
We've been calling, have not
been able to get ahold of her.
Okay. Forced entry?
No, alarm company registered entry
through the garage, which is...
You two gentlemen? You're with me.
Copy that.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
So the murder weapon used
in the home invasion
was an MK-18.
Soldiers call it the street sweeper.
It's fully automatic.
It can rake an entire city
block in about 30 seconds.
ATF, they ran into a dead end
on the train robbery.
Their working theory is that
a high ranking gang member's
the one selling the guns.
- Anything on the victim?
- Yeah.
Kirby Reed. Successful investment banker.
His wife had no idea who would do this.
She said they stole jewels, cash,
and a vintage collection
of Rolex watches.
Yeah, a neighbor saw
two African Americans
run toward a blue car, possibly a Nissan.
So they were for sure
not from the neighborhood.
All right.
Kev, talk to Robbery
about home invasion crews.
You two, get an alert to pawn shops,
anyone moving vintage Rolex watches.
Vanessa, cast a wider net
on that blue Nissan.
Hey, Kim. Kim, Kim, hey.
Last night, your message,
you said it was important.
- What's going on?
- Yeah, let's talk tonight.
No, no, no. Come on, you know me.
It'll torture me all day.
Just talk to me.
- Is everything all right?
- Everything's fine.
Did you make a decision or something?
Yes. I'm having the baby.
♪ ♪
Hey. We got some photos from CPIC.
We should go.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
- How are you?
- I'm all right.
Yeah? I got you some
gyro from Greek Islands.
- I thought you might be hungry.
- That's really sweet of you.
Thanks.
And I got you some clean
clothes from the apartment.
Thank you.
Have we heard anything about Jay?
No.
He's gonna freak out when he wakes up.
The man hates needles.
[STIRRING MUSIC]
I can't figure him out.
He's the first one through the door,
a war vet.
And he'd rather take a bullet
than get the flu shot.
[SCOFFS]
Hailey, I know how hard
this must be for you.
It's always hard when
something like this happens.
It's hard because you love him.
Of course I love him. He's my partner.
[PHONE BUZZES]
[PHONE CHIMES]
Ruzek got a lead on the home invasion.
Yeah, uh, I'm gonna stay.
- Okay.
- Okay, thanks.
All right, so CPIC conducted
a security camera grid
within a one mile radius
of the home invasion.
They ID'd the getaway vehicle.
It's a blue Nissan
registered to Kristy Pierce.
Kristy works at this bar
over here, Mr. D's.
Just spotted the Nissan parked
in the back lot.
Kristy's got a minor
rap sheet, all gang related.
According to Robbery-Burglary,
this joint is a hustler's
paradise for stolen jewels.
But specifically, Rolex watches.
I think we can wait on picking up Kristy.
Let's find out how many players
are involved first.
Kev, you and Rojas go undercover.
Shop for Rolexes.
Hey, just remember,
people we're dealing with
got MK-18 assault rifles.
You get a bad beat, you abort.
Are we clear?
Copy.
- You good?
- Yeah.
[SENSUAL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Guy at the bar. Black jacket.
There's a man who knows his ice.
Yeah, and he don't hide it.
What can I get for you guys?
We're thinking about
two Hennessys on the rocks
if that's okay.
And his jeweler's name.
I mean, that watch would look
way better on my man.
You help me out?
I can get the Hennessy,
but as far as the watches,
you're on your own.
- It's not my business.
- We understand that.
Two limes for the Hennessys, please.
- All right.
- Thank you.
- 'Sup, baby?
- You know not to call me baby.
Hey, why you gotta be like that?
Come on, Trey. I'm try...
- Hey.
- Yo, come on.
I'm trying to go make these drinks.
- Can you let go of me?
- Why are you making a scene?
Why are you holding me?
Relax, it doesn't have to be like that.
Hey, get off.
[TENSE MUSIC]
Stay off it, punk!
[GLASS SHATTERS]
♪ ♪
- Hey!
- Stop!
BOTH: Break it up, break it up!
[GRUNTING]
Chill!
I'm telling you, careful.
Hey, I got this one.
Get off me, man. Get off me.
What the hell are you doing here?
I be asking you the same thing, man.
Who is this kid?
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
He's my brother.
Jordan, the hell are you
doing in Chicago?
You're supposed to be
on a road trip to Houston.
- I'm visiting friends.
- Nobody told me.
I knew you wouldn't approve.
Because you're not safe here
to be in the city, Jordan.
We're calling Auntie right now.
- Your ass is going back to Texas...
- No, no, no, no. I'm not.
You were the one who always
told me to create my own lane.
Stand ten toes down, right?
That's exactly what I'm doing.
We can't talk about this here.
There ain't even nothing to talk about.
Man, I'm going back to see my friends.
Nah, you don't got
no damn friends in there.
I'm working, Jordan,
which means ain't nothing
going on in there but trouble.
Is that what you're in town for?
No,
Officer.
[SIRENS BLARING]
Yeah.
It's time to go, okay? Get out of here.
Go.
Hey.
Voight wants us to pick up Kristy
and head back to the District.
Like I already said,
I don't want to press charges
against anybody,
so can I just go?
Look, we don't care
about that bar fight either.
You're here 'cause your car was
used in a home invasion robbery
in the Gold Coast yesterday.
The owner was murdered.
Whoa, hold on.
I-I never go to Gold Coast.
Oh, yeah?
Your blue Nissan was the getaway vehicle.
Nah, it can't be true.
Kristy.
You're looking at
felony murder, you understand?
Look, I can tell by your priors
you've been riding with gangs.
So you probably think there's loyalty,
but that's only for the boys.
First sign of trouble, they
throw the girls under the bus.
MOB, "money over bitches."
Now do you really want to take the fall
for one of these bastards?
[EERIE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I loaned the car to my cousin.
Okay, who's your cousin?
- Mitchell Adams.
- Good.
Were you with him yesterday?
No, I was at my sister's all day.
It's the honest to God truth,
so can I go?
[SCOFFS]
Yeah, if your alibi checks out.
Until then, you're staying in lockup.
One more thing.
Why was Trey Woodson
hassling you at the bar?
He's my ex-boyfriend.
He just hasn't accepted
the fact that it's over.
When were you gonna tell me about Jordan?
First time I've seen
my brother in a year, Sergeant.
He's fighting gang bangers
from Englewood.
I'm still processing the situation.
I wasn't even thinking.
All right. I get that.
It's still not safe for him here.
- And if it gets out...
- It won't.
Okay?
Listen, he testified in front
of a secret grand jury.
The killer he testified against
is being held in a cell
23 hours a day, no contact
with the outside world.
I made sure of that.
There's practically nobody left
out on the streets
who even knows what he did.
Sarge, it only takes one person.
Kev, you're a lot older than Jordan.
You've always been more
like a father than a brother.
Sooner or later,
the son breaks from the father
to make his own mark.
I just wish it wasn't this soon.
Mm-hmm.
You don't get to choose.
Sarge? We got something.
Come on.
I spoke to the crime lab.
Kristy's car tested positive
for gunshot residue.
It's got her prints and her cousin's.
Meet Mitchell Adams. Nice long rap sheet.
Just did a two year stint
for aggravated robbery.
And we're sure Kristy's not involved too?
Yeah, her alibi is solid.
I got three witnesses that put
her at her sister's house at
the time of the home invasion.
Okay, we got an address
on this Mitchell Adams?
Nothing since he got out of Stateville.
Then we pull out all the stops.
I want to know where this
prick, Mitchell, is staying.
I've got news about Jay.
How are you feeling?
Like I was asleep for a year.
You needed a little rest.
Hailey?
- You know I hate hospitals.
- I do.
You got to get me out of here.
It's not optional, no.
[SHUFFLING]
- Hey.
How's the shoulder?
It feels like I'll be flying
a little crooked for a while.
I went and talked to Will,
and he said no structural
damage, so you got lucky.
I guess you could call it that.
How's Angela doing?
She's under arrest.
Sarge, is there anything
we can do for her?
Jay, she tried to kill you.
Okay, she's getting charged.
Full freight.
She knows the truth.
And what happened to Marcus,
that's on us.
[SHUFFLING]
I'm sorry, we need to run
some tests on our patient.
Just worry about getting
better, that's all, okay?
[PATTING]
- Hailey?
- Yeah.
[PHONE CHIMES]
What do you think?
I think Jay's right.
This Angela thing's a ticking time bomb.
We need to take care of it.
That was Burgess.
They got an address
on the home invasion crew.
Look, you run point on that,
I'm gonna put an end to this thing.
I asked for a lawyer.
I heard that.
I have the right to tell my story.
You do.
You should understand that
if you exercise that right,
you're gonna be charged
with attempted murder
of a police officer.
And acting as an accomplice in a drug rip
where someone got killed.
That means you'll be looking
at your son through prison bars
for the next 20 years.
You gotta ask yourself...
[SOBBING SOFTLY]
How bad do you want to be right?
[SOMBER MUSIC]
You took my husband away from me.
He wasn't perfect,
but he was trying his best.
And now my son doesn't have a father.
That's why he needs his mother.
I'm not sure I understand
what you're saying.
Here's what.
Understand...
It's a one-time offer.
You decide to tell your story
some time down the line,
I'll find you and I'll bury you.
Yes?
Hi, I'm with Catholic Charities.
Mm-hmm?
I need you to do exactly as I say.
Everyone, I'm with Chicago Police.
I need you to get under the table now.
I know you're scared.
Let's do this calmly
and quickly, all right? Let's go.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Chicago PD. Let me see those hands.
I'm good, I'm good.
You're clear, you're clear, you're clear.
Turn around, Mitchell,
put your hands on the wall.
- I'm good over here.
- All right, let's move.
Gun!
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
A fighter down. You guys okay?
- BOTH: Yeah.
- Kim, call out.
Are you okay?
Call out.
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
Yeah, I'm good.
We're all good.
We recovered the
stolen Rolexes at your place,
along with the weapon used
to commit the murder.
But honestly, Mitchell,
I can't figure out
how you could have made this
any easier for us.
I mean, you got any other colors
you want to add to this picture?
It was an accident.
[SCOFFS] An accident?
You accidentally shot
Kirby Reed nine times.
I didn't shoot him. My associate did.
The associate that died at the duplex?
Yeah.
Right.
Look, dude came home
while we were in the house.
We were just gonna put him in the closet,
- but he tried to be a hero.
- Okay.
He grabbed the gun, and...
bam, bam, bam, bam, bam!
- That thing just exploded.
- Hmm.
All right, look, Mitchell.
There's a man dead, and there's
no way to make that right.
No way.
There is still one good thing you can do.
♪ ♪
Now, where'd you get the MK-18?
What's in it for me?
You give us who sold you the gun,
and I'll see what I can do.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I want it in writing.
Mitchell said he bought the MK-18s
from this guy right here.
Trey Woodson, 22 years old.
He's the cat that got into it
with my brother.
One and the same.
And he's got a history of violence.
Grand theft auto,
assault with a deadly weapon.
He cut off the nose of a rival
banger with a straight razor.
Spent four years in Juvie, got out,
and he's been clean ever since.
Yeah, now Woodson
has a store in Englewood
with his own clothing line, "Trey Lit."
Okay.
His landlord also happens
to be his business partner,
Darius Walker.
Trey Woodson. I knew I knew that name.
When I was undercover on Darius Walker,
that name came up a lot.
Yeah, well, if Darius is
that close with Trey,
then Darius knows Trey's dealing guns.
Hey, Kevin, your brother's downstairs.
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[OVERLAPPING CHATTER]
What are you doing here, Jordan?
I'm waiting for Kristy to be released.
The hell you waiting on her for?
[SCOFFS]
Look, she's my girl, bro.
[EXHALES]
That's why you came back.
Nah, that's not
the only reason, but yeah.
I wanted to see her.
You know Trey Woodson is her ex?
I know that.
Which means that she's
a part of that world.
'Cause he's a problem,
which makes her a problem.
Look, I can handle it, all right?
What can you handle?
And why would you even put
yourself in that position?
Listen, I didn't come here
for advice, all right?
Jordan?
Come on. Let's go.
Sergeant Voight.
You always choose exotic,
new places for us to meet.
It's almost like we're dating.
Yeah, well, we're
in a relationship, all right.
Given the information I got, though,
I think it might be coming to an end.
I wish I could say I was heartbroken.
Yeah, you will be.
You know, I look the other way
for a lot of your drug activity.
That's the price
of the information you provide.
But guns are a red line,
Darius, and you crossed it.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
There's MK-18s being sold on the streets,
- military assault rifles.
- Yeah, I heard
about those guns, but I
don't know who's running them.
I got a witness who's willing
to testify he bought an MK-18
from Trey Woodson,
who works directly under you.
Get out of here. Who is your witness?
- He's credible.
- He's wrong.
- Mm-hmm.
- Trey is an artist.
And he's legit, and he would
never go behind my back.
Darius, you may want to believe that,
but I got a witness who says otherwise.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- I'll look into it.
- Damn right, you will.
You got a witness.
[CHUCKLES]
All right, we got Trey Woodson in pocket.
Black SUV, plates match.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
What's up, Darius, I didn't
know you was coming through.
What's up, Black? [LAUGHS]
- Good to see you, man.
- You too, man.
Yeah.
You know what, man,
you're like a son to me.
And I always
support your artistic endeavors.
Mm-hmm, that you do. I'm grateful.
And in return for that support,
you stay out of the game.
That's the understanding
- we had, right?
- 100%, yeah.
So why am I hearing that
you're selling military assault
rifles in my neighborhood?
Behind my back?
Now, who told you that?
You know what? People just gossiping.
Everybody jealous of what I got going on.
Yo.
Trey.
We always talk about...
Accountability, right?
You're selling guns?
Yeah.
Yeah, I am.
I'm sorry, man.
Look, Darius,
I'm just trying to diversify
like you taught me.
You're the person that said
I got to create my own lane.
I got to learn to stand
on my own two feet.
I got to be strong, right?
It's no way this thing
is coming back to you or me.
Then why are we having this conversation?
Hmm?
I just needed a little bit
of cash to market my brand.
Come on, Darius.
Get him to say where the guns are.
Look, man, I ain't mean no disrespect.
Hey.
You just did what you thought you had to.
Damn right.
So what's up? We good?
Yeah. Yeah, we're all good, all good.
What's the matter with you?
Why'd you cut it off?
I did what you asked.
You got what you needed.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
You were supposed to get Trey
to tell us where the guns are.
I know what I was supposed to do.
All the young men want
to make it on the streets.
And the streets are gonna kill them all.
Darius, I understand
how you feel about Trey.
He's selling those guns.
You got to set up that buy.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I will not be there when you bury him.
All right, there's no sign
of this Trey Woodson.
You said the meet was at 6:00.
It's almost 7:00.
We sure this is happening?
Darius confirmed the meet
with Trey, so we wait.
All right.
[ENGINE REVVING]
Beige pickup coming your way.
Yeah, we got eyes.
[MELANCHOLIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
All right, nobody moves
until we see the guns.
On my order.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where's Trey?
You got the money?
We don't know you.
Trey wanted me to make sure you're legit.
Yeah, we're legit, all right.
50K. It's all there.
You got something for us?
- Whoa, hey.
- Cell phone.
[OMINOUS MUSIC]
♪ ♪
He's not answering.
All right, well,
maybe you just take us to him.
Nah, it don't work like that.
You're just gonna walk away from 50K?
Nah, I'ma drive.
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
Boss, what do you want to do?
Do you want to take this guy?
It's your call.
Take his ass now.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Show me your damn hands!
Cover me, Rojas!
Get over here!
- [YELLS]
- Got his gun?
- Yeah, we're good.
- You broke my damn arm!
Yeah, we're just getting started, buddy.
Stand down, stand down, stand down.
I got him. Come on, get your ass up.
- [GROANS]
- Get up!
- [PANTING]
- Hey, listen to me.
You got five seconds
to tell me where Trey is.
Ain't telling you nothing, man.
You ain't got nothing on me, man.
Didn't he ask you something?
[SCREAMS] All right.
- Huh?
- All right, all right.
He keeps a crib above
his warehouse over on Racine.
[PANTING AND GROANING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Chicago PD.
Body.
Ruze, how we looking?
Clear.
Sarge, we got a body.
It's Trey Woodson.
Patrol responded to a shots
fired call on this block
earlier in the afternoon,
but they came up empty.
All right, canvass for witnesses
and check for surveillance.
There's 45 rifles here.
All right, notify ATF.
Let's get them back
- to the military.
- Copy.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
I know what I'm feeling ain't right.
Part of me is relieved.
- I get it, Kev.
- Burgess?
Collin, over here.
I want the whole room printed, okay?
Got it.
- Kev?
- Yeah?
I talked to a patrol officer downstairs.
They pulled security footage
from across the alley.
We got a clear view of the shooter.
It ain't good.
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
♪ ♪
That's 4:20 this afternoon.
You can see the gun clear as day, man.
Kev, you know I got your back.
How do you want to play this?
You just tell me.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I don't know.
What the hell are you doing here?
Me and you outside, right now.
- What happened?
- What are you talking about?
Don't play with me, Jordan.
I don't got time for it.
What the hell happened?
I don't know what you want from me, man.
Trey Woodson got shot to death,
and you got caught
on surveillance cameras
leaving his warehouse
with a gun in your hand.
♪ ♪
Listen.
I didn't shoot him.
The gun was in your hand, Jordan.
Look, I was trying to get rid of the gun.
- I didn't shoot him.
- Then who shot him?
- No, no, no.
- Jordan.
- No, no, no, no.
- Jordan, look at me.
- No...
- Jordan.
- Was it Kristy?
- Yeah.
Look, I don't know what happened.
But she needed me.
The gun was in the apartment,
and I went up there,
and I cleaned the place up.
I wiped everything down,
I cleaned all the fingerprints.
I even went out back
so nobody could see me.
Well, that was the only place
there was a camera, dumb-ass.
[SIGHS]
So what did you do with the gun?
I threw it in the river.
I didn't know what else
to do with it, man.
Okay.
[SNIFFLES] Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Listen to me.
You are gonna go home.
You're gonna stay the hell away from her,
and you're gonna keep
your mouth shut, okay?
No, no, no, no.
I can't walk away from her.
Boy!
Stay the hell away from Kristy,
and keep your damn mouth shut.
♪ ♪
Do you understand me?
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Go.
All right, Kevin, did Jordan
give you any other details?
What her motives might have been?
No.
All he told me was that
Kristy killed Trey.
And he got rid of the gun.
Well, the good news is we
still got control of this case.
So we still got a chance
to tie things off, but...
We gotta move fast before
Homicide starts sniffing.
'Cause that happens...
He's not going down for murder.
Mm-hmm.
Well...
Then our best play is
to get her to confess.
You're wrong.
I did not kill Trey Woodson.
Kristy, we got your prints
all over his apartment.
That's because we used to date.
- Uh-huh.
- I already told you.
We contacted your cousin,
and Mitchell Adams told us
that you were supposed
to get a thousand dollars
for letting him use your car.
Is that right?
So you went to Trey's house
looking for money,
he didn't want to give it
to you, and you shot him.
I ain't gonna lie to you, Kristy.
We know everything.
Everything.
- We got a cooperating witness.
- What?
He ain't stupid.
Jordan?
He's ratting me out,
that's what you're saying?
What I'm saying is, it's obvious
that you've been playing him
like a punk this whole time.
You're still hooking up with Trey.
- That's not true.
- No?
It doesn't matter what's true
or not true, you understand?
What matters is what I can prove.
- What are you saying?
- What am I saying?
I'm saying I got you on this murder.
We know Trey owed you money.
We know you went to Trey's apartment.
And we know you told Jordan Atwater
you're the one that killed him.
The only thing we don't know
is your side of the story.
So if you tell us the truth,
we can help you.
[SOLEMN MUSIC]
♪ ♪
I went to Trey's to get that
thousand dollars he owed me.
He told me, "Get out."
I was so tired of the way he acted,
the way he treated me.
And then I saw his gun
sitting on the table, so...
I grabbed it.
Told him to pay me.
He just laughed.
Called me a whore.
And then I heard this loud...
Pop.
He was on the floor, bleeding.
- Hey.
I got your badge and
undercover phone from before.
Before it all went to hell?
Yeah. Here, let me give you a hand.
[GROANING]
Listen, um...
when you were in surgery,
no one knew what was gonna happen.
And it made me realize that...
I wanted to tell you something.
Okay.
[PHONE CHIMES]
It's Bobby. It's Angela's son.
What are you doing?
I want to make sure he's okay.
Hey, he's with his mom.
He's okay.
You just caught a bullet for this.
You gotta let this one go.
Just let it go.
All right.
What were you gonna say?
Never mind, I'm gonna
pull the car around.
I'll meet you in front.
[SOMBER MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Jordan?
Jordan, where are you at?
I need you to call me back, bro.
Love.