You're under arrest for
the murder of Kevin Bingham.
You can't save everyone, Hank.
Just make sure I get bail.
Alvin Olinsky has
dedicated his life
to the people of this city.
He dedicated his life to you.
It should be you in there.
Not him.
It has been a tough day.
But we still have jobs to do.
Chicago PD!
Okay, okay, okay...
You shot him in cold blood!
- I didn't see what happened.
- It doesn't matter!
We're talking about the guy
who killed Al here.
- Watch yourself, man.
- I'm right here!
All right, enough!
I'm sorry, Al.
Hank?
All right! All right!
Hank!
- Come on in.
Okay, okay. So.
You're alive.
I have been calling and calling.
We've got two DOAs in Grant Park.
My God, Hank! What the hell happened?
Can I take you to the hospital?
No, I'm okay.
Must look worse than it is.
I know you're going
through hell.
But if you, if you need help,
if you need someone to talk to...
- I'm good.
I'm good.
Yeah. Right.
I mean, I know I'm overreacting
because you look just great,
and I don't even know why the
idea popped into my little head.
Trudy.
Listen, I want you to do me a favor.
Just the next time
you... you talk to Meredith,
just...
you tell her I'm gonna
take care of the funeral, okay?
Okay.
Hey.
Sergeant Hank Voight. Intelligence.
What's going on?
It looks like there's
a hot batch out there.
We got five ODs so far this morning,
It's not even 1000.
Sergeant!
Get the hell off my crime scene.
Excuse me?
I called you three times.
- This about the De Leon shooting?
- Yes, it is.
Well, like I told
the review board,
it was a good shoot.
The problem is I have two
credible witnesses both say
the victim had his hands
raised up above his head.
You listen.
First of all,
that guy is not a victim.
He's an offender.
He ordered the hit on Alvin Olinsky.
And second...
that's not what happened.
Well, it's your word
against theirs.
Yours is selling at quite
a discount these days.
State's attorney is
circling this as a homicide.
Best you can do is call your FOP lawyer.
There's bad drugs on the street.
Kids are dying.
It's better I'm out here.
Well, I appreciate that
you want to help.
But the facts are the facts.
This got nothing to
do with facts.
Meaning what?
Meaning I think it's a good time
for you and your boss, Kelton,
to bury an old-school white
cop with a bad reputation.
You're wrong.
It's an absolutely fantastic time
to bury an old-school white cop
with a bad reputation.
But that's not what I'm doing.
I'm following the facts,
doing what's best for the department.
You are benched
until further notice, Sergeant.
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com.
What happened to
your face, boss?
Listen.
There is some bad dope out on the
street and we are gonna find it.
Fast.
Now, Antonio is gonna take the lead.
So get on the horn with CFD right away.
Get a list of all the ODs
the past two days,
the exact locations
the bodies were found.
Track down the 911 tapes, tox reports...
- I got it, Hank.
- I'm good.
Sarge, you want to
tell us what's going on?
Why aren't you involved?
The COPA thing. They're still
investigating the shooting.
Listen, I'm on the bench
until it's resolved.
Way to step up, bro.
Stay out of this, Adam.
Hey. Enough.
Now listen, everything is gonna be fine.
So stop talking,
and track down that bad dope.
Okay, let's get to work.
That's my son.
- That's my baby!
- I'm sorry...
- Let me go!
- Let me see my baby.
Ma'am.
It's okay, it's okay.
Same tox report for
all five DOAs.
Heroin cut with battery acid.
- Battery acid?
- Really?
That means it's intentional.
It means somebody's trying
to put bodies on the street.
Wait, so, is this business
or is this some sicko serial killer
out here just trying to kill people
with dope instead of bullets?
Well, all five ODs
are on the West Side between
Sacramento and California.
It's confined to one area,
which is a good thing.
What about the crime scenes?
Detectives found packets
at three out of five locations.
They all had the same logo A spider.
Yeah, well, maybe we
should call Voight,
see if he can at least point us
in the right direction.
No. We can't.
Hank's off the books until COPA's
done with the investigation.
Right, yeah, I know that, but
there's five people dead
and the clock's ticking, so...
Voight's not involved,
you understand?
He's been stripped.
It's violation to even talk
to him about any of this.
All right, talk to Narcotics.
See who the shot-callers
are and who's supplying
product with a spider logo.
All these kids copped somewhere.
Hopefully that somewhere is
connected to the same corner.
- I think they are. I ran the phones.
- All five trace back
to the same burner. Gotta be the dealer.
Pinged it, looks like he's doing business
on the corner of Sacramento and Fillmore.
Okay.
Here's what we're gonna do.
Dealer's name is Andre
Thompson, AKA Little Dre.
5'9", 135 pounds.
19 years old, two priors.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
I think I got him.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
He's working near the
southeast corner, you see that?
- Blue jacket.
- Yeah, yeah, I see him.
So this Antonio thing.
I don't want to talk about that.
- He didn't see the shooting, Ruzek.
- My God.
That doesn't matter.
- Yeah, it matters.
- No, it doesn't.
It doesn't matter. Not in
this situation, it doesn't.
Not when the dead guy got
exactly what he deserved.
We're talking about the guy
who ordered the hit on Al.
- I get it.
- No. Hey.
Antonio was right that.
Voight's future hinges on his word.
He had the opportunity to back
up his brother and he didn't.
And I don't know why.
But he didn't, and that's
the end of the story.
- End of your story, maybe.
- Hailey.
Look, what I'm saying is
it's not as simple as you make it sound.
Just keep that in mind.
Found his jab.
Where?
Deflated basketball.
It's in the shopping cart.
Jay, we're up with solid
eyes, ready to roll.
Copy that.
Yo, what's up, bro?
Looks like you in the wrong
neighborhood, homey.
No, Dre, I'm here
to see you, man.
We just talked on the phone.
I'm friends with Nick, from Evanston.
Long black hair?
No. No, it's light, like mine.
And it's shaved like a Marine.
Come on, man. Just help me out, bro.
How much you want?
Couple grams.
- I could do that.
- All right, cool.
Heyo, 5-0!
Chicago PD, hands on the hood.
Hands on the hood.
- Hey! Hands on the hood!
- Get on the hood!
Hold on, hold on.
I ain't got no dope.
I told you, I ain't got no dope!
- You keep your head down.
- You got the wrong man.
Jay Campbell from Winnetka.
What you doing on the West Side, Jay?
- I'm lost, man.
- I'm looking for directions.
- You good?
- Yeah.
Okay. Y'all good to go.
Sorry for the inconvenience.
That wasn't no inconvenience.
That was a violation of
my Constitutional rights.
People are dying because
of this dope you selling.
Now's a bad time to give me
lectures on the Constitution.
Kevin.
Andre's hot.
He should be.
Just lost thousands of dollars'
worth of someone else's drugs.
"Do I call my supplier
and admit I screwed up,
"or keep my mouth shut and pay the G note
out of my own pocket?"
And the answer is...
choice A.
Always is.
All right.
Okay, we got a phone number
and an address,
8660 West 54th Street.
- Let's go get this punk.
- Yeah.
We've got five dead
bodies, Jalen.
Make that six.
Patrol just found her in
an alley off Lexington.
Amy Moore, 19.
Last number she dialed,
same as the other five...
your boy, Andre.
Sorry, I don't know no Andre.
No? He's the skinny black dude
who works the corner of
Sacramento and Fillmore.
You know, the one you sell heroin to?
The one who just called
'cause he lost his jab.
Y'all must have me
confused with someone else.
Like, for real.
I don't know nothing about no dope.
Really? Nothing?
Yeah. Nothing.
What's that?
We found that in a hidden
compartment in your passenger door.
It's not mine.
Look, man.
If you give up your supplier,
you'll get out in five.
If you don't, we're gonna charge
you with narcotic-induced homicide
and you die in prison.
So why don't you do
yourself a favor, Jalen?
Start talking.
All right, sure thing.
Good.
But only after you
get on your knees
and kiss my black ass.
Pass.
But I'm sure you're gonna meet
some new friends in prison
that are gonna be happy to
take you up on that offer.
He's laughing at us.
There's people dying
and this kid's laughing.
He doesn't want to talk, there's
nothing we can do about it.
All right, I know you're
supposed to be on the bench...
I told you, Antonio
is in charge.
We got six dead.
They're all under 20.
It's not even lunch yet.
Six?
They found another one.
All right, I'll see what I can do.
- But this stays between us.
- Of course.
All right, everybody. What
else do we know Anabout Jalen?
Um, he's affiliated
with the Black Tiger Posse,
has two priors, both drug-related.
Okay, so we work
this up and down.
Burgess, Atwater, start
with the kid on the corner.
Andre. Wave those homicides
under his nose, see if he bites.
The rest of you work your sources
and find Jalen's suppliers.
Who sold the product to him?
Who's behind the spider logo?
And coordinate with Patrol.
I want them to put up fliers
so that everyone in the neighborhood
knows what's going on out there.
All right, put up fliers?
We sure that's a good idea?
Demand usually goes up
when ODs start happening
because the junkies think that
the dope's super-charged.
Put word out, that might
do more harm than good.
I get it, but it's better
to be transparent.
This way the people decide
for themselves.
Right, even if it's gonna
kill more people?
- Okay, let's go.
- We don't have much time.
All right, man.
Adam, hang back a sec.
Yeah?
Look.
I know you're upset
about Al.
About Voight.
But we got work to do here.
So no more crap.
Whatever you say.
You're the boss.
- All right, I got a name for you.
- Phil Gamble.
Supplies the product
to all the black gangs
this part of the West Side.
Phil Gamble?
- I've never heard of him before.
- He's a pro.
He minds his own business,
stays under the radar.
Why would someone like that
pump bad dope onto the streets?
That doesn't seem to make sense.
Well, that I don't know.
What I do know, he's the man
behind the spider logo,
which means he's involved,
intentionally or unintentionally.
So talk to him, see if
you can catch him dirty.
He owns a bar called The Trick.
- Copy that.
- Hey, boss.
This...
shooting investigation.
You gonna be all right?
You got an angle to play?
Yeah.
It's called the truth.
I told you.
I ain't got nothing to say.
We've got six kids
on a slab at the morgue
because of your dope,
and you're gonna pull
the "I got nothing to say" card?
- My dope?
- What makes you say that?
Phil, it's being sold
in an area you control,
and it's got your logo on it.
You sure about that?
Very.
- Come on, Phil.
- What's going on here?
Who's cutting your product
with battery acid?
That doesn't happen by accident.
Look, bro, it's clear you don't
know what we're talking about.
So help us.
Help us get this crap off the street
before it kills anybody else.
And we can work out
some sort of deal, all right?
But you got to help us now.
No.
Like I said before...
I ain't got nothing to say.
Now it's best you leave...
Officers.
No luck, man. Talked to a
bunch of low-level dealers.
Kids, really, like 16, 17.
They don't know anything.
Did confiscate half an ounce, though.
Yeah, we struck out too.
Tried to squeeze this guy named
Gamble but he wasn't having it.
Gamble? Who the hell is he?
Word is he controls the spot where
the hot loads were being sold.
But, like I said,
he shot us down pretty quickly.
Yeah, he seemed more
confused than anything.
Like he had no idea the ODs
were connected to his dope.
How'd you hear about this guy?
Adam's CI.
- Yeah, I've got a source.
- He knows the area pretty good.
- A source.
- Yeah.
This source on the books?
No, not yet.
He got a name?
Excuse me?
Are you talking to Voight?
I'm talking to whoever can
give us good info...
So you're talking to him?
Antonio, we got six people dead.
What does it matter who I talk to
or where I get my information from?
I'm trying to solve the case!
This is insane.
Look.
I know you're pissed about
this Voight thing.
But that's your issue. Not mine.
Don't jam me up in all this.
Understand?
Yeah, the guys are
loading it up right now...
Hey. Sergeant Hank Voight,
Chicago PD.
Let me call you back.
Listen, you got a
surveillance camera
on the roof. I think it's facing east.
I need to see the footage.
This about the shooting
the other day?
Yeah, listen.
I just need to see the tape.
It shouldn't take long.
I'd give it to you,
but some people already came for it.
People?
Police. Guys in suits.
Said they were with Internal Affairs.
Hold on a sec.
- So you gave them the tape, right?
- Yeah.
About an hour ago.
You see the video yourself?
Were you in the room when the
police were watching it?
No.
I just, I let them in the office,
showed them where everything was,
then left.
Ten minutes later they're walking
out the door with my machine.
They give me the machine back, right?
Yeah.
I'd be happy to show you
the footage if we had any.
There's no surveillance video?
So I've been told.
Well, I think you might have
been told wrong.
Excuse me?
- There is video of the shooting.
- It exists.
And you and I both know it.
What I didn't know until just now,
until you denied its existence...
That video confirms it was a good shoot.
- That's preposterous.
- Why would I withhold evidence
of a good police shooting?
- Yeah, why would you?
- I don't know.
Could ruin your next campaign speech.
Like that one you give...
The one about the...
CPD cleaning up its act,
getting rid of all those white,
middle-aged, cowboy cops.
That one?
I mean, it's worth a hell of a
lot more on the campaign trail
than a good police shooting.
Like I said. No tape.
You're excused, Sergeant.
Guys, that was Meredith.
She asked us to be
the pallbearers tomorrow.
- Platt...
- Yeah?
- We need more officers on the street.
- We gotta be two deep
on every dope corner
in that neighborhood.
I'll try, but I've only got
so many bodies.
Hey, I've been going back
through Jalen's phone,
and the last three days he made 22 calls
to the same burner in Pilsen.
- Pilsen?
- So a black dealer named Jalen
who works the West Side
is chatting with a Mexican cat in Pilsen?
- That's right.
- Yo, Jay.
I ran that name you gave me through HIDTA
and it came back hot.
Guy named Ernesto Varga.
Plugged to some major suppliers
in Mexico.
All right, track him down fast.
- Chicago PD.
- Ernesto Varga?
Anybody home?
Body.
Yeah, he's dead.
Shots fired! Shots fired!
Copy that, 50-21 David.
We've got cars rolling your way.
Everyone else stay off the air.
Agh!
- What?
- It's a kid.
Hey, buddy.
It's the police. Okay? We're the police.
- Put the gun down.
- Son of a bitch.
- All right?
- We're here to help you.
Okay?
You speak English? Habla ingles?
Put the gun down!
All right? No more shooting.
All right?
- Screw this, man.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Stay right there.
Don't shoot, don't shoot.
Don't shoot.
- I got this.
- Hey.
What are you doing?
- No mas pistola.
- Kev.
- Okay?
- Kevin.
Put your gun down, I got this.
Kevin, pick your gun up.
It's on the floor, okay, buddy?
- Kevin. Kev.
- You see that? I got this.
Don't. Don't.
- Hey.
- Don't.
- It's okay.
- Kev.
- No, please don't do this.
- I got this.
- No, man.
- Let me do this, okay?
You see that? It's just me and you.
Don't.
Me, you.
Okay?
My hands up, gun's on the floor.
Hey, hey.
Stand down. Stand down.
Stand down, Ruz, I got it.
I got it, just let me do this.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, look at me.
Look at me.
See? Put the gun down.
Down.
Slow.
It's okay. Put the gun down.
Take your finger off the trigger.
Finger off the trigger.
Okay? He's gonna be okay.
He about to put it down.
Finger off the trigger. There you go.
Bueno. Down.
There you go.
Lo siento!
Lo siento...
- Lo siento...
- It's okay.
Everything's all right.
You're good.
Varga was dead when we got here. We
missed the shooting by ten minutes.
Give or take.
Yeah, blood was still fresh.
But the kid is okay?
The Patrol took him down
to Chicago Med to get checked out.
Was he able to ID the shooter?
No, he was hiding in his room.
Said he heard someone
arguing with his dad
and two gunshots.
- All right, what's it look like to you?
- A robbery or what?
No, we found $20,000 in cash
and a Rolex, so...
definitely wasn't just a robbery.
Yeah, more like
a straight-up hit.
All right, you two need
anything, let me know.
Yeah.
- What the hell was that, man?
- Why'd you go in like that?
What was that?
Worried about the kid.
And you thought I was
gonna shoot him?
Yeah. And if you did...
I wasn't gonna shoot him.
Adam, I hear you.
And that is the right call.
It's a kid with a gun.
He wasn't listening.
But I couldn't watch that happen.
I said I wasn't gonna shoot him.
All right, look, I know
it's a tough play.
I didn't know what to do.
But, Kev, you go in like that...
the position you put me in, what
choice do I have right there?
I shoot a little kid or I...
watch him shoot you?
That ain't right, man.
It's just...
I can't bear to have
another one of my friends die this week.
I can't bear it, man.
Recognize that dude?
This dude right here.
That dude?
- Ernesto Varga ring a bell?
- No.
You called him 22 times
this week.
I don't know what you're
talking about.
Jalen, it's over, man.
We all know what's going on.
And if we know,
you can be damn sure Gamble knows.
Knows what?
The game that you
and Varga are playing.
Putting out poison
under his logo.
Trying to convince people
it was him killing folks.
Or maybe you were just trying
to frame his ass.
Hoping that we'd blame him for the ODs,
get him off the street,
open up the market.
- I get it.
- Look, either way,
it's clear the two of you were
trying to roll up old Phil Gamble,
take his customers. That's clear.
Did you know about
the battery acid?
Or was that Varga's idea?
Because if you didn't,
we can work with you, man.
All right? We can blame it
on the dead guy.
Yeah, I keep telling you. I don't
know what you're talking about.
Jalen, I'm starting to
lose my patience.
- Give me my lawyer, bitch.
- "Bitch"?
"Bitch"? I'll give you your bitch.
You and me, we're gonna take a walk...
You're going to tell where is the dope.
Let him go, Adam! Enough! Enough!
Kevin, bring him downstairs.
- Get him processed now.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Move, move.
- What the hell are you doing?
- What the hell am I doing?
He knows where the dope is!
- It doesn't matter!
- He lawyered up!
You hear me?
Hold on.
No, no, no.
- What do you mean it doesn't matter?
- Adam, just let it go.
- Everyone's doing everything we can.
- No, we are not.
No, we are not, not by a long shot.
Antonio, if Voight was here
the dope would be off the street by now!
- But he isn't here, is he?
- Yeah, why's that?
We're doing it my way!
- Hey! Hey!
- And if you don't like it,
- then get the hell out!
- Hey!
I have an update.
- Three more dead.
- My God.
- Two female.
- Both white, both 18.
One male, Hispanic, 20.
Same spider logo on the empty packets.
- Come on, let's go.
- Go.
You heard her. Get to the scene.
I'm doing the best
I can, Sarge, but
this kid Jalen, he's not talking,
and I can't do anything about
it 'cause Antonio's on my ass.
All right, I'll take it
from here.
What do you mean?
Been talking to Phil Gamble. He
gave me some useful information.
- Like what?
- Doesn't matter.
I'm gonna call you in 30 minutes.
Just make sure your phone is
on, you have access to Jalen,
and you're alone. You got it?
- Yep.
- All right.
- Dawson, right?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Close it.
- Yep.
- What the hell is going on out there?
- We got nine dead.
I know. It's a bad situation,
but I assure you we're doing
everything we can.
These overdoses are
a black eye on this city,
on this police department.
Drug arrests are up 34%
yet we got bodies dropping all over town.
You need to find these drugs
before another body drops.
I'm trying my hardest.
Nobody cares how hard
you try, detective.
This isn't kindergarten.
We don't give A's for effort.
Get it done.
Yeah, they're having
their anniversary sale,
so, like, everything's 50% off.
Yeah, girl, no.
You're telling me.
No, she's doing great.
You know.
You know, with poor people,
it's, like, a lifesaver.
No, I'm making dinner right
now, and then...
um, yeah...
- Shh, shh.
- Stay calm.
Stay calm.
Tell her you'll call her back
and hang up the phone, you understand?
Okay, good.
I-I'll call you back, all right?
Give me the phone.
Listen. Just relax.
- Please don't hurt me. I...
- Shh.
Where's the money?
Where does Jalen keep the cash?
- He'll kill me.
- Jalen is in jail.
He's gonna be there
for 15 years, maybe more.
Look, you help me,
I'll help you.
Come on.
Yeah, boss, I'm almost there.
Jalen.
Nah, I told you I ain't talking.
Yeah, we're gonna give you
one more opportunity
to tell us where the product is.
Jalen, look at the phone.
Yo, look at the phone.
Hey, Jalen, guess who I'm with?
Vanessa.
The mother of your beautiful son.
Yo, what the hell are you doing?
- Easy, easy.
- Just shut up and listen.
Now you tell me where
that hot dope is
and you can keep all the money.
All $170,000 of it.
You don't...
and I'll burn every dollar.
- Yo, that's hers.
- You can't touch it.
Yeah, you think I'm bluffing?
Jalen, come on, please.
Jalen, tell him where it is, come on.
Start talking, Jalen.
Or I'll burn every dollar.
That's a lot of money.
Okay.
Man, I'll tell you what you need to know.
But I-I promise I didn't know
Varga cut it with battery acid.
He was supposed to use
some sort of laxative...
- Yo, yo.
- Make people sick.
- The time for feeling bad...
- He didn't say nothing about.
Listen to me. We need to
know where the product is.
All right? Tell us now.
Jalen just confessed.
He gave up the stash house.
- What?
- He lawyered up.
You weren't even supposed to
be talking to him.
The address is
3220 Edgemont Road.
There's 1/2 kilo sitting there
just waiting to kill
another 10, 20, 50 people.
And he just volunteered this.
- Yes.
- You're lying.
You wanna be right
or you wanna save lives?
It's your call.
Let's gear up and hit
this place now.
Hands up!
Now, get your hands up and turn around!
- On the wall, on the wall!
- Don't look at me... turn around.
Hands on the counter.
- Let's go, let's go.
- Get down.
Nobody move.
Everybody keep their hands
where they are.
We're just gonna make the rounds.
Go.
Come on, come on...
- You hear that?
- Yeah, I hear 'em.
You guys good? You're good?
- Yeah.
- Police!
- Hey! Hey!
- Nobody move!
Put your hands against the wall!
Hey, put your hands up.
Hey, why don't you three come
to me, okay?
- Move against the wall!
- Now!
Come to me, yeah.
Now go up against the wall.
Keep your hands
where I can see them.
Why don't you put
your hands down?
Everything's okay, I'm Officer Burgess.
Are you okay?
Are you okay and are you okay?
Has anyone hurt you?
Real slow.
No? You're all right?
Hey, hey.
Okay. So you found the dope, congrats.
Now we talk about what just happened.
We just solved the problem.
- That's what just happened.
- No.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. And
that's all you need to know.
So back up.
What did you say?
I said back up!
- Hey!
- Come on!
Get off me!
This ain't over, you hear me?
Let's finish it now!
Get outside!
- Let's finish it now!
- Turn around!
Turn around and shut up!
Come on, man! The hell is wrong with you?
Give it a look,
email should be sent by now.
I appreciate you doing
this, Franny.
- You do what you gotta do, man.
- Just leave me out of it.
We gotta talk.
Congratulations, you guys
are all over the news.
What happened?
I had an angle and I played it.
Why?
To make me look bad
because I didn't cover for you?
I was trying to help.
I'm trying to save lives.
Yeah. Then why didn't
you tell me?
- Hey, come here.
- Come on.
Why didn't I tell you?
'Cause I didn't want to jam you up.
What's that mean?
Antonio, I need you clean.
I know things've been choppy, but...
Bro, I like the fact you
have your own code
even if it's different from mine.
Listen to me.
The best thing you can be
is you.
The best thing I can be is me.
I mean, it's not easy. I get it.
Bro, we pull it off...
Everybody wins.
Sorry I'm late.
Such a beautiful city.
That why you texted me?
To talk about Chicago architecture?
No.
I wanted to thank you
for finding the bad dope.
Wasn't me, I'm on suspension.
Dawson told me everything.
Said if it wasn't for your intel
there would be 50 more dead
bodies on the street.
And I wanted to apologize
for our conversation earlier.
I was wrong.
Turns out there is some
footage of the shooting.
You get a chance to review it?
You bet.
It was...
more ambiguous than I was led to believe.
It's not ambiguous.
He reached for his gun so I shot him.
I'm not sure COPA would
agree with that...
without my help.
- It was a good shoot.
- I don't need any help.
Don't be stupid.
We all need help.
I guess it depends on the cost.
I want you to support
Kelton for mayor.
Support him how?
I need someone I can rely on
to help solve cases in a hurry.
Or...
not in a hurry, depending on the facts.
Or the circumstances.
So you want me to be...
My friend.
I need something too.
Like what?
A letter of exoneration
for Alvin Olinsky.
So his wife and child
can collect his pension.
That's a big ask.
That's my price
for being your friend.
I'll see what I can do.
Hey, you back on the job?
Got the official call
an hour ago.
All right.
Good to see you, boss.
You too.
- Hailey. Kim.
- Hi.
All right.
- I'm glad you're back, Hank.
- Yeah, well...
Me too.
Listen, um...
It has been a very long few days.
With a lot of pain.
A lot of anger.
I get it.
And I don't expect these emotions
to just disappear overnight.
But going forward,
we need to be a team.
One team.
No more fighting.
No more crap.
Hey. Everything all right?
Yeah.
Hank, I tried calling.
But, um...
What is it, Trudy?
I just got off the phone
with Meredith.
She would prefer it if you
did not attend the funeral.
I understand.
Okay.