Think we found our guy.
Logan Peters.
We got intel he's hanging with the Southside Hustlers.
Roman said he'd call you once he found the guy,
Wait a second, you talking about Sean Roman?
- Kim's ex-partner? - Yeah.
What's he got to do with this?
My little sister Sarah, she went missing last week.
I need to know what happened.
Sean is in Chicago?
You are not a cop anymore!
No, But I'm Sarah's big brother.
'Cause I can't blame Sean for putting his family first.
I mean, let's do what we can to help him.
Here we go.
- What do we got? - Fire's contained.
Got a couple smoke inhalation injuries.
They're on their way now to Med with the GSW victim,
Travis.
Believe he started the fire.
Smelled gasoline when we entered.
So the, uh, shooter's the dealer, Logan Peters?
Yeah, he's in the wind. Fled during the fire.
It's too late for a perimeter.
All right, well, Kim will take your statement.
Someplace quiet, huh?
Okay, what's going on?
I arrived here after tracking Logan.
I'm not actually asking for your statement.
I'm asking why the hell you didn't come to us.
My sister's missing. I'm looking for her.
Yeah, we have an entire unit that specializes in just that.
Not to mention, you have me. And Intelligence.
I went to Fire first because of the ODs.
No...
I rode in a car with you for two years.
- I know when you're lying. - I couldn't come to you.
I don't care that we broke up.
It's not that.
Do you realize how bad this looks for you right now?
You're at the scene of a shooting--
- I can book you as a suspect. - You gotta be kidding me.
- I was a cop. - You're not anymore.
All right?
So if you want, I'll take you down to the station,
then you can answer my questions in the box.
Your choice.
She's dealing for him.
What?
My sister's an addict. She has been for a while now.
And I think she's dealing for her boyfriend.
And if she is, and a teenager died,
then she's staring down a drug induced homicide charge.
So yeah, I went to Fire first and lied my ass off.
Look, I need you to trust me now, okay?
Just...trust me, okay?
We've been treating at least three ODs an hour,
like stopping running water.
This kid who set the fire?
- Yeah. - Travis Butler.
Paramedics brought him in 15 minutes ago,
GSW to the stomach, smoke inhalation.
- He's still in surgery, but-- - If you're saying this place
is too busy, then you see my daughter first.
No, but my son's in worse condition than your daughter.
Sir, sit down.
This kid could've killed everyone in there.
Hey, what's going on?
Victims from the fire were brought here,
and so was Travis.
- I do know that you-- - Get your hands off of me!
Police! Hey, police!
Police! You need to calm down!
- Calm down. Calm down. - My son's in worse condition.
- Calm down. - Okay.
Come on, let's go this way.
I'm sorry. I would never hit a cop. A woman.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay, I'm fine.
They say my son started the fire.
Uh, we believe the guy who shot your son
is also involved in other crimes.
- What? - He was in the apartment
- where the fire started. - No witnesses saw Logan flee.
- Mr. Butler? - Yeah?
Surgery went well. Travis is stable.
Can I see him?
Thanks.
See you guys. Thank you.
- Good work. - Thanks.
No, I didn't see where Logan went.
He, uh, he shot me,
I saw him leave the room, but that's all.
How well do you know Logan? You know where he might run to?
I don't know him at all.
Friend of mine told me where to find him.
Told me he killed my girlfriend.
He dealt to her?
She was happy. She was perfect.
Then he started selling to her.
He's responsible for this.
I was just trying to make it right.
I'm going to jail, aren't I?
Oh, man.
I should've told you to come here from the jump.
I'm sorry. I steered you wrong.
Well, I'm here now.
You, uh, you gonna talk to Voight?
- Yeah. - Hey, O'Malley.
Oh, come on, I finally got detailed to TACT.
But who needs a three-house raid when there's the honor
of covering your desk?
- Hey, welcome back. - Thanks.
- Sorry to hear about the-- - Thank you.
Sorry for your loss.
- What's he talking about? - Uh, I got injured on the job.
That's all.
My mother called me last week.
She found pills in Sarah's room.
Flushed them, then accused her of dealing.
- Which didn't go well. - She ran?
She's been gone nine days.
We thought she ran off with her boyfriend.
I didn't even know his name until yesterday.
Logan Peters.
If she did sell to those kids that OD'd...
She's looking at a big charge.
I know her, Sarge. She's a good kid.
She's just down on her luck, needs our help.
Well, we find her first,
- we'll do what we can to protect her. - Okay.
All right.
You can roll with Kim.
On a short leash.
I'm gonna tell you something, you go off on your own
while you're with my unit...
you're gonna see a whole other side of me, you understand?
Yeah.
Okay, he's yours.
Thank you.
Ann Hoffman, 15. Clarke Preston, 17.
Two more ODs pronounced at
Med in the last 24 hours.
And their tox report
matches our original DOA, Brandi.
Mass amounts of fentanyl in their systems.
Same compound product our dealer Logan Peters is pushing.
The kid's got a few priors for possession, theft,
and a statutory rape charge.
He was 23, his girlfriend, 15.
- Charge was dismissed. - All right, and the pills?
Thinking Mexican oxy. Looks, feels, tastes like
regular oxy, but it's fake. Made with fentanyl, instead.
Comes directly from cartels,
and is dealt to Hispanic gangs in the city.
I got something.
Latin Players said Logan wasn't getting product from them.
Southside Hustlers were granting him asylum.
Well, begs the question, where's he getting his product?
- Witness popped. - Okay.
Guy across the street from the fire says
he saw Logan running towards the L.
I pulled the footage. He got off at Wilson.
All right, so run all Logan Peters' known associates
near that stop.
I mean, the guy's hiding somewhere, right?
We find him, flip him for his supplier,
get this product off the street before that board grows.
Hey, you, uh, you want me to ride with you, or...
No.
Smaller numbers, it's a quicker spread.
- Right, okay. - Yeah.
Well, we'll see you back here.
- What was that in there? - What?
You seem different.
No, we just haven't spoken in years.
Your unit seems to be walking on eggshells around you,
especially Ruzek.
You should've stuck around, Roman.
You would've made detective.
And you seem different too.
No, hey, you can't just come in.
You answer the door high, holding a joint.
- Not sure what you expect. - I ain't high.
And it's legal now.
No, man, you're high on something
a lot stronger than marijuana, and you're on probation--
Baby, can you please not be so loud?
Come here. Get over here.
Let's go.
You trying to get to the drugs before we do?
Have a seat. Sit down!
All right, you answer my questions,
I won't search this place, we have a deal?
You know this guy, Logan Peters?
- I don't know him. - You do know him.
He listed this address for two months
after he got out of prison. Try again.
- Hey, look at this. - Haven't seen him in a long time.
What about her? Sarah Roman.
You know her? She dating Logan?
- Don't know her. - Do you know her?
We don't know her.
Hey, does it look like I'm talking to you?
Do you know her?
- She's my little sister. - Baby, no.
Well, she doesn't look like that anymore.
Oh, my God.
- So you've seen her? - Day--day--days ago.
Okay, where, where's the last place you saw her?
Logan doesn't date these girls.
He just...plays with them.
Listen, I don't care about that,
I want to know where the last place you saw Sarah was.
Look at me, not at him.
Where's the last place you saw Sarah?
The old lake house.
We break in there to party sometimes.
- I want that address now. - Yeah.
No. No.
Clear.
Clear. Roman.
Now we're clear.
- Might as well start in here. - Okay.
You okay?
Yeah.
What happened on the job? Injury?
Sex trafficking case.
I went in without backup, I got worked.
You lose a victim?
The PO at 21 said, "Sorry for your loss."
Ruzek and I got together, I got pregnant,
and I'm not anymore.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry. I-I can't even imagine.
It's okay. It was early. It was an unplanned pregnancy.
I'm fine.
Look at this.
It's the Southside Hustlers' emblem.
Yeah, you said Logan was getting asylum from them, right?
Looks like an oxy pill.
Let's hope it's one of the fake ones.
Kim. That's Sarah's.
What?
- Sure? - Yeah, it's her jacket.
Okay. Sarah?
- Sarah! - Sarah?
- Sarah! - Sarah--
Sarah!
Sarah.
I believe Sarah died a week ago.
Her body indicates she struggled to survive.
Someone strangled her, beat her.
There's presence of internal bleeding in her stomach.
But none of those factors are the actual cause of death.
It's likely she appeared dead to her assailant
but survived these injuries.
Ultimately, she froze to death.
Your body tricks you when you freeze.
You think you're warm.
Probable she took off her jacket trying to cool down,
- went to the water and-- - How long?
How long was she alone outside?
I would guess she was alive outside for around 19 hours.
Sean.
Kim?
Sean?
What's going on?
Sean.
We found Sarah's body, Mom.
She died a week ago.
No.
She's gone.
No, no.
- No! - She needed you!
- No, no, no, no. - We needed you!
Please, please stop, please.
- You all right? You all right? - I'm fine!
How'd it go with Roman's family?
- It went. - All right, M.E. confirmed the DNA
found under Sarah's fingernails popped in the system.
It was Logan's.
All right, somebody tell me we got something on this prick.
We ran the pill we found at the lake house through ISP.
They did confirm that it matches our ODs,
but it ain't Mexican oxy.
That pill is way too sloppy for the cartels.
ISP believes it's homemade.
Might have something.
Reran Logan's GPS stats.
The tower pings up against known Southside Hustler hot spots.
One hit an old stash house leased to a Leon Miller.
Guy's a bit of a heavy.
Known for leasing dope corners.
It's a long shot, but that stretch of the city
is dead man's land. There ain't nothing there.
I mean, it's a damn good place to hide out.
Yeah. Let's roll on it. Nice work.
Thanks.
All right, we'll take front, you guys--
5021 Frank, we got shots fired
coming from inside a warehouse at 1600 West Racine.
Get us some cars over here.
Copy that.
Go, go, go.
Hold on, hold on.
Body.
Crossing.
Ruz, you good?
Yeah, I'm good. We got Logan Peters.
DOA, looks like two gunshot wounds to the chest.
Cross.
Rear, possibly side of the building.
Copy that.
Chicago PD! Don't move!
Don't move.
Where's the gun? You got the gun?
I don't know, I don't see it. I don't see it.
Buddy, where's the gun?
- He's foaming at the mouth. - What is he, an OD?
- I don't know, you got Narcan? - No.
- Oh, God. - 5021 George, emergency.
Roll an ambo to 1600 West Racine,
we got an OD victim. Nonresponsive.
Advise responding to set up a four-block perimeter.
We still might have a shooter here.
His pulse is strong.
- Let's get that Narcan or we're going lose him. - Yup.
- Stay with us. - Here you go.
- Come on, come on. - Come on, come on, come on.
There you go. There we go, that's it.
Okay, let's get going.
Easy, easy.
I gotta get his gloves checked for GSR.
We've really gotta get him to the hospital.
- All right. Can we go? - Yup.
It's hard to imagine this guy's capable of firing a gun.
Looks that way, but you never know.
- Right behind y'all. - One, two, three.
Okay, all right, drop him.
What can I do?
- Buckle him. - Got it.
Hey, how's Roman? Is he doing okay?
He's tough. Losing his sister like that.
- It's hard to accept. - Yeah, more like impossible.
You get the other guy to Med?
Yeah.
Looks like Logan was hiding out here.
Yeah, well, someone found him.
He's got plenty of self defense wounds, bruising on his knuckles.
Looks like he was in quite the scrape before he got shot.
Logan's getting a lot of heat for the ODs,
supplier gets spooked.
Beats him, kills him, ties it off.
Do you want us to work this, Sarge,
or do you wanna wait for Homicide? They're on their way.
Well, if this punk's murder can get us to our supplier,
get these pills off the street, yeah, we'll work it.
I mean, for that. Not for this.
Why do you still have that sonogram up, Adam?
I don't know. Just couldn't get rid of it yet.
That doesn't really make sense, but okay.
It does to me.
Look, I'm not trying to weird you out.
I'll take it down right now if you want me to.
No, if you want to keep it up, that's your call.
- You sure? - Yeah, you do what you need to do.
'Cause, you know,
I don't know if we're in the same place with all this.
We haven't really had a chance to talk.
Okay, let's do it. Let's talk. Let's talk.
No, no, no, we don't have--
No, we should because
it's better than us avoiding each other and--
You just--you just go ahead,
you say what you're gonna say, and you get it off your chest.
Okay. What am I meant to get off my chest?
- Your feelings, your anger. - What do you mean?
Adam, I can tell-- I can feel it.
You blame me for losing the baby.
- Blame you? - Yeah.
I don't blame you. What are you talking about?
'Cause I wasn't supposed to be in the field,
I wasn't supposed to be at the motel--
And you were.
And because you were, you saved a kid's life.
Yeah, but I could've waited three minutes--
No, you couldn't have. That man would've beat
that girl to death, had you waited outside.
Kim, you were doing your job. You're a cop.
You were at a scene--
I wasn't supposed to be on the scene!
I wasn't supposed to be in the motel!
I wasn't supposed to lose the baby!
Don't you get that? I don't want pity.
And I don't want support.
- What do you want? - I want you to be angry with me,
as angry with me as I am.
I can't do that.
I'm sorry.
Yes, okay.
Got it.
Okay, yes, thank you.
GSR on the junkie is negative.
Dude ain't no killer, just a stone cold addict.
I just talked to him at Med. Good news is he's stable.
Bad news is he didn't see a damn thing.
He said as soon as he heard the shots, ran off scared.
All right, so what do we got on Leon Miller?
Confirmed he's the one that's paying rent on the warehouse.
It's bad paper, but the money traces back to him.
Narcotics says that he's well-established, smart,
and strategic.
He's a good fit for Logan's supplier.
All right, so dig into it. See if we can put him
or one of his associates at the scene.
- Sarge? - Yes?
- Okay if I update Roman? - Yeah.
We found Logan in an abandoned warehouse.
He was beaten. Two shots to the chest.
He's dead, Roman.
We think that his supplier, Leon Miller, looks good for it.
He also owns the warehouse where Logan's body was found.
Doesn't really matter now, does it?
Who cares if he's dead?
She's still gone.
I know. But down the line it could help, you know?
Knowing the man responsible for her death is gone too.
I doubt it.
Sean, it's not on you.
This is on Logan.
What's not? That I left her?
- No-- - My sister needed me, Kim.
She was coming apart, and she needed me
to just get on the plane and come home to her.
But I didn't.
So you can give me any platitudes you want
but you didn't want to hear them from me, okay?
And I don't want to hear them from you.
This is on me.
Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm not sure-- - Jay?
- Yeah? - Any new leads?
No. We can prove that they knew each other from texts,
social media, but there's no tower pings,
there's no footage, nothing that puts Miller or anyone
associated with him near Logan's murder.
Guys.
- Who was that? - He's a potential witness.
He says he was near the crime scene, saw a black Range Rover
speed away a minute after hearing two gunshots.
That's the lead we've been waiting for.
Miller drives a black Range Rover.
Yeah. He also got a partial plate. Time to move.
Go.
- Ready? - Yeah, let's go.
Police! Gun!
I got you. Move up.
Move up, move up. Come on, come on.
- Shots fired at the police. - Gun!
Go, Burgess, go Burgess, I got you.
Sarge, I got a runner! He's headed straight for you!
Don't shoot.
Shut up, Leon.
Keep your hands up.
Sarge.
Stand back.
Leon, we found 2,000 counterfeit oxy pills.
Plus a boatload of uncut fentanyl.
Ain't mine.
Okay, here's what we're gonna do.
I'm gonna pretend you didn't start there.
And you're gonna pretend you give a damn your pills
killed three teenagers.
It ain't mine.
You can't connect me to none of that.
I ain't never seen or touched those drugs--
Kid, you tell your lawyer to play that.
I promise you it ain't gonna work for the murder.
Murder? What the hell is you talking about?
Logan Peters.
I ain't kill Logan.
He was hiding out at your warehouse.
You're the only person who knew where he was.
Look, man, I told him he could hide out there.
No way I killed him.
I'll tell you whatever you want on that, but I ain't kill nobody.
I ain't been at that warehouse in years.
We got Miller on tape eating at Frank's Grill
over on Marquette 12:31 to 2:18.
Son of a bitch is telling the truth.
Well, maybe he didn't pull the trigger himself,
doesn't mean he didn't order the hit.
Keep looking.
Hey, we finally caught a break with a bus cam.
He was passing Racine, two blocks out,
three minutes after the gunshots.
Caught this blue Nissan sedan driving westbound.
Unfortunately, because of the glare on the windows,
you can't make out the driver.
And the black Range Rover?
No, it's just the blue Nissan, no plates.
Okay, so we start looking for owners of blue Nissans.
- Hey, Kim. - Yeah?
Talk to that witness again, maybe he saw a blue Nissan too.
Copy you.
Did you see any other cars, anybody else?
Uh, no, only saw a black Range Rover.
Okay, did you get a look at the driver?
No, just the car.
And which way was it headed?
Not sure.
I was driving to my sister's house,
thought my tire was flat, pulled over, checked the tire,
heard two gunshots.
And then what?
Got the hell out of there.
What happened to the flat?
Wasn't as bad as I thought.
Where does your sister live?
In Englewood. Lancaster Road.
And where were you coming from?
Uh, I was at home. In Pilsen.
Okay. Question.
See, Pilsen is here, and Englewood is here,
and the location of the warehouse
where the shooting took place is about here.
Now, the shortest distance between two points is a straight line.
That line ain't too straight, Christian.
I'm not so good at directions.
Not so good at lying, either.
Anything else?
Why are you lying to me, Christian?
I ain't lying to you.
I told you exactly what happened.
You know what? I don't need this.
Platt. I need you to do a deep dive on that witness,
Christian Lewis.
I'm not handing out work.
I just need this done off the record.
- Okay, fine. - Thank you.
You guys are fishing in the wrong pond here.
Hit men do not drive Nissans.
Exactly why a smart one would.
- Hey, we have anything? - I don't know.
I got three accountants, two teachers, and a dentist, so...
Hold on, Ruz, I think got one.
Robert Harper, age 43. White as hell.
I mean, makes Halstead look like Lil Wayne.
This man is very legit.
He's got three outstanding parking tickets.
And if that's not gangster, he's got a jaywalking citation.
I say we grab his ass up.
Where are you going? You just got here.
It turns out your witness, Christian Lewis,
used to be an informant.
He was on our books for a couple years.
- When? - 2014 to '16.
I don't know what's going on,
I don't wanna know what's going on,
but you're making me nervous.
Oh, I'm fine.
- You like it here, right? - Of course I like it here.
Then be careful.
Keeping secrets from Voight is not a game many people win.
Kim, you know you're not alone in this.
You got people. Me.
People tend to lighten the load.
Hey, what's up? It's almost midnight.
We need to talk, now. Here, someplace else.
- Come on in. - Thanks.
Yeah, my parents are finally sleeping.
The doctor gave them some sleeping pills.
Good. That's good.
- So what's going on? - I wanted to talk to you
before too many people got involved.
- What's that mean? - It means that things are starting to break
a certain way in Logan's murder, Sean.
- What way is that, Kim? - In a way that points to you.
Our key witness, Christian Lewis,
the guy who saw a black Range Rover--
the exact car that Leon Miller drives--
is one of your old CIs.
And the car that was actually at the scene, a blue Nissan,
just so happens to be the same type of car
that your cousin, Tamra Riley, drives.
I've met her, Sean, at your house, at parties.
I've met her, and according to social media,
she has been in Florida the last five days--
It's late, and I need to get ready for my sister's funeral.
Sean, I don't think you meant to kill him--
I'm giving the eulogy,
- and I wanna make sure I do a good job, Kim. - Sean.
I appreciate you coming by.
Get some rest, Sean.
Where we at?
We find any blue Nissan owners
with a connection to Leon Miller or the DOA?
So we went through all of Miller's known associates.
Nobody drives a blue Nissan.
So, other than the car, the only piece of evidence
we got is this witness, Christian Lewis.
Who popped up out of nowhere
and luckily saw a black Range Rover speed from the scene.
Maybe Miller let one of his associates
drive the Range Rover to do the hit.
It's possible, but Miller seems smarter than that.
So that leaves you-- the killer drives the exact
same car as Miller, with similar plates.
Or witness is lying his ass off.
All right, Kim, you talked to the witness yesterday.
He seem credible to you?
You know, I-I couldn't tell that he was lying,
but his story did have some holes in it.
Bring him in.
We got open door.
Chicago PD.
Christian Lewis. Chicago PD.
What the hell?
Lewis packed up fast.
He's gotta be playing us. Made up the Range Rover
to get us to focus the investigation on Miller.
Why do that?
'Cause someone pays you to.
Let's go knock on some doors.
Good afternoon, sir, I was hoping you could help me out.
Thanks so deeply for your concern about the city of Chicago.
No, no, no, what I'm saying is Christian is a good dude.
I mean, he ain't gonna run for president,
but he's doing the best he can.
Well, what do you mean by that?
He's an addict. Heroin, crack, you name it.
But he's been getting himself right,
going to meetings, making amends.
Landlady say he just gave her an envelope
filled with fresh hundreds.
This landlady, she live in the complex?
Yeah. Apartment 2C.
How's it going? Any leads?
Best one I have so far is Lewis is trying to make amends.
He just handed the landlady an envelope full of cash.
- Yeah, I just talked to her. - Okay.
Lewis gave her three grand in cash, squared up his whole debt.
Fresh cash, too, so we can trace the serial numbers.
That's good.
Yeah, we identify the bank where the money was withdrawn,
I'm guessing that'll get us to the guy who paid Lewis to lie.
Unless, of course, you already know.
No. I-I'm just doing the math, like you.
- Do you want me to run the cash? - No, I got it.
Okay.
Funeral for Roman's sister is in a few hours.
You should go.
- Go. - Okay.
Good morning, everybody.
On behalf of the Roman family,
I would like to thank you all for being here today.
I'd like to start with a reading from Ecclesiastes.
"My child, when you come to serve the Lord,
"prepare yourself for trials.
"Be sincere of heart and steadfast,
"and do not be impetuous in times of adversity.
"Cling to him, do not leave him,
"that you may prosper in your last days.
"Accept whatever happens to you;
"in periods of humiliation, be patient.
"For in fire gold is tested, and the chosen,
"in the crucible of humiliation.
"Trust in God, and he will help you;
make your ways straight and hope in him."
Word of the Lord.
Thanks be to God.
I love you.
Did the right thing to call me.
My sister Sarah, she died alone in a ditch.
Temperature was minus-4 degrees.
Can only imagine how scared she was.
How alone she was.
Growing up...
My sister was never alone.
Uh, she was always surrounded by her friends,
cousins, kids from down the block,
kids I didn't even know where the hell--
heck they came from.
You know, they'd just be there,
in the kitchen one day, drinking pop out of a two liter,
waiting for my sister.
She drew people to her because she was warm.
She was loving, and she was always herself.
Strong and stubborn.
She was a fighter.
When they found her...
My sister had scratches
on her hands and knees from crawling,
from fighting.
But there was no one there to save her.
She screamed for help, but no one heard her.
She was screaming weeks before.
Sarah needed help.
But I wasn't there for her.
"Whoever conceals his transgressions will not prosper."
"But he who confesses
and forsakes them will obtain mercy."
Proverbs 28:13.
If you ask me, that's a lie.
You can't just recite a passage, say a few Hail Marys,
and then wash away your sins.
And we shouldn't be able to.
We should be required to carry around our sins
for the rest of our years.
All the pain and guilt too.
We need to feel them
so we can do better next time.
So that we can be there the next time
someone screams for help.
- That was a hell of a eulogy. - It was honest.
You believe in absolution?
Kim, I don't think like that.
Yeah, I know.
I appreciate you waiting till the service was over.
So how we gonna do this?
We're not.
Logan Peters deserved what he got.
As for the person responsible...
Well, we're gonna continue our investigation,
but it's no longer a top priority.
I mean, we'll keep you--
keep you posted with any new information, but
other than that...
I wish you the best.
What just happened?
I don't know.
Sean.
I think you're right.
Maybe we should be required to carry this pain...
But then don't we get to decide what we do with it?