Dad! Is he all right?
He was above the fire floor.
Swallowed a lot of smoke.
We... we gotta take Dad off the vent.
Let him go.
[FIRE BLAZING]
She's alive!
♪
Sir, I'm gonna need you to go
back into the waiting room.
♪
What happened to our Jane Doe?
We were treating Jane Doe
for third degree burns
when she developed compartment syndrome.
It became clear Jane had
been beaten before the fire.
Nurse went to do rounds,
saw her room like this.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
How long has she been gone?
Not long. We checked security tapes.
She walked out alone at half past.
What is that?
That is a GPS chip.
She must have cut it out of herself.
Someone was tracking this girl.
She's got life-threatening injuries.
She's not gonna get far by herself.
♪
Hey. Jay, I, uh...
Just heard about your father. I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Jay, take some time. Be with your family.
It's not what you think, Sarge.
Me and my dad had
a complicated relationship.
We didn't really see eye to eye.
I'm not proud of it. It's the truth.
Five other people died in that fire.
I want to help.
Mmm.
♪
Okay.
Platt's briefing everyone
in the parking lot.
All right.
♪
Jane Doe, approximately 20 years old.
5'4", fled Chicago Med
less than 60 minutes ago.
She exited the west rear door
and was last seen headed north on foot.
She is believed to be all alone and hurt,
so we have to move fast.
Populorum, you and Henry
are on public transport...
- Hey, you wanna take north?
- Yeah.
- Just, Jay, I'm sorry...
- Thanks.
So, uh, just fill me in.
Okay, she dug out her own GPS chip,
so obviously she doesn't wanna be found.
She has third degree burns,
multiple broken bones.
She couldn't have
got out of there too fast.
So where would you go?
I don't know. Find someplace to hide.
Someplace to die.
- You go that way, I'll go this way?
- Yeah, I'll go over here.
[CROWS CAWING]
[GROANING]
Jay?
- [SHUDDERING]
- Jay!
5021 Eddie, emergency.
We need an ambulance
at the southwest corner
of Bryers Park.
Hey, hey, hey! Hey, hey, stay with us.
Hey. Hey, hey.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
I don't know what's wrong.
She's bleeding really bad.
We need that ambulance.
They're never gonna find us.
I'm gonna flag them down, Jay.
I repeat, we're in
the southwest corner...
It's okay. It's okay.
Can you look at me?
Hey, can you look at me?
It's gonna be okay. I'm Jay.
I'm a detective with the
Chicago Police Department.
You're gonna be okay. What's your name?
He came to kill them.
Who came?
I was hiding, but he set a fire.
Who did this to you? Who set the fire?
- You know who he was?
- He killed them.
Who? What's his name?
Who was he? Who was he?
Did you know him?
- Ah... I'll be free now.
- [SIRENS WAILING]
♪
Yeah, you'll be free. You'll be free now.
It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
Come on, come on!
♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
She said she was hiding
and he came to kill them.
Then before she lost consciousness,
she said that she would be free now.
I'm running her prints and
her DNA, but no ID yet.
All right, Chief?
Fire originated in apartment 20E.
We found Jane Doe's body here
outside of the apartment.
Burns indicated she was
most likely crawling,
trying to escape the flames.
Door to 20E was open.
That's how the fire spread.
The other John Does were found
inside the apartment...
one in the bed, one near the front door.
All right, so she said that
he came to kill them.
So the offender enters the apartment,
he kills both John Does,
the Jane Doe's hiding,
the offender goes to light the fire,
she tries to escape, and then
she gets beaten unconscious.
Injuries run against that, Sharon?
It could be consistent.
Jane Doe suffered a ulna fracture,
internal injuries, third degree burns.
We also treated her for
heavy smoke inhalation.
So the offender beats her,
thinks she's dead,
but Jane Doe comes to during the fire,
opens the front door,
and attempts to crawl
to the elevator.
Arson was just a cover up
for the double homicide.
The rest of them were collateral damage.
[KNOCKING]
Jane Doe didn't make it.
Pronounced her a minute ago.
She never regained consciousness.
All right, we need to get going.
Thank you.
- Anything you need.
- Appreciate it.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Let's start with apartment 20E.
Antonio, get Jane Doe's GPS
chip to OCD tech right away.
I'll run it up with Vice, too.
It's common practice these days for pimps
- to chip their property.
- All right.
I'm guessing Jane Doe was
a victim of sex trafficking.
So we start with what was left behind.
I want every piece of paper
on that apartment...
who was living there,
every in-service call.
Just scour that crime scene.
Work the bodies.
Find out what the hell happened
in that apartment.
♪
We've been working round the clock.
I've only done a full autopsy
on your first John Doe.
What about dental?
Did you get anything from that?
Didn't match any of our records.
And honestly you're not gonna get much.
Bodies burned this badly
rarely have a ton
of forensic evidence.
Tox was clear on John Doe one.
W-what is this chipping
of the hyoid and spine?
It's usually cracking from the fire,
but what's strange is both bodies had it.
Cracking of the hyoid?
On one, it's an anomaly.
- On two...
- It's a pattern.
Same kind of cracking
you'd get from a weapon?
- From a knife.
- So they were stabbed?
Yes, and throat sliced.
- Sarge?
- Yeah, I'm still listening.
All right, M.E. also found
three old bullet holes
and a severed finger on John Doe two.
We ran that through
every system we've got.
So far no hit on an ID,
but those are pretty unique identifiers.
So, flag it up the ladder with FBI.
See if they'll run it.
Hit hospital records too.
I've got spotty elevator
and lobby cameras,
but the camera nearest the entrance
got fritzed out in the fire.
The building across the street
got surveillance from the front.
I got POD footage from
the exit in the back,
but it's not perfect.
When Chicago Fire responded,
they blocked the camera.
All right, well,
start clearing through it fast.
Hey, we got anything on that apartment?
Nothing but sand, Sarge.
It was registered under a dummy
LLC called Cyde Holdings
that does not exist.
There's no in service calls,
no priors on anyone so far
in the apartment. Burgess is still there.
She's debriefing the current residents.
So far everybody's saying they thought
the apartment was vacant.
Hey, Sarge, OCD tech lab pulled
coordinates off Jane Doe's GPS chip.
I've got every place she's been
the last two months
outside Chicago... all two of them.
Tracked a farmland outside
Durango, Mexico,
and a compound two miles from Cleveland.
I ran those coordinates
for John Doe's bullet wounds,
for the finger injury.
Got a hit.
♪
Edgar Torres.
You're saying Edgar Torres
of the Sinaloa Cartel
just got hit in Chicago?
Hey, Hank.
You got a problem downstairs.
Come on, Antonio.
- You and me.
- Yeah.
Hey, find out what Torres
was doing in Chicago, Jay.
♪
Wondering why the hell
you ran DEA's number five
most wanted and requested sixes
without picking up the phone
and calling us.
Well, I'm wondering
why the hell you weren't aware
your number five target was in Chicago
and that he was just murdered.
We been trying to track him,
but it's not easy.
When Torres comes to Chicago
he stays low...
holds a few meetings,
oversees a few loads,
and we don't hear about it until after.
And he doesn't communicate.
No cell, no email.
He stays inside. He eats in.
It's just him, his security,
and his girl of the month.
Those are the other bodies you found.
Okay, well, someone knew
he was here this time.
We're not here to hinder
your investigation, Voight.
Okay, so why are you here?
We'll be taking Edgar Torres' body.
You want to confirm his death,
cross a name off a list? Be my guest.
And we want you to low-walk the case.
There it is.
We have wires up
on every cartel with holdings in Chicago.
Not a single wire indicates
that anyone knows
Torres is even dead,
let alone that it was a hit.
It would be best it stays that way.
Soon as they become aware,
every phone will go dark.
- And bodies will drop.
- With all due respect,
this was a mass murder,
so we're not gonna stop till
we find the son of a bitch
that lit the match,
cartel repercussions or not.
We can tell the press
the fire was accidental
and we can move quiet,
but you gotta give me
every piece of paper you have on Torres.
No blacked out lines.
No red tape.
You do that,
I'll tiptoe anywhere you want.
This is the last batch.
I mean, there's hundreds
of people who wanted Edgar Torres dead.
Hundreds who'd want him dead,
but only a few who would have access.
And the guy was old school... no phones,
did business face to face.
That's why the DEA
never got close to him.
15 years they had Torres ID'd.
They could never find a way
to infiltrate. Guy was a ghost.
Think someone was involved on the inside.
So let's start in his inner circle.
People who were loyal.
Yeah, people who would never roll.
Carlos Mendoza, 56 years old.
Been in Chicago for the past 30.
DEA caught him up seven years ago,
thought he was Torres' driver.
Held him for 48, grilled him,
and they got absolutely nothing.
Carlos never said a word.
All right, so where's Carlos now?
Lives right here in Chicago.
Lives alone in Fuller Park.
Also has two adult sons.
But we still believe
he's involved with the cartel.
Gets paid every week
from a trumped-up LLC.
Ran Carlos' cell.
Pinged a tower outside
Colima, Mexico a few days ago.
Matches Jane Doe's
GPS coordinates to a T.
Right, so, picked up Torres' girlfriend
and the bodyguard down in Mexico
and drove them all back here.
- Just to sell his ass out.
- Mm-hmm.
We got Carlos on footage.
Traffic cam caught him in a silver SUV
parked outside the apartment
for eight hours.
Was he there during the fire?
Whole time.
Let's move.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
All right, we move careful and silent.
Ruzek, you're with me.
Burgess, Upton, you take downstairs.
Halstead, secure the back. Do not enter.
Okay? Let's go.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
[DOOR CLANKING]
[SHUFFLING]
[DOOR THUDDING]
Freeze!
What the hell are you doing?
Damn it, Jay.
- Why did you come inside?
- 'Cause I saw movement.
Jay, I almost shot you.
Yeah, but you didn't, all right?
You broke the plan.
I almost put a bullet in your head.
Carlos was going for the back door
so I had to make a move,
all right? Let's go.
Target apprehended. We're coming out.
Copy that.
Come on.
♪
Edgar Torres...
cartel head, drug trafficker,
and the DEA's number five
Oh hurrah! most wanted.
That's him three weeks ago.
Oh, wait, I got a picture too.
That's him today.
Now, Edgar Torres is also your boss.
You're one of very few
who knew he was here.
And that's you
outside the building
while Torres is being stabbed to death.
And I'm just doing the
math here, Carlos, but...
I wouldn't want to be you.
You know I'm not gonna talk to you.
Yes, you will,
because right now, me and him...
we're your best shot
at seeing the light again. So the quicker
you start talking to us,
the more honest you get,
the better this goes.
And if you had the evidence
to make that true, you'd be charging me.
When you're charged that's
the least of your problems.
Bro.
Cartel's got to be asking
the same questions we are.
And if that were true,
I'd already be dead.
I don't talk to you.
All right, you be cute all you want.
That's up to you.
But this isn't just bad guy on bad guy.
Five other innocent people
were killed in that fire.
Know what that means?
That means you're never leaving this room
unless you talk.
Then you and I are at a standstill.
And one of those innocent people?
He was a cop's father.
You understand it yet, Carlos?
You know, it wouldn't be a bad thing
to sit this one out.
- Need me to talk to you?
- I don't need anything, Jay.
All right, look, my father and I...
we never clicked.
He didn't want me to enlist.
He didn't want me to be a cop.
Guy didn't even show up when I graduated
from the academy.
He was embarrassed.
So I learned to keep my distance,
and now he's gone. That's it.
I'm learning how to deal
with it on my own.
You don't have to question
if I'm all right.
[INDISTINCT INTERROGATION]
Carlos isn't talking yet.
We need leverage.
I've looked through
every hour of footage.
There's no evidence that Carlos
ever enters the building.
We got Torres, Jane Doe, his security.
They all come in
five hours before the fire
but after that it's only residents.
And I've gone through it twice.
Yeah, we've cleared
everyone in that building.
None of them look like they're involved.
All right, so we go back to basics.
Antonio, keep working Carlos
while we backtrack.
Look, no one just wakes up
in the morning and decides
to make a play on a cartel boss.
There was planning.
Someone got in that building,
did those murders,
set that fire.
Find out how. That'll get us to who.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
First body was found in here,
inside the door.
Well, if he came in through the hallway,
security let him in.
Security knew him.
I mean, that fits with Carlos, right?
Second body was found in bed there.
Arson said the body was prone.
Guy never got up.
All right, so offender comes in,
takes security out of the equation,
moves in here. Torres is asleep.
He takes him out nice and easy.
Starts the fire here unaware
that Jane Doe is hiding.
- There's no other exits?
- Only the front door.
These windows are a 20-story drop.
♪
Or he came from next door.
The roof next door had
a hidden security camera.
Facial recognition ID'd Daniel
Mendoza in under a minute.
Carlos' oldest son.
He's caught on this roof
four times in the past week
including an hour before
the fire went off.
All he would have had to do
is hop over to the window
once the fire was going.
Cameras are being destroyed.
People were evacuating.
He could have walked out the front door.
Daniel Mendoza is the black
sheep out of the two brothers...
in and out of behavior programs.
Got kicked out of Harper
College after a semester
for anger issues.
Daniel's working for a trucking company
that's hauling produce
from Mexico to Chicago.
They changed their IDOT
four times in the last year.
The company's owned by
the same trumped-up LLC
who's paying off Carlos.
He's cartel. Like father, like son.
It's the same boss too. Torres.
Yeah. Huh.
You know, it could be a power play.
Cartels are organizations,
so if Daniel and Carlos
are working beneath Torres,
Torres holds their fate.
If he isn't willing to promote...
You get rid of him,
find a new boss who is.
Get an expedited warrant.
You had your son killed for you.
And you told him, "Torres is inside."
He sneaks in, takes care
of the messy details.
You both profit,
except something went wrong.
Kid didn't expect Jane Doe
to survive, right?
It's not possible.
There's seven bodies on
you and your boy right now.
I mean, you wanna take
any of that weight off,
now's the time to talk.
No.
I got nothing to say.
Warrant's ready to go.
♪
Chicago PD!
[ELECTRONIC WHIRRING]
Whoa, everybody stop.
Do not key your radios.
♪
The cameras are motion censored?
Yeah, motion censored and hooked up
to Daniel Mendoza's cloud.
As soon as we moved in, cameras recorded
- and sent images digitally.
- That's smart.
I mean, this apartment's gotta
be his contingency plan.
He set it up as a fail-safe.
If his plan failed and
the cartel came for him,
the apartment would alert him.
Hey, here he is. What's up?
Hank, it doesn't look like
there's any sign of explosives.
The place is clear of chemicals.
Just looks like the apartment
was rigged with the cameras.
We're almost finished clearing.
So we're waiting for nothing.
He's probably in the damn wind.
We basically just told him to run.
All right, so we get ahead of him.
Get out a BOLO, investigative alert,
- emergency ping.
- All right.
- Thanks, Sully.
- You got it.
Kelly, appreciate it.
Jay.
Yo, I've been meaning to tell you, I'm...
Don't, don't.
Kelly, honestly, man, you're...
you're, like, the only guy
that hasn't given me some
half-ass sympathy speech.
- So you don't have to, all right?
- No. It's all good.
I wasn't going to.
I was gonna say I wanna
be here when you find him.
We pulled bodies out of that fire.
I watched Stella almost lose her life...
for a cartel hit?
Anything I can do to help...
anything... I'll help.
All right. Thanks, man.
♪
All right, transport teams are up...
airports, trains, buses, and highways.
- Thank you.
- Yep.
We got BOLOs out on his vehicle,
checking the traffic cams and PODS.
We tapping into the El.
CTA has all his descriptors, and
Antonio's hitting his contacts now.
- Cell?
- Dark.
Daniel turned it off. No movement.
Yeah, he's gonna know better than that.
He'll have an exit strategy.
An exit strategy he
wasn't expecting to use.
I mean, I don't know if
it'll be easy to execute.
He hasn't had more than
a grand in his bank account.
He's gonna need help
getting out of Chicago.
Or he just steals a car
and he heads for the border.
Hmm.
We need another access point.
Carlos is our only option.
Daniel followed his father's
footsteps into the cartel.
Whether or not Carlos ordered him
to kill Torres doesn't matter.
He got where he is because
his father led him there.
Phone records indicate him
and his father talk a lot,
at least twice a day.
Yeah, so he's gonna know
where his son is,
or how to get in touch with him.
We gotta force him to talk.
All right. You and me.
[DOOR OPENING]
- Hey, rise and shine.
- [GROANS]
- Come on, wake up.
Let's go.
- I'd like a lawyer.
- Huh.
Yeah. Yeah, we could do that.
Or we could just tell you the truth.
We got jack on you.
I mean, we can't prove
you entered the building.
We got no bead on your kid.
Okay, then release me.
You sure about that?
'Cause all we gotta do is
give your name to your people
and we'll let you go.
♪
You're a dead man.
You're a smart guy, Carlos.
You worked with Sinaloa for decades,
but you know how this
is gonna end for you,
for your son.
Nice and slow.
Gonna tie you down with barbed wire.
They're gonna probably burn you first...
your feet, genitals.
Make you beg.
Then they'll wire you to a generator.
They're gonna electrocute you.
They're gonna cut your heads off
and hang you upside down from
the Franklin Street Bridge...
♪
Unless you wanna help us.
Tell us what happened.
Help us find Daniel.
Come on.
I mean, prison ain't great,
but it's better than that.
You know what?
I dug my grave a long time ago.
Whatever you think of me,
I tried like hell
to give my kids a good life...
♪
A better life, a different life.
But Daniel, he chose this.
He... there's nothing I could do.
These men could find
him or me just as easily
in any jail cell.
You can't protect us.
You know we're dead either way.
Hmm.
I will not help you.
♪
I'm not gonna help you kill my son.
Juan Mendoza. He's 28 years old.
He's Carlos' other son.
He's got no connection to the cartel.
He's married. He's got three kids.
He's got a good job downtown.
We pick him up, he's our
access point to Carlos.
We ran Juan. We got nothing on him.
They don't know that.
Contrary to public opinion,
fathers have favorites.
If we squeeze Juan,
Carlos rolls on Daniel.
Okay, it's too risky.
We get Juan involved,
then he's actually involved.
The cartel starts gunning for him too.
Yeah, man. That ain't right. There's
gotta be a better way to do this.
Like what?
♪
Exactly. We're at a dead end, right?
I don't even know why
we're debating this.
Because we're playing with
an innocent man's life, Jay.
Five other innocent people
died because of this guy's
not-so-innocent brother and father.
So I'm sorry if my heart
doesn't bleed like yours.
- Excuse me?
- Okay.
That's enough.
It's what we have. It's what we'll use.
Bring him in.
♪
[WHISTLING]
That's him.
Juan Mendoza.
Chicago Police. I'm Officer Ruzek.
This is Detective Upton.
What's going on?
Just wanna bring you down
to the district, ask you a few questions.
- It's gonna be nice and easy.
- Questioning for what?
We'll clear all that up at the district.
- I don't think so.
- Listen, man, listen, hey.
We just need to talk to you,
ask you a few questions.
That's all.
No.
- Sir, if you could please...
- Look, I just said no.
You have information that can help us.
I assure you, I don't.
You know why we're bringing you in.
Your family's all hooked up.
Your brother...
Look, what my family does
is of no concern to me...
No concern? No concern?
Jay, we're outside.
Mass murder's no concern to you?
Jay, not here, man.
Not when I know nothing
that could help you.
We're not asking you.
We're telling you... move.
Hey look, man, you just need to...
- Move!
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Jay, back off!
- It's harassment.
- It's harassment!
- Back off!
- Keep walking.
- You good?
Yeah, I'm good.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪
I don't even know
what you're talking about.
Accessory? Conspiracy to commit murder?
Your father told us he told you that
Edgar Torres was in town.
No, he didn't.
We never talked about him
or drugs or any of it, ever.
You had breakfast two weeks ago?
Yeah.
He's my father. We had breakfast.
Are ham and cheese omelets
suddenly illegal?
No, but homicide is,
and he told you where
Edgar Torres would be and when.
That's right, then you called Daniel
and relayed the info to him, right?
And helped him with the murder.
[SCOFFING] This is insane.
Look, I know my brother's no saint,
but that has nothing to do with me.
You're not seeming to understand
what's happening, Juan.
You're in the middle of
a very bad situation.
Look, I've got three kids. All right?
A job... a real job that
you dragged me away from.
You think this is gonna work?
I don't know,
but we're already down
the road, so I hope so.
Get up.
What?
We're letting you go. Come on.
- How's that possible?
- 'Cause time's up.
We don't have enough
evidence to charge you.
So let's go.
- What's going on?
- Hey, come on.
- Let's go.
- Well, that's... that's my son.
- What's Juan doing in there?
- Just keep moving.
- What is he doing in there?
- Sir, you need to keep moving.
What is Juan doing in there?
Juan's there because
we believe he's involved.
- Look, that's not possible!
- Yes, it is.
He's your son. He's Daniel's brother.
It makes perfect sense he's involved.
No, you can't have him
in there, all right?
- He didn't do anything.
- Yes, he did.
That's why we're taking him to county.
He can't go to county! No, no, no!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- I got it. I got it.
Calm down, or I'm gonna book you, too,
and let them kill
the whole family in county.
You can't have him in there!
They're gonna kill him!
It's already done! He's going!
I never talked to him about my job.
- Juan is straight.
- Well, what about Daniel?
I told Daniel that
I was picking up Torres.
Please. Please, whatever you want.
Just let Juan go.
He's not involved in any of this stuff.
Please.
So you told Daniel Torres was in Chicago?
Yes, but we were just talking.
I had no idea he was gonna take him out.
You didn't tell him to kill Torres?
No, of course not.
Look, I'm a driver.
I don't sell drugs. I don't kill people.
I drive.
I never imagined Daniel
would do something like that,
- but he must've seen a chance.
- For what?
For power.
All Daniel wanted
was weight in the cartel.
I don't give him any... the opposite.
I'm the help... no different
than the maid or a gardener.
But with Torres gone,
Daniel would move up.
Now that's the truth.
Now, just let Juan go. Please.
The truth is, none of that matters
unless you tell us how to find Daniel.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
It's an easy choice.
It's the son who did everything wrong,
or it's the one who listened.
Look, you are not a father!
This is not how you love your children!
Carlos! We need to go now.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
You give us Daniel,
or we are gonna go charge Juan.
What do you want?
I could get in touch with Daniel.
♪
Just let Juan go. Please.
Please.
So Carlos and Daniel have a
shared disposable email account
that Carlos set up
for hazards of the job.
Yeah, they only
communicate through drafts
so nothing ever leaves the server.
We can't ping them through email alone.
All right, but Carlos reached out.
He told Daniel that he wasn't safe.
He was gonna help him get out of Chicago.
Daniel agreed to keep his phone on.
4:00 p.m. today.
Daniel's gonna keep
his phone off until then.
All right, well, you're with Carlos.
He makes a call,
you ping Daniel's location.
Rest of us, we're gonna
set up a citywide grid.
Okay? Get everyone on board.
We're gonna be in teams of two.
As soon as Antonio calls with a location,
we move in quick, steady, silent.
Let's go.
- [RADIO CHIRPS]
- We're in position.
West side, 33rd and Normal.
All right, copy that.
Just below the north side.
All right, as soon as we get
the location, teams move out.
You get there first, you hit it.
All right, Antonio, you set?
We're good to go. Wire's up.
♪
All right, now,
when Daniel turns his phone on,
longitude and latitude
will come up on the screen instantly,
but you need to keep Daniel on the phone
as long as possible.
- If he shuts the phone off...
- I understand it.
Look... [SIGHS]
You're doing the right thing
for both your children.
There is no right thing.
♪
Two minutes out. Be ready to move.
Jay.
You're not coming.
What?
Give her your keys and your two-way.
You gotta be kidding me.
It's for the best, Jay.
Keys and the two-way.
You're too close to this, Jay.
The hell does that mean?
He's your dad. I didn't say anything...
You don't know anything about my dad.
- I'm not pretending to.
- No, you're just projecting
whatever daddy-daughter crap
got you screwed up.
Okay, I'm done being your punching bag.
Give me your keys.
Give me your damn keys!
[KEYS JINGLING]
Two-way.
[SIGHS]
You ready?
♪
Danny?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
♪
You said if I needed help
that you would help.
I need help.
- Did you bring your radio?
- Yeah.
You're not gonna get a police frequency.
That's all right. If he's shot,
they're gonna need an ambo,
if they're in pursuit,
they're gonna shut down traffic.
Ambo 26, adult female,
short of breath, 6400 Racine.
You're on Englewood. Switch to Main.
Turn it all the way to the left.
Ambo 62, Engine 83,
we got a pin-in accident.
Dearborn and Monroe, multiple victims.
CPD not responding.
They got an officer assistance
call near the Michigan Bridge.
Squad One, possible drowning
North Avenue Beach.
Be advised we got Stenson
being closed off by CPD
and CTA is rerouting
at Wacker and Columbus.
Ambo 64, Unit 1800,
CPD Commander Meldune
requesting you stand by at Michigan.
Reports of an armed
Hispanic male in the area.
That's him. He's running.
[ENGINE TURNS OVER]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Whoa!
What are you doing?
Lieutenant Kelly Severide, CFD.
- What's happening?
- Man with a gun, but hey...
- We got eyes on the offender?
- No.
Last seen on foot headed eastbound,
- but Intelligence...
- I'm Intelligence.
- Give me your radio.
- My radio?
- Give me your radio, man.
- Hey, hey.
- Kelly.
- We're good, just find him.
- [CARS HONKING]
- What are you doing?
Columbus and North Water.
1811, 12, 13, 16,
19 per 1800 Commander Meldune.
Need you to head over
to Wacker and Dearborn.
5021 Ida, get me a couple
guys up on the bridge.
I see two units up there.
Tell them to shut down Northbound.
♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Stop! Police!
Out of my way. Out of my way.
Out of my way!
Police! Stop!
♪
[TRUCK HONKS]
[PANTING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GRUNTS]
[STRAINED VOICE] Please.
Help me, please.
- [COUGHS]
- [PANTING]
Please.
Please!
[LABORED BREATHING]
Help me!
I wanna see my father... [COUGHS]
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
This... this is 5021 George, emergency.
Shots fired.
Offender down. Need an ambo.
Lower Wacker and Columbus.
Just try to get him some help.
Get him help.
Copy that. [RADIO CHATTER]
[GRUNTING SOFTLY]
♪
[TIRES SQUEALING]
That's Jay. That's Jay.
5021 Henry! Officer down!
I repeat, officer down.
Lower Wacker and Columbus.
Get us an ambulance. Jay?
- You okay?
- [RADIO CHATTER]
Come on!
[GRUNTS, PANTING]
- It didn't go through.
- Hailey, what's going on?
It didn't go through. It's okay.
- [SIRENS WAILING]
- Jay, Jay, breathe, breathe.
Okay. You're okay.
Guys! Can you block off the street?
Do whatever you gotta do
to get an ambulance in, now!
- All right?
- Copy that!
Okay.
♪
Jay, do you hear me?
You understand?
Yeah.
I still need you to go to Med
to check for internal.
You have no broken ribs.
The bullet didn't hit anything.
The second bullet that got your
side was a through and through.
Bruising's gonna be a bitch, though.
That pain'll knock you backwards
once the edge wears off.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
You all right?
Yeah.
Damn lucky.
- I...
- No. You are done talking.
I mean done.
You should be dead.
Do you get that?
You do not disobey
a direct order from me.
I don't care how angry you are.
You're mourning, grieving...
man, I don't care
if your whole damn family
just got murdered.
You listen to me!
It's my job to keep you alive,
to look out for you.
I will always do my job,
and you will always do yours and listen.
That's the deal.
♪
When your head is on straight...
we are gonna talk about this again.
All right.
[INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER]
Daniel?
He was pronounced at Med.
Antonio's with Juan and Carlos.
He's taking them into protective custody.
DEA says bodies are already
dropping in Mexico, so...
So a happy ending?
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪
Hailey, um...
I just couldn't stop myself.
Thanks, guys, appreciate it. Thank you.
Hey.
- Hey.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Oh.
Ah, yeah, that's the adrenaline.
- I thought he was dead.
- Yeah, me too.
You know what?
You want to get out of here
and grab a drink?
- Yeah.
- All right, let's go.
♪
[SOMBER MUSIC]
[SCOFFS]
♪
[CRIES SOFTLY]