Twenty years ago,
this neighborhood
was all deep-dish.
Now it's flatbread and kabobs.
Things change.
Yeah, I hear you.
Welcome, brothers.
That's Akeem.
Welcome.
America is not
the land of freedom.
It is the land of inequality.
Minorities don't wear chains,
but they are still slaves
to a system
that serves the rich.
The shiny toys of capitalism
mean nothing to Allah.
This is why Islam
is such a threat to America.
What they want,
what they live for,
can only be accomplished
by our elimination.
So that the wheels of greed
and capitalism
can continue to turn.
Only through Allah
will we deliver
the equity and the sovereignty.
So we must fight
at whatever cost
to serve the eternal truth.
Allahu Akbar.
Allahu Akbar!
I got eyes on Akeem.
Copy.
Why are you here?
I came to talk to Akeem.
Wait, wait, wait!
Give him a sec.
Kevin doesn't have a gun.
He's got this.
He's not seeing visitors.
Peace, brother.
Relax. I'm only here to help.
Understand me?
Jamel.
What is it?
I found Abdul walking around...
Abdul.
You know this part of the mosque
is forbidden to you.
Yes.
Brother Akeem,
I'm terribly sorry,
But I have to talk to you.
About what?
I want to join the fight.
I can't wait anymore.
What are you talking about?
The bombing.
Last week at the Army
recruiting station.
Tell me, Abdul.
What is your opinion
on this action?
My opinion is
you didn't go far enough.
A bomb is nice,
but it's gotta do damage.
People have to die.
I feel your anger, Abdul.
But we had nothing to do
with that bombing.
We fight with our hearts
and minds.
The time is coming
when much will be asked of you.
Be patient.
Be ready.
- You good?
- Yeah, I'm good.
I tried to get Akeem
to talk about the bombings.
- He shut me down.
- Are you sure
his security guard
didn't make you?
Jamel just hates Americans
on principle.
My cover's still good, though.
All right, so stay under.
Keep pushing.
I don't know
what we're waiting for.
These guys already
detonated one bomb.
Let's bring Akeem in.
We don't have any evidence
he's involved.
The "Chicago Must Burn"
manifesto
was uploaded from a computer
inside that mosque.
You ask me, that's proof enough.
Well, if you ask me, it's not.
We need solid evidence
before we move on Akeem.
There's too many eyes on this.
Another bomb threat.
VA Hospital.
You and Hailey go check it out.
All right.
Be safe.
What do we got?
So far, nothing.
Just like the last four
bomb scares.
My dogs are gonna put in
for overtime.
The witness who called it in
said he saw a guy with a beard
and a backpack
who looked Middle Eastern.
And he got a bad feeling.
Great, so we're chasing
bad feelings.
The joke is our witness
is here for cataract surgery.
He's legally blind.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Cordon off this area,
I want a one-block perimeter.
Are you guys okay?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we're good.
- I need some help over here!
- Hey, hey!
You're gonna be all right.
I got you, okay?
- Femoral?
- That's what it looks like.
- All right.
- I'm gonna get a doctor.
- Yeah!
- No time.
Here, give me
some pressure on this wound.
I'm gonna tie it off.
Here. Hey, hang in there.
Stay with us, all right?
- You're gonna be okay.
- Okay.
You're gonna be all right.
Hang in there.
Come on, come on, come on!
Get her up!
Get a clamp on that femoral
or we're gonna lose her!
You're gonna be all right!
Guessing that wasn't the first
fragmentation wound you've seen.
No. 75th Rangers. Jay Halstead.
Chicago PD now.
5th SF Group, Fort Campbell.
Jake Miller.
I know the name.
I've heard epic stories, man.
Yeah.
Excuse us.
What do we got?
Single detonation.
We're sweeping the premises now.
Trying to sort out the damage.
All right, we need to anticipate
secondary devices
targeting first responders.
I want you to widen and ziplock
a four-block perimeter.
- Nobody gets in or out.
- Gotcha.
Hey, Sarge.
Talked to a vet
named Jake Miller.
He confirmed the initial ID.
Bearded Middle Eastern man
with a backpack.
- Okay, we'll run with it.
- All right.
- Hey, you okay?
- It's not mine.
This is ground zero.
- Got it.
- Some kind of shape charge.
Little structural damage,
but most of the force
went into the monument.
Hit a couple
of these cars as well.
Bomb Squad's still
collecting forensics,
but it appears to be
the same type of device
that was used at
the Army recruitment center.
All right, find
surveillance video
and look for more witnesses.
Lot of windows in this building.
Somebody saw something.
Hank.
Will Graff.
You're a long way from D.C.
I'm gonna need
all your intel, Hank.
We'll be taking this over.
- It's my city.
- My jurisdiction.
I'll need the files.
Look.
Before you blow this up,
you should know
I got a man undercover
inside Akeem Dabiri's mosque.
Okay.
What's his name?
Forget it.
So what are you proposing?
We share intel.
We'll do the legwork,
you take the glory.
I want regular reports.
And, Hank, do not
screw me on this.
Come on, guys.
Bomb tech Sarah Scott.
Sergeant First Class, retired.
Senior NCO.
Made it through three tours
in Afghanistan for this.
Left behind a husband
and two daughters.
Witnesses?
Just the two vets.
Both saw the same thing,
a bearded man with a backpack.
And both said that
he looked "Middle Eastern."
What about surveillance
video at the VA?
This is all we got.
Cameras are garbage,
but this is our suspect
walking into the VA.
Labs came back on the explosive.
Peroxide, acetone.
It's highly unstable
but it's still an ISIS fave,
becauseget this...
Dogs can't smell it.
The bomb was on a timer
loaded with 16 penny nails
and ball bearings.
Same as the bomb
at the recruitment center.
Forensics is tracking it.
All right, see if anyone
in the mosque
is in the trades.
You know, framing, roofing,
that kind of thing.
Here's CTA's footage
at the time of the bombing.
Found a guy that matches
our description.
Gray hoodie, beard.
Now that's him exiting
the L at Taylor Street.
It's a block away
from Akeem's mosque.
It was 28 minutes
after the blast.
All right, enough is enough.
We know that Akeem is involved
so let's go pick him up.
I agree. Bring him in.
All right.
Jay.
Look, I know
these kind of cases,
they can bring up bad memories.
Sarge.
Somebody just died.
Just follow the facts.
All right.
Where was I this morning?
This sounds like a line
from one of your movies.
This is not a movie.
To answer your question,
I was leading prayers
this morning.
And then I took my wife
to the dentist.
She needed a root canal.
This man was seen
in the VA this morning
at the time of the bombing.
Do you recognize him?
Why would I recognize him?
Because he looks Muslim?
No.
Because we have a photo of him
28 minutes after the bombing
exiting the L station
a block from your mosque.
Lots of people
live near my mosque.
But I promise it wasn't me.
We didn't say it was you.
I don't know this man.
And I had nothing to do
with the bombs.
I find that pretty hard
to believe.
Why?
Because I exercise my right
to free speech?
No, because I read
your anti-American,
hate-spewing manifesto
posted the day before
the first bomb went off
at the Army recruiting center.
I know nothing
about any manifesto.
But it came
from inside your mosque.
Over your Wi-Fi.
We have the computer forensics
to prove it.
Your forensics prove nothing.
I don't control the internet.
Or any other people
in my community,
or what they do or say.
Tell us about the Gauge Park
Islamic Relief Fund.
Yeah, we ran your financials.
I assumed as much.
So what is it?
A charity
for displaced refugees.
Do you think we're stupid?
It's a 501c3.
You can look it up
yourself, please.
Now,
if you're going to charge me,
charge me.
If not, I'm leaving.
We should have held
onto him, Sarge.
Yeah, but we have no evidence.
Yeah, but we could have
kept him in a cold cell
for 47 hours
without evidence, right?
Relax.
We kicked the hornet's nest.
Now let's see how Akeem reacts.
Sarge?
We found another security camera
near the VA, outside a 7-Eleven.
Look, this is our suspect
walking towards the VA
five minutes before the bombing.
This is the suspect right after
the bombing, no backpack.
Did you text these pics
to Kevin?
Yeah, he recognizes the guy.
His name is Tariq Hassam
and I just got a match
on facial rec.
He works at a loading dock
in Little Kabul.
Hit it.
Hey. You the foreman?
- Yeah?
- We're looking for
one of your workers,
Tariq Hassam.
Why?
Because we're looking for him.
Where is he?
He's loading a truck.
Tariq Hassam!
Chicago PD, on the ground!
Chicago PD, hands in the air!
Nowhere to hide, man.
Hey, I'll get the back!
The target's on the roof.
We don't have eyes.
Right here, right here.
Antonio!
Antonio.
We got a problem up here.
Put the phone down!
Put it down. Show me your hands!
Keep your hands
where we can see them.
Come on, man.
We don't want to hurt you.
Keep your hands
where we can see them!
Allahu Akbar!
I'll take it. Thanks.
Got the phone.
Or what's left of it.
All right, get it to OCD.
Find out who he called
before he jumped.
It confirms he's working
with a partner.
No, it confirms
he made a phone call.
That's it, that's all we got.
Sarge, these guys
don't work alone.
Jay, I told you.
We're gonna take this
one step at a time.
So call the bomb techs,
get into Tariq's house,
scrub it.
I'll loop in the Feds.
Door's safe.
No wires, no triggers.
Living room looks clear.
All right, we're good here.
We're gonna take the lead.
You guys get upstairs.
- All right.
- Crossing.
- You ready?
- Go.
Clear.
Go, go.
- You got me?
- Yeah.
Standbypossible target
in the basement.
Copy that.
Chicago PD.
Let me see your hands.
Don't move.
Show us your hands now.
Everybody clear the area.
Possible offender with a bomb.
No, no, hold on,
hold on, Jay, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait. Hailey, stop.
Hailey, what are you doing?
We're not gonna hurt you.
We're not gonna hurt you, okay?
Hailey.
Hailey, she might have a bomb.
What are you doing?
Okay?
We just want to see your hands.
Can you put your hands up?
Hailey! Get out of the way.
Just wait. Hold on!
We're not gonna hurt you, okay?
Let me just see. Let me see.
Hailey.
It's a baby. It's a baby, okay?
She's just scared.
- Show us what's underneath.
- She's scared, Jay.
Hold on.
Okay.
She's unarmed.
It's okay. Aw, okay.
Okay.
You okay?
Yeah, I... yeah.
You?
Yeah.
We're not mind readers, Hailey.
We didn't know what was
underneath that burqa.
I know. Until we did.
Until we saw it was a baby.
Well, not necessarily.
She's not gonna hurt
her own child.
I have seen it happen.
I know, but you're not
in Afghanistan anymore.
Her name's Ara Hassam.
She's Tariq's sister.
Documents are good.
Not on any watch list.
She came from Kabul
three weeks ago to visit Tariq.
Interesting timing.
Background check looks clear.
You guys, I got something.
Jay, you know what that is?
Yeah, it's a NATO
service medal for valor.
It belongs to Tariq.
Hold on, the guy
who blew up the VA
has a NATO service medal
for valor?
I got something else.
Application to become
a U.S. citizen.
And look who the sponsor is.
Thanks.
Do you know who this is?
Yeah.
Yeah, that's Tariq Hassam.
We did two tours together.
He was my translator.
You wrote him a letter
of recommendation.
Yeah, I did.
Easiest letter I ever wrote.
Why is that?
Tariq saved more American
lives than I can count.
Okay, what's going on?
What happened?
We believe Tariq planted
the bomb at the VA.
What? No.
No. That's impossible.
I-I don't believe that
for a second.
The evidence is pretty solid.
Where is he now?
What, did you arrest him?
No, he's dead.
When we went to arrest him,
Tariq killed himself.
He jumped off a building.
If you don't mind me asking,
why didn't you ID Tariq
at the VA?
Excuse me?
You were 50 feet away from him.
Like I told you.
Okay? I barely saw the guy.
I just, I caught
a glimpse of the beard
and the backpack.
Not to mention Tariq is, like,
the last person on Earth
I would ever think would do
something like this.
Why, because he loved America?
No.
Because he hated extremists.
When the Taliban found out
that he was working for us,
they raped and killed his wife.
When's the last time
you saw Tariq?
I don't know. It was...
a while ago.
We kinda lost touch.
But make no mistake.
The Tariq that I knew
was a good man.
He was a patriot.
You buy his story?
Miller's? Yeah, why wouldn't I?
You really think
he didn't recognize Tariq?
A guy he did two tours with?
I just think he wasn't
paying attention.
Or he's covering for him.
He's got two Purple Hearts
and a Silver Star
for saving the lives of a
couple downed Apache pilots
who were under fire.
He's not covering for anybody
detonating bombs.
They got a hit on Tariq's phone.
Last call is to Akeem. Shocker.
Now we got to find
some evidence.
All right, I'll call Atwater.
Approaching Akeem's office now.
All right.
I hope he knows what he's doing.
He'll signal if he needs us.
Yep. I'm in.
Pretty simple office.
Lots of paperwork.
Prayer books.
Got a spot for a bug.
Move and you die.
It's Homeland.
You violate our right
to free speech!
Our right to assemble!
This is America?
This ain't right!
This whole city can go to hell.
We gotta get him out of there.
- No, we can't blow his cover.
- Adam...
Abdul, right?
Tell me everything.
First of all, I don't even
know why the hell I'm here.
I told you,
I didn't do anything.
Yeah, we just want to
talk to you.
And your brothers.
Get me a lawyer.
That's not the way
it works, Abdul.
I need answers.
Slow down.
Doesn't have to
go down like this.
Turn around and face the wall.
You don't know what the hell
you're doing.
We're gonna find out
where you and your friends
planted the next bomb.
Come on, man. Listen to me.
You have three seconds.
Listen to me! I'm an undercover
cop for Chicago PD...
Agh!
Shut the hell up
and give me something!
- Hey! Hey!
- Hell is wrong with you?
What the hell are you doing?
- Who the hell are you?
- Who am I?
Stay calm. Hank, relax.
Like I said, we made a mistake.
I told you I got a man under.
You don't give me a heads up?
I asked who your guy was.
You told me to go to hell,
remember?
Look. We're sorry.
If we'd known beforehand,
it wouldn't have
gone down like this.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Let's move on
and talk about these bombs.
So why the raid?
Is there something we need
to know about?
We picked up some chatter
this morning.
Another attack is imminent.
So we hit the mosque.
Now what?
We're gonna talk to Akeem.
Do what we have to
to get him to talk to us.
In the meantime,
I suggest we put you
back in the cell
with the other suspects.
See if you can gather
any more intel.
You okay with that, Kev?
Yeah, I'm okay with that.
Okay.
Me and you gonna
sort this out one day.
Next time no zip ties,
no batons.
Graff interrogated Akeem
for five hours.
Didn't crack.
Claims he knows nothing about
the bomb, manifesto,
Tariq, none of it.
What about the other guys?
Same thing.
Yeah, and I got nothing
on Tariq.
Everybody I talked to said
they thought he was off.
Nobody actually knows him.
Some people said they thought
he was undercover.
Well, regardless, we have intel
that another attack
is in the works.
Right, Graff said
that the new threat
was posted online yesterday
at a Chicago public library.
All right, we got people
looking through surveillance
but so far nothing.
Antonio and I have been
scrolling through.
Tariq's various phones.
We found five or six photos
of Tariq and another man,
about the same age,
same ethnicity.
That was taken three days
before the first bomb went off.
- You run the photo?
- Yeah.
Came back negative.
But we did get a hit
on bomb fragments.
- Yes.
- Sixteen penny nails,
to be exact.
All right, track down
the specific batch number
and find the distributor.
Already on it.
We got the lot number
and delivery dates.
We're just closing in
on retailers in the area.
More witness statements
from Patrol.
We're wasting our time.
We know who's responsible.
Well, we might have
missed something.
Kim, Adam, split them up
and dig in.
Kev, I want you back
at the mosque.
See what you can learn.
You two go find Miller.
Maybe he can ID the guy
in the photo with Tariq.
Sherie Miller?
Yeah?
Detective Halstead
and Detective Upton,
Chicago PD.
We're here to see Jake.
Why, what's the matter?
Nothing's wrong, ma'am.
We just have a few questions.
Um, well, he's not here.
When does Jake usually get home?
That depends.
Whywhat's this all about?
Do you know these two men?
Yeah, that's Tariq
and his cousin Rafi.
And how do you know them?
Jake and Tariq served together
and his cousin Rafi
is visiting from Kabul.
We just had dinner last week.
So they still see each other?
Yeah, of course. Those two had
a pretty powerful bond.
The things that they saw,
that they did?
They're like brothers.
They'd die for each other.
That's a call to prayer.
Happens five times a day.
Makes Jake a little crazy.
Why is that?
You come home
after years at war,
looking for a little
peace and quiet
only to learn that
the very people
you were fighting
just moved in next door.
I get it, but...
it's not the same people.
Just the same religion.
Well.
It's easy for you to say,
'cause you weren't there.
Thank you so much for your time.
Will you let Jake know
that we stopped by?
Yeah.
So Miller's lying about
still being in touch with Tariq.
Yeah.
We got a hit yet
on that wholesaler?
The one who was selling
the nails used in the bomb?
Antonio was on it.
Let me call him.
All right.
Like I said on the phone.
I didn't sell it
to no terrorist.
I only had three sales
on that batch.
Just show us your video.
Yeah, I got it queued up.
Figured you guys
would be asking.
Here's the first purchase.
That don't look like
no terrorist to me.
Save the commentary and scroll.
Next purchase, 412.
Freeze it.
Thank you.
We'll need an expedited warrant.
I'll call Voight,
and have a judge lined up.
You tell the team we'll stage
a block away
from Miller's house.
Chicago PD, open up!
- Where's Jake?
- He's not home!
We have a warrant, ma'am,
if you could step to the side.
What the hell is this?
We think Jake's involved
in the bombing attacks.
- This floor is clear.
- What?
- Jake?
- Where is he?
He was here,
and then when I said
that you were looking for him,
he grabbed his keys
and he took off. Where'd he go?
I-I don't know, but
I could tell that something
was wrong.
Something's really wrong.
What do you mean?
Just in the way
that he looked at me.
The way that he...
That he said good-bye.
I swear I don't know
anything, but he...
he hasn't been okay
since he got back.
He needs help.
I got something.
You know anything about this?
It's for a storage trailer.
He rents it from our landlord.
What does he keep there?
He works there.
He flips motorcycles
to make extra cash.
Sit on the house.
Make sure she doesn't
warn him off.
He might come back.
I'm gonna hit up Voight,
fill him in.
Roger that.
Please, just promise me
you're not gonna hurt him.
Ma'am.
Are we really doing this
without bomb tech?
Damn right.
We don't have any time.
It's clear.
Okay, this is...
Scary as hell.
Yeah.
Acetone and hydrogen peroxide.
That's his cocktail.
He's still cooking.
What is all this?
It wasn't Akeem's call to prayer
that triggered Jake.
Listen to this.
"Six U.S. soldiers were killed
"when their patrol triggered
an IED near Lashkar.
"Lone survivor was Jacob Miller.
"Sunni warlords credit funding
from sympathetic parties
in America."
He underlined "funding."
Jake must think that Akeem
is funding terrorism
against American soldiers.
Okay.
So where's Miller now?
What's the strategy here?
It's an end game tactic.
You create a false retreat.
You flank, you ambush,
and you take out
the objective yourself.
He's going after Akeem.
We gotta call Kevin.
Come on, Kev, pick up, pick up.
5021 Henry...
Jake Miller's involved.
He's on his way to the mosque.
You gotta get everybody out now.
Hey.
No phones in the prayer hall.
Sorry, that was my cousin.
The FBI are at my house
right now
and they're on their way here
to round us all up
all over again. We gotta go.
We should leave right now.
No.
We stay.
We have done nothing wrong.
Freeze!
Nobody move!
Everybody get down
on the ground now.
- I said down!
- Stop, stop.
Get down on your face!
Put your hands above your head.
No.
You!
Down on your face! Now.
Please tell me
someone's listening
over the COH.
I got 30 people in here.
Miller has a gun
and an explosive.
I am unarmed.
I need help now.
Where is he?
Akeem's not here.
Homeland security,
they grabbed him up.
He's in lock-up.
If you want Akeem, you need
to let these people go.
Everybody crawls
to the wall now.
If anybody speaks another word,
I press this button,
we all blow up together.
Move.
Move!
- Talk to me, Trudy.
- Mobile command just landed.
We're pushing out four blocks
and trying to clear
all these buildings.
- Can you make it happen?
- Yeah.
Atwater inside?
Yeah. We can hear him,
he can't hear us.
Sounds like Miller's got
the IED strapped to his body.
He's got the remote in his hand.
Kev won't be able
to take him down alone.
It's too risky.
Bomb Squad's three minutes out.
- Sarge?
- Yeah.
There's no line of sight
into the prayer room.
I can get us elevated positions,
but unless he moves
to the front...
No, no, no. Let me get inside.
I can talk to him.
Hang on.
Atwater convinced him to open up
a line of communication.
They're sending someone out.
5021, I got a hostage
coming out.
Get me an ambulance
past that barricade.
Copy that, 5021.
Hey. I got a hostage coming out.
It's all right. Come on out.
It's okay.
Don't worry.
No one's gonna shoot.
These guns are here
to keep you safe.
It's okay.
It's all right.
The phone's for me.
Just keep walking.
That's right. Come to me.
Atta kid. It's okay.
All right, just hand me
the phone.
Hand me the phone.
All right. Now get behind me.
Stay between me
and the building.
Stay between
me and the building.
We're gonna be fine.
We're okay.
I'm gonna take this call.
This is Sergeant Hank Voight.
How we doing in there, Jake?
I want Imam Akeem Dabiri
brought to me.
Okay.
Okay, we can talk about that.
But you know,
you know, Akeem
is in federal custody.
So it's gonna take some time.
But I'll set the wheels
in motion right now
but you gotta
work with me, okay?
No. You have half an hour.
That's not enough time.
You have half an hour!
Or I will start killing them
one by one.
Go around the back.
Lock is broke.
- Miller, are you there?
- It's okay, FBI.
Hank.
Man, we sure as hell
got this one wrong.
Yeah, and we kicked Akeem.
He's on his way.
You established contact?
- I did.
- Good. We're setting
a breach plan.
We'll be ready to move in 20.
Wait a secondAtwater
is inside with 30 hostages.
That's why we're moving now.
We'll give your men
a tactical plan.
Wait. The second you breach,
he'll detonate.
Look, we got a line of contact.
We got 30 minutes to get inside.
Not enough time, Hank.
Sir, I can get to Miller.
This is our jurisdiction.
Will.
Stand down.
Sarge.
Sarge, let me do this.
Atwater said the rear entrance
isn't secure.
- Jay.
- No, I can do this.
I get Miller.
Let me talk him out.
You know what happens
if you can't.
Jake? It's Jay Halstead.
I'm unarmed, all right?
Everybody face the wall!
You take another step,
I blow this place.
I hearl hear you, man.
We're working on Akeem.
That's why I'm here.
I gotta see proof of life, Jake.
You know how this works, right?
So I'm coming out, okay?
I'm unarmed.
See?
No vest.
I got no gun.
Keeping my hands raised, okay?
Just gotta make sure
everybody's okay.
That's good. That's good,
it looks like nobody's hurt.
That means you and I got a way
out of here.
'Cause I'm gonna be honest,
Jake,
things are gonna go bad
for you really quick
if you don't let me help you.
You bring me Akeem
or I drop these people
one combatant at a time.
Please, Jake, don't...
Don't do this, okay?
There is another solution.
You just gotta let me help you.
Just let me help.
Put the gun down.
Hand me the remote.
You and I can walk out
the front door together.
I promise you I'm not gonna let
anything happen to you.
Okay?
You gotta let me help you.
Jake.
Look atlook at them.
They're terrified
right now, Jake.
They're not combatants, man.
They're civilians, Jake.
They're citizens.
They're people.
Jake.
They're Americans.
You swore to protect them.
What are you doing?
That's as far as you come.
Okay.
What, you think I'm crazy?
No, no, I don't. I don't.
You think this is PTS,
this is...
trauma from the war?
You think I'm having an episode?
Maybe, Jake.
I don't think I'm over there.
No. I'm in my own backyard.
I'm standing on my soil.
Don't you get it, Halstead?
You were there! You remember!
These people have come
to destroy us.
But nobody gets it
because we're all too busy
tweeting about the president.
We're posting pictures
of our dogs.
You want to help me?
You bring me Akeem.
Bring me Akeem.
Buddy.
Think of your wife right now.
Think of your wife.
You bring me Akeem now,
or I kill them.
Please don't do this, Jake.
You don't think I'll do it.
Miller.
You are a war hero, Miller.
Act like it.
Yeah, you're damn right I am.
And this ends now.
Go. Go.
We got hostages coming out!
Jay, we gotta go.
Thank you.
I really appreciate that.
Praise Allah.
Where the hell's your detective?
You knew we had
a breaching plan.
I told you to stand down.
Back off, Will.
Back off?
I'm gonna have his badge.
He defused the situation.
I mean, you want to report it
differently, feel free.
When you do, maybe I should
have my undercover officer
report the treatment
he experienced.
Or the interrogation techniques
used on Akeem Dabiri,
an innocent man.
And he's right over there.
Maybe we should talk to him.
Just let it go.
Take the win and walk away.
Hey. Give you a ride home?
I'll buy you a beer.
Thanks, I think I'm just...
Yeah, I know you
want to be alone,
but this is just
part of the thing, so.
What thing?
It's a thing that works
between us. Bad case.
One of us doesn't want
the other one around.
The other one stays anyway.
We talk.
We feel better and we're able
to go to work the next day.
It works.
I screwed up, Hailey.
It didn't even occur to me
that Miller could be involved.
If it's on you, it's on me too.
No, you had a bad feeling.
I couldn't even see it.
A lot of horrible things
happened when I was overseas.
And I know I can't just, like,
flip a switch and turn that off.
But I do the work.
You learn to deal with
the triggers and the stress.
The war was a part of my life.
It's not who I am.
Not anymore.
I just had no idea
I had any anger.
Or bias.
You just saved 30 lives.
Thirty Muslim lives.
That's a good day.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
Thanks.
Buy you a beer?