Hey, how'd it go with the lawyer?
Yeah, pretty straightforward.
Um, state's attorney is moving forward
on the obstruction charges.
There's no trial date set or anything,
but the lawyer thinks it'll
happen sometime next year.
Then don't do anything
stupid between now and then.
I'll do my best.
Hey, listen, I wanted to
talk to you about something,
- Huh?
- Um...
Can a cop choose to be
in general population?
I mean, if I lose, I don't know--
I don't know how well I'll do
23 hours a day alone in my cell.
- Uh, well, we'll talk about
that down the road
if we need to.
- Yeah, um, is Kev all right?
I've been reaching out to him,
and, uh, he's gone silent on me.
- Yeah, he's working a case.
- All right.
All right, thanks, boss.
- Yeah.
- I don't think women
understand how hard it is
to be a man these days.
Think about it, bro.
We've got to be
the bread-winning alpha dogs,
we've got to be strong, but we
also got to be sensitive.
- Right.
- Right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Understanding.
Pretend like we want to change the world.
That's a paradox, Peanut.
- See, there you go again
trying to show off
with all them big words.
- Come on, man,
all I'm trying to say is--
- Contradictory.
I know, but trust me,
no woman is asking you to save the world,
and no good one is asking you
to pay her bills.
Look, just end of the day,
it's simple, okay?
We're just asking you to be nice.
Girl got a good point.
Ain't nothing paradoxical
about that neither.
- We is gonna find you a book.
- Man, shut up.
- You're always clowning.
No wonder you two fools are broke.
Oh, so you're planning
what exactly, Kevin?
- Don't worry about all that,
Dre.
- It's Andre.
Don't worry about all that, Andre.
Just know I'm working off
of big things, bro.
- Big things?
- Atwater's losing his touch.
It's been two weeks and Andre
still can't stand him.
- Andre needs
a new line of work
'cause that dude is always moody.
- Working for Darius Walker
will do that to you.
- I told you, man.
His mother and my mother grew
up next door to each other.
Now that's family, bro.
D, you good?
Man, Darius got that look.
What look is that?
One that says stay the hell away.
- Nina.
- Yo, what happened?
- Smokey's gone.
- What you mean?
- He's dead.
Someone shot him, man.
Took his buy money too. 20 grand.
- You think Garcia--
- I don't know.
You know anything about this?
Excuse me?
You've been hanging around the bar,
you've been asking
a whole bunch of questions,
then one of our own
gets robbed and killed.
Andre, you don't got to like me, bro,
but what you ain't gonna do
is accuse me of anything.
Kev, you've got to be careful, bro.
Careful about what?
I ain't seen your ass in ten years,
then you just show up,
trying to reconnect?
Peanut, hell are you talking about--
I know you did your time in Stateville,
but maybe they let you out early.
Maybe you told them you had
a friend named Peanut.
You done lost your damn mind, man.
- Peanut pulled a gun.
- Hold it, hold on.
Let it play out.
Peanut, I understand
that you wanna show out
in front of your boy,
but if you're gonna pull that thing out,
you're gonna have to stop
talking and start shooting.
Don't push it, bro.
You're gonna follow me, bro?
- You damn right I am.
- You did good, boy.
- Bro, I ain't had no choice.
Andre wasn't playing around.
He don't trust your ass.
- It's all good, bro.
We breaking them down.
- Happy to help as long as you
don't write no paper on me.
- What did I tell you
when I arrested you?
You do me right, I'll do you better.
- Right on, bro.
- I'll holler at you.
- Hey, yo, next time,
just grab the gun.
There no need for you to hit me, bro.
- I hear you, dawg.
Chicago PD
S07E02- Assets
- Talked to Homicide about
the Smokey thing.
Turns out he's a high ranking guy
in Darius Walker's organization.
- Any suspects?
- Nothing real yet.
All we know is two male Latinos
were spotted near
the crime scene a few minutes
after it happened.
- Smokey had 20 grand on him,
which means he knew the sellers.
He probably did business
with them before.
Otherwise he wouldn't have
had that much money on him.
- So it's an inside job.
Seller steals the cash,
keeps the product.
Wouldn't be the first time
we've seen that happen.
- No, but it's the first time
it's happened
to somebody working for Darius Walker.
- Well, the good news is it
does open up an angle for us.
Look, if we know the
Latin Players were behind this,
you can be damn sure
Darius Walker knows too.
That means he's going to be
looking for a new supplier.
Jay, I want you to go under
as that supplier.
- Sounds good.
Hey, Sarge?
- Hmm?
- So all that stuff last week?
We're good?
- We are where we are.
Let's move on.
- Man, this place is slammed.
I should've been selling baked goods.
- Right? And it's less
risky
'cause I don't know a brother who ever
got popped for moving scones.
- Yeah, this place does
$800,000 a year in revenue.
The one on Ashland does 1.2.
- Damn, we are
in the wrong business.
- Oh, the big boss.
What's he doing in here?
He got a sweet tooth?
- Yeah, for money.
He owns the joint.
He owns the whole damn chain.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- He gave two smart,
young brothers
300 grand to start this whole place up.
All legit.
- It's a good way
to clean your cash too.
- Nah, it's more than that.
See, Darius wants to change things.
Educate young black folks
to think and act
like those dudes up in Silicon Valley.
- Well,
I'm all about business too.
I sell premium product at a fair price.
- Where does your product
come from?
- Juarez.
I got a cousin down there.
- Cousin?
Bro, your cousins are
from Cape Cod or Lake Forest,
not no Juarez.
- I was born and raised
in Pilsen,
but, uh, been in the game
for a long time,
and I got a lot of connections in Juarez.
- Okay, well, I'm gonna have
to run this up the chain.
- Naturally.
- I appreciate the opportunity,
Andre.
- All right.
- See you later?
- Yeah, man.
Later.
Darius is giving these donuts away
to clean off his dirty-ass drug money.
That's it, that's all.
- What, you don't buy
the Robin Hood rap?
- Not so much sold
on this selfless,
black empowerment thing.
It's hypocrites like that
that are the reason why
I can't wake up with my brother
and sister every morning.
- What can I do for you,
Detective?
- Just wanted to follow up
on a few things
regarding the Adam Ruzek case.
- Well, I'm not talking without
my FOP lawyer present.
- It's not a big deal.
I just need to clarify a few statements.
- Okay, I'll schedule a meeting
with your FOP lawyer
if that's what you want.
- I'll tell you what I want.
I want this case to go away.
- Excuse me?
- And you and I both know
the only reason
you opened this case
is 'cause Kelton squeezed you.
He wanted me, so he told you
to go after Ruzek and Antonio.
Yeah.
I mean, Kelton's dead.
Why are we wasting our time on this?
You wanna know the truth?
I don't care about this case,
but the ship has sailed, Hank.
It's with the state's
attorney's office now.
- All right, you know the ASA?
- Yes, of course.
- Maybe you take
his temperature.
Why don't you see
how invested he really is
in prosecuting a good cop
over the accidental death
of a rapist/kidnapper?
- I could do that.
- Even if Adam did do
what you say he did,
you know the only thing he's guilty of
is being a good partner
and a loyal friend.
- I'll see what I can do.
- Andre tells me
you've got a friend
who's got a cousin in Juarez.
- Yeah, my homie Jay.
We used to hoop together in high school.
- Well, what's your take?
- 10% the first time.
- Outside of introducing people
to your friend who's
got a cousin in Juarez,
what are your professional aspirations?
- At the moment,
I'm just waiting for the state
to give me my license back
so I can start a construction job.
- Okay.
How do you and Peanut know each other?
- We grew up on the same block.
Mom's were real tight.
- What block?
- 47th and Calumet
in Bronzeville.
- Hey now, that's a real
African American neighborhood
right there.
Louis Armstrong grew up there.
- Yeah, I know.
Now there's a Starbucks on every block.
- You think that's a bad thing?
Come in.
- What's up?
You wanted to see me?
- I hear you're moving product
near a grade school.
Is that true?
- Man, who said that?
- I'm giving you
an opportunity
to be accountable here, Bryce.
Did you sell dope in front
of Clara Barton?
- Yeah, I did.
- You know that's against
the rules, right?
- I know.
I...
I'm sorry, Darius.
I just...
I...
- School needs
a baseball coach.
Be there tomorrow at 4:00.
You're done selling dope.
Get out.
- Your goldfish die
or something?
- Nah, I'm just deep
in thought.
- About what?
- Business.
- What kind of business?
Wait, don't tell me.
I don't even want to know.
Buy you a drink?
- No, I got to go.
Rain check?
- I don't do rain checks,
sweetie,
especially on a sunny day.
- But you know how
that Chicago weather is.
Just talked to Andre.
Walker's not doing the deal with you.
- I'm offended.
- Well, he wasn't feeling it.
- Does he have
another dealer lined up
or is he still doing business
with the Latin Players?
- I don't know.
Walker doesn't talk about it.
- Units in the 7th District
and units on the citywide,
we're getting multiple calls
of shots fired
at 1221 South 58th Street.
- That's like
three blocks away.
- Let's roll.
- All right, stay here.
Don't blow your cover.
- All right.
- To your right.
- Bodies.
- Go, I got you.
- Two of them.
Looks like they're both gone.
- Don't come any closer!
- Police! Put it down!
- We're the police!
- How do I know?
- You see this?
This says we're the police.
Put your gun down!
- How do I know
you won't kill me?
- Because if we wanted you
dead, you'd already be dead.
You need to put your gun down now.
We will shoot.
You're not giving us a choice.
Put your gun down now!
- Oh, God!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, I thought
you were trying to kill me.
I'm sorry.
- Safety was on.
- Our two vics are Luis Tores
and Benji Rodriguez.
Our girl is Gloria Romero,
she's Benji's girlfriend.
Took some persuading,
but she's confirmed that
they're Latin Players.
- She see anything?
- No, she said she was hanging
out with her friends.
She went on a cigarette run,
she came back,
she heard the shots, so she ran and hid.
She said she heard a male voice say,
"This is for Smokey."
- All right, so Darius is
looking at revenge for Smokey.
Is that what we're thinking?
- Makes sense.
You kill one of mine,
I kill two of yours.
- All right, well,
somebody had to see something.
The shooter didn't
just fall from the sky.
Let's dig in.
Find witnesses, surveillance cameras.
- Sergeant?
- Sir?
- Is it true
their throats were slit?
Darius Walker's crew?
- Yeah, it sure seems that way.
- You know, a gang war
is not exactly an ideal way
to kick off one's tenure
as Interim Superintendent.
- Especially if you want that
interim tag removed one day.
- I just want to do what's best
for the people of this city.
- Enough said.
- Keep me posted, Sergeant.
- I was just trying to help.
- I know.
- He's out here selling product
in front of children and parents.
You know?
It's why I restrained him,
I called patrol.
- You punched him in the face
and threw him on the ground.
- Hold on,
he swung at me first.
- You're off the job, Adam.
You don't have the authority.
- Sarge, I mean,
he's out here
just slinging crack
in the broad daylight.
- It doesn't matter.
- What do you mean
it doesn't matter?
Of course it matters.
- You can't get involved
in things like this, Adam.
Not anymore, not until
your stuff gets resolved.
- I was just trying to help.
I mean...
- Have you been drinking?
- No.
I'm fine.
- Okay.
Come on.
- How did it go out there?
- Pretty damn good.
I found a witness who lives nearby.
She saw a young black male.
Skinny, 5'10, running
from the back of the building,
and she said she'll do an ID
once we have an offender in custody.
- Okay, good.
What about you two?
- Well, we got some video.
Uh, this is from an
auto part shop down the street
from the abandoned building.
We got a blue Ford Taurus, pulls up.
It's got a--a dent in the side panel.
Now it idles in front of the building,
and then the shots go off at 3:29.
It just takes off.
- All right,
did you run that plate?
- Yeah, it's a dummy.
It came back empty.
- So if the car was idling
when the shots were fired...
- It means the driver's
not the shooter.
- Could be the getaway driver.
- All right, so let's find
that blue Taurus, fast.
Talk to Kevin. Get him up to speed.
- Hank?
- Yeah.
- Can I talk to you?
- Yeah, what's up?
- I just talked to Adam,
and I'm worried.
- I'm working on it.
- Work harder.
As tough as he is,
he is not gonna last a month
on the inside.
- Listen, if you're telling me
there's nothing
you need me to do, I'll leave it alone.
But dawg, if there's something I can do
to keep this deal back on track--
- Bro, it's dead.
Just leave it alone.
- Okay, I'm just making sure.
Who's the kid?
- Name's Jerald.
Darius helps him out.
- Okay.
Pretty sure Jerald helps out Darius too.
Ain't nothing for free.
- That don't concern you, bro.
- What you mean it don't?
Come on, man, I'm trying
to do business with y'all.
Obviously, he prefers working
with fifth graders.
- Yeah, he just left the bar.
We'll track him.
- So how long we got
to do this, man?
- Until I say stop.
- No, no, this ain't right,
and you ain't my boss.
- Not here, man.
What are you--
- I'm sick of all
this damn lying.
- You're gonna be sick of being
dead if you don't shut up.
You're doing this
until the job is done, Peanut.
Okay?
- All right, yeah, it's my bad.
- Is it mine?
- The more we dig into
our bartender, Nina Rodriguez,
the less we know.
Plates are fictitious, no DL,
no criminal info.
- We know she rented
a studio apartment
three months ago,
and is paying cash for it.
- So it could be tips.
It could also be drug money.
- Well, what do you think, Kev?
Is she part of Walker's drug crew?
- I'm not sure,
but it's possible.
- The real question is,
is she the shooter,
the getaway driver, or is
someone just using her car?
- Hey.
Let's find out.
Put some pressure on her.
See if you can catch
her dirty in a drug deal,
Get her to flip on Walker.
You talked to the ASA?
- Yeah.
Got a second?
- Come on.
All right, I talked to Heller.
He worked a little magic.
Prosecutor is willing to cut you a deal.
12 months, you do six.
- If I roll the dice at trial?
- You lose, you're looking at
three to five.
- Well, maybe I'll win?
Lawyer says it's 50-50.
- Yeah, well, your lawyer
doesn't have to do the time
if he's wrong.
- Yeah, but...
what happens when I'm out?
My career's over,
I've got to find a new job?
All I know is being in the police, Sarge.
It's who I am. It's, like, all I got.
- Then we fight it.
- Look at you.
Just the person I wanted to see.
I've got a little opportunity for you.
- Yeah, what kind
of an opportunity?
- The kind that gets you more
of those gold necklaces you like.
One of my guys sells premium H,
and he's gonna give me 10%
of everything I bring in.
I figure with your line of work
and place of business,
you might know some people
other than Darius.
I took a run at him. He ain't going.
- What's my end?
- 5%.
- And what kind of weight
are we talking about?
- I'm talking about four bricks
at a time at 50 a pop.
You smack them with a five-stack tax
on your back end that's 20 grand total.
10,000 apiece, me and you.
- Man, you sure
know your stuff.
- Well, I'm trying
to make this money, Nina.
You down or not?
- I'll make some calls.
Mm-hmm?
- Let me holla at you.
- What up, what up?
- Sup?
This is my boy, Trey.
- What's up, Trey?
- Nothing much.
I understand y'all got
some candy you want to shift.
- How much can you handle?
- Two pieces of taffy.
Maybe three.
Nina say you got some pure stuff.
- Mm-hmm.
- You tight south
of the border?
- Juarez.
- How about 100 for three?
- I thought you said
this guy was serious.
- And I thought
I said 50 a pop.
- All right, how about this?
My boy gives you 100 grand right now.
Okay, that's for two.
You front him the other brick,
for trust and all.
If the product's as good
as you say it is,
I mean, we're in business
for a long time.
- Makes sense.
- All right.
Where and when?
We're on the move for the dope.
- Copy that.
You're covered in back. Hailey, you set?
- Yup, set.
- You wanna test it?
- Nah.
You say it's pure. It's pure.
It's about trust, right?
- Oh, they're coming.
Kim.
Oh, these two don't look like altar boys.
Jay, we got two bogeys
maybe coming your way.
Sarge, you get that?
- Yeah, keep an eye.
Jay, stay focused.
- What's wrong?
What's wrong is I don't see any money.
- Calm down, bro.
I've got it right here.
- Gun!
- Jay, two armed offenders
coming your way!
- Hands up! Chicago PD!
Put your guns down!
- Police!
- Put your hands down!
Hey!
- Get down!
- Put it down!
- Put your hands up!
- Hands up now!
- I'm a cop!
- We're cops, not--
- Drop your weapon!
- We're police!
- Hey, everybody shut up!
Shut up!
- Chill!
Just chill!
I'm a cop!
- Let me see some ID
and badges.
My button's in my pocket.
I'm Raul Acosta, assigned to Squad E66,
long-term investigations.
My Commander is Marty Belmont.
- It's legit.
- Lower your weapon.
- Thank God it's not like
the old days.
Shoot first, ask later.
- How long you've been working
these guys?
- We've been up on Walker
for about three months now.
- You have anymore
undercovers working?
- Just our rookie.
- They plucked me straight out
of the Academy.
- Who's they?
- OCD Deputy Chief Morales.
Didn't think he knew I existed.
- Wait, hold up.
So the blue dented Taurus
outside the murder scene,
what were you doing?
- Walker mentioned the address.
I was checking it out, trying
to take down some plates.
Next thing you know, I hear gunshots.
- So you take off
not to blow your cover.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
- What's your real name?
- Vanessa.
Vanessa Rojas. You?
- Kevin Atwater.
Nice to meet you.
- You too.
So now what?
- All right, I just brought
the deputy chief up to speed.
Per his orders, we are joining forces.
Walker remains the priority target.
All right, Vanessa, you've got the
best relationship with this guy.
Anything you can tell us about
this recent double homicide?
- No, all I heard was him
mention the address.
That's it.
- What about where he does
most of his business?
Can you plant a wire in that back office?
- Too dangerous.
- I can do it.
- Remember what I told you.
- I know.
Being a hero will get
you fired or get you dead.
But this is easy, I promise.
- All right.
- Nina, I'm running late.
You got this?
- Yeah, I'm good.
- Good.
- Where you going?
- House warming party
for my cousin.
I just helped him buy his first house,
and the man is so happy,
he won't stop crying.
- Scotty, I'm gonna go grab
some stuff in the back.
All right, I'm in.
- Copy that.
All clear.
- Rojas, get out of there.
Walker's coming back.
- Hey.
- What the hell
are you doing in here?
- We ran out of cognac.
Well, the good stuff, actually.
Had to raid your private stash.
You can check the bar
if you don't believe me.
- I'll do that.
How'd you get in?
- Your spare key.
You told me about it, remember?
Yo, I was just trying to help,
but if you don't want me
in here, that's fine by me.
- I don't.
- I won't come in here,
whether or not you invite me.
Want me to leave the cognac?
- Take the cognac.
Leave the key.
- Rojas did a nice job.
- Yeah, she's quick on
her feet and--
- Boss, we intercepted a lot
of chatter on Walker's wire.
We're going through it all now.
Good news, we found his heroin supplier,
a guy named Mateo Garcia.
- Garcia from
the Latin Players?
Walker's supposed to be at war with them.
- Sounds like they made peace.
- Well, Garcia's insisting
on meeting Walker in person
as a sign of good faith.
- Okay, we got
a time and place?
- Yeah, today at 5:00.
I'm not sure where yet.
There's a lot of code
and a lot of addresses.
They mentioned Ashburn,
but more recently,
he's been talking about
his bakery on 21st street.
- All right,
let's sit on the bakery.
- Okay.
- We wait for Garcia to arrive,
observe the exchange,
and arrest everyone in sight.
- All quiet.
- All clear in the back alley.
- Sarge, maybe they're doing
the meet in Ashburn.
- Standby.
Let's wait it out.
- The hell?
- It's Jerald.
The kid Walker's doing business with.
- Yeah.
I've seen him around.
- Sarge, we've got an employee
that just walked out of the bakery.
He gave Jerald a bag. Could be the place.
- He's getting on his bike.
- All right, stay with him.
See if he rolls towards Ashburn.
- All right,
pull up right here.
He just went down Clarke.
I've got to get him on foot.
Chicago PD!
- Please don't shoot.
Please don't shoot.
Sir, I--I was just bringing some muffins
to Mr. Marley here.
He's a part of the program.
- Program?
What program are you talking about?
- Mr. Walker's food bank.
They give all the food that
they don't use to the poor.
- Stand down.
Throw me your wallet.
University of Chicago.
- Yeah.
I just started school last month.
- What the hell are you doing
with Darius Walker?
- He--he helps me out.
He pays my tuition. Bought my books too.
- Hands down.
I'm sorry. Misunderstanding.
Sarge, we followed the kid.
He did not have drugs or cash on him.
We've got to go to the Ashburn location.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
- Okay, head over there now.
- Deal's going down on Ashburn.
Let's move.
- All right, Jay, we're
pulling up on 19th street.
Looks quiet around here.
- Copy that.
Nothing yet.
- Over there in the alley.
- Hmm?
Yeah, we got eyes.
- Well, what do you see?
- We see Mateo Garcia
and Darius Walker.
- This looks like
they're negotiating right now.
I don't see any product or cash.
- Just wait for the exchange.
- Copy that, Sarge.
Okay, Garcia just pulled out a bag.
- That looks good.
I see product.
- Mm-hmm.
Come on, Darius.
That's quality stuff right there.
Show him the money, huh?
- Bingo.
We've got a positive.
- Copy.
Jay, you guys take the lead.
Kevin, Vanessa, cover the perimeter.
Let's go.
All right, let's get
these people out of here.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
- Kids, hey.
Move.
- Can you guys move back
the other way?
Just go to the other side. It's okay.
- You two, leave the park.
Get out. Go!
- Gun!
Gun!
- Down!
Get down!
Everybody down!
- Get down!
- Run!
We've got a runner!
Get your hands up!
- All hands up!
- Get on the car!
On the car!
- Don't move!
Drop your weapon right now!
- On the car!
I've got Walker.
- Get against the wall!
- Do it!
- No!
You okay?
- Yeah.
- Vincent-21-Davis,
shots fired at the police.
- Copy that...
- Let's go.
- Stop the car!
Stop the car!
- Go, go!
- Hey!
- Get out of the car!
Hey, run! Run!
- Get out!
- Police!
Hey, police!
Stop the vehicle!
- Vanessa!
- Yeah, Darius Walker,
I'm the police.
You're staring down
pretty serious charges too.
- I've got some
really good lawyers.
- It doesn't really matter
how good your lawyers are.
We've got you dead to rights.
I think you know that.
Those murders, that's a different story.
We're still investigating those,
so you've got a little leverage.
Tell me how those two Latino kids died,
and I can break you off
with a better deal.
- I've got nothing to do
with those murders.
- Come on, brother, do you
expect for me to believe--
- Don't call me brother.
And no I don't expect you
to believe a damn thing I say,
but I did not kill those two boys.
- Tell me who did.
Garcia.
- Garcia took out
his own people?
- Damn right he did.
He wanted to make amends,
get back in business with me.
So that means the only thing
that you and I have to discuss
is this drug case.
- Mm-hmm.
Which is not murder.
But that's a serious case.
We're talking about a lot of weight,
a lot of dollars,
enough to put a low life
like you away for a long time.
- You just don't get it,
do you?
- What don't I get?
Hmm?
- Whether I'm here or not,
users are still gonna use.
The only difference is they're
gonna be buying the product
from some 19-year-old punk
with too much to prove.
Some badass half a gangbanger
willing to shoot up a city block
over a Twitter dispute
or a spat with some fatass girl
in tight jeans.
But the biggest difference between me
and the person who is about to replace me
is that I reinvest my profits
in the community and the people.
- So you're the Robin Hood
for black folk, huh?
- No.
No, Robin Hood stole from the rich,
gave to the poor.
Hypothetically speaking,
I take from the weak
and give to the strong
so they can get even stronger.
Let's be honest, brother.
Some folks out there ain't got no chance.
They're weak, uninspired.
All they think about is getting high.
So I sell them what they want, heroin.
With that money, I invest
in brothers and sisters
who got game, who got smarts,
who are willing to put in the time
and the effort to make
something of themselves.
Legally.
Like it or not,
that's the only way black folks
are gonna get out of these streets.
It ain't pretty,
it ain't fashionable to say out loud,
but it's the truth.
And I know none of y'all
in blue want to believe this...
But Darius Walker is good for Chicago.
Ballistics came back on the gun
found in Garcia's car.
Striations match the bullets
that killed the two Latin Players.
Okay, so Darius was telling the truth.
- Yeah, well, we still got
a solid drug trafficking case
on this guy.
- True, but Sarge
just think about it.
I mean, we get rid of Darius Walker.
- Right.
- Whoever else takes his place
isn't going to be as disciplined,
not as intelligent,
sure as hell ain't gonna give a damn
about the black community
the way he does.
- And here I thought
you didn't like this guy.
- I can't stand his ass, but...
As crazy as it sounds,
he does make the city safer.
- Yeah,
maybe we are better off
with this guy on the street.
- That is a hell of
a proposition, Sergeant.
You really think you can
persuade Darius Walker
to play ball?
- Well, he's a businessman.
- Mm-hmm.
- I think he'll realize that
helping the police arrest his competitors
is a hell of a lot better
than doing ten years in prison
for drug trafficking.
- Big risk cutting a deal
with somebody like that.
If word gets out...
- It won't.
Look, you want big results, big arrests,
you've got to take big swings.
Now Walker will be logged in
as a reliable cooperating defendant.
I'll be his personal handler.
I mean, your only role here
is to ring the bell,
and talk about all
the high profile arrests
your new and improved
police department is making.
I mean, if things go as planned...
That interim tag will
be removed before Halloween.
- All right.
I want plausible deniability
on this across the board, okay?
- I do have a favor to ask.
Actually, it's...
It's more like a condition.
- When things are
too good to be true, huh?
- Yeah, well,
it's a good rule of thumb
in this town, anyway.
- What is it?
What do you want?
- Hey, man.
- Hey.
What's going on? Is everything all right?
- Yeah, we're good.
Here you go.
- I don't understand.
What's--what's going on?
- ASA is dismissing
the charges.
Insufficient evidence.
You're good.
What'd you do?
- All that matters
is it's done.
- Thank you, Sarge.
- Yeah.
- I owe you.
- I owe you everything.
- All right.
- I'll see you in the morning.
- Yes, sir.
Synced & corrected by
Zinho_1976