So this really something you're doing
- with every officer from CPD? - Yes, sir.
Hey, you don't have to call me sir.
It's pretty formal for somebody
who's gonna ask me my deepest, darkest secrets.
It won't be that, I promise.
I'm simply asking questions
designed to forecast future problems.
To predict the future?
Oh, that'd be nice, wouldn't it?
But no.
This is just another supplement to Early Intervention Strategy.
Right, to predict if I'm gonna do something stupid
on the job in the future.
It's purely supportive, not punitive.
What if I answer a question wrong?
There is no wrong.
Any answer would just help us understand you.
- Who you are. - Well, I get that.
I've been to therapy before, so lay it on me.
So how do you like your coffee?
Black.
How do you like yours?
I don't drink coffee.
And have you always taken it that way?
Yes, one cream, one sugar, every morning.
Does that say something about me?
Would you consider yourself a creature of habit?
Uh, no, no, I drink all the drinks.
Have you ever used a racial slur?
That's a hell of a segue. No, no I have not.
Have you ever heard a family member use a racial slur?
I don't know. Maybe.
Yeah.
Would you say you have a good relationship
- with your family? - I'd say it's fine.
Do you consider the police force your family?
My unit.
And the rest of the police force?
No, coworkers.
Have you ever felt
what you would categorize as anger issues?
Nope.
And what about trauma?
Yes.
Have you experienced post-traumatic stress?
Have you ever made a mistake on the job?
Have you ever had to fire your weapon?
Have you ever killed someone?
Have you ever felt fear on the job?
Do you believe you are the wrong fit for this job?
Are you proud to be an officer
of the Chicago Police Department?
Do you believe you're capable, worthy, right?
What the actual hell do they think
they're gonna get out of all of that?
They should check my police record
if they wanna know if I'm a good or a bad cop.
Am I right? Am I?
Nah, nah, they don't wanna know who you are now.
They wanna know who you gonna be then.
One hour with them, and you're a psychic too?
Maybe I got the future in me,
but if asking us questions is gonna help us find prejudice,
prevent problems, and progress policing,
then I'll sit for it all damn day.
I get the intention.
It's just, I don't know, seems a little overzealous, right?
I'm just saying, you don't punish the many
to get to the few, you know?
Grill good cops looking for cracks that ain't there.
I just wanna know what my coffee order
- has to do with anything. - Hey, guys.
What's going on? We got a case?
An officer-involved shooting.
- A bad one. - No.
What happened?
A buddy of mine in patrol
sent over this civilian witness video.
Somebody caught it on a cell phone.
I said get your hands all the way up
and turn around.
Stop pointing your gun at me!
Hands up! Turn around!
Your gun is pointed at me, and I did nothing wrong.
So no.
Then this is the last time. Okay?
You're gonna get your hands away from your weapon,
and you're gonna turn around.
Hey, hey, Wheelan, let's just relax, all right?
I'm not moving. I know my rights.
Call your supervisor.
Hey, hands away from your weapon, up!
Mine aren't nowhere near my weapon!
- Get them up! - Let's just calm down.
- Turn around! - I ain't gonna move.
- I said turn around! - Wheelan!
- Now! - Wheelan!
Now!
Oh, my God!
No!
The kid die?
On the pavement.
Who was he?
His name is Jeff Duncan. Zero priors.
Had a legal gun in his waistband.
Pulled over for going seven over the speed limit.
Graduate of Whitney Young.
Student at University of Chicago.
And the officers?
The FTO who fired the shot, Dave Wheelan.
PPO a month out of the academy is named Andre Cooper.
Cooper's talking?
Oh yeah, to IRT and COPA,
and his statement never changed.
Jeff never went for his weapon.
There was zero justification to use deadly force.
I also have three witnesses
and two POD cameras.
IAD is on their way to Officer Wheelan's house now,
but I would like two undercovers
to make the transport.
That's... That's not what my unit does.
I mean I think you'd be hard pressed
to find any Chicago police officer
- who wants to step in this. - I know.
I know history tells us that this
is not something to step in,
which is why I'm asking a unit I trust,
and I hope trusts me.
I've watched this footage three dozen times, Hank,
as has the SA.
And it's as clear as this moment ever comes,
it was a bad shoot.
Can you spare two officers, Sergeant Voight?
The video's not yet viral,
but we will be putting every officer on immediate 12s.
We expect mass protests and violence,
so we will move fast.
Officer Atwater, Officer Ruzek,
I want you to go to Officer Wheelan's home
and arrest him for murder.
Officer Dave Wheelan, on the job 30 years,
16 department commendations, only one complaint a year.
You can read about him all you want, but listen to me:
you're both nothing more than an Uber, okay?
Read him his rights, arrest him,
drive him, drop him off at south detention.
You do nothing, you say nothing.
Do not get involved.
Not one word that can get you in trouble
if you have to testify,
- you understand me? - Yeah.
All right, car's been cleared.
It's unmarked.
Should be another unit doing this.
I feel like any good cop
should be able to arrest a cop like this.
I mean this file's real sparse. This can't be the whole of it.
It makes him look like a good cop
who murdered a kid at a routine traffic stop.
Yeah, routine all right.
He didn't have guns in the house.
He's got a wife and kids. They're gonna be all emotional.
- Hey, Linette. - Hi, guys.
- Imagine Jeff Duncan's family. - I have.
Only we're not going to Jeff Duncan's house
- to arrest nobody. - Thank you, Linette.
Yeah. You're welcome.
Look, brother, I know that this is a situation
that can spin us in a lot of different ways.
Most of those ways are above our pay grade.
So like Voight said, this got nothing to do with us.
Let's just go arrest this guy like the criminal he is,
nice and easy, get back to doing our real jobs, yeah?
Copy that.
Murderer!
Come on.
Well, the arrest clearly leaked.
Knew we were coming.
My partner's in there. I just wanna talk.
Is that Wheelan's trainee?
Hey, man. You're not gonna touch me,
and you're not gonna tell me to walk away, all right?
I have every right to be here.
He should be on mandatory leave.
Come on, Kev. Let's go.
It's all right. Hey, we all right?
Hey, I just need to know why he shot him.
Can we have a minute?
Come on, man. Cooper, right?
- Yeah. - Atwater, Ruzek.
You ain't been in there, have you?
No, I haven't. I get that I shouldn't.
You should not.
Hey, yeah, man, I was right there.
I was right there next to him.
I rode with that dude a month.
Brother, I just need to know why.
You know why.
And you know you gotta go home. Get out of here, man.
It's okay, we got it.
Come on. We'll be back in a few.
Don't take too long.
Mrs. Wheelan, I'm Officer Ruzek.
This is Officer Atwater.
Thank God. Come in.
Thank you.
Our phones have been ringing nonstop.
Ma'am.
Where's your husband?
He's upstairs with the kids. They're scared.
What is this? You're with the FOP, right?
I assume you're here to help my husband.
Uh, no.
Annie, I'm guessing they're here to arrest me.
- No. - David Wheelan, you're under arrest.
- Can you step down please? - No.
Dad, what's going on?
Kay, look, I only got one ask.
Okay, spare my kids, huh? Cuff me outside.
Yeah, we can do that.
Protocol is that we cuff you inside.
- Turn around. - Kevin...
Kevin, uh... kids around.
Do you have any weapons on you?
- No. - Is this his jacket?
Hey, Katie, sweetheart, it's gonna be fine.
Dave Wheelan, you're under arrest
- for the murder of Jeff Duncan. - All right?
Kay, take your sister upstairs.
- Dave. - Zach, take her upstairs.
- What am I supposed to do? - Go to your room, Katie.
It'll be fine, honey.
You have a right to an attorney.
If you do not have an attorney, one will be...
I did nothing. You know what, I did nothing.
You're gonna get a call soon. I already called an attorney.
- I did nothing wrong! - Stop talking.
My life was in danger! I did nothing wrong!
I did my job, and I'd do it again!
- Stop talking! - I'm innocent!
Back up!
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
Back up! Get away from the car!
Please step away from the vehicle, ma'am.
Stand back. Hey, hey, back up.
Easy, Ruz, easy, Ruz, easy.
What the hell was that?
The truth. Because they need to hear it.
Adam, Kev?
Yeah, Hailey, we made the arrest.
- We're in transit. - We got a problem.
There's a video we didn't know about.
Jeff Duncan had an app on his phone
that recorded the traffic stop
and sent the full video to all of his emergency contacts.
How many people saw the video?
It's gone viral.
We've got unruly crowds at headquarters, City Hall,
the jails, and south detention.
We got death threats against Wheelan.
Okay, Hailey, what are you telling us here?
I'm saying you can't bring him in yet.
Not until we clear this out. Sorry.
There's a safe house about ten minutes from you.
I'm gonna send you everything right now.
Just stay there, and we'll be quick, all right?
Okay. Copy that.
Hey, come on with these cuffs, huh?
They're cutting off my circulation.
- I can't feel my shoulders. - Here.
Thanks.
Put your jacket on.
Should be another unit doing this, man.
This ain't too bad, huh?
Usually it's just a crappy motel room somewhere.
Put your hands out.
Oh, you gotta be kidding me. It's just us three here now.
Yeah, what'd you think was happening here?
Put your hands out.
There. Sit. We shouldn't be here long.
Yeah.
We shouldn't have to be here at all.
I'm here over a video showing me doing my job.
Come on, man.
We're here because a mob of people want your head.
So cut out all the commentary, all right?
I get what you think you're seeing when you look at me.
Some racist white cop prick, right?
But the video speaks for itself.
It sure does.
You know, anything you say to us
can be used against you,
so how about we just all stay quiet?
No. Watch the video.
You didn't see the full thing.
So go ahead and watch all of it.
I know you want to. So watch it.
Yeah.
All right.
License, registration, and proof of insurance?
Why am I being pulled over?
Driving above the posted speed limit, sir.
Come on, I wasn't going that fast.
This is just a routine traffic stop, sir.
Just cover the passenger side.
Last time.
License and proof of insurance.
Officer, I wasn't speeding. I don't know what this is--
Ah, ah, ah. Hey, watch the tone
and calm down so I can do my job.
That's what this is.
Is harassing people your job?
'Cause that's what this feels like.
And for the record, because I am recording this,
I am legally carrying a firearm in my waistband.
I have a concealed carry permit in my wallet.
Okay, I'm gonna need for you
to step out of the vehicle now.
What? Why?
Am I being arrested?
I just gave an order. Step out.
Call your supervisor. I'm not moving.
Why the hell is a gun pointed at me?
Step out of the vehicle.
Wheelan, sir, let's just calm down.
Yeah, Wheelan. Calm down.
Step out of the damn vehicle.
- Search the car. - You need a warrant for that!
Sir, that's an intrusive search.
Kid, do it or find a new job, now!
Hands up! Turn around!
Your gun is pointed at me, and I did nothing wrong.
- So no. - Last time.
Get your hands up, away from the weapon,
and turn around.
Hey, hey, Wheelan. Let's just relax, man.
I'm not moving. I know my rights.
Call your supervisor.
Turn around. Hands away from the weapon!
My hands are nowhere near my weapon!
- Let's just calm down. - Turn around!
I ain't gonna move so you can shoot me.
Now!
Let's just calm down. Wheelan--
Now.
You see now?
He wouldn't comply.
He--he was hostile,
he was armed, and he moved.
I feared for my life, and I acted.
You mean to tell me all--
Hailey didn't say we were getting backup, did she?
Get down!
We got two shooters!
Get your head down. Follow me.
Keep your head down. Head down, come on.
Get in the truck.
- Kev got me, you got me? - I got it, I got it, I got it.
- They're in the house, Ruz.. - Get in the truck, dude.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
- You got it? - Yeah.
- Son of a bitch. - Damn.
10-1, 10-1! Shots fired at the police.
Keep your head down.
We got another shooter!
Are we clear? Tell me we're clear.
Uh, yeah. No tail, no follow.
They're trying to kill me!
I shot one of them. There's at least two shooters.
Take these cuffs off. Take them off.
- I'm a cop, same as you! - Shut up!
- God. - Tell me you got your ears on!
- Sarge, our guys got ambushed. - What?
I'm here.
Are you okay? I heard the whole thing over the radio.
Yeah, somebody hit the safehouse.
What the hell does he mean, hit?
- Are you all right? - Uh, we're fine.
We hit one of the shooters, maybe two.
Both were masked.
I mean, the place was clearly compromised.
They were there to kill Wheelan.
Adam, are you still at the house?
No, no, no, we're driving.
Patrol said they were a minute out,
but driving feels safer right now.
Okay, we are heading to the safe house now, see what we can learn.
Find a location off road, hang tight until we get you an escort,
and use only your DCs to communicate.
All right, copy that.
- Yo, Ruz. Garage. - Yeah.
I wasn't hit. Take the cuffs off.
- Turn around. - I'm not hit.
But you know you can't take me to another safehouse
'cause if they found us at the first one,
they're gonna find us at the next one.
They're hunting me!
What the hell do we do now?
There's something very wrong here.
Those shooters just made a safehouse.
I know. What we gotta do is ask ourselves this question:
was it an inside job?
Only people that know about the safehouse is CPD.
Not to mention, they just beat patrol by two minutes.
All right.
I think the safest thing is we keep this between us,
we take him off book,
we take him somewhere nobody knows about,
till we can figure out what the hell's going on,
who the hell's hunting him.
Take him off book.
Boss, we got a plan. Disregard that escort.
Copy that.
What are we looking at?
Looks like Atwater caught him center mass.
- We got a name? - No, not yet.
They just printed him, but I'm thinking we're gonna get a pop.
He's got prison tats.
Let me show you this.
There's .32 caliber shell casings here.
Got 9 mil casings all the way over here.
And then there's blood going down the gangway.
So the second shooter, he's in the wind, but he's injured.
So they both had street sweepers.
Oh, yeah, they were coordinated,
but they didn't care about crossfire. This is a do or die crew.
- We're probably not looking at teenage foot soldiers. - No.
And when did Miller get here?
She got here before us.
Hey, can I show you something?
Ma'am.
Guys, give us the room.
- You heard from your guys? - I have.
- Well, they all right? - No injuries.
Where are they?
I don't know.
They're transporting Wheelan off book.
They turned their cells off.
And they made that call with you?
They did. Look.
My men are not gonna bring Wheelan in
if there is any chance that he or any civilian
could take a bullet while en route, okay?
You need to try and give me an order
'cause of the political dirt we just stepped in, go ahead.
I'm here because I had you step in the dirt with me.
I'm not giving you any orders.
Whatever your call is, that's the call.
In the meantime,
I got a team digging into a potential leak at CPD.
You trusted me, Hank.
I trust you.
Okay, you need to take my cuffs off now.
Nobody's taking them off. Stop asking.
I'm not gonna be a defenseless animal.
- Sit down. - I'm not the criminal here.
No? Who is?
The 19-year-old Black kid you shot down?
I defended myself.
From a college student?
I had the right to defend my life.
From what?
Kev. Don't.
No. From what?
I just watched the video. You told me to.
You murdered a kid,
and you're gonna stand here in front of me and defend yourself?
- Just let it go. - Let it go?
He's standing in front of you too.
All I'm saying is, we might be here a while.
None of this is helping. That's all I'm saying.
Let it go. He's not worth it.
Uncuff me. You know I'm right.
I wanna make something really clear to you, man.
The only reason we brought you here
was to keep you from being assassinated.
It doesn't mean either of us think that you're innocent.
Now sit down.
Now.
Ruzek and Atwater can't move
until we determine that leak wasn't inside,
and we got that second shooter in custody.
So who the hell is going after Officer Dave Wheelan?
Hey, mobile techs just sent over the fingerprint card
on our dead shooter. Ray Macks, 25.
Gangs has him hooked up with the Rollin' Reapers.
His boss, T-J Jones,
just so happens to be the half-brother of Jeff Duncan.
T-J runs a crew of hired guns.
They think of themselves as the "police of gangland."
So T-J's half-brother gets killed by a police officer,
and he sends two of his guys to kill that police officer.
He's keeping order on the street.
We got anything on T-J?
No, no open warrants, no longer on probation,
I seriously doubt he's carrying.
I mean, Gangs has been on it for a while,
but they have nothing to arrest him on.
Yeah, well, he knows our second shooter,
so we're gonna make him talk to us anyway.
Jay, you and me. Grab that file.
Okay.
We're just here to talk to T-J.
Yo.
TJ
T-j.
You're expecting us, huh?
My brother was murdered by your people.
I'd hope you'd come for that,
if that is why you came.
We want you to come in and talk to us.
I don't talk to police without a witness.
Listen, talking out here with all this...
It's just not gonna work for me.
Then I guess we won't talk.
You don't have anything to arrest me on.
No, I don't.
Is this your friend, Tom? You Tom Greggin', right?
AKA Gregs.
You're two months into probation.
That's Walter Culmin. Six months.
Who we got out here? That's Jimmy Markey.
Russell Wall, you got your two kids living with you?
And I know this is Joe Hart, who's got his mom living on his dime.
I could keep going,
but it's pretty clear you're all fraternizing with felons.
We've got parole officers on their way unless we call them off.
What do you say you come in and talk,
so we don't have to keep ruining everyone's day?
Am I under arrest?
No, sir.
- Call my lawyer anyway. - Yeah, got you.
Keep filming.
You know who he is?
Nope.
Ray and a second man
tried to kill a prisoner and two cops.
Ray is dead now,
and the second guy got away.
We need to find them.
Do you know who he is?
No.
He doesn't work for you?
You didn't order him and Ray to kill Wheelan?
No.
Where were you two hours ago?
Live on the Gram with my girl,
but you know that already.
I willingly gave you my phone. You asked.
I imagine that call with your lady friend must've been rough.
I mean, losing your half-brother like that,
another Black man gone, shot by a cop.
I get it.
I do.
T-J, that cop was being brought in on murder charges.
You understand? Murder.
CPD is doing this one right.
One thing I would appreciate
is if you wouldn't call Jeff my half-brother.
He was my brother.
My blood.
You guys were close. We understand that.
But shooting at the cops, T-J?
Not the right move.
To get justice, even us cops have to trust the system.
It's what we got.
It's what you got.
It's your system.
Our system doesn't protect your neighborhood.
So you do, right?
I didn't say that.
But trust the system?
You willing to bet half a billion on that
instead of paying police misconduct bills?
I think if you both looked at yourself,
we'd know the same thing.
Y'all ain't in my neighborhood camped out to protect us.
Y'all only there to make sure
we don't leak out into the rest of the city.
But I shot no one. I never shot anyone.
I don't even own a gun.
You have nothing on me.
So I'd like to go now.
His alibi's rock solid.
He's definitely not our second shooter.
Hey, did his lawyer show yet?
Yeah, he's already threatening to sue.
He says we brought T-J in unlawfully,
and he wants a release right away.
What about T-J's phone?
We're good there. We downloaded everything.
It's mostly burner phone contacts.
The guy's really smart, but our OCD techs are on it.
Okay, okay.
So we'll release him.
Just get a tracker on his car and put a tac team on it too.
We're gonna take everything we got
and put it up against everything in T-J's phone.
Believe me, that second shooter
is gonna be buried in there somewhere.
Find him.
All right, Ray Macks.
- He's one of the shooters. You recognize him? - No.
- All right, T-J Jones. - Nope.
You've been in Englewood 30 years,
and you're going to tell me you've never seen those faces?
Sure, I've seen those faces a bunch of times.
Okay, that's a start.
You tell us who's in their crew.
No, I mean I've seen those faces.
The "I hate cops" faces.
Do you have any personal beefs in Englewood?
Come on, man. Help us out here.
Yeah, yeah, we all do.
Where I work, it's us versus them.
We show up, they see an occupying force.
Nah, not all of us.
Oh, come on, man.
Sure, every time we show up,
we starting a bad relationship.
You know why?
We're the city's secret thoughts and fears
dressed in blue with badges and guns.
Yeah, my dad used to say the same stupid thing.
We cannot leave here until we get this other shooter in custody.
- I know that. - Then help us.
I am helping you out, but I don't have any names, all right?
They're just shooting at me
because I was doing my job, you got that?
- Your job, huh? - That's right.
- Yeah? - Yes.
Explain your job to me.
- Hey, I didn't wanna die. - There's no talking.
- So I did-- - Shut up!
Listen up.
Miller's office just confirmed the leak was not from inside CPD,
so where are we at with that second shooter?
We're close.
OCD tech pulled all the numbers from T-J's phone.
Only 11 of those were also on the dead shooter's phone.
Five of those, including the dead shooter's,
were purchased and activated together three months ago.
- We're guessing T-J got them first. - Okay, I got it.
Only one number pinged to every tower
alongside the dead shooter's phone.
This has gotta be our guy right here.
- Okay, find out where that phone is now. - Yup.
Hey, guys. I just got off with OCD tech.
And they finally got something from POD footage.
A silver SUV was caught on eight cameras.
It was parked a block away from Dave Wheelan's house.
Then they caught it at two stoplights
behind Atwater and Ruzek,
and then it's right out front of our safehouse.
- Okay, it was a physical follow. - Yeah.
The car is registered to an Antoinette Clark.
She's 22, lives in Englewood.
Halstead, give me that address.
It's 63rd and Marquette.
That's where our second shooter's phone is sitting right now.
- Get that guy in custody now. - Let's go.
Chicago PD. Open up.
- Antoinette Clark? - No one called the police.
Is he in there? Did he hurt you?
No one hurt me. You don't have a warrant.
I don't have to let you in. Nobody even called you.
Antoinette, we know he's hurt.
We can help.
He's still bleeding, isn't he?
He was shot hours ago.
If he's still bleeding, then he's dying.
You know that.
I got her.
Gun.
5021 George, I need an ambo to 6850 Marquette.
GSW victim.
Copy that, 5021 George. Ambo on the way.
Look, I'm just saying, okay?
Three decades I protected those people,
and now I'm getting judged for five minutes on a video
showing me being police.
- You hear this dude? - I'm trying not to.
...but this guy wasn't that!
All right? He was not compliant from the start!
Please, I just-- Please.
Let's just ignore him. Stay calm.
Why?
Why am I keeping calm? Why are you so calm?
How can you just sit there with me
listening to this man defend himself
acting like we didn't just see the same tape?
Bro, I--it was a bad shoot. What do you want from me?
I'm just trying to get through this, okay?
I just wanna go home.
I don't want to get involved in things that are above us.
That's all!
Let me tell you what we ain't gonna do.
We ain't gonna say this is above our paygrade.
We are not going to dismiss this man as one bad apple
because we are in this, all right?
- We got stop hiding behind-- - Behind what?
Being white.
Being white? Really?
You don't gotta be Black to know wrong from right.
I never said that anything that that man did was right.
Did you hear me say that?
Think about what this white man did
and how the next Black kid is gonna look at you
- the next time you go out there. - I know.
I know, but I'm not doing this with you right now.
Why not?
Why not? We're here.
We might as well. We have been shot at,
chased down, all while protecting the white cop
that killed the Black kid, and I gotta live with that.
Why not you?
I gotta be angry. Why not you?
'Cause you the good white cop
that can't understand?
Who has nothing to do with any of this?
Is that what you're trying to say?
Because I don't! That's not me.
What's inside of him is not inside of me,
and you should be the one to know that!
How dare you, man!
I'm sick of you questioning me all the time.
Why is it me?
Why is it me that has to answer for this guy?
Huh? Ask yourself that question!
Yeah, you see?
He knows I'm innocent.
Shut up!
You know I am,
and your old man would say the same thing.
Do not talk to me about my father.
Okay, yeah. I feared for my life.
Your life wasn't even in danger!
And you don't think I can feel when it is?
I did 30 years in a warzone.
You know how many men I put away who shot
then got right back out on the street
and shot again?
How many dying kids I held in my arms?
How many bullets went past my head?
And you're gonna tell me that I don't know
when my life is danger? Huh?
I feared for my life!
You feared Jeff Duncan.
You saw another Black thug toting a gun.
Oh, man, it had nothing to do with race ever!
It everything to do with it.
Jeff was noncooperative, okay?
And you saw that.
No, I saw a man who lost empathy
for the people he swore to serve and protect.
- He resisted-- - I saw a man who was scared.
- He was-- - Scared of those people,
and you were scared way before you even pulled the trigger.
My life was in danger.
You ain't gonna do that. Not this time.
You're not gonna defend yourself
by blaming a dead Black victim.
Look at that.
Let's just calm down. Wheelan!
Now!
What did you do to it?
That--that ain't the video.
He moved. His hand moved for his weapon.
It moved!
- He did not move. - Yes, he did.
What, did you alter it?
You altered it.
And why would you do that? Why would you do that?
I know he moved, okay?
'Cause I saw him move. He moved.
Wheelan.
He never moved.
What on Earth would make you think he--
Adam, Kev. We got the second shooter.
You're all clear.
You go ahead and bring Wheelan in.
Copy that.
We just need you to cooperate.
I don't wanna answer your questions.
All right, talk to me.
It's a Scorpion.
Ten to one it's a match to our hit.
I got the shooter's phone.
Hank, there's a tracking signal on this phone.
Active?
Yes. And it's tracking a vehicle,
and the signal's being shared with someone else.
There's an outgoing message.
"Can't go. Bleeding's worse.
- You take Wheelan." - It's another shooter.
Kev, Ruzek, listen to me close.
You got on an active shooter tracking you right now.
Take cover. We're on our way.
Probably one of those people at Wheelan's.
All right, copy that.
How the hell did he get a tracker on your car?
When they were banging on the car,
they probably placed a tracker.
We gotta get the hell out of here.
We gotta go. Kev, you got anything?
- Anything, Kev? - Got it.
10-1, 10-1, shots fired at the police.
Copy that.
Go, go, go.
I gotta reload.
Kev, we got any extra mags in the car?
Naw, man, we were supposed to be a damn Uber.
Damn.
- We gotta retreat, man. - Come on.
Go, go, go. I got it.
Move, move, move.
- All right, move, move! - Cover me, cover me!
Stay down! Come on!
Come on, come on.
5021 Ida, three plainclothes officers on foot.
We are taking heavy fire, we are pinned down.
130th and Ewing. We need backup.
Copy, cars are rolling your way.
Everyone stay off the air.
Stay down, all right?
You got eyes on how many shooters?
- One. - There could be more.
I ain't see anybody else.
- Give me a gun. - Shh, shh.
How many doors on this place?
Just the two.
Well, we can't go out that way.
We're stuck right here.
I'm out of ammo. How many rounds you got?
Two or three.
You gotta take my cuffs off now.
No, stop, stop, stop talking. Stop talking.
- I'm not gonna die like this! - We're not.
Backup's on the way. You gotta stop talking.
We get clear for a sprint, I'll uncuff you.
We're not alone.
Come over here, come on.
Dispatch, we're going dark.
All I want is the man who killed my brother!
I'll die for that!
But tell me this:
are you willing to take a bullet for Wheelan?
Leave him now, and I'll let you walk away.
He's a murder!
This is the easiest decision you're ever gonna have to make!
Leave him, you walk!
Stay, you die with him!
You know I have the shot.
Leave him!
Drop the weapon!
Come out with your hands high!
He's upper level, right corner.
It's just him. There's one weapon.
Draw his fire. I'll move.
Ready?
Go, go.
Wheelan, move!
Leave me.
What?
Just get the hell out of here, okay?
No one will ever know.
I'm serious. Go!
Listen, listen.
The only reason for him to stop shooting
is because he's trying to get on top of us.
- I need you to stay down. - Okay, listen.
I was--you were right. I was scared.
Okay, I was scared.
I don't know why,
but he saw it, okay?
I murdered that kid, didn't I?
Stay down.
I said leave me!
Hang on! I got this.
Here I am! Here I am!
Stay down. Kev, you good?
- Kev! - I'm good.
Yeah, I'm good.
Hey. Wheelan!
Uh-uh. Not like that.
Uh-uh. That's too damn easy.
That's too damn easy. Come on.
You ain't gonna go out like that!
Not you!
Not like that.
- Ruz, you good? - Look at me.
Yeah, up top.
- Sarge, I'm gonna go up. - Come on.
Come on, Wheelan. Come on.
He's gone, Kev.
It's not fair. It's not fair.
That's too easy.
It's okay. You did your job.
Mm, I got my psych results back.
"Officer Ruzek has an uncompromising loyalty
to the police force. This could be problematic."
How about, "Officer Atwater has a lack of trust
"for his fellow officer.
This could be problematic."
"Appropriate loyalty,
"Commendable level of empathy...
Appropriately tempered to protect and serve."
They made you take the test, Sarge?
Those were Dave Wheelan's results
a week ago.
People are a thousand things, you know?
You throw them in this job, this system,
one moment,
you know, blink of an eye, what comes out...
Comes out.
I mean, how are you supposed to stop something
you can't see coming?
Yeah.
You both did good today.
I guess I should be getting home too.
You good?
I'm here.
Wheelan believed Jeff moved.
Swore he saw something that didn't happen.
Wheelan didn't know he had it in him.
What if you can't see it coming?