.
- All right, so that's
two bedrooms upstairs--
both the guest and the master.
- That master bedroom
is incredible.
- Right? It's like a--
a king lives in there.
- [soft laugh]
- Guest bathroom
for all the guests
that one would have
over for dinner in
your sweet, sweet kitchen.
- It's nice.
- This is, like, bigger than any
house I've ever lived in before.
- It's really nice.
- This is what they call
a "waterfall" countertop.
Look at it, it's glorious.
- You should get it.
It's really nice.
- It better be nice for
the price that they're asking,
which I'm hoping maybe
someday you'll split with me.
- What?
- I'm playing with you.
I'm playing with you.
- That's not funny.
- I'm playing, I'm playing,
I'm playing, I'm playing.
But seriously, you like it?
- I like it.
- Okay, 'cause I would hope
that you'd spend
a little bit of time
with me over here.
- We'll see.
- We'll see?
All right.
- Mm, I'm pretty sure
that this is illegal.
- I'm pretty sure I know
a few cops
that can help us out
just in case we get in trouble.
- Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's good.
[sultry music]
♪
[phone buzzing, ringing]
- No.
- [laughs]
- Hold on.
- We gotta go.
- Unfortunately, yes.
Okay.
[kisses]
[grunts]
You got that?
- Yeah.
- All right.
[clears throat]
[phone buzzing]
- [groans]
[buzzing]
[beep]
[knocking on door]
[door opens]
- Well?
- Everything looks good,
Antonio.
There's no tears,
no fractures, no arthritis.
- All right, then, why does
my shoulder still hurt so much?
- I'm not sure.
So when you say "pain,"
what type of discomfort
are you experiencing?
Is it stiffness, soreness?
- I don't know.
Uh, pain.
- You probably just need
to give it some more rest.
- Yeah.
Hey, uh, I'm gonna need
a refill on that prescription.
- Another one?
- I need something
to help with the pain, so.
- It's been three months
since the injury.
There's no structural damage.
- It's the only thing
that helps with the pain.
- I get it, but this would be
your fourth refill.
I mean, that's a lot
of Oxycodone,
especially for
an injury like this.
- Like I said, it still hurts.
- I understand, but--
- You know what, look,
I'm not some junkie
looking to hustle my doc
for some pills.
[tense music]
I'm a cop.
I just need help with the pain
so I can do my job.
- Look, I'm sorry.
I could lose my license.
If you need any help,
anything at all--
- I don't need any help, Doc.
I'm fine.
♪
[bottle clatters]
[breathing heavily]
♪
[grunts]
[groans]
♪
- What happened?
- [shaky breathing]
Nothing, I--
- Your hand is bleeding.
- I'm okay, sweetie.
I was just--
I was fooling around.
I was shadow-boxing and I--
I hit the stupid mirror.
- You sure you're okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
What are you doing home, anyway?
I thought you had mid-terms?
- I forgot my notebook.
- Well, I suggest
you find your notebook
and get back to the library.
Go.
♪
[phone buzzing]
[sighs]
Not right now.
- Where's Antonio?
He's not picking up his phone.
- Huh.
- So what's going on?
- Jay busts some punk
this morning with
an ounce of heroin in his car,
gave up the drug house.
Supposed to be moving
a lot of Fentanyl.
We're gonna hit it,
and see what we can find.
[guns cock]
- Yeah, and who we can flip.
- Yeah, so I want you
to bust them all, too.
Junkies, dealers,
girlfriends, everyone.
Hey, you know
where Antonio is?
- No, I've been
calling him but...
- Huh.
- Right, so Hailey, Burgess,
and I will take the front.
Ruzek, Atwater,
you guys take the back.
- All right, hit it.
I'll see you all
back at the district.
- Do we have any
names or pictures?
- No, we're flying blind.
But that makes it fun, right?
- Yeah.
[dramatic music pounds]
- Chicago PD, nobody move!
- Cops! Cops!
Go, go-go-go-go!
- Damn it.
Nobody move!
Hands in the air, now!
- Runners to the right!
- I said hands in the air, now!
- Get up against the wall.
- Get your hands up!
- This has gotta be
some kind of mistake, man.
- Hands where I can see them!
- Turn around!
- This must be
some kind of mistake.
- This is a mistake?
What is this, aspirin?
[brooding music]
What's all this, man?
♪
Look at the wall.
- Hey! Chicago PD!
- Face the wall,
put your hands behind your back.
♪
Adam, I got four
coming out the back!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Put your hands up!
- Come here!
I want to see hands!
- It's cool. It's cool.
- Hands up!
- Get on the ground!
Come here.
- It's cool. I'm cool.
- Oh, my hand, man!
- Hey--
- You, look--look at the wall.
Don't look at me,
just get on the wall, okay?
- Put your hands behind
your back right now.
Hands behind your back...
- Damn!
- Damn it.
- Burgess, you got her?
- Go, go, go!
I got her.
Hey, you got anything
that could hurt me in there?
- No, I don't know those guys.
- Hey! Do not--
You do not turn around.
- I didn't do anything.
- Hey.
- Whoa-whoa-whoa-whoa!
- I got him, I got him!
Chicago PD!
[dramatic music pounds]
♪
Police!
Freeze!
[dogs barking]
♪
[panting]
[metal clangs]
[metal rumbles]
Chicago PD!
Get down!
Get down right now
or I will shoot you!
Put your hands up.
Hands in the air!
Now turn around real slow.
Real slow.
What the hell?
- Don't shoot.
It's me.
- Antonio?
[dramatic music]
♪
- Antonio,
what the hell happened?
You were--you were
doing a buy in the house?
- It's not that hard
to understand, Adam.
I got a tip from a CI.
Came to check it out
so I did a buy.
- You didn't want
to tell anybody you were here?
We could have covered you.
- Oh, I got the tip
20 minutes ago.
I was in the area,
figured I'd come check it out.
It's no big deal.
- Yeah, it is a big deal, man.
I almost shot you.
- [sighs]
I'm sorry.
I should have
identified myself earlier.
- Antonio, look.
I don't mean to pry but, uh--
- Then don't.
- But we all called you
like a bunch of times.
- I came here to do
some undercover work.
Things got screwed up.
End of story.
- You break protocol,
it's end of story.
One of us does it,
bro, you would want our badge.
- I swear to God, Adam--
- Antonio, it's a little
out of character, man.
She almost shot you.
- Hey, listen, listen.
Nobody got hurt.
There's a lot of eyes around
so let's just leave it
alone for now.
- Okay.
[soft dramatic music]
- You okay?
- No.
♪
[knocking on window]
- Hey.
Can I get a ride?
- Yeah, sure.
- Thanks.
I, uh, drove here with Jay
but he's stuck doing
the paper work so he's gonna be
like another hour or so.
Are these yours, or...
- No, I did a buy, remember?
- Right.
Okay.
So I'll just take them
and lock them with the other--
- No, no, no, that's okay.
I can do it.
- Uh, no.
I almost killed you.
I mean, it's the last I can do.
- I'm good.
- Look--hey--uh,
I mean, I'm your partner...
and your friend.
If something's going on...
- I'm fine.
[scoffs]
[engine turns over]
[gear shift clicks]
- All right, Patrick Carter.
He's a mid-level player
according to Narcotics.
All his priors
are cocaine-related,
so he must have just started
pushing synthetic opioids.
- Controls on legit oxy
are getting tight,
so this fake stuff,
it's everywhere.
- Yeah, killing a lot
of people, too.
- 11 overdoses last month
in that neighborhood.
- Hey, why don't I
take a run at this guy,
see if I can get him
to flip up to his supplier?
- Uh, too late.
He lawyered up
the second they brought him
into interrogation.
All right, let's dig
into Carter's phone,
digital footprint,
known associates.
See if we can ID
who's supplying the pills.
Hey, give me a sec,
will you, Antonio?
- Yeah.
- Help me out.
Why you flying solo
at that drug house?
- Well, it's like
I told the other guys.
I got a tip from a CI.
I was in the area.
I figured I'd act on it.
- Huh.
Why'd you run?
- [blows raspberry] Man.
I thought it was a rip.
Guns were coming out,
heard yelling, so I took off.
- Hurt your hand?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Cut it moving some bricks
in the backyard.
It's no big deal.
Didn't even need stitches.
- Huh.
- That it?
- Thanks.
- You got it.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- Come on.
- Hey, hey.
- Shh.
- You'd better have a damn good
explanation for this, Antonio.
- I don't, and keep it down.
- Hey, we had a deal.
You keep me safe
and I get you pills.
Instead, you set me up.
- I didn't. It was a mistake.
I didn't know
they were gonna be there.
- You work with these people.
How did you not know that
they were looking at me?
Man, you must think I'm a idiot.
- I'm doing everything I can
but it's not gonna be easy.
- I don't care if it's easy.
Okay, just get it done,
'cause I ain't going down
for this alone, Antonio.
I can promise you that.
- Look, look, look.
The only way I can make a deal
is if you offer up
your supplier.
- You want me to flip?
Get my family killed?
What the hell are you thinking?
- You gonna cooperate?
Yes or no.
Yes or no?
- Fine.
But no jail time.
I'm 47 years old.
I can't go back to prison.
I won't go back.
I'm gonna walk.
I want full immunity.
- All right,
I'll see what I can do.
You just keep your mouth shut
or I'll bury you behind this.
♪
Good news, Sarge.
I just talked to Carter.
- I told you he lawyered up.
- I know.
I had an angle,
so I took a run at him.
- What are you talking about?
- Listen, he said he'll flip
if we can work out a good deal.
- How good?
- He wants full immunity.
- That's it?
What about a beach house
in Malibu? A new Tesla?
- Look, I'm just
telling you what he said.
- He's got two felony priors.
Unless his supplier
is Pablo Escobar,
he can forget about it.
- There's gotta be
something we can work out.
- Antonio,
it's an election year.
No one is gonna kick
a known pill dealer
with two priors.
The optics are terrible.
- Since when do you care
about optics?
- What the hell is going on?
- What do you mean?
- You don't look so good, bro.
Something you want to tell me?
- I'm fine.
♪
[phone clacks]
[click]
- Yeah, listen--
I want you to move Carter.
I don't want Antonio
anywhere near him.
You understand?
Thanks, Trudy.
♪
- Yo.
Looking for some Oxy.
- Don't carry that.
- How about Vicodin?
- I got rocks and blow.
That's it, jefe.
- [shaky breathing]
Give me a dime of H.
- My man over there
will hook you up.
- Give it to me.
- Hank, what the hell
are you doing?
- Where is it?
- Where's what?
- Come on,
don't make a jerk out of me.
- What are you doing?
Get off of me!
♪
- Uh, hey, you should know--
- It's all right,
it's all right.
- No, wait, look--
- Hey.
- I was meeting up with a CI
and he--
- Don't do that.
- No, I was--
I was meeting with a CI.
- Hey, don't do that.
Listen to me.
I'm gonna help
get you through this.
- [sobs]
I don't need help.
I don't need any help.
- Come on, hey.
- [whimpering]
- It's all right.
Hey.
- [sobbing]
- Come on.
[pounding on car]
Come on.
It's gonna be fine.
- [stammers]
- It's all right.
- I'm sorry.
I don't know
what the hell happened.
- It's gonna be all right.
- [sobbing]
[sniffles]
No, it--it's not.
[mutters]
That dealer, Carter...
- Yeah.
- I know him.
- Okay.
- [weeping]
He was giving me pills.
I--[sobbing]
- You promised
you'd look out, right?
It's okay.
Listen--hey.
We're gonna deal
with that, too.
We're gonna deal with that.
- [weeping]
- Listen to me.
Listen.
- [sniffling]
- Right now we gotta
get you clean, okay?
- I...
- I'm gonna take you home.
- [cries]
- I'm gonna take care of you.
okay?
- I'm sorry.
- Come on.
It's okay.
- [sniffles]
[weeping]
- It's okay.
[somber dramatic music]
♪
- There's nothing there.
- Come on, pack your bag.
You're going into
rapid detox today.
- I don't think
that's a good idea.
- Yeah, well, I'm not asking.
Look, I'll cover for you
while you're gone.
Won't go any further
than this room.
[phone ringing]
- It's Eva.
She's cooking dinner tonight.
- Hm.
- Hey, sweetie.
Listen, I'm gonna have
to call you back.
Who is this?
What?
What are you--
what are you talk--
Put Eva on the phone!
Hey, put her on the phone!
- What's going on?
[suspenseful music]
- I think someone
just kidnapped my daughter.
♪
.
[knocking on door]
- Antonio.
All right, the team's here.
Come on.
Just get your head on straight.
Eva needs you.
- Yeah.
[shaky breathing]
- So Antonio
got a call from Eva at 1:24.
Then the last call
from Eva's phone
was from the kidnapper
at 2:21.
- I called OCD Tech Lab
and put an emergency ping
on Eva's phone.
- Already checked all
the outside doors and windows.
There's no sign
of forced entry.
- There's no sign of struggle
outside the house either.
- No.
- That's because
she never made it home.
She always puts her backpack
right here on
the kitchen counter.
It's not here, so...
- I mean, you sure it's not
something to do with school?
Maybe a boy from school?
[suspenseful music]
- The guy on the phone
said I made a mistake.
That dealer, Paddy Carter?
He wasn't supposed
to get arrested.
That's because
I wasn't at that drug house
to do a buy-bust.
I was there
to score Oxy for me.
- Hm.
- I'm sorry, guys.
♪
- I assume I'm free to go.
[door clicks shut]
- Where is she?
- Where's who?
- Antonio Dawson's daughter.
- "Daughter"?
What the hell
are you talking about?
- You had a deal with Antonio.
You think he screwed you so you
had someone grab his daughter.
- [laughs]
You think I'm stupid?
I'm trying to get out of jail.
Why would I kidnap
a cop's daughter?
- You better be telling
the truth, Paddy.
Or you and me?
We're gonna have a problem.
[door clicks open]
- No, no.
Antonio, wait.
- Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I told you, stay upstairs.
- What'd he say, Hank?
- Nothing.
He said he had no idea
what we were talking about.
- He's lying.
- Maybe not.
I checked the logs.
He hasn't had any visitors
or phone calls
since he's been in lockup.
- You check
the security cameras?
- I did.
Until now, the only person
he talked to was you,
and we should probably
make sure that conversation
is accidentally erased.
- Okay, we'll take care
of that later.
Come on, let's go.
Okay, so the question is...
do we want to do this
off the books,
or do we want to
involve CPD and FBI?
But if we go big,
you're gonna have to
come clean about everything.
- I don't care
about any of that.
I just want to find Eva.
I'll do whatever you want,
whatever gives us
the best chances.
[phone buzzing]
- Jay, what do you got?
Good.
Chase it down.
Jay and Hailey
just found a witness.
- I heard somebody screaming.
I looked out my window,
I saw a man and a woman
up near the alley.
- Why didn't you call it in?
- It looked like
they were in an argument.
You don't call the cops
every time
somebody gets into a beef.
It was right here.
They went up the alley.
I didn't see what happened
after that.
- Can you describe the man?
- White guy, blue jacket.
I've seen her
around the neighborhood
but I've never seen him before.
- Jay?
- What do we got?
- We pinged Eva's phone.
It was recovered on
the median of I-94
near the Damen underpass.
I guess he tossed it
out the window.
Fortunately
the nearest camera is
two mile markers up the highway.
- Prints?
- Not yet, but we did
hand-deliver it to the lab, so--
- We pulled surveillance
from an apartment
two blocks
from Antonio's house.
It matches the timeline
of the kidnapping.
[keys tapping]
Are you sure you want
to see this?
- Play it.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Okay, right there.
[keys clack]
Should be able
to pull the plate.
[keys clack]
- Run that plate.
[keys clacking]
- All right, vehicle's
registered to a Jason Rizzo.
- Antonio,
you recognize this guy?
- He looks familiar.
I think he might have
worked with Carter.
- He's got two priors
for possession,
one for aggravated battery,
and--
he did two years in Stateville
for statutory rape.
- Address is in Uptown.
804 Christopher.
- All right, listen up,
before we make our first move
I'm gonna make something
crystal clear.
From this moment on,
we are off the books.
You want to walk, walk now.
No one's gonna judge you.
♪
- Let's go get Eva.
[rousing dramatic music]
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Clear.
- [grunts]
Show me your hands!
- Okay, okay, okay!
Who are you?
What do you want?
- Get up!
- Okay!
- Come here. Come here.
Where's Rizzo?
- Uh, he's not here.
- Where is he?
- I don't know, I swear!
- Why were you hiding?
- Because I'm scared of Rizzo!
He's an addict.
I've been trying to kick him out
for a month but he won't leave!
- When's the last time
you seen him?
- About an hour ago.
I told him that I was
gonna change the locks
and he said that he'd kill me.
- Was he with anybody?
- I don't know.
Whenever he's around, I stay
in here with the door locked.
- Sit down, shut up.
Don't move.
♪
[objects clattering]
- [grunts]
[soft dramatic music]
♪
- Antonio?
There's something in the garage
we need you to take a look at.
[somber music]
♪
- It's Eva's.
.
- So along with the backpack
we found, uh,
zip ties, duct tape.
Standard kidnap kit.
- [clears throat]
- The blood on the rag
is fresh.
- Okay, so that means
that Eva was just here.
So let's hit the streets,
find some witnesses.
Come on, pull it together.
Let's go.
[phone ringing]
- Dawson.
- Hey.
Put it on speaker.
- Who am I talking to?
- You're talking to the guy
who's gonna
put a bullet
in your daughter's head
if Paddy Carter don't walk.
- I'm working on it.
It's--it's gonna take
a little longer.
- You got four hours,
Detective.
- Don't--don't hang up.
I need proof of life.
- What's that mean?
- I need to know
my daughter's alive.
- No, you need
to release Paddy Carter.
- No, I need to know
my daughter's alive.
If I don't hear her voice,
then you got no deal!
- Daddy, please help me!
Help me!
[hard slap]
- Shut up!
- Let me go!
- Sweetie, don't worry.
- Dad!
- I'm coming for you.
- Help! Help me!
- You just be strong.
- Shut up!
You got four hours,
Detective, or I kill her.
- Hang on, hang on, hey-hey-hey.
Let's--let's figure this out.
You and me,
let's--come on, man.
Hey, you there?
Rizzo?
- Hey, hey.
He hung up.
All right, we're already
up on Antonio's phone.
I want you to trace that call.
Let's hit the streets.
We're gonna find
some witnesses.
Let's go.
- Keep Antonio away.
- Copy that.
- I want my lawyer.
- Step back.
- Hey, where's my lawyer?
- Jason Rizzo is your cousin!
- So?
- So he kidnapped Eva Dawson.
- Wait, what the hell
are you talking--
- You told him to kidnap
Dawson's daughter!
- No, I didn't, I swear--
ow!
- His only ask
was that you walk.
Why would he do that
on his own?
- Because he's an idiot
and an addict,
and every time I try
to help him out,
it bites me in the ass.
- How does Rizzo know Antonio?
- Because he's been
helping me out lately.
Okay, he knows the deal
that I have with Antonio.
He delivered a package
to his house last week.
Look, he probably only
wants me out to get more drugs.
He doesn't think
right in the head, this kid.
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
All I can tell you is
if you don't
do what this monster says,
he'll kill her.
[tense music]
♪
- Where you going, boss?
- Hey, Sam.
Thank you for meeting me.
Listen, I heard you caught
that pill case
we just brought in.
- Yeah, it's a good one.
I'm looking forward to it.
- Yeah, well, I need a favor.
- Name it.
- I want you to
let Carter walk on this.
- [scoffs]
- Look, there were some
unintended consequences
to that bust, and I can't
get into the details right now.
But the only way
to fix it is to kick Carter.
- Look, maybe I can hold off
the probable cause hearing,
buy you guys some time.
- It's gotta be within
the next three hours.
- It's election season.
Every candidate in Chicago's
stomping on each other
trying to prove
they're tougher on crime.
I'm not sure
I can make that happen.
- Look, one of my guys
is jammed up bad.
- [sighs]
- I need this.
- It's a tough ask.
- I know.
But you know I'll make it up
to you down the road.
- Okay.
Uh, I'll recommend
expedited release
based off of
insufficient evidence, huh?
[hands clasp]
- Thank you.
- Parked in the same place.
- Uh-huh.
- Any word yet?
- Nothing yet.
- Voight said
it was a done deal.
What's taking so long?
- I'll make some calls,
see what I can do.
Antonio, Antonio.
Antonio.
- Antonio?
Hey.
Where the hell's Eva?
I've been calling her
all afternoon
and she doesn't pick up.
She's not at the house.
What is that?
"Taken."
You--you mean kidnapped?
- Yeah.
It happened right after school,
so--but don't worry.
We're, you know--
- No, no, no-no-no.
You're--you're wrong.
She's just with a friend.
She's--did you try
calling Grace or Noa?
- She's not--
she's not at a friend's.
- Well maybe she's with a boy.
She was always afraid
to tell you about boys
because you get
so freaked out all the time--
- No!
She's not with a boy.
Listen--listen to me.
She was kidnapped.
- [inhales sharply]
This can't be happening again.
- Look--
- No, no, no, Tony, it can't.
- Listen--
- This can't be happening again.
- Listen, I promise
I'm gonna find her.
- I told you to quit this job
when they took Diego.
There were a million
other things you could have--
- We got Diego back
and we're gonna get Eva--
[somber music]
[both breathing shakily]
- You chose this job
over your family.
I hope it was worth it.
♪
- [weeping]
.
- That's actually the special
mayor's division...
- Come in, Hank.
What the hell are you thinking?
- Kate--
- The ASA wants to kick the guy
we just busted
for selling opioids
on your recommendation?
- I know what it looks like.
- One of the ODs
in the neighborhood
is a kid that goes to school
with Brian Kelton's kids.
- Listen, I can't
get into the details--
- His entire campaign is run
on tough on crime,
tough on drugs.
- I get it.
Look, one of my guys
has a problem.
I mean, a real problem.
The only way to fix it
is to kick Carter, Kate.
[somber dramatic music]
I'm asking you a favor.
- I'm sorry, truly.
My hands are tied.
Kelton just did a press
conference on the Carter bust
an hour ago.
He already rang the bell.
There's nothing I can do, Hank.
♪
[lock clicks]
- You got 30 seconds
to give me something good,
something that helps me
find Rizzo,
or today's gonna be the day
you end up hanging yourself
with your own shirt.
- I don't know anything.
I'm the one getting
screwed here, not--not Dawson.
[blow lands]
[grunts]
[groans]
[choking]
- Tell me where Rizzo is,
who he runs with,
who might help him,
give him money, a car.
Give me something, Paddy,
or I'll choke you out
right here and now.
- Okay, okay, just let me go.
- [grunts]
- [groaning]
Ah--ah--
- Start talking, Paddy.
- Okay, okay,
let me just catch my breath.
- Start talking!
- There's a--there's a guy.
His name is Gary.
He's got a scrap yard
out in Cicero.
They like to go out there
to get drunk and get high.
- That's all you got?
Nothing else?
- No, nothing.
They find Dawson's daughter,
that mean I get released?
[hollers]
- That means
you might get to live.
- [choking]
[groans, gasping]
[coughing]
♪
- You Gary McCoy?
- Yeah?
- When was the last time
you talked to
your friend, Jason Rizzo?
- None of your business.
- That's the wrong answer.
- I'm gonna look around
over here.
- You talk to him today?
- You got a warrant
or something?
- I don't need a warrant
to ask you questions.
- Questions about a kidnapping.
What do you know about that?
- I fix cars and I drink beer.
- Right.
- Yo, check this out.
Rizzo's car back there.
- Oh, you'd better
start talking fast,
'cause things are gonna go bad.
- "Go bad"?
The hell are you
gonna do about it?
- Rizzo switched out
his car here.
- What'd you give him, Gary?
- Make and model.
We need it now.
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- You're not going anywhere.
- Do not grab me, lady.
- Hey!
Come here. Come here.
- The hell is wrong
with you, huh?
- Say you're sorry.
Say you're sorry!
- It's fine!
We're talking about
a kidnapping, here, Gary.
That's life in prison
for Rizzo and for you
if you don't cooperate.
What car did you give Rizzo?
[tense music]
- Car's out front.
Rizzo's in Room 201.
- Okay, listen up.
We're moving in fast and dark.
This offender
is armed and dangerous,
so you all have a green light.
Let's hit it.
Antonio.
I need you to hang back, bro.
- Hank, there's nothing
you can do or say right now
that's gonna
keep me from going in there.
I'm going in first.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Go.
- Watch out, watch out.
[grunts]
Eva!
- All right, come on.
Get up!
Get up and put
your head on the wall.
Hands up.
- Okay, all right.
- Sweetie?
[gentle dramatic music]
It's Daddy.
I'm here, I'm here.
Can you hear me?
[soft crying]
[radio clicks]
Can you hear me?
- 50-21, roll an ambulance
to 1900 Fisher now.
- Copy that.
[indistinct radio chatter]
.
- You're gonna be okay.
You're safe now.
Just stay strong, sweetie.
I'm gonna take care of you.
[somber music]
Hey.
How's she doing?
Any serious injuries?
- Not sure.
We need to do more tests,
but she appears to be
in stable condition.
- I saw scratches on her face,
and I saw
some down below
by her waist and legs.
Do you know if--
did she say if the offender--
- No, she didn't say anything.
But when we get to Med,
we'll do a rape kit.
♪
- Rizzo is still in the wind.
- Yeah, but his truck's
still here.
- You know, maybe
he got spooked when we rolled in
and took off on foot.
- All right, so let's fan out.
Talk to witnesses,
look for cameras,
do whatever we gotta do.
Just find this prick.
[dramatic music]
♪
- We're gonna get you
all the help you need.
Nothing to worry about.
- I'm sorry, Dad, I--
I shouldn't have let him
push me in that car.
- No, no, no.
[shushing]
Don't blame yourself.
It's not your fault.
It's his.
And we're gonna find him.
He's gonna pay for what he did.
Do you know, did--
did he say anything?
Was he gonna meet someone or--
- No.
No, he just wanted drugs.
He's a loser.
He's an addict.
He took my ATM card,
made me tell him the PIN.
He was gonna buy drugs.
Meth, I think.
- Okay.
That's good.
[door chimes]
- ATM.
- Hey, what's up?
- Not here.
- CPD, bro.
Did this man come in here
and get some cash out the ATM?
- Yeah, he was here
like ten minutes ago.
- Okay, did he pull up
in a car or was he on foot?
- Uh, he was walking,
and he looked like
he was in bad shape, too.
- If anybody wanted
to score around here,
where would they go?
- Uh, the old factory.
Lots of drugs, lots of junkies.
Looks like one of those
zombie movies.
[door chimes]
[radio clicks]
- Me and Burgess
found the store
where Rizzo got his cash.
We're going to a drug spot
near the old factory.
Ten minutes away.
[dramatic music]
♪
- There he is.
[tires squealing]
[engine roaring]
[pounding on door]
[glass breaks]
- Chicago PD!
Stop running!
♪
[grunts]
- Put 'em down!
- Get off me!
Get off me!
- Hey!
Come on now!
- [grunting, struggling]
- Make a move.
Please.
- [laughs]
Come on, you won't do it.
- Then move.
- Come on, I want you to do it!
- Reach for something.
Hey!
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
We got this.
- Just give me five minutes
with him.
- No, Antonio.
- Five minutes.
- [panting]
- Give me your gun.
- Quit struggling.
[grunts]
- Adam.
- What's up?
You want to talk?
[both grunting]
♪
- Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
Whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, easy.
Come on.
That's enough.
That's enough, it's over!
Hey, whoa.
- Get up.
- How old is Eva anyway?
[soft chuckle]
She 18 yet?
She was good.
[laughs]
- [grunts]
[glass shatters]
- [screaming]
[loud thud]
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
♪
Whoa, what the hell
just happened?
- Antonio.
- He got what he deserved.
- Hey, hey--
- He took my daughter.
- Hey, Antonio.
You gotta shut up
and listen to me.
Are you clean right now?
- What?
- Hey, look at me.
Be honest.
I don't have time
to play games.
- Antonio!
- Today.
It was a few hours ago.
I needed a little energy
so I...
- Whoa, stop talking.
[approaching sirens wailing]
- [sighs]
What the hell are we gonna do?
[sirens wailing]
[dramatic music]
♪
[wolf howls]