Hey.
Uh, I got to go. I got to meet Jay.
All right.
How did I not know you went
to the University of Chicago?
My dad wanted me to be a lawyer.
Adam, I got to go.
I-I don't have pants.
- Pants.
- Thank you.
- So...
- Mm-hmm?
How do you want to play this?
Uh, low-key.
Like, um...
Like really low-key,
don't say anything to anyone,
this didn't happen low-key.
Okay. Copy that.
I will grab my stuff and leave.
Look, I, uh...
You know, just for the record,
that thing that didn't happen,
that was pretty fun.
Yeah, it was.
♪
What's up, Sarge?
What are you guys doing?
That's Al's desk. What are you doing...
what are you doing with Al's desk?
The district is doing a yearly audit.
They're going to reallocate it.
- Here we go.
- Sarge...
I...
♪
They left us his hat.
Has there been any progress
on Olinsky's letter of exoneration?
I'm working on it.
If there's no letter,
there is no pension.
They're cut and dried about that...
Trudy, I said I'm working on it.
Okay.
- Hank.
- Yeah?
My CI's story checks out.
There's been incident reports
at six different restaurants
in Little Village.
They have to be robbers.
Then why aren't the Robbery Dicks on it?
Well, if it's Little Village
that means it's immigrants.
Probably too scared to file a report.
Don't want to get deported.
That's right. No complaint, no crime.
So I say we put boots on ground,
monitor calls over the zone.
Maybe we catch 'em in the act.
Maybe we find a needle in a haystack.
We're dealing with
a crew that's preying on
the most vulnerable people in the city.
I know and I feel bad for
'em, but we got a lot going on.
If they're not gonna work with us...
It's our job to find a way.
Wait... wait, there's a call
going over City-Wide right now.
Possible armed robbery in progress
saying shots fired in the Little Village.
Okay, so let's roll on this.
As a team.
♪
- What happened?
- Mom and pop joint.
Pop caught a bullet to the throat.
Carlos Coto. He's the owner.
Waitress said two guys showed up,
told everybody to hit the floor,
and then they started shooting.
- She make an ID?
- They were wearing masks.
Hey, this witness said
the robbers grabbed a hostage
on the way out... a woman.
He give a description?
Yes, young Caucasian, denim jacket,
definitely not from the neighborhood.
Pulled into a blue Honda.
All right, let's hit the streets
look for witnesses.
See if any blue Hondas
show up on surveillance cams.
Crime techs found a key fob by the door.
Hm.
Let's go.
♪
People in glass houses
shouldn't throw stones.
This is the same guy who sued
the Chicago Police Department.
- Evan Gilchrist?
- Yeah.
Sergeant Hank Voight, Chicago PD.
You mind if we come in?
W-what is this all about?
Well, we found a BMW registered to you
in a parking lot in Little Village.
It's at the scene of a crime.
Yeah, that's my daughter's car.
Is she here?
Look, what the hell is going on?
We think she may have been abducted.
♪
What?
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
So they dragged Valerie into a car
and drove away, and that's all you know?
Well, at the moment, yes,
but we're still gathering information.
Let me ask you, this taco joint
in Little Village, that's in
a pretty rough neighborhood. Any idea why
she might be there?
Yeah, she's a foodie. So she travels
all over the city looking for dives
with exotic cuisines
and she blogs about it.
I warned her about
some of these neighborhoods.
All right, we're gonna need consent
to search all of Valerie's
electronic devices.
Yeah, I'll give you her passwords.
I keep tabs on her social media.
Is there any reason that you're
monitoring her so closely?
Yeah, she's my only child,
so I tend to err
on the side of over-protection.
Look, I know when someone goes missing
there's only a short window now.
I have 400 employees. I have access
to all kinds of data. I can help here...
I understand the impulse,
but the best thing you can do
right now is just sit back,
let us do our jobs.
Anyone contacts you,
you call us right away.
Sergeant, can I just talk
to you for a second?
Yeah. What's up?
You know I'm the one who financed
the Police Transparency Initiative.
What's your point?
Well, I just want
to make sure my politics
don't get in the way
of you doing your job.
Doing everything you can to,
please, find my daughter.
Sarge.
Just leave your phone on, please.
We just got a ping
on Valerie's cell phone.
♪
We found Valerie's phone
in the car, Sarge.
This car was stolen from
Little Village this morning.
Same make and model as the one
seen fleeing the taqueria.
Give me a minute, will you?
First Deputy.
Any update on the Gilchrist girl?
Well, we just found her phone,
but she's still in the wind.
Kidnapping?
No demands have been made,
but we do know she witnessed a murder
and the robbery crew grabbed her.
All this crime, this situation,
is gonna attract a lot of attention.
I know.
Evan Gilchrist has been
a royal pain in our ass.
I wanna get this buttoned up quickly.
Don't worry, I haven't forgotten
your boss is running for mayor.
There's a girl missing. Let's find her.
♪
This mean I get more boots on the ground?
Whatever you need.
♪
Hey, what happened this morning?
- What do you mean?
- You're, like, never late.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, sorry.
- It won't happen again.
- What do we got?
Valerie Gilchrist, 19 years old.
Just graduated from
the Culinary Institute.
No priors, no red flags.
Her sister died when they were kids,
but other than that,
she's led a privileged life.
Do we buy her dad's story
that she was there in Little
Village to blog about tacos?
Her social media's mostly about food.
Best salsas, hole in the wall.
According to "The Reader,"
Coto's has the number three
ranked taco in Chicago, so...
Wrong place, wrong time.
Check this out. We looked at the pattern
of the previous robberies.
The crew knew when these places
would be fat
and how to slip away
without being detected.
They case these joints,
probably ate there.
Makes sense they're
from the neighborhood.
If they're worried about
her being a witness
why not just silence her there?
She's a white girl. Maybe they
thought she was worth something.
Or they grabbed her for other reasons.
When we find this crew, we find her,
so search databases for anyone convicted
of robberies living around
Little Village.
Now let's get some extra
patrol units in here,
and pull in every banger
with an open warrant.
Hank, these are going up
all over Little Village.
♪
Hey.
Sergeant, any news?
I asked you to sit back,
let us do our job.
I'm not gonna sit on my hands
while my daughter's missing.
You put 500 grand on the street.
Now everyone's gonna try and grab it.
Unless that reward is coordinated with us
it's gonna pull this investigation
two separate directions.
I don't want the reward tied
to Chicago Police Department.
Okay, there are a lot of
undocumented immigrants
in Little Village and they're
scared of being deported.
Look, sir, I understand
you want to find your daughter,
so do I. But it's my job
and you're getting in the way
of me doing it.
Look... Hello?
Yeah. Right, give it to me.
I'm sorry, but that's
probably a different woman.
Thanks for your help.
No, I don't think you need to be
a legal resident to collect the reward.
Do you remember seeing her,
or are you chasing the money?
But do you
have any more information?
What, are we a bunch of telemarketers?
Hank, the phones just started blowing up.
People are calling us directly. - 500
grand's got a way of making people
remember things they've never seen.
Hang up the phones.
How 'bout we focus on police work?
I got something. I checked the
traffic cams by Coto's Taco
and I got a hit on that blue Honda.
Nice work. Hayley, you and Jay
head over to Streets and San.
Get this guy's name
and go talk to him.
This girl was in the blue Honda
parked next to your truck,
and you're sure you didn't see her?
Like I told you, I can't help you.
That's the girl on the posters.
- Did you see her?
- Mama, leave us alone.
Hugo, there's a $500,000 reward.
Did you see her?
Answer your mama, Hugo.
Okay.
Yeah, I saw her. Earlier today.
She was out on the street, running.
Some guy was chasing her.
Can you describe the man?
Latino, 30, little chubby.
Never seen him before.
And which direction were they going?
That way, toward a warehouse.
You saw a man chasing a woman
and you didn't call the police?
I get paid to pick up garbage.
I don't get nothing extra
for solving crimes.
♪
Over here.
There's blood. Looks recent.
♪
Body.
Victim, gunshot wound.
Roll an ambo.
50, 21, George, emergency.
Roll an ambo to our location.
We got a female victim, gunshot wound.
Copy that.
Okay, just... you know, take your time,
and then tell us what happened
Shaw Direc at the restaurant.
Um...
went there to, uh, get a taco.
I was...
walking in.
I didn't... realize what was happening.
Um...
I saw two men.
- They had masks.
- Okay.
One of them had a gun and, um...
the other guy came out from the back
and he started screaming
in Spanish and, uh...
Uh, the larger one shot him.
You didn't run?
I was... I was freaking out.
The one with the gun
grabbed me.
Shoved me in the back seat of his car.
Forced me to keep my face down.
One man said that they had to...
kill me.
Um...
He pulled over. He had to pee, and...
♪
I just... I took off running and I...
remember going into this building and...
Um...
Do you remember anything else about them?
Any tattoos, any scars?
No, I'm sorry.
Don't be sorry.
Okay, thank you.
♪
I'm gonna grab Halstead and dig
back to the other robberies,
the ones that didn't get reported.
Makes sense. Someone somewhere
had to have seen something.
Two weeks ago someone
from this restaurant called 911
and said that was a robbery in progress.
I already told the police when
they came, there wasn't a robbery.
Why would someone make that up?
Don't know.
I... was arguing with a customer.
Maybe the person who called got confused.
Thought I was being robbed.
Look, Miguel we know
that there's a stickup crew
going around targeting
Hispanic restaurants in the neighborhood.
You have nothing to be scared of.
This has nothing to do with ICE.
I'm not scared of you.
I've got my green card.
Why don't you, uh...
why don't you tell me more
about this misunderstanding.
You were here
for the robbery, weren't you?
Miguel's a victim.
We want to help.
You're his wife?
Engaged.
Okay.
Can you tell me what happened?
They're taking everything away from him.
Who? The people that did the robbery?
No, the guys who came after.
They asked for protection money.
I told Miguel to go to the police,
but he didn't listen.
Because you don't have papers.
If keeps paying those ladrones
he's gonna lose his business, his dreams.
That's not right.
Can you help us?
Yes, I can.
♪
Okay.
Shh. Get up.
Yeah, straight up.
Johnny Marquez.
What is this?
I'll you what this is.
This is you on surveillance cam.
Looks like you're running
a protection racket, Johnny.
It's a rough neighborhood, Voight.
We provide a service.
Oh yeah? Well, it proves
you're the shot caller.
And that means you ordered
those robberies.
I need the names of that crew, bro.
Ain't got nothing to do with robberies.
Yeah? Well, we just locked up 32 bangers
from this neighborhood
and let me tell you something,
they're singing.
They're lying to save their
own asses and you know it.
Well...
I'm about to tell you what I know.
You're Aunt Gloria Valdez, she's keeping
15 guns over at her place
on Maple Street,
and you're ex-baby mama,
she's got a few kilos over at her house.
But me...
I got a team of guys and they're waiting
to take 'em down right now.
So give me the names of that crew.
Okay.
I know something about the stickup
guys, but I ain't part of it.
I just get a little taste. That's it.
♪
I need names, Johnny.
Pablo Sosa. According to Marquez
he's the leader of the stickup crew.
He's got a rap sheet to the floor.
He just did four years of Stateville
for accessory to murder.
No current address.
Yeah, and Marquez says
that he thinks Sosa's
working with a young banger
named Jorge Luna.
Pablo's the fat guy,
so that's our shooter.
All right, we got any leads?
Yeah, Jorge Luna
has one prior for possession,
sentenced last month;
200 days of community service.
Right, and didn't his parole officer say
that's he's working off that
case at Clean Up Chicago?
Well, find out where they're cleaning
and pick him up now.
♪
Strike two!
- Hey, Coach.
- Yeah?
You need you to move the kids
out of the way.
Get 'em off the field. Do it now.
- Stay calm.
- Time!
All right, everybody,
bring it in. Come on.
There's lots of families
and children out here,
so we do not engage
under any circumstances.
No weapons.
We box this guy in on my orders.
Are we clear?
♪
We got eyes on the target.
Guys, he made us.
♪
- Don't engage.
- He's gonna jack that van.
Stand down! Stand down!
♪
Stay down.
Hey, Adam.
- What was that?
- We caught the guy.
I told you to stand down.
There were civilians.
He could have had a gun.
Yeah, I thought he was gonna
jack that van, so...
- I mean, we caught the guy...
- That's not the point.
Are we seriously...
we're gonna do this again?
And again and again...
I gave you an order.
♪
Thank you.
Detective, you're working on
Youthe Gilchrist case, yes?
Yes, Officer Kim Burgess.
Um, we have a person of interest.
I showed Valerie some photos.
Unfortunately, she wasn't able
to make a positive ID, so...
Mr. Gilchrist.
Kate Brennan, Deputy Superintendent.
I hear your daughter's going home today.
- That's great news.
- Thank you.
I just got off the phone
with Superintendant Kelton.
He wants you to know
that he's doing everything
he can to make sure that the men
that hurt your daughter are apprehended.
Well, I-I appreciate that.
Well, we may not be perfect,
but we deliver.
If you need something, give me a call.
If you're looking
for an attagirl, Ms. Brennan,
you're gonna be disappointed.
My daughter's safe
because I put out a reward.
That's why the witness came forward.
- That's why you found her.
- That's not true.
We found your daughter bleeding to death
in a warehouse through our police work.
Garbage man talked because of the money.
I mean... if you think I'm gonna
shill for your boss
or for Chicago PD,
it's never gonna happen.
I told you already.
I was at Pablo's yesterday.
We didn't have nothing
to do with those stickups.
Then why'd Johnny Marquez hang it on you?
'Cause Marquez, he's an old head,
he thinks he owns the neighborhood,
but he don't own me.
I don't follow his orders
and he don't like that.
Why'd you run at the park?
Simple.
You were chasing me, right?
Jorge, stop.
We know Pablo organized the stickups,
and a witness said Pablo's the one
who shot the manager,
so if you confirm that,
you give us Pablo, we'll help you out.
I mean, you'll do some time,
but you're young.
I mean, you still have a good life.
Nah.
I'm not talking. Hm.
Well, you may want
to reconsider 'cause...
the girl...
the one you thought you killed
can put you at the crime scene.
So even if you didn't pull the trigger,
we can still hang the murder on you.
- You screwed up, bro.
- No.
I had nothing to do with that.
Nothing.
I would never hurt a woman.
I'm not saying another word
till I get a lawyer.
♪
Okay, so Jorge said
he was chilling with Pablo
at the time of the murder, but that can't
be confirmed 'cause Pablo's in the wind.
Phone records?
Neither one has a registered phone.
I'm assuming they have burner phones.
Jorge had one when we busted him.
This kid's lying.
We just gotta push a little harder.
Yeah, but we have no prints,
no surveillance,
nothing to put Jorge at the scene.
All we got is the word of Johnny Marquez,
which, at this point,
ain't worth too much.
Jay,
you find that sanitation worker, Sanchez?
Yeah, I did, but he won't be much help.
Patrol found his body.
- Any witnesses?
- No, but we'll keep looking.
Well...
Hugo Sanchez just got popped.
Looks like Pablo's silencing
all witnesses.
Tough way to earn 500k.
All right, let's get Valerie in here.
- What for?
- Make an ID.
I already showed her a photo
right at the hospital.
Well, this time we'll show her a line-up.
Maybe if she's Jorge in person,
something'll click.
Got it.
♪
I already told you, they had masks on.
No, we know, but maybe there's
some other physical characteristic
like... like their arms or their
neck... maybe their hands.
I already said I-I don't remember.
Valerie, they can't see you,
so don't worry.
Okay, you're protected.
I don't know. Sorry.
Look, why do you keep hammering her?
We're trying to ID a killer.
Get him off the street.
Yeah, I understand,
but she didn't see the guy.
Can I go, please?
♪
Come on, hon. You're okay.
I mean, there's no good
reason to drag her down here.
She already looked at the photos.
Look, man, we are just trying
to nail the guy who hurt your daughter.
Yeah, well,
it sure doesn't feel that way.
Explain to me what that means.
- Reporters out there.
- Oh.
Your boss is trying to use my daughter
for political profit.
You know what? That might be.
Then again...
those reporters might be there
to talk to you about
that $500,000 reward.
The one that got
the sanitation worker killed.
♪
What? Hugo... Sanchez?
No.
You posted that picture on Twitter.
♪
Come on, there's a back exit.
There's no press.
Kim, take 'em out the back, will you?
♪
Hey, Sarge, we pulled footage
from the Sanchez homicide.
We got a positive ID from facial rec.
Pablo Sosa is definitely our shooter.
- Okay.
- Problem is,
we still don't have an address
on this guy.
He's a ghost.
We have Tact and Gang officers
hunting him down and so far nothing.
Then we try a different angle.
♪
It's your lucky day, Jorge.
You're good to go.
You mean I don't need no bail?
Nope.
Here's the thing, though,
as soon as you leave,
you're a marked man.
- Pablo's gonna think you're a snitch.
- I ain't no snitch.
Well...
that's not what Pablo's gonna think
'cause we're putting word out
on the street that we own you.
You're a cooperating witness.
Nah, Pablo knows I ain't no snitch.
Yeah, well, then you got
nothing to worry about.
Get out of here.
I bet the first person
he talks to is Pablo.
- Well, that's the plan.
- I got you.
♪
All right, Jorge just turned
on Race Street.
We relocated. We got him.
♪
All right, he just went into an apartment
at 1200 Race Street.
We're running everyone in the building,
So far, no nexus for either target.
Copy that.
♪
Yo, bro, I been wanting to rap with you
about this Antonio thing, though.
It's time to move on.
I know. I get it. I'm trying,
but... I don't know, man.
It's pretty tough.
He's always judging and critiquing.
He plays by the book.
True, but that doesn't make him
a bad person or a bad cop.
In my humble opinion,
he's a baller.
He's always the first one
through that door.
♪
50, 21, Henry, shots fired,
emergency 1200 Race Street.
♪
It's Pablo.
- Out the back.
- We can't leave him.
You go. Go!
♪
Police! Freeze!
Offender out the back!
♪
Jorge, stop! I will shoot!
Westbound in the alley.
♪
Hey!
50, 21, Idaho, carjacking,
on-site, gray pickup truck.
Stop the truck!
♪
Plates are 8, 4, 9... that's all I got.
Plate's 8-4-9, gray pickup truck.
Be advised, offender is armed.
♪
We lost Jorge.
He jacked a gray pickup truck,
so I put out a flash message.
Pablo didn't make it.
I found this next to the body.
It's a .380, same caliber
as the other murder.
Yo, I just got a hit on that gray pickup.
It's in a restaurant in the West Loop.
- Let's go!
- We'll meet you there.
♪
Went to the restaurant. Jorge's gone.
- He's in the wind.
- Check this out.
Valerie works at the restaurant
part-time.
The manager said
that he was looking for her.
He's looking for Valerie?
Yeah, we got a beat car sitting on it
just in case she comes back.
How does he even know where she works?
Hey, guys, they're dating.
What?
They're dating?
Yeah, they're dating.
I found a private DM app
that she downloaded
so messages stay off the radar.
According to this, they've been
hooking up for about a month.
♪
Find Valerie now.
Maybe we should wait till my...
my dad's lawyers get here.
Maybe you should tell us
what the hell's going on
since you've been screwing us
around this whole time.
I'm sorry, but my father told me
to always ask for a lawyer.
All right, look, Valerie,
the choice is yours.
We can do that,
but then the gloves come off.
We put you in handcuffs, charge you
with felony obstruction
and take you to jail.
And there's nothing that
your father can do about it.
But...
we'd rather not do that.
We know things aren't always
what they seem, so...
just help us out.
We had this...
really amazing connection.
It was, like, intense,
like there was no way
to stop us from happening even though
I knew he was a little crazy.
Do you know what I mean?
Yeah.
You fell for the bad boy.
Felt good. Felt right.
And you said to hell
with the consequences.
Did you know he was a criminal?
No.
I knew he lived in a tough part of town,
that he'd been in trouble.
Why don't you tell us about the robbery.
I was...
out with Jorge.
He got a-a phone call.
He said he had to go back
to Little Village
so...
I drove him to the restaurant and...
and he met up with this... this guy.
Uh...
Yeah, that's him. I, um...
I think his name is Pablo.
So I...
I dropped off Jorge...
You know, he told me to go back home,
but I stuck around 'cause
I wanted to spend the night with him.
And then I heard
all of this yelling and I went
to see what was happening
and that's when, uh, Pablo shot...
the guy.
♪
Yeah, that's him.
Everyone was...
was freaking out.
Pablo was yelling and screaming, and...
he pulled me into the car.
He...
He dropped Jorge off. He said he would...
He would take me back
to the house, but...
uh, but he was lying. He tried to kill me
and that is why I ran.
Where's Jorge now?
I don't...
I don't know,
but he is not what you think.
He's always been very respectful,
and Pablo, that is the killer.
♪
Valerie, you need to tell us where he is.
This thing with you and Jorge,
it's not gonna last.
It never does with the bad boys.
♪
The sooner you realize that, the better.
What's your take?
She's a stupid kid who fell in love
with a handsome punk
and stumbled onto a robbery.
I think she's hiding something.
All right, so dig back into
her phone records,
social media accounts,
anonymous and otherwise.
See if she tried to make contact.
- Hank, you got a sec?
- Yeah.
I had one of the FOP lawyers
draw up a full letter of
exoneration for Olinsky.
All it needs is one signature.
It's on your desk.
Trudy, I said I'm working on it.
I know that, but the signature it needs
is sitting in your office.
First Deputy.
I just want to make sure
that my intel is correct.
Gilchrist's daughter
is dating one of the offenders.
Well, dating might not
be the word for it, but...
Yeah, they had a relationship.
She lied to us.
It's called felony obstruction.
- What are you waiting for?
- We need her.
She's our best shot at
catching the offender, Jorge.
He's still out there.
We have two dead innocents.
She's in the middle of it.
- Get her booked.
- Huh.
I get it.
If we put Gilchrist's daughter in jail,
his criticism of CPD becomes meaningless.
He's just another bitter father
with an axe to grind, right?
I don't like coddling the rich.
- Huh.
- Makes us look bad.
You know what else makes you look bad?
- Hm?
- If Jorge kills more people
and the press founds out
that you had a chance to use Valerie
to get him off the streets,
but you decided to play politics instead.
What are you saying, Sergeant?
You know what I'm saying.
♪
I got something, Sarge.
That was four hours ago.
Get Evan Gilchrist down here.
♪
You grab my daughter? You drag her
down here and you don't even call.
- Hey.
- No heads up
I'm trying to help you, okay?
Listen to me.
Your daughter is shacking up
with the killer.
- Killer?
- Yeah.
And it looks like she's trying
to help him get away.
What are you talking about?
I'm telling you this wasn't a kidnapping.
It was a date gone bad.
Look, I don't know what kind of game
- you guys aren...
- I am not playing a game.
I'm telling you she is head-over-heels
in love with this guy.
Look, she withdrew five grand
in cash this morning.
Wha... so? It's not a crime
to withdraw money.
Yeah, well, it is
if you give it to a fugitive.
A killer.
If it turns that she's helping
this guy Jorge,
I am telling you...
there is no way to walk that back.
She'll do time. You understand?
I mean...
real time.
Me?
All I care about is catching the killer.
That's it.
If your daughter can help us,
I'll make sure she doesn't get jammed up.
♪
You have my word.
Jorge, where are you?
I'm almost there.
I'm at the place we were at last week.
I have the money.
Look, there's something
I need to tell you.
Just keep her talking till we locate him.
♪
What is it?
I had no idea Pablo was gonna do that.
He told me he was gonna take you home.
But then the police...
they showed me that picture.
I saw what he did to you.
That's why I killed him...
Because I love you.
Bingo.
♪
I would never let anybody hurt you.
Ever.
I love you so much.
Jorge, I'm so sorry.
No, no, I'm the one who's sorry.
It's a trap! You have to drive!
Right now! You have to go!
You have to go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Go. Go. Okay... go...
♪
Go! Come on. Come on.
Come on! Go! Go! Go! Go!
Run, kids! Run!
Come on. Move. Move. Move!
Move. Move. Move. Move. Come to me!
Faster, kids. Come on!
Come on. Come on. Come on!
♪
There's kids inside.
Kids.
He went that way. He went in there.
- You get the ones in front.
- Okay.
I'll go in front. Go in there.
Go. Go outside!
Kids, I want you to get behind me now!
Get behind me now!
Get behind me, kid! Get behind me!
Now hold hands, hold my hand.
I want you to walk quickly
and walk me to that door.
- Y'all got it?
- Walk me to that door.
Yeah. Get him out.
♪
No. No. I'll go.
Stand down, that's an order.
♪
- Go, you go.
- Come on.
♪
Shh.
Come on. Come to me.
Shh. Come to me.
Stay down.
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
Hey. Hey.
♪
Go. Go.
Let's see. You're gonna have to hold.
How's your shoulder?
Ah, it's okay. I just hit it wrong.
Shouldn't have hit it in the first place.
That's what the young guys are for.
Yeah.
All right, I called ahead to Med.
They're expecting you.
Appreciate it.
Hi.
- Val.
- Hey.
- Dad. You have to help me.
- Wait...
What the hell's going on?
Why is she in handcuffs?
You can't talk to her right now.
- Please, I'm sorry.
- She's under arrest.
- Are you kidding me?
- Felony obstruction.
We had a signed cooperation agreement!
Well, she didn't cooperate.
Deal's off.
- I'm very sorry.
- You're sorry?
♪
Thank you.
- Hey, Hank.
- Hi.
I'll meet you inside.
- Ma'am.
- Thank you for coming.
I hear you arrested the Gilchrist girl.
Felony obstruction.
Talked to the ASA, she's gonna write
the full ticket. She'll do time.
All right, do you really
think that's necessary?
♪
I thought you'd be happy.
At the end of the day,
she doesn't really pose
a threat to the city, does she?
Huh.
♪
So she walks?
She walks 'cause her daddy's rich,
and he's gonna play ball.
Because she's a kid.
She deserves a second chance.
♪
I need something too.
It's good to hear.
Yeah, I'll talk to you later.
Antonio got released from the hospital.
Oh, that's good.
♪
Hey, I want to revisit that
thing you said about bad boys.
Mm-mm.
Something about they're, uh, fun,
but they never last. Something like that.
First of all, you're not a bad boy.
- Well...
- Second of all, I was questioning a suspect.
All right, I was just asking.
♪
Damn it.
You're up.
♪
But since we're talking about
the thing that never happened...
- Yeah?
- Um...
What's the deal with you and Burgess?
Well...
I don't know. Kim's an amazing woman.
I love her.
We had a lot of bumps in the road,
and, at the end of the day,
she didn't want to be with me,
so we're friends.
Simple as that.
Yo, you know,
if you want to tie this off,
I get it. I'll respect that.
But I personally think
we should keep it going.
Have some fun. See what happens.
No pressure.
You know?
But I will do whatever you want to do.
Okay? It's up to you.
♪
We expect our police
officers to be perfect,
but they're just human.
♪
They deserve our respect and support
and, in my case, gratitude.
Thanks to the CPD,
I got my daughter back.
Does this mean that you're
gonna bury the hatchet
with Brian Kelton?
Well, I'm gonna do a lot more than that.
I've actually decided
to support him for mayor.
♪
Hey.
You wanted to see me?
Yeah.
♪
"The Internal Affairs investigation
"into criminal allegations against
"Detective Alvin Olinsky...
"revealed the detective
violated no rules,
"regulations, nor general orders.
"He is hereby exonerated of all charges
"and his reputation restored.
Signed Deputy Superintendant
Katherine Brennan."
♪
I'm impressed.
Don't be.
♪
Does this have anything to do
with the Gilchrist kid walking?
Sometimes things just work out.
♪
Uh-huh.
To Al.
♪