Yes, I know you've been calling.
I just--I haven't had time to schedule a follow-up.
Understood, Dr. Eli,
but I have no plans to get pregnant again, so...
I'm at work. I have to call you back.
- Is that all right? Thanks. - Everything all right?
Yeah, just a thing I'm pushing.
You just missed our bud Barkey again.
He dropped the price 5K.
Adam, what are you actually gonna do with a boat?
I don't know, sail the seven seas,
become a new man.
Park it in my garage, drink beer on it.
Exactly, kind of boat Barkey's gonna sell you,
garage is a lot more likely.
Anyway, I'm just saying...
- Yeah? - The change is good, you know?
Like, for instance, you and I, we don't date,
and yet somehow we've become my Gammie and Pawpaw.
You still call them that?
Well, that is their name.
We go to the same diner every morning.
We go to work. We go to the same bar.
We do nothing new. We go nowhere new.
We meet nobody, date nobody.
- We have no boat. - See? Exactly.
This is what I'm talking about.
See, you're even finishing my thoughts here.
Change is overrated, Adam.
The whole world's looking for a little same old right now.
Yeah, not guys like me and Barkey.
No. You and Barkey are a set of real revolutionary thinkers--
Yeah, exactly.
- Yeah, I'm an adventurer. - Of course.
I'm like a Renaissance man over here.
You are, mm-hmm.
Adam!
Oh, my God.
Get out of the road, kid!
Stay in your car. Stay in your car.
- Is she alone? - Close your door.
- kiddo. - Where's her family?
It's all right.
It's okay. It's okay.
Let's get you out of the street, okay?
Where's your family?
What are you doing around here? Do you live around here?
- Did you run from someplace? - All right, keep moving.
Are you lost, honey?
There. Do you live right there?
Is that where you live?
Are you lost?
She's not talking.
There's nobody out here. I mean, there's nobody around.
Where's your family? Do you know?
Okay, let's start again. I'm Kim.
This is Adam. And we're police, see?
That's what that star means.
I'm a police officer. I'm gonna help you.
Okay? I promise.
Yeah, this is Officer Adam Ruzek, Intelligence.
- Recovered a tender age child... - I like your outfit.
Could I check something really quickly?
Just--I'm just gonna... really fast.
- Adam? - One sec.
Makayla Ward.
- Yeah, I got a name. - It's okay.
Everything is gonna be okay, all right?
Public school system has the mom listed
as Gabrielle Ward.
- 4818 should be- - Over there?
Yeah, there it is.
She's sleeping.
- I'll have the parents come out. - Yeah.
Soft door. Don't wake her up.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - All right.
5021 Eddie, requesting backup at 4818 South Wells.
Copy that, 5021 Eddie. Backup on the way.
What's going on?
There's blood splatter, a lot of it.
Ready?
Ah, it's open.
All right.
One, two, three.
- Cover me. - Yup.
Cover, cover, cover.
- Body. - Gotcha.
Clear.
I got another body.
- You hear that? - Yeah.
The back door.
Backyard's clear.
Adam.
Look at these little footprints.
That little girl, Makayla, she was here.
All right. Call it in.
I'm gonna go check on her.
Burgess took the girl to Med. They're checking her out.
- Witnesses? - Not yet.
We're working the block.
ID the victims?
So they're all members of the same family, the Wards.
They all live in the house.
And the little girl, Makayla?
She's the only family member that survived.
All right, let's keep a cap on the media as long as we can.
Means no one but the techs and us
step foot on this property.
It is absolute overkill in here.
Had to be personal.
This is Claudia Ward.
She's the matriarch of the family.
House is in her name.
One GSW to the back of the head.
Looks like she was running to the front door.
Her kill is the cleanest out of all of them.
This is her son Benny Ward, 22.
He's got bruising, defense wounds.
Looks like he was pistol-whipped.
His sister's here in the kitchen.
Gabrielle Ward, Makayla's mother.
One GSW to the stomach, two to the back.
She...bled out slow.
No sign of robbery yet.
Cash was left on the table in the front.
Purses and wallets in plain view.
No forced entry?
No, doesn't look like it.
Front and the back door were unlocked.
- It's the little girl? - Yeah.
Prints match Makayla's shoes. We think she was inside.
She was probably hiding, maybe here in the pantry.
Shooter makes his way to the front.
She finds her mom bleeding,
takes off out the back.
Mom told her to run.
Yeah.
Med cleared the girl. No injuries.
Yeah, Burgess is with her. We're waiting on DCFS.
All right, talk to me. What do we got?
Ward family, no priors except for Benny,
who has a year-old possession charge.
Thinking the shooter might've used a suppressor.
No one heard or saw anything, and zero cams.
I connected with Forensics. It's gonna take them some time.
Three bodies, that's a lot of DNA.
Four people living in one house,
that's a lot of foot traffic.
Well, we work the why first.
Home invasion gone wrong? A hit?
Family disagreement? Murder turned triple homicide?
There can be plenty of possibilities,
but it's gonna be the why that gets us to who.
I got a possible why.
Benny Ward's yearlong possession charge
is not the full story.
Kid's got a couple gang dispersal cards,
quite the social media presence.
According to the Gang Unit and CPIC,
he's been the enforcer for the Gangster Prophets
for the past two years.
Okay, so he had enemies.
He's got a lot of enemies.
CPIC sent over a whole list.
Over a dozen death threats online.
So wait. We think this is gang retribution?
They'd do a whole family like that?
Listen, no reason is ever gonna feel like enough, Adam.
- DCFS is downstairs. - All right, so run it down.
Talk to your CIs.
If this was a gang hit, the streets will know.
Sarge. They're here.
Lieutenant, good to see you.
Hey, wanted to work this one myself.
30 years. Juvenile cases.
Happy to have you on this one.
This is Alanah Mercer with DCFS.
Is someone from Makayla's family on the way?
Unfortunately, most of the girl's family was in that home.
She doesn't have any father on the birth certificate.
Only immediate kin is a cousin of Gabrielle's.
We're trying to track her down.
I understand you believe Makayla is a potential witness.
We have evidence that she was in the home.
As of now, she might be our only witness.
She still hasn't said a word, though.
At her age, that's pretty expected.
Trauma like that, fear, it floods the system.
Doesn't go away quick.
Might be days, weeks, months before she talks about it.
Well, we would like to question her if possible.
You can try as long as it's not harming her,
but Alanah and the hospital need to be kept apprised.
No problem.
Kim, you run point.
Sarge, I don't have any experience
working with children.
- A youth detective would be-- - You were her first contact?
Yeah, I was her first contact.
Priority is to make her feel safe.
She certainly won't talk or move forward until then.
Right now, you're the best option
to make her feel that way.
Okay.
She hasn't talked yet.
How am I supposed to make this kid feel safe
after what happened?
Honestly, I don't know.
But I don't think there's just one right way.
All right.
I brought you something to eat.
So I--
I was hoping and thinking
we could maybe talk a little about what happened
before I found you on the street.
What do you think?
Okay?
Did you run there from your house?
Do you remember being at home?
Makayla, do you remember anything about what happened?
Anything at all?
Okay.
Nah, nah. You told me we were done.
You told me you was going to New York.
I'm back now.
Nope.
Look, I ain't stepping foot near no massacre.
That's very perceptive of you, Marv.
I never told you why we're here.
It's bad karma.
You can't go pirouetting around a whole family murdered.
- Pirouetting? - It's not good for the soul.
- Nah. You can't bribe me on this one. - No?
'Cause your sister called me last week
saying you broke into her place looking for cash.
Scared the hell out of your niece.
- I didn't mean to do that. - All we need is a name.
Benny was a Gangster Prophet,
and we know the streets are talking,
so who are they saying killed his family?
Marv, when have I ever
asked you a question not worth answering for me?
The streets are saying
a Southside Hustler took them out.
Okay, you got a name?
Tru!
Goes by Tru. He killed them.
Why?
Benny and Tru got into it a couple of weeks ago.
Guys broke it up
but not before Benny jacked a beer bottle into Tru's eye.
The killings were payback,
karma.
This him?
Yeah, that's him.
He usually hangs at the Y courts.
Plays ball there.
Call your sister and apologize.
Truman Powell, 27.
Got two priors for assault.
CPIC has him on for multiple threats against Benny online,
and he's got an open warrant for aggravated battery.
Works for me.
I got the front door covered. Let's take him outside.
You got an anchor?
Yeah. Got my eye on you. Got your six.
He's coming out.
Truman Powell, Chicago PD! Stop!
Truman, Chicago PD!
Arm up! Arm up!
Okay, we're done! Stop fighting!
Turn over.
Don't move.
All right, let's go. Get up!
Get up!
You got an outstanding warrant,
History of violence,
multiple threats against a dead man,
and we ran your car, Tru; you're four blocks
from the Wards' house two hours before the killings.
What, you just wanna sit there and smile at me?
Hey, if I were you,
I'd at least give us the bare minimum.
You got an alibi you wanna give us?
I got a lawyer. I'll call him now.
- You catch that? - Yeah, he knows something.
He's good at pretending he's not scared, though.
Hey, Upton.
Not just calling me anymore.
Now the feds are sending me packages for you.
- Thank you. - You're gonna have
to rein this in at some point,
not that I don't like being your mail lady.
I know. Thank you.
The feds?
Look, I don't care if Tru's not talking.
He's still looking good for it.
And ballistics came back.
The bullets match an unsolved Southside Hustler shoot.
Would make sense if it was a gang pass-down piece.
All right, so we hold Tru for 48,
see if we can place him at the scene.
Hey, Kim make any progress with the kid?
Not yet.
Family Services are gonna have to relocate her tonight.
Kim's out trying something right now.
All right, let's hit it.
What did the feds want?
It's a job offer.
Well, that's good. Where at?
New York?
Cool.
- Stayed in the same place? - Yeah.
Okay, great.
I went and I grabbed what I hoped were favorites.
Got this guy. Seemed nice.
How about--oh.
Penguin, huh?
and I brought your mom's sweater.
Thought maybe you might wanna wear it.
Let's put it on you.
'Cause I have some friends I want you to meet.
This is my friend Alanah, the lady you met before.
This is Trudy. You know her.
And that's Claire.
Claire has this really nice house she's gonna take you to.
You're gonna go, you're gonna get a good nice rest,
and then you're gonna come here,
and then you and I are gonna talk in the morning, all right?
Ready to go, kiddo?
Do you want me to come with you?
Okay.
All right, we'll grab your things.
Bedroom's just down the hall to your right.
Okay. You're going the right way.
It's this door right here, all right?
Wow, look at the stars. Those are cool.
I brought you something,
your pajamas.
You know what I used to do when I was younger?
I would line all my stuffies at the end of my bed
so it was like this little army keeping me safe.
Kind of dumb.
It's okay if you're scared, Makayla.
I've been scared before.
I know the feeling pretty well.
Oh, yeah. Adults get scared for sure.
There was a time a few months ago.
I was doing my job, and somebody tried to hurt me.
And I was so scared, but...
that's the good thing about being scared.
Sometimes it's like this reminder
that you have to be brave, you have to fight.
So I fought.
But I ran.
That's okay.
Running is a kind of fighting.
I ran outside.
But she came looking.
She? You saw a woman in your house?
What was her name? You know her?
Okay.
But she was looking for me.
She was calling my name.
But I hid outside.
Okay.
Can I go to sleep now?
Yeah, Makayla. You can go to bed.
I will be right back, and I will...
tuck you in, okay?
Give me two minutes.
Claire? What's wrong?
I just--I thought I saw someone.
- It's probably a shadow. - What exactly did you see?
Someone along the side of the house,
like they were trying not to be seen.
Get down!
- What's going on - Just get down.
Makayla?
Makayla!
I'm here.
Get behind me. Get behind me!
Grab my hand, okay? You're okay. You're okay.
You're all right.
Stay behind me no matter what. No matter what.
Claire, get down low.
Get low and come to me. Come to me!
Come to me quick. Take my phone.
Call 911. Get in the bathtub.
Leave the line open. Take Makayla.
Come here, sweetie. You're okay, Makayla!
You're okay. You're okay.
Two intruders in the house. I'm with Officer Kim Burgess...
So patrol arrived after three minutes,
Spotted an SUV fleeing the sence.
black Nissan Pathfinder, no plates.
- They lost the vehicle? - Yeah.
They followed it all the way to Wacker for a mile,
- and then they lost it. - You okay?
Yeah, I saw two different offenders,
both masked and gloved up.
I wasn't able to discern race, height.
Things happened very fast, but they were here for Makayla.
What makes you think that?
They crashed this location ten minutes after we arrived.
They hit her window first.
They must've followed us here.
Opens more questions than answers.
- You think it was a hit - I don't know what it was.
But Makayla had finally started talking.
She said she saw a woman in her house at the time of the murders
and the woman was calling out her name.
Okay, either way, we do need to protect the child
until we have answers.
I'll call WITSEC and get her into protection.
She's staying with me.
No, she can't. That's not protocol.
Well, let's go against protocol.
- Right now, your job is - My job is to protect the kid.
- Is she always like this? - Yeah, she always is.
Well, she's not wrong, and if it was about Makayla,
it's probably best we keep it in-house.
Someone ID'd her location.
Lieutenant, with all due respect,
you can play it by protocol or not.
You can take me off the case.
You can detail me to WITSEC.
I don't care how it happens,
but that kid stays with me.
Okay, we'll get a safe house approved.
Thank you.
You gotta have the teddy bear.
That's a classic, right?
And one more. Which guy here?
You point.
This guy? This is your favorite?
Okay.
What am I looking at here?
- What is this? - Platypus?
A platypus.
How could I forget the shiny-tailed platypus?
Right here. Is he your favorite?
Yeah, he stays with you, then.
Okay, it's bedtime. Let's go.
You want us to stay with you?
Okay?
Okay. Go on.
All right.
Scooch down.
There you go.
Good night, Makayla.
As we've repeatedly said,
my client won't be answering any more questions.
And as I have said, I'm not asking any questions.
I'm just giving him the info.
We learned that there was a woman inside that house,
so clearly, we're missing something.
- He's got nothing to say. - Look, Truman,
you're gonna get booked on your warrant at the end of the day,
so we don't have to release you in 48.
We can keep pressing till we make this fit.
All right, this is enough.
You got motive, no alibi.
You're in the area.
You see how easy I can make it that you and your girl,
you go for a little joyride,
you're looking to settle some scores,
you entered the house and slaughtered everyone inside?
I'd never stepped foot in that house.
You would never step foot in that house?
Why'd you say it like that,
you would never?
Oh, no.
No. Hey, hey, hey.
It was just, um-- it was just a truck, okay?
But what if they come back tonight?
What if who comes back tonight?
This little girl...
watched her mother get killed in front of her.
Her whole family...
was murdered in front of her.
This tiny kid
has to deal with those moments of violence
for the rest of her life.
Look at me.
You said you would never step foot in that house,
and I'm guessing that's because of retribution,
because of Benny.
It's not because of Benny.
Truman, I am advising you--
I would never step foot in that house because of her.
She's the reason why. She's protected.
I go near her, I end up dead.
When you say "they," who are you talking about, huh?
Mm, my daddy and her.
Your daddy?
At your house?
The woman said he was there.
She told me to come out,
that my daddy was there to take me home.
All right. This is Tariq Morris.
He is a notorious Southside Hustler.
He's extremely violent. He's got 12 priors.
He's feared by his faction.
According to Truman,
Tariq is Makayla's father.
So Tariq and Gabrielle
dated briefly years ago.
Gabrielle got pregnant.
Tariq ended up in Stateville on a six-year prison sentence.
Before the baby was born,
Gabrielle broke it off with him.
- And Tariq just got released? - Three days ago.
Makayla said there was a woman in the house
calling out her name,
saying her father was there to pick her up.
They were looking for the girl.
So it's been about Makayla this whole time.
They were there to kidnap her.
Okay.
Stateville sent over visitor logs for Tariq,
so we firmed up a theory.
Gabrielle went to visit him once
at the beginning of his sentence.
Didn't bring Makayla, and she never went back.
I talked to a few guards, Sarge.
Apparently, that was the exact visit
that Gabrielle broke up with him.
Took the chance to get her and her daughter the hell away from him.
Stopped answering his messages and his letters,
just completely shut him out.
And he spent six years in prison ruminating on it.
Right, so he goes to that house.
The entire family tries to protect Makayla,
and they get killed for it.
Think we've ID'd the female accomplice.
Nia Benson.
Girl from the neighborhood, half a dozen arrest priors,
not a single charge on her.
Started visiting Tariq in prison about a year ago.
There's phone calls. There's emails.
There's hundreds of visits between the two of them.
This is a full-on prison romance.
She also has a black Nissan Pathfinder,
which is the same SUV that we found at the foster home.
Ruzek's running her LKAs right now.
Yo, I think I got her.
Patrol just responded to our BOLO
at Nia's sister's house.
There's a black Nissan Pathfinder parked in the back alley.
Go grab her.
Please!
Can somebody tell me what's going on?
This cop won't tell me anything.
I don't even get why I'm in here!
All right, let me clue you in.
We found your SUV at the scene of an attempted kidnapping.
You match our descriptors for a triple homicide.
Your sister admitted to us
that you asked her for cash and a car.
Said you wanted to skip town.
Should I keep going?
'Cause we searched your sister's complex,
found no trace of Tariq.
So why don't we start there, only this time
without the cute?
Where is he?
I don't know.
I-I-I-I don't know, okay?
- Look, it's not what you think. - Okay.
Tariq was going crazy. He put a gun to my head!
He told me he would kill me if I didn't drive him.
I never left the car.
That sounds terrible,
but see, the only problem is, I read your record.
Nia, I know you've been in rooms like this before,
and yet you never been charged.
So this routine, it usually works for you, huh?
Four times a person of interest,
three arrests, zero charges.
You know, the saying goes,
you only get lucky so many times
before cops start thinking you're smart.
- Where's Tariq? - I have no idea.
You were supposed to pick him up.
No, I got away from him.
See, we got your phone. You understand that?
I read your texts. I know your plan.
No, no. I was lying to him.
I never even knew what he was up to, I swear--
I think you two wanted a whole new life
on the outside, a perfect family.
Only thing missing:
a baby.
So you two walked into his ex-girlfriend's house
to steal a child.
And when her family tried to defend her,
you murdered every one of them.
I'm sorry.
I don't know anything, okay?
Tariq thought his ex-girlfriend was a bitch,
but the rest is news to me.
I never left the car.
I don't know where he is.
- Any progress on Tariq? - Zero.
Transit teams, state police have been alerted,
but so far, nothing.
Guy's hiding out, waiting for his gal.
What about a lure? We got her cell.
- We could do a bait and switch. - I don't know.
I mean, the texts on her phone made it sound like
she already knew where she was picking Tariq up.
If we change locations now,
chances are, he's gonna know it's us.
Look, it's simple. We need Nia to talk.
We're gonna have to use Makayla as leverage.
I mean, she was at the house.
She can ID her as an active participant.
But I want no legal loopholes.
We jump straight to a lineup,
put Makayla in front of it.
All right, let Burgess know.
Okay, you're gonna look at a line of people,
and then you're just gonna point to the lady
that you saw at your house.
They cannot see you,
and it is gonna go really fast.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
If we're waiting all day,
can I at least get a water or something?
No, no, no, no, no.
Hey, hey, look at me. You're okay.
You're okay. Shut the door.
Hey, take a deep breath. Come here.
I'm right here. I'm not going anywhere.
I'm not going anywhere! Come here, come here.
We're not going in there.
She was doing okay.
We'll just go check on her in a little bit.
Kid's all right.
She's with Platt and a paramedic now.
Okay, give her a few hours. Try again.
Or we resort to a photo lineup.
No, I'm not putting her through that.
I'm not putting her through any of that.
If there's a chance it's not good for her,
we don't do it.
Okay, so what's the play?
'Cause we got zero leads on Tariq.
Barely got a murder case on Nia, and she knows it.
Nia doesn't know if Makayla's behind the glass or not.
So you wanna do a lineup anyway.
Yeah, I'll lie my ass off.
Okay.
Just...
make it as airtight as you can.
The witness ID'd you from the lineup.
They saw you enter the Ward home,
exit the Ward home, and proceed into the backyard,
where you were heard calling a young girl's name:
Makayla.
From the DNA they swabbed from you,
they matched half a dozen samples inside the Ward home,
including on the body of one of the victims.
They are still running your SUV,
but they were able to confirm two traces of blood
not visible to the naked eye:
one on the driver's mat
and the other on the passenger seat.
This is quite a lot of evidence, Nia,
more than we hoped for,
so it won't matter if you shot anyone yourself.
You were there. You participated.
You will be charged one count of home invasion,
two counts attempted aggravated kidnapping,
and three counts of murder.
So this right here, you and me,
it's gonna be your only chance to help yourself.
I need you to tell me where Tariq is.
Six counts, Nia.
These are charges you do not walk back.
Where is he?
Bitch, I don't believe you.
You don't believe what?
She's gonna keep going.
That this is your last chance?
You understand, right?
I walk out that door, the ball rolls on from here.
You understand that?
Guess I should call my lawyer, then, huh?
Yeah, sure.
Call your lawyer.
See, the truth is, Nia,
I don't need your cooperation.
I came in here 'cause I was obligated to.
And I sure as hell was hoping
I wouldn't have to give you a damn thing...
bitch.
Hey, Fernandez?
Patrol officer will be here soon.
He'll take you to booking. You can call your lawyer there.
I'm guessing you'll be transferred out of state
- in the morning. - Out of state?
Mm, Indiana.
Claudia Ward, the grandmother, she was a postal worker.
- Is that true? - No.
What the hell does that matter?
She's a federal employee.
You kill a federal employee,
the government picks up the case.
Federal charges.
You'll be transferred to Terre Haute.
I know Terre Haute.
Don't they have death row at Terre Haute?
They do.
I told you the charges, Nia.
Where'd you think you were going?
No, no.
Nice play.
Fine!
I'll tell you,
but you gotta say I helped.
Upton, you good?
Parked and ready.
All right, heads up, Tariq is coming out.
Nia, you here?
- Gun. - That you?
Move in now.
Chicago PD! Put your hands up!
Put your hands up, Tariq.
Look around, man.
You got six guns trained on you.
It's over.
Put your hands up.
She was my baby.
- She's still your baby. - I just wanted my baby!
They took her from me, man!
Tariq, you listen to me.
You calm down, all right?
You raise that gun even a little, you will be shot,
and not once.
Every cop here is gonna shoot,
and that is six bullets.
After everything you did,
I don't think that's how you want this thing to end:
bleeding out in the dirt,
never seeing your baby girl again.
Tariq, you listen to me.
You toss that gun, you still have a chance
'cause you still got a kid,
that kid's still got a father,
and you are still alive.
Toss that gun.
You toss that gun, Tariq!
On your knees!
Drop the phone!
I'm never gonna see her again, am I?
I sure as hell hope not.
Ooh, didn't expect that.
DCFS tracked down Makayla's family.
- Cousin's on the way. - Oh, that's great.
You know, it's your instincts that got the case
and protected her.
It's good work.
You could let it count for something.
What?
I don't know. I was just thinking.
About what?
When we got pregnant.
I'm a cop.
I love being a cop. I'm good at it.
I didn't think I'd have the instincts to be a mom too.
And then what happened happened.
No, you would've been good at both.
You're always giving me the benefit of the doubt.
No, I'm not. I know you.
You would've had instincts for all of it.
That's all.
That's just how it is.
Yeah.
Maybe it makes you better at both.
Are we hanging tonight or what?
I don't know. Can you stand the monotony?
Yeah, you know what? About that, I spoke to Barkey.
Apparently, that boat was not his to sell.
He stole the boat?
No, he won it in a not-so-legitimate parlay.
He did steal that boat.
He stole it.
I will meet you at the bar.
- I'm gonna wait with Makayla. - All right.
See, mine don't do it.
Got all your stuff, okay? So don't worry about that.
- Look who's here. - Kathy!
- Hi, I'm Kathy Ward. - Hi.
- Kim Burgess. - Good to meet you.
You too. This is her stuff.
Okay.
And here's my card.
You call if you need anything or if you wanna keep in touch.
- Thank you. - Yeah.
All right, let's do this.
Just rip the Band-Aid off.
What did the FBI offer you?
Hmm, okay.
Joint level task force with the HIG.
All interrogations. All high-level targets.
Sure. Sure, sure, sure.
Yeah, that sounds awesome.
- Is it good pay? - It's great pay.
Honestly, it made me a little embarrassed
about what we get paid.
Well, you'd probably be really good at it.
Yeah, maybe. I don't know.
You liked it out there, right?
I don't know if I liked it.
I think it was just what I needed at the time.
Okay, but you don't need it now?
No, why? You think I need it?
Are you trying to tell me I should take it?
No, uh...
I'm saying that it's a good job for a good cop.
You could tell me you don't want me to take it.
It was an option.
I want you to do whatever you wanna do.
I'm just practicing self-preservation here.
The agent on the phone said the only reason
a good cop doesn't take a job like this
is 'cause they're scared,
implying that I'm afraid of change
and I wanted to stay here where it's safe.
So he's a dick.
I don't think that's why I don't wanna take it.
I don't wanna take it because of you.
I'm better...
with you as my partner.
You know, you, 21, with Voight.
I know I'm better here.
So I'm not gonna take it.
You sure?
Yeah.
All set.
He wasn't really wrong, though, was he?
You gain something. You give something up.
Maybe, but...not always.
It's been a long time
since I saw you as just my partner.