I don't wanna go to work today.
Just tell the bad guys to take a week off.
I like this plan.
Don't get it.
I have to.
- Dude, I have to. - No. Don't do it.
- Don't do it! - I have to.
What's up?
Looks like my dad collapsed.
He had a heart attack. He's at Med right now.
What?
Is this out of the blue? Is he not feeling well?
Uh, no--I don't really talk to him anymore, but...
my mom said he's doing better.
I don't know, not drinking, exercising,
you know, "Changed." Whatever.
Let's go. I'll take you to Med.
Okay.
I'll let you out when we get there,
and I'll look for parking.
That's okay. You don't have to come in.
You sure?
Yeah. Thank you.
Units on the city-wide.
We got a call of a man down in an alley,
possible homicide. 4220 West Maypole.
That's five blocks away. Come on, let's roll.
Roll? What about your dad?
I'll go later.
5021 Henry, plainclothes officers responding.
Halstead and Upton, intelligence.
- What do we have, officer? - Homeless guy found him.
Notified a store owner who called 911.
Two gunshot wounds to the back.
What is this?
He's ice cold.
Oh, man, he's a cop.
Patrol Officer Mike Blaine. He's got 22 years on the job--
- You gotta be kidding me. - What?
Man, I knew him.
We worked together four years in Vice.
- Like, I knew him well. - I'm so sorry, Sarge.
- All right, what else? - Two shots in the back.
We found two .45 caliber casings
about ten feet from the body.
- Time of death? - Around 11:00 P.M. last night.
- Robbery? - Don't think so.
Watch, wallet, cash-- all found on him.
There's no sign of a struggle, either.
- Sounds like an ambush. - Yeah.
We know what he was doing over here?
No, sir.
Doesn't sound like he was on the clock.
You telling me he wasn't on OT?
His sergeant said he turned in his squad keys at 10:00 P.M.
Checked his car.
Saber radio, duty rig, vest--all packed.
Everything indicates he was done with his tour.
Right, I don't have to tell you there's gonna be a lot of eyes on this,
so we do it by the numbers, understand?
PODs, cameras, witnesses. Let's go.
I'll see you on the other side, Mike.
- Any word on your dad? - Uh, yeah.
Doctors confirmed it was a heart attack.
But he's in stable condition, so...
If you gotta take off, I totally get it.
Nah, they're doing tests.
Can't do anything for him, anyway.
Okay--I mean, are you sure?
It might be nice to just go see him.
A cop just got shot. Let's focus on that, 'kay?
- All right. - Sergeant!
- Look, he's my partner. - Hey, it's okay!
Let him through.
Had to see it with my own eyes.
- Rodriguez. - Hank Voight.
You're Sergeant Voight?
Mike spoke highly of you. I'm glad you're on this.
Listen, you guys got anything on the books over here?
No, sir. Been working a burglary detail.
Gold Coast, all year.
I assume everything's good with Dana, right?
Yeah, happily married. 18 years.
Listen, man, this is a rough neighborhood.
You got any idea why Mike would be over here?
No.
Shift ended, said he was going straight home to Dana.
Said she made lasagna.
Anything unusual the past few weeks?
Not really.
The only thing I can think of is, he went off-book
two days ago for a couple of hours.
Said he had a doctor's appointment.
Didn't ring true.
Tom?
There's Dana.
- Look, I have to go... - No, no.
Let me talk to her.
Here, just remember it's an active crime scene.
- Thanks, Sarge. - Dana...
Hank...
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I'm so sorry.
Sarge.
So techs found faint tire impressions near Blaine's body.
It all points to a small model vehicle.
Corroborates what a witness saw,
a compact vehicle speeding away with...
lightning bolts for taillights.
That adds up to a 2017-to-19 Prius model.
Problem is, no Priuses are registered
- to anyone in the area. - Okay, keep chasing it.
Yes...
What?
We also got some suspicious texts
from Blaine's phone to a burner phone a couple days ago.
Blaine says, "You got it?"
Five minutes later, he gets a text back--
"Wilson Park, 2:00 p.M."
So we pulled security footage from the park,
and, uh, we got Blaine here walking at 2:05 p.M., same day.
Then this dude with the tats walks up.
There's a hand-to-hand exchange.
So we ran him through facial rec.
It's Marco Perez.
He is a shot caller for the Latin Jokers.
This Perez, he's got a long sheet,
including an armed robbery with a .45
that was never recovered.
Kevin's waiting for his LKA.
He did three years in Stateville
on a distribution charge.
The arresting officer on that pinch was Mike Blaine.
So we got Blaine, on-duty, receiving a suspicious envelope
from a known banger that he arrested.
Two days later, he's shot with a .45 while he's off-duty.
None of this looks good.
Doesn't matter.
We follow the leads wherever they take us.
According to narcotics,
they're taking us to 2321 Holden Street.
He's got a stash house in Little Village.
Okay, good. Let's roll.
All right, listen.
Until we know more, I wanna keep this video
of Blain and Perez off-book.
You got it, Sarge.
Jay, you set?
In position, ready when you are.
Copy that. We're moving in.
Clear. I'll take the right.
We got a runner!
- Don't do it, Marco! - Hands up!
You know the drill! Show me, now!
- Hands up! - Hands up.
Get your ass down.
Stand up. Walk back towards me.
Back just real slow.
Well, business must be good.
Recovered 20 grand at your stash.
I don't know what you're talking about, bro.
We found your gun, too. Sig Sauer .45.
Slugs are a match to a gun used in a cop murder.
That's a lie.
Two days ago. That's you.
Talking to the dead cop.
I didn't kill Mike!
I was in Gary last night. I had my gun with me, too.
- But you knew Mike Blaine? - Yeah.
He busted me four years ago.
After I got out, we crossed paths from time to time.
Said hello, that sort of thing. Became friends, kind of.
When's the last time you saw him?
That day.
Tell me what's in that envelope.
Money.
Three grand.
He needed a loan, so I took care of him.
Gave him a good deal, too.
Mike tell you what he needed the money for?
No, just said he needed it quick
to help out a friend.
Anything else?
He was driving away...
Some white boy pulled up, though.
Started taking pictures with his phone.
- Okay. - Mike lost it.
Started screaming at him.
This white boy just flipped him off and drove away.
You think he knew this kid?
I don't know, man, it looked that way.
You get a good look at him?
White, brown hair, 20s.
Drove one of those electric cars,
like a Prius or something. That's all I know.
That's all I know.
Hey, Sarge. Perez's alibi checks out.
There's video of him at a gas station in Gary.
Same time Blaine was shot.
So we eliminated Perez, but take a look at this.
We dug into his story about the angry kid in the Prius.
Led us to this guy, Zach Phillips.
I found traffic cams
four blocks away from the crime scene.
Silver Prius registered to that same Zach Phillips.
11:19 P.M.
That's the same night Blaine was shot.
On top of that, he filed an excessive force complaint
against Blaine a few weeks back.
We showed Perez a six-pack.
He confirmed Zach is the guy taking photos.
Okay, so what do we know about Zach?
He's 25 years old. He owns a graphic design firm.
No priors.
His only blemish is a disorderly conduct pinch
at a recent protest,
where Blaine was the arresting officer.
Two days after that bust,
Zach started posting on an anti-police website.
Goes by the name FTPNow.
We got him saying, "Copaganda must end.
"If CPD won't punish Officer Blaine,
"Perhaps someone else will.
Remember, Mike, karma's a bitch."
And this is three days ago?
All right, split up.
Check all possibilities. Track him down now.
- He's in apartment 3G. - Yeah, I just don't know if...
- Yeah, okay. - Zach Phillips?
Yeah? What's going on?
Chicago PD. We need to talk to you.
Ma'am, can you give us a few minutes, please?
It's okay, babe. I'll call you later.
What's going on? What is this?
It's about the murder of a Chicago police officer.
We need you to come down to the district,
help us clear up a few things.
Am I under arrest?
We wanna talk to you about Mike Blaine--
I said, am I under arrest?
She just told you, we need to--
I don't have to go anywhere.
I know my rights.
Okay, now you're under arrest.
Put your hands out to the side.
Since you know so much, you probably know that
your latest post about Mike Blaine is in violation
of Section 20-12-9 of the Illinois Criminal Code--
That's aggravated assault.
You have the right to remain silent.
Anything you say or do can and will be used
against you in a court of law.
You have the right to an attorney.
Where were you last night around 11:00 p.M.?
On my way to my girlfriend's apartment.
Does she live on 109th Street?
No.
Were you driving on 109th Street at that time?
Possibly.
Let me refresh your memory, Zach.
That's you, caught on a traffic cam at 11:19 p.M.
on 109th Street.
That's four blocks from where Officer Blaine was shot.
Guessing I wasn't the only one on the road at that time.
No, you weren't.
But you were the only person on the road at that time
who filed an official complaint against Officer Blaine,
who made online threats against Officer Blaine.
He practically broke my kneecap with his nightstick.
Then the bastard handcuffed me
and put me into the back of a police car
for three hours.
I told him I had asthma. He didn't care.
Left me there to die.
You threw a rock at him, Zach.
I didn't throw a damn thing.
I swear to God.
He thought I did, so he stopped me
and started bullying me.
So that's why you shot him, for revenge?
No, I didn't shoot anyone.
Okay.
So what were you doing on 109th Street?
All right, Zach's apartment was pretty clean.
I gotta show you something.
He had pictures that he took of Blaine
the night before the murder.
He was definitely following him and stalking him...
That doesn't mean he killed Mike.
I mean, this kid seems more like a choir boy
than a cop killer.
Either way, he dug up some dirt.
Digital footprint puts Blaine at South Bishop Street at 9:00 p.M.
Now I know you know it's a high crime area--
drugs, hookers...
Blaine waits by his car.
An unknown woman approaches.
They share a quick hello.
He then slips her an envelope--
I'm guessing it's the envelope
he got from Perez with the three grand in it.
She proceeds to get into his car.
They stay there for ten minutes...before she exits.
Don't know what happened inside,
but obviously, that doesn't look great.
Were you able to ID the woman?
No, it's just...it's not enough for facial rec.
Blaine got any CIs that match her description?
No.
- So I'm guessing - Well, you don't get to guess, not on this one.
Show the photos to his partner. Maybe he can help.
All right.
You got it, boss.
Sarge.
Hank, you got a visitor.
- Dana. - Hank.
- You okay? - No.
I'm trying to keep it together, but...
I'm getting the runaround from Mike's district.
I'm hearing that because Mike might've been off-book,
that the city won't pay a full pension
- for a line-of duty death. - Look, it's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna look into it. I'll see what's going on.
My kids need to know that their dad died a hero.
I know it doesn't sound like much, but--
Hey, I understand.
And we need the benefits, Hank.
We're low on cash. Real low.
I'm gonna take care of it.
Thank you.
Come on.
Hey, take her home.
Sure.
Mike was a good man, and a good cop.
I know he was.
You should know, IAD is looking into Blaine's murder.
Rather than send him off with a salute and a pension,
they wanna catch him dirty.
Thanks, Trudy.
Did you open an IAD investigation into Mike Blaine?
I did.
This how we treat dead cops now?
Open an IAD investigation?
What, we gotta make sure they're squeaky clean
before we console the widow, pay their benefits?
I was just doing my job.
Come on, what's going on? What am I missing?
The press is all over this. I'm getting a lot of heat
from FOP to give a "slain hero" speech.
But before I do that, I need to know who he was.
And who he wasn't.
Then you should probably hold off
on giving that hero speech for now.
We still can't explain some of his movements.
So just...let me do a little more digging
before you put yourself out there.
So what's the word with your dad?
Yeah, he's okay.
He's got two clogged arteries,
so they need to do a bypass surgery.
- When? - Two days.
What, are you gonna go see him?
Yeah, maybe tomorrow.
Hailey--
Look, I know who your dad was, and I know what he did.
But if something happens... and you don't go see him,
then you're gonna carry this for the rest of your life.
So don't do it for him, just do it for you.
What do we know about the woman
- in the photo with Blaine? - Not a damn thing.
Rodriguez didn't recognize her, so I've gotta keep digging.
I got an email from forensics--
they said the mud on Zach's tires is a match
to the mud and rocks at the crime scene.
Okay, great, so Zach was there.
But we got no evidence that he actually did the murder.
I checked surveillance cams in the area,
came up with nothing.
I mean, do we really think this dude did this?
Two in the back?
That's pretty hardcore for a graphic designer.
We know he was there,
and he's still our only suspect.
All right, so let's go back,
try talking to Zach one more time. Just...
play nice.
Let's see if we can get this kid to open up.
All right, Zach.
The evidence is piling up.
The mud and rocks on your tires are an exact match
to the mud and rocks at the crime scene.
So we know you were there.
We also know that you've been following Blaine,
taking pictures.
You're right, I was.
I wanted to prove that he was a bad person, a bad cop.
Because I know you guys - the Chicago Police Department--
would never look into him,
investigate the misconduct report that I filed.
Well, it's not a perfect system.
You know, we get hundreds of complaints every month.
It takes time to sort this stuff out.
But I do understand how that level of frustration
could lead to a confrontation.
What are you saying?
I'm saying maybe you confronted Blaine.
You wanted to get some things off your chest.
Maybe he didn't like what you had to say so he got aggressive.
Maybe he reached for his gun.
You just did what you had to do because you were afraid
he might cause you serious bodily harm.
That would be self-defense.
You wouldn't be responsible for his death.
Nice try.
- But that's not what happened. - Zach...
Right now, you're our only suspect.
This would be your opportunity to prove us wrong.
I did not kill Officer Blaine.
I'll take a polygraph.
Swear on a Bible, my mother's grave.
You name it, I'll do it.
Was Blaine with this woman the night of the murder?
I'm not doing this. Sorry.
If you're not the guy that killed him,
why not help us find the person that did?
Because I'm not a hypocrite.
What the hell are you talking about?
I don't like the police. Never have.
And that was before Officer Blaine attacked me,
wrongfully imprisoned me,
and none of you did anything about it.
He thought that you threw a rock at him.
- But I didn't! - Okay, so he made a mistake.
Just like every other human being on this planet.
So can we rise above this petty anger?
- Maybe see the bigger picture? - Why would I want to do that?
'cause that's what good people do.
They realize that people are flawed.
They do stupid things, sometimes.
What he did to me was not just stupid.
It was an abuse of power
and a violation of my civil rights.
This guy is unbelievable.
What?
Your speech.
"Good people know that people are flawed,
that they do stupid things sometimes"?
Hailey, I wasn't talking about you.
I was talking about Zach.
I know who your father is and that he was abusive.
You don't know the half of it.
No, you're right, I don't. I'm sorry.
You know I'm on your side.
- I'm just trying to help. - I don't want your help.
Not with this.
How'd it go with Zach?
He's not talking.
All right, take him home.
All right, Zach.
You're officially released from police custody.
Don't leave town.
We're probably gonna have some follow-up questions.
I told you, I'm not cooperating.
Yeah, you made that very clear.
Hey, there he is.
Zach, Zach--were you questioned about the murder
of Officer Mike Blaine?
Have you been charged with a crime?
Oh, that's Platt.
A witness just called in, saw a car pull into an alley
two blocks from the crime scene.
Driver ran in, and then, 30 seconds later, ran out.
Witness'll meet us there.
Two blocks? If we're lucky, that's our offender dumping a gun.
Yeah, makes sense to me. Let's go.
- Anything? - No gun.
But it's disgusting.
It's almost been an hour.
Is this witness ever gonna show up?
I don't know. Maybe he got nervous.
Or maybe someone told him there's a new law
that prohibits good people from cooperating with the police.
Yeah, God forbid.
Used to be, a cop got shot,
people'd come outta the woodwork to help.
Gun!
Ballistics confirmed the gun is the same gun
used to murder Officer Blaine.
They weren't able to pull any prints,
but they did trace the weapon to a...Maria Guerra.
Female Hispanic, 25, no priors.
She got any connection to Zach Phillips?
No, none that I could find, anyway.
I also tracked down that no-show witness.
He's letting CPIC in now to look at the security footage.
- Yo, Sarge. - Yeah?
Maria's the woman in the photo with Blaine.
- You got an address on her? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A two-flight in Pilsen, moved out two months ago.
Looks like she's been off the radar ever since.
Let's track her down.
Cell phone GPS puts Maria on this block.
All right, well, we find her car, find where she's hiding.
Here.
Blue Dodge.
Plate matches.
Okay, I'm gonna hold down the front
just in case this ain't it.
Yo, Sarge, if you got ears,
we got eyes on Maria's car.
Copy that. Keep me posted.
Chicago PD! Open up!
What's going on? How can I help you?
We're looking for Maria Guerra.
- She's--she's not here. - You sure about that?
We're investigating the murder of a Chicago police officer.
You wanna get wrapped up in this?
Ruz!
Get back. Step back.
Maria?
Maria, come on. Easy.
Put that down. Chicago PD.
- Why are you here? - To talk.
But not if you got that knife in your hand.
- You gotta put that down. - No.
Nobody's gonna hurt you. Okay?
Put the knife down.
Maria, put it down. You wanna drop that.
So put the knife down.
All right?
There you go.
Thank you.
What? What are you doing?
Your gun was used to kill Officer Mike Blaine.
We just gotta take you to the station--
You think--no, I'd never hurt Mike!
- Why's that? - Because he saved my life.
I told you, I didn't kill Mike.
I get it, you liked him; he saved your life.
The problem is, Maria...
the murder weapon is registered in your name.
I know.
But that's because...
That's because of what?
If I tell you,
you need to protect me and my family.
Protect you from who?
My ex-boyfriend.
Who's your ex-boyfriend?
His name is Jose Torres.
He took my gun,
and used it to kill Mike.
Okay, why do you think Jose killed Mike?
Because Mike was trying to help me.
I broke up with Jose about a month ago,
but he was angry.
He kept showing up at my house, wanting to have sex.
When I say no, he gets violent.
So I finally called 911.
- And that's when you met Mike? - Yeah.
Mike came to my house, he talked to Jose...
He had a bat in his hands, but Mike talked him down.
- Mike arrest Jose? - No.
He put him in handcuffs, but...
I didn't want to press charges.
I pleaded with Mike not to arrest him.
I still don't understand why you think Jose did the murder.
A few days ago... Jose found me at my cousin's.
I told him to get out, but he went crazy,
started punching walls and breaking dishes.
I was terrified, so I pulled out my gun.
I told him to leave, but he took it out of my hands,
started hitting me. So I called Mike.
Is that the last time you saw him?
Yeah.
He showed up with some money, three grand,
told me to stay in a hotel for a few weeks.
He said he was gonna talk to Jose,
tell him to leave me alone.
Why didn't you come to the police?
I was scared.
Jose said that if I ever talked to the police about him,
that he was gonna kill my daughter.
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
That's not on you.
It's on Jose.
- Jose Torres. - Maria's story checks out?
It seems legit.
The 911 tape confirms her call from last month,
and a neighbor said he's heard lots of fights over the years.
All right, Torres got a sheet?
Yeah, he's got two DUIs
and an assault with a deadly weapon.
It was a bar fight that got out of hand.
Okay, what about the night of the murder?
So the best lead that we have right now is
a hit on Torres's credit card.
He was at a bar two blocks away from the murder.
He paid his tab at 10:45.
He must've met up with Blaine right after that.
I mean, we could put Maria in play.
Wire her up, get her talking to Torres--
No, that's too dangerous.
Can't put Maria and Torres in the same room.
I agree.
All right, we gotta find another way to nail this prick.
What about Zach Phillips?
He was there the night of the murder.
- Maybe he saw Torres. - Yeah, she's right.
Give it a shot. Let's go.
That's him pulling up.
Zach, we need to talk to you one more time.
I'm not talking to you.
Look, we know you didn't kill Mike Blaine.
We just want you to look at some photos, okay?
Did you see any of these men
the night you were following him?
I told you, I'm not getting involved.
Get down!
5021 Georgia, got shots fired at the police.
It's a black Audi traveling westbound on 19th street.
- Hailey, you good? - Yeah.
- Are you okay? - Yeah, yeah, he missed.
- You okay? - Thank you.
You saved my life. Thank you.
Can we get you something to drink?
- Coffee, water? - No, thanks.
I'd offer you food, but we don't have much.
Maybe the odd candy bar--
I'm not hungry, but thank you.
Okay.
Well, now that you've had some time to calm down--
I refuse to answer.
Okay.
Zach, we believe the offender saw you on the news,
talking to reporters, so he knows you were there,
that you saw him arguing with Blaine,
maybe even shooting him.
Okay, that makes you a witness. It also makes you a target.
He's not gonna stop coming after you.
That's my problem.
I'll move out of state
until all this nonsense blows over.
It's not nonsense, and it's not gonna blow over,
not without your help.
Zach, she just saved your life.
Without this woman, without this evil cop right here...
you'd be dead.
You get that, right?
I do, and I'm very appreciative.
- But that doesn't change-- - Yes, it does!
It does.
You need to quit hating.
And if not for yourself, then do it for Blaine's family,
- and help them get justice. - Justice?
W-we don't know what he was doing with this guy.
He could've been dealing drugs--
We do know what he was doing!
He was trying to save a young woman's life,
to stop this guy from continuing to abuse her.
That's what he was doing there.
That very well may be true, but--
No, it is true! That's a fact!
And what he did to me is a fact.
And if I choose to hate him for that, that's up to me,
not you.
Zach, let it go. Just let it go.
Accept the fact that he made a mistake.
No, that was not a mistake. That's who he was.
I could see it in his eyes.
He was a mean, violent man.
What he did was unforgivable.
Okay, that's it.
Sarge. Patrol found the stolen Audi.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
There's blood in it. It's a match for Torres.
He got caught in the crossfire?
It would make sense, I mean,
Jay said he got off five or six rounds.
Good. That puts him at the scene.
We know where this guy is?
He's on the run right now.
All right, get a BOLO out on him and his vehicle--
Already done. It's a gold Dodge pickup.
- 'Kay. - We'll follow up.
All right, this is the spot.
Yeah, patrol got it right. That's Torres's truck.
Gold Dodge Ram.
Sarge, you got your ears on?
Yeah, Hailey, go with your traffic.
Torres is here; he's parked in a lot off Whipple and 26th.
Right by the hot dog spot.
All right, keep eyes and an anchor down.
Everybody on the air, start heading that way.
That's him.
Sarge, Torres just stepped out.
Take him.
- I'll block the entrance. - Wait for my signal.
- I'm gonna cover the other side. - All right.
Listen, I gotta go.
Damn it.
Jay, I gotta move!
Chicago PD, get your hands up!
Hands up! Hey--
I'll shoot her.
Just take it easy, man. No one's gotta get hurt.
- Just let her go. - I'll shoot her.
- Let me go, please! - Take it easy, take it easy!
Put the gun down. Just let her go!
Get back in your car and out of my way...
- No! - Or I'll kill her!
Get back in your car!
- Drop the gun! - I said get back in your car!
- Torres-- - Or I'll shoot her!
Get back!
- Ma'am, are you okay? - Yeah, I'm okay.
Jose Torres, you're under arrest for the attempted murder
of Zach Phillips,
and for the murder
of Chicago Police Officer Mike Blaine.
I got some really good news for you.
Yeah, I'll take it.
We got a hit off a security cam near
- where Torres dumped the gun. - Okay.
That's Torres right there, holding the murder weapon
two blocks away from the crime scene
three minutes after the shooting.
That should seal it.
Best movie I've seen in a while.
All right, I'll talk to state's attorney's office,
get the paperwork going. Nice work.
Um, boss, about the file.
You remember we left some stuff out?
I want everything you got, good and bad.
- I'll take it from there. - All right.
You've been saying you wanted transparency.
Well, this is me being transparent.
That's--that's everything I got.
You loop in the state's attorney's office?
Writing up charges as we speak, first degree murder.
The only thing left to talk about
is the legacy of Mike Blaine.
Yeah, well, it doesn't look good.
I guess that depends on your point of view.
Excuse me?
Sam, everything he did,
he did to help protect a victim of domestic abuse.
He borrowed $3,000 from a convicted felon,
failed to report the domestic abuse incident,
and violated countless rules and regulations.
Okay?
What's your point?
- Blaine was far from perfect. - You're right.
But he was a good man.
He died trying to protect
a scared, vulnerable young mother.
And how he did it?
I mean, what rules he chose to ignore?
Who cares?
He was trying to do something good.
That's what matters.
You know, there was a time we actually forgave people
for their mistakes.
We understood that human beings are fallible.
So you look at the sum of the parts.
Does the good outweigh the bad?
I mean, Mike Blaine--
he gave his life doing something good...
brave...
Noble.
And that makes him a hero.
I don't have to hide anymore?
He's actually in jail?
Yeah, and he will be for a long time.
You just have to testify.
Tell the jury that he took your gun.
Yes, I will.
What he did to me... I can't forget, but...
knowing that he's out of my life forever--
that's good enough.
Gives me what I need to move on.
If you ever need anything...
Come on.
All good?
Yeah, they moved my dad's surgery to tonight.
I'm not gonna tell you what to do--
I'm going to the hospital right now.
I'll see you later?
Today, we apprehended the man we believe murdered
Officer Michael R. Blaine, a 22-year veteran
of the Chicago Police Department.
Officer Blaine died the same way he lived his life:
trying to do what was right,
trying to serve this city with dignity.
And like most of us,
Officer Blaine was not perfect.
But when you look at the sum of the parts...
at the man in full,
it's clear that the good offset the bad,
that he was a brave and decent police officer
who died on the job trying to save
a young woman, who was tragically stuck
in a violent and abusive relationship.
To me, that makes Mike Blaine a hero.
He represented the best
of what the Chicago Police Department is all about.
That being said, it's important to acknowledge
that we don't always get it right.
The Chicago Police Department is not flawless.
We've made some mistakes.
We've committed certain unforgivable acts.
But those misdeeds, no matter how egregious,
should not define us,
but rather motivate us to do better,
to be more complete and compassionate
human beings and police officers.
- Beer? - Yeah, sure.
So how'd it go?
Good.
Glad I talked to him.