.
- I told you to walk it back.
Tell Trudy's friend it was me
who got in the altercation,
not you...me.
- Sarge, listen.
I thought about it.
I thought about it long
and hard,
and I just--I did what
I thought was best
for you and for everyone else.
- It's not your job
to protect me, to protect us.
- Why is that?
Why are you the only one that
gets to live by a code?
I don't understand.
Boss, this is who I am.
I'm always gonna do whatever
I can to protect you all.
It's how I'm built,
like Al was,
like you were,
and I just don't understand
why you don't get that.
- Because you're no Al,
and you're not me.
You're a kid, got your whole
life in front of you.
- Well, I can handle whatever
comes my way--
- We had one chance to make
this right, you hear me?
One and you blew it.
- Sarge, listen to me--
- This is my unit, my unit.
I take the heat,
I take the bullets.
Is that clear?
- It's clear.
I'm sorry.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Is Antonio coming back,
Sergeant?
- It's up to Antonio.
- Bernie.
- Hey.
- Are you wearing
a bulletproof vest?
- I live around the corner.
I had to come and risk it.
- Oh.
- Some cops actually like me,
Hank.
- Yeah, name one.
- You.
- Don't confuse "respect" with
"like."
Kim, this is Bernie Hoffman,
plays for the other team.
- I'm aware of your work.
I thought most defense
attorneys were against Kelton.
- Hmm, I prefer mayors who
empower police,
not pull their pants down.
[phone buzzes]
Oh, I gotta run.
Nice to meet you, Kim.
- Nice to meet you.
- Let's grab dinner sometime,
Hank.
Ann would love to see you.
- Tell her I said "hey."
- Ladies and gentlemen,
if I could have your attention.
Thank you.
It is a true honor to introduce
this man
that I have worked with
for 27 years.
He has protected this city
where he was born and raised.
He is a true Chicagoan.
He is the man that needs to be
Chicago's mayor now.
The Superintendent of Police,
Brian Kelton.
[applause]
- Thank you, Kate.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Thank you all very much.
Before I begin, I want to
acknowledge the rank and file.
Let's--let's show 'em how
we feel.
[applause]
- [whistling]
- Thank you, I...
I may have just seen
Sergeant Hank Voight
crack a smile.
That's real police,
best of the best.
Now, my opponents talk about
unifying Chicago.
That's a noble word, unity.
But unity to my opponents means
working with gangs,
creating programs
to--to help gangs,
and that's just not what
Chicago needs right now,
nor is it anywhere on
my agenda.
Coddling criminals will
do nothing
to help the law abiding
citizens of Chicago.
To be clear, I don't wanna work
with gangs...
I'm gonna crush 'em.
[applause]
♪
- Thank you. Thank you.
- All right.
I'll wait to hear from you.
Thank you.
- Anything from COPA?
- Still investigating.
[clears throat]
Thanks, man.
Appreciate it.
Now what do you say we get out
of these monkey suits,
grab a drink and talk about,
I don't know, anything else?
- Think I'm gonna go home.
- Okay.
- Units in 18 and units on
the citywide,
reports of shots fired
coming from the inside
a residence at
224 East Scott.
- Oh, that's right around
the corner.
- Hey, Sarge, shots fired
a few blocks out.
[tense music]
♪
- You first guy on the scene?
- Yes, sir.
- All right, come in the back.
- All right.
- Come on, let's go.
♪
- Body.
- Where's cover?
- I got you.
- Boss, it's Bernie Hoffman.
- He's gone.
[thud]
♪
- [shrieks]
- Drop your weapon!
Drop your weapon now!
- Hold--stand down, stand down.
Ann, Ann, Ann.
Relax, it's me, Hank Voight.
- [gasps]
- Put your gun down.
It's okay, put the gun down,
it's Hank.
- Hank?
- It's okay.
I'm here to help.
Look, it's okay.
It's okay.
- [whimpering] Hank.
- Oh, my God.
[gasping]
They shot Bernie.
- It's okay.
- Oh, my God.
- It's okay, I got you.
- [sobbing]
- I'm so sorry.
[tense music]
♪
- What do you got?
- Well, wife's jewelry box
was rifled through,
a few drawers were tossed.
No sign of Hoffman's
cell phone,
I looked high and low.
- And the techs swabbed
Mrs. Hoffman for GSR,
she's clean.
They also did a quick test on
the thirty-aught-six,
it has not been fired.
- And the shell casings
are from a 9-millimeter.
- You know, there's no sign
of forced entry,
so either the offender
pulled off some kind of ruse,
or Mr. Hoffman knew
the attacker,
was having a meeting in here,
things went south.
- Well, I'd say real south,
his jaw is broken.
- Yeah.
- Well, we know what kind of
people Bernie rep.
Start with his clients.
- I got a neighbor that saw
a gray Honda
idling outside at the time
of the shooting.
Two African American males
inside, didn't get a good look,
but said they seemed
suspicious.
- Well, they could have
just been
looking for a parking spot.
- Well, what about PODs
or shot cams?
- Nothing so far.
- All right, keep digging.
- Yeah.
- Sir.
- We got word it was
Bernie Hoffman.
- Afraid so.
- What else you know?
- It's all preliminary now,
nothing solid.
Chance Hoffman knew
the offender, maybe a client.
Either of you talk to him
tonight?
- Yeah, I damn sure talked
to him.
I thanked him for coming
to the fundraiser.
- How'd he seem to you?
- Good.
We talked Blackhawks and...
And then that was it.
It's the last time I saw him.
It's unbelievable.
We had a roomful of officers
one block from here,
including me.
And some animal had the
audacity to...
I want no stone left unturned,
Sergeant.
Do you get me?
- I get you.
- Good, keep me in the loop.
- Sir.
Ma'am.
♪
- So, Bernie Hoffman had
multiple cases in pretrial,
including seven homicides.
All seven of those defendants
are in jail.
- Yeah, he's also got
23 violent offenders
awaiting their day in court,
and they're all out on bail.
- All right, did you talk
to his firm?
- Yeah, one client stood out,
Andre Griffin.
He's a major player in
the Southside Hustlers.
He calls for half of Englewood.
Hoffman repped Griffin
on three major drug offenses,
two agg assaults...Griffin
walked each time.
- Griffin visited Hoffman's
work office.
Apparently behind closed doors
things got pretty hot.
Furniture was thrown,
it was a big fight.
Hoffman told the partners that
Griffin was just upset about
a bill, and he cooled off.
- All right, you talk
to Griffin?
- Yeah, he's on his way in
right now.
- So, Englewood makes sense.
Uh, we haven't gotten into
Hoffman's phone,
but techs got into the cloud.
And he got a text message
an hour before he was killed.
It says, "It's a deal.
On my way."
And the text originated from
a burner in Englewood.
- Maybe Griffin's was the deal
that went south.
- Where were you last night?
- I was home last night.
- Mm-hmm.
Were you alone?
- Wait, what's this about?
- Your lawyer.
- Damn.
- Mm-hmm.
- I don't know nothing
about that.
Besides, why would I hurt him?
I liked the guy.
He saved my ass plenty of
times.
- Yeah.
When's the last time you talked
to Bernie?
- Yo, this is crazy.
One thing Bernie taught me,
you get brought in,
you call a lawyer.
- Well, we're just having
a conversation, Andre.
- Law-yer.
[dramatic music]
♪
- I got something from
property crimes.
- Mrs. Hoffman's stolen jewelry
just popped up at a pawn shop,
black male dropped it off.
The caught him on
security camera.
- Where's the pawn shop?
- Englewood.
- Check it out.
Hey.
- You look familiar.
Welcome back, man.
- Thanks.
- Glad you're back.
Let's go.
- Okay.
- Hey.
- Late on my first day back.
It's not a great look, right?
- Don't worry about it.
- I had to drop my daughter
off.
She's seeing a therapist.
- Good for her.
It's a hell of a thing.
How you feeling?
- Ready.
- Good.
- Hey, um...
I had a lot of time in there,
and I did some thinking.
- Mm-hmm.
- There's no way I can let Adam
go through with this COPA
thing.
- Antonio, we're way past that.
- I know.
- Look, you say anything now,
we all pay the price.
Hang tight, let the process
play out, understood?
- [exhales deeply]
[door buzzes]
- Hey, man.
Adam Ruzek, Chicago PD.
- Basir, pawn shop guy.
- Is this the jewelry, Basir?
- Yup, take it before I change
my mind.
- Why, what's it worth?
- 50 thou, give or take.
The kid had no clue.
- How much did you pay?
- 500, am I gonna get that
back?
- Well, uh, not anytime soon,
sorry.
- Yeah, it's a match for
Ann Hoffman's.
- Fantastic.
All right, I hear you got
this genius
on security camera too, yeah?
- Yep, right over here.
[tense music]
♪
- Uh, does that look like
Griffin to you?
- No. Maybe his, like, nerdy
younger brother.
♪
Who the hell are you?
Let's see if anything pops
on facial rec.
♪
- Busy night, DeVante.
You got two priors,
and you're still at it.
Persistent.
What'd you do, clear a grand?
- I was just holding that
for someone.
- Well, you hold away,
'cause we don't care.
'Cause we got surveillance
of you in a pawn shop
selling this man's stolen
jewelry...
Ten hours after that.
- I-I found those jewels
in a dumpster.
- DeVante, stop lying.
You're staring down life
for murder.
Now you tell us what happened,
you got a shot at seeing
daylight again.
- You got the wrong black man.
- Okay, who's the right one?
- 'Cause we got witnesses that
say they saw you
and another guy outside
that man's house
right before that happened.
- I never went inside.
- Hmm.
- Hmm, so you were there?
- No, I didn't say that.
Y'all trying to trip me up.
- Okay, let's talk about
your cousin, Andre Griffin.
- What about him?
- Hoffman was Andre's lawyer.
- Is that the dead dude's name?
- Was Andre with you?
[ominous music]
Is he the other man
our witness saw?
DeVante, you gotta come clean.
- Sarge, I got something.
It's important.
♪
- So, this is from a CTA
bus cam last night.
The route goes right past
Hoffman's house.
This was taken at 9:42.
♪
That's Brian Kelton.
He said he last saw Bernie
at the fundraiser.
So, he lied right to our faces.
Why?
♪
.
- Under my administration
you're going to see
more police on the street,
more arrests of violent
gang members,
more homicides solved,
and your neighborhoods
are going to be safe again.
And I understand I have
a long road ahead
before I can gain your trust.
We can do better.
But under my leadership,
police reform is working.
And to keep Chicago pointed
in the right direction...
I need your help at
the ballot box.
- You wanna help us?
Stop murdering our children.
all: Yeah.
- Yeah.
- That's right.
[indistinct chatter]
- Sergeant, how are you?
- Good.
You got a minute?
- 100%, walk with me.
Got an update on the Hoffman
case?
- Well, not exactly.
We're having a little trouble
with our timeline, though.
You know, from the cell phone
we know Hoffman got home
around 8:35.
- From the fundraiser, yeah.
- Uh-huh.
As far as we know
he was alone there
till the offender showed up
around ten.
[dramatic music]
♪
- I was in there, Hank.
- Okay.
- I stopped by for
a few minutes.
- Uh-huh.
- I was gone by 9:30.
If I saw or knew anything
relevant,
I'd have mentioned it to you.
- That's a hell of an omission.
Look, I'm not looking to bury
anyone,
I'm just working the case.
♪
Well, we know that Hoffman
was shot with a 9-millimeter,
so...I'll need to see
your service weapon.
It'll be processed anonymously.
I don't wanna see a good
policeman's name
get raked through the mud.
- I'll make sure somebody
gets it to you.
Bernie...was working on
a personal matter for me.
- It's none of my business.
- Let's keep it that way.
- We're ready to go, sir.
- Good.
Sergeant.
- Superintendent.
Thanks for the update.
♪
- How'd it go with Kelton?
- Admits he was there,
let's see what his gun says.
- Sarge, I talked to
Cook County jail.
I got some potential DeVante
leverage.
Patrol pinched his aunt
last night
on some drug charges.
She basically violated
her parole.
- DeVante's close with her?
- She's been taking care of him
since he was a shorty,
seen a situation like this
before.
She'll feel like he owes
her one.
- Work it.
- Got it.
- How much you love
your auntie, DeVante?
- Hmm.
Love ain't the right word.
I'd be dead without her.
- Well, she's looking
at six years.
Six.
You cooperate with us,
she can be cooking dinner
tonight at the crib.
So, we do know that you were
at Bernie Hoffman's house
last night with another man.
Was that man your cousin,
Andre Griffin?
Hey, listen, I know.
Nobody wants to snitch on
family.
But you gotta step up.
Okay?
I think you know you do,
because who do you owe it to,
the woman who raised you
or the punk who put you
in that seat right there?
[tense music]
♪
Were you with Andre Griffin
last night?
♪
Okay, what did you see?
- I was outside in the car
the whole time,
but Griff told me what
went down.
He went there to pick up
something from that white guy.
- Okay, what was he picking up,
money, drugs?
- I don't know.
All I know is Griff caught
the guy
recording them with his phone.
And the dude said he couldn't
trust no one, got crazy.
Griff shot him and tried to
make it look like a burglary.
- That's good, DeVante.
Yeah, it's real good.
But we need more than
your word.
- [breathes shakily]
What do I gotta do?
♪
[breathes shakily]
Yo, something's wrong.
Griffin's never late.
- If DeVante gets
too squirrelly, Kevin,
you pull him right out of
there.
- Copy that.
- [sighs]
- What's wrong?
Haven't taken a long-eye
in years.
- I get it, but Voight wants
you to go slow.
It makes sense.
- Is that the second time
that blue sedan hit the block?
- I'm not sure.
Listen...
Anytime you wanna talk about,
you know,
what went down...I'm here
for you.
- Thanks, Kim.
- Yeah, yeah.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Yo, this ain't working, man.
[breathes heavy]
- Sarge, this kid's losing it,
man.
- It's your call, Kev.
- I'ma pull him.
♪
- Yo, Griff's a busy man.
I told you he wouldn't
have time.
- DeVante, just go home, okay?
If he contacts you,
you contact me immediately.
You understand that?
- Is my aunt still gonna be
okay?
- DeVante, just go home, okay?
[gunshots]
- [screams]
- [shouts]
- Kevin, you hit?
- [pants]
- I'm good, I'm good.
You got him?
- Go, I got the kid.
- Oh, God, it hurts, it hurts.
[groaning]
- Did you see who did it?
Who did it, man?
- No. No!
[tires screeching]
- Police! Stop!
[gunfire blasts]
- [screams]
[gunshots crack]
- [panting]
- [grunts]
- Kevin!
10-1, 10-1, officer down.
Repeat, officer down,
5650 South Loomis.
- [moans]
- It's okay, it's okay.
You stay with me, Kevin.
- [groaning]
- Stay with me.
You stay with me.
- [gasps]
- Come on.
Come on!
.
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey, thanks.
- Yeah.
- Any word?
- Nothing.
[indistinct chatter]
- I knew something wasn't right
about that car.
I should have called it out
to Voight.
I don't know how the hell
I missed it.
- Hey, I missed it too,
Antonio.
You gotta let it go.
- No, this is on me.
I had one job to do.
- Hey, hey.
You look at me, look at me.
All right, this is not on you.
I need you to keep it together,
okay?
Okay?
- Okay.
- Doctor, thank you.
Thanks a lot.
Okay, I got good news.
Kevin is gonna be fine.
It was a tricky surgery.
They took a bullet out of
his shoulder,
but it wasn't life threatening.
The best thing we can do
for Kevin is
get back out there and drag
this prick in.
So, I wanna know where
we're at.
- The, uh, PODs are a negative
for the blue sedan,
but a witness thinks they saw
an African American driving.
- Shell casings recovered
from the drive-by
are a match to the gun
that killed Hoffman,
9-millimeter.
- Well, that's enough to snatch
his ass up.
- Oh, Sarge, we've been
looking.
Griffin's in the wind.
- All right, so let's find him,
hunt him down.
Squeeze his crew till it hurts.
Whatever it takes.
[ominous music]
♪
- Headache, headache.
[grenade blasts]
Chicago PD, let me see
your hands.
Hands in the air now.
- Get up.
- On your feet!
- Get up against the wall.
- Turn around.
- Police! Freeze.
♪
Hey! Stop! Police!
- [grunts]
♪
- Antonio!
- [grunts]
Don't move, I'll light you up.
Get those hands where
I can see 'em.
Get out, get out.
- Slow down, man.
- Shut up.
- I'm doing what you say.
♪
Here you go.
Who am I looking at, Kim?
- Reggie Watt.
Reggie's on parole for distro.
- Is that why you ran, Reggie?
Huh?
You holding product?
You give me Andre Griffin,
I never saw this bag.
- Last I heard he's held up
in the stash house,
5858 South Racine.
- Okay.
- Put your hands behind
your back.
Hey, that was a hell of a jump.
You all right, Superman?
- Definitely gonna feel it
tomorrow.
- Listen, you got that baggie
of pills?
I'll do the paper.
- I can handle it.
- You sure that's a good idea?
- Yeah, I can handle it.
Wait, hold--hold on.
What, you don't trust me?
- Right now with what happened,
no.
Do I love you, Antonio?
Do I want you to beat this
thing for good?
Yeah, this is how I do it.
Thanks.
Let's go get this guy.
[suspenseful music]
- Chicago PD!
Clear.
- Crossing.
♪
Guys, you gotta get in here.
I found Griffin's bankroll.
That's not the headline,
though.
♪
What's a gangbanger like
Griffin doing with
"Kelton for Mayor" signs?
♪
.
- All right, thanks.
Hey, guys, techs ran
the envelope
we found at Griffin's
stash house.
Hey, Sarge.
It had 40 grand cash inside,
and there was prints on
the outside of the envelope
and on the cash.
We got a hit.
- [scoffs]
Kelton.
- I was hoping he was better
than this.
- Yeah, well, he's not.
That son of a bitch been
lying to our faces
from the second Bernie Hoffman
got shot.
- So, the 40 G's is a payout
from Kelton to Griffin
for votes.
- Yeah, it makes sense.
I find a legal pad at
Griffin's place
with names and neighborhoods,
places to disrupt,
pastors to bribe.
All in the service of helping
Kelton win.
- Chicago politics never
disappoints.
- Okay, what happened
that night?
- All right, so, the hotel is
about a block away from
Hoffman's house.
Kelton leaves the hotel
around 9:30,
gets to Hoffman's...9:35,
he delivers the cash.
The sometime after 10:00,
Griffin gets there,
collects the money.
- Hoffman's the bagman.
- Yeah.
And Hoffman records
the meeting,
'cause he wants to protect
himself.
He doesn't trust Kelton.
Griffin realizes the meeting's
being recorded,
things go south,
goodbye Bernie.
- All right, we know the who
and the why.
Now we gotta prove it.
- Sarge, the way things
are headed...
- We follow the evidence
wherever it leads.
This turns back on Kelton,
he ordered it,
even if he just covered it up,
so be it.
We arrest his ass.
Anyone got a problem with that?
[dramatic music]
♪
All right, good.
Let's get back out there.
- [exhales deeply]
Kevin.
Ho--you're out of bed
already.
- Yeah, well, come on in .
- Wow, I was hoping for
a little more drama.
A hand hold or something.
- Oh, I'm sorry, Trudy.
You know, you can't keep
a good brother down.
- Uh-huh.
[chuckles]
I was--I was really worried.
So, don't do that again.
Okay?
- I'm not planning on it.
- What you got there?
- Trying to remember the tags.
- Mm-hmm.
- I had it,
I lost it.
Kept repeating it over
and over.
Crazy, 'cause...
It might be my last breath
on God's green earth,
and all I can do is try to
remember a license plate.
This job, boy...
- Did you see the driver?
- No.
But I saw the plates,
it's, uh, Indiana customs.
- Uh-huh.
- D-G...I don't know,
something.
L-16 maybe?
- But hey, it's a start.
- How's DeVante?
- Kevin, he died on the table.
- We any closer to Griffin?
- No, but, you know, maybe
your partial will help
get us there.
[solemn music]
♪
- [muttering]
[clicks tongue]
D-G-L-1-6.
We're in business.
- What's up?
- Atwater was one letter off.
I got a blue Taurus sedan
reported stolen,
Gary, Indiana, two weeks ago.
- You got a VIN?
- Yeah, give me one sec.
- I'll call the techs.
- Superintendent,
how can I help you?
- I'm just checking in
with the Sergeant.
Don't let me get in your way.
- Superintendent.
- Sergeant, I apologize I
didn't
make it over to the hospital,
but I understand
Officer Atwater
is feeling better.
- Yes, he is.
- Progress on the shooter?
- Chasing leads.
Can you excuse me a minute?
- Yeah, 100%.
- This is Voight.
[dramatic music]
♪
What's up?
- Techs got into the navigation
system.
The shooter's car is parked in
a small apartment complex,
address 232 South Watson.
- Anyone we know live there?
- Tenants name is
Deisha Wallace, two priors,
a mom to a one-year-old girl.
Father's Andre Griffin.
- All right, hopefully
Griffin's with her.
Get over there with Adam,
confirm the car, move in.
- Yeah.
♪
- What can I do for you, Brian?
- Just checking up on
the Bernie Hoffman case.
I, uh...
I wanna make sure you have
all the resources you need
to nail the prick
who did this.
- Appreciate the offer,
we're good.
- That mean you have a lead?
- Means we're working the case.
- I asked you
a direct question,
and I damn sure expect
a direct response.
- Direct?
I'm sorry, it's just
a funny word choice.
- Why's that?
- Well, 'cause nothing about
this case
or your involvement in it
has been direct.
♪
- Do you have a lead suspect,
Sergeant?
- Like I told you, sir,
we're working the case.
- You're playing a dangerous
game here.
- So are you.
♪
- Why do I get the feeling
I'm investigating
the end of my career?
- Yeah, well, we stick to
the truth,
we should be all right.
- Like the truth matters
these days.
Why does Kelton need Griffin's
vote anyway?
He's just some drug-slinging
punk.
- But he's a punk that can
help deliver
half the South Side vote.
- Yeah, I know, but, still.
- Politicians and gangs
have been in bed together
in this city since Al Capone.
It's Chicago.
- There it is.
- Yeah.
- New tags, huh?
- Bullet holes.
- All right, we're 100%
on the car.
We're gonna sit right back
here.
Jay, do your thing.
- Yeah, copy that.
[door closes]
[knocks on door]
[door clicks]
- Hi there, ma'am.
I'm Jay, building maintenance.
- You don't look familiar.
- I've worked for the building
for, like, two years.
Come on.
- What you want?
- Uh, we got reports
of a gas leak,
uh, from this floor.
So, we're just going around,
we're checking the units.
It's only gonna take, like,
five minutes.
And it's freezing outside,
so we don't wanna evacuate
you guys.
You know, we're just--we're
looking out for you.
- Which other units?
- Uh, it was 212, Ms. Diaz.
- All right.
Hurry up.
- It's a cute kid.
- Come on, baby, it's okay.
Aw. Baby hungry.
- [cooing]
[indistinct chatter]
♪
- What the hell are you doing?
- Sunrise.
- You son of a bitch.
You ain't no maintenance man.
- Drop it. Your child is here,
I don't wanna hurt you.
- Drop it.
- Jay, you good?
- I'll be better when she puts
this knife down.
- We're not gonna ask you
again.
One...two...
[baby crying]
♪
- Look, I swear I ain't seen
Griff in days.
I don't know where he is.
- Stop lying, Deisha
it's not helping.
We got the car you stole
at the scene of this homicide.
We recovered a bullet
from the officer who pursued.
You're facing murder.
- I didn't kill no one.
I don't know anything about
this.
- Deisha, we checked your car
for gunshot residue,
it's all over the interior.
- Y'all insane.
Is this what you do to folks?
You say stuff till people
start believing it?
- You understand that if
you don't cooperate,
you are never gonna see your
kid again?
You get that, right?
- Look at me, Deisha.
Andre is going down.
That's a fact.
You wanna join him,
that's up to you.
- [exhales deeply]
- Now who was driving
your car yesterday?
Come on.
- Andre.
He dropped me off at work.
- But where'd Andre say
he was going?
- He didn't say.
- Come on, Deisha, we need more
than that, let's go.
- What am I supposed to say?
We had coffee,
I walked him outside,
I kissed him goodbye,
he got in the car.
Last thing I remember
was some big, fancy black SUV
pulled up next to him,
and he started talking to
some lady who got out of
the backseat.
- All right, what this lady
look like?
- White lady, blonde hair.
- How old?
- Looked like my mom's age.
She had glasses,
looked like some kind of
college professor or something.
- Is that her?
- Yeah.
That's the one.
[suspenseful music]
♪
.
- Sarge, we got the Deputy
Superintendent of Police
tipping off our target.
I don't know how to proceed.
- Bury it.
- What?
- Keep it out of your paper.
It's too hot.
Listen, I'm gonna take
the lead on this, only me.
I'll deal with Brennan.
- Sarge.
The Glock we recovered
at Deisha's,
it's a match for all of
our vics,
Hoffman, DeVante, Kev.
- I've also got a CI who puts
Griffin hiding
at a flophouse on Monroe.
We got this prick.
- All right, start typing
a warrant.
I'll get a judge.
We move in hot, fully loaded.
I don't care if he comes out
in a bag.
[dramatic music]
♪
- You ready?
- Yeah.
♪
- Here we go.
Got eyes on Griffin.
- All right, standby,
he's pulling up.
♪
- He's on the phone.
- Wait till he gets out,
Antonio.
♪
- Take him.
[tires screeching]
[exciting music]
- Chicago PD.
♪
- Put your hands against
the car.
Put your hands on the car now.
You got me?
- Yeah.
♪
- Why are you smiling, Andre?
- You think you've won.
It's amusing.
- They can't protect you
anymore.
- You don't know nothing, fool.
- Let me ask you something.
That funny too?
Where were you when they shot
your cousin?
Answer that.
- I'm done talking.
My lawyer's on the way.
- I hope he's a good one.
[door closes]
- Hank.
- What can I do for you, Kate?
- [sighs] I need you to release
Andre Griffin.
- Excuse me?
- I talked to State's
attorney's office.
The evidence is weak.
There's no fingerprints on
the gun,
there were no witnesses.
The defense is gonna tear
this case to pieces.
- Case is strong, so...
If there's nothing else...
- We have an agreement, Hank.
We made it after I helped
Olinsky.
- Don't bring Al into this.
- I told you...
I told you there would be
a time when I ask you to
solve cases in a hurry
or not...in a hurry.
This is one of those.
- I know it was you who
tipped off Griffin.
- Excuse me?
- His girlfriend saw you
talking to him
a couple hours before
he killed his cousin.
And tried to kill my man,
Atwater.
- I am three generations
police,
don't question my loyalty.
- You're not loyal to the job.
You're loyal to Kelton.
- I am. He's a good man,
and he's a good cop.
He is responsible for
my career,
I am not going to let him down.
- How long has he been in bed
with the gangs?
With Griffin?
- He had absolutely no idea
that Griffin was involved.
- Until Bernie got shot.
- Nobody wants this, Hank.
Nobody.
- When Atwater was in
surgery...
I mean, you stood right next
to me, looked me in the eye.
You told me you'd do whatever
you can to help.
The whole time you knew it was
Griffin who did the shooting?
- All I did was tell him
that he was up for the murder,
that the police were
looking at him, that's it.
I didn't know that he was gonna
shoot Atwater.
- You crossed a line.
- You wanna lecture me about
crossing a line, Hank?
This is our line of business.
Sometimes we do things
we're not proud of.
You know that better than
anyone.
[sighs]
- What does that mean?
- You look the other way.
You release Andre Griffin.
- Get the hell out of
my office.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Thanks for coming.
- Hey, I heard about Griffin.
I thought you might be here.
- Get out of my way.
- Calm down, let it go.
You gotta let it go, all right?
- It might as well have been
them that shot Kevin.
- Kevin's gonna be all right.
- That's not the point.
- I know, you think I like
this?
Calling them out in public
makes you look bad.
These two are more dangerous
than ten Griffins.
So, we gotta be smart,
and we gotta be patient.
We're playing
the long game here.
This is Chicago.
[tense music]
♪