So imagine this neighborhood
is restored to glory, dawg.
Imagine this block right here.
Masks are just a bad memory. Imagine the crowds,
the dope restaurants, the powerful bars--
I'm imagining the rats too.
Imagine not interrupting me.
And imagine the cash flow in your pocket.
Ah, Kev, what? Because I'm the bartender?
No, 'cause you own the building, Ruz, damn.
I got an "In," okay?
A couple smart as hell business guys, they owe me a favor.
They said as soon as the zone clears,
- we can turn this thing around. - I don't know, buddy.
I think we're gonna be dead and buried
by the time this neighborhood comes up.
Come on, bro. Think about the West Loop.
I mean, we'd be rolling in cash right now
if we would've thought about the West Loop.
I just know what this place used to be, dawg,
and I feel like we could bring it back.
I feel like I'm wondering about the beer
that you promised me. What's happening here?
I feel a little hoodwinked. I want my beer, man.
Come on, bro. I got you.
Units on the Citywide.
We're getting multiple calls of shots fired.
34th and Wilson. Caller states
the shots are coming from inside a hardware store.
5021 David. Squad, repeat that address.
34th and Wilson. Southeast corner.
5021 David. Squad, we're five blocks away.
- What? You know the place? - No, the owner.
Copy that. We'll show you en route.
Ma'am, can you move on down the way, please?
You ready?
Mr. Roy!
Chicago PD. Anybody in here?
Mr. Roy...
Squad, roll an ambo. We got one down.
GSW to the chest. Male. 60s.
It's okay. It's okay. I got you.
I can't leave him. Go. Go.
Don't go anywhere, Mr. Roy. I got you.
I got you. Just hold on, OG.
All right? Or Mama Claire will kill us both.
Come on, Mr. Roy.
Come on. Look at me. Look at me.
Look at me.
- Ruz, you good? - Yeah.
5021 Ida, shots fired at the police.
Offender's fleeing out the back door.
- Black jacket, blue jeans. - Copy that.
Backup en route.
Stop! Police!
Police! Freeze!
You knew him?
You know, Englewood was my first beat.
Me and Mr. Roy hit it off from the jump.
He was real good people, Sarge.
He cared about his family, the community.
Okay.
All right, what are we thinking?
- Armed robbery? - The register was cleared out,
but his wallet was still on him.
The M.E. said there was fresh contusions
and abrasion on Roy's face.
He was beaten and shot at close range.
Oh, yeah. This was personal.
All right, what do we know about the offender?
I didn't get a good look at all.
5'10". 170.
Masked up. Ruzek said he was fast as hell.
Surveillance?
No security cameras inside, Sarge.
I told him to put those things in years ago.
He didn't like the message they sent.
Well, let's get him the justice he deserves.
Okay, check PODs, talk to witnesses.
- Hit the streets hard. - No! No! No!
- No! No! - All right, let's go.
Mr. Roy's wife. I'ma talk to her.
Yeah. Okay.
- Kev! Kevin, is my Roy... - Ms. Claire.
Sergeant?
I heard about the murder. Any leads?
Chasing a few. Nothing to report yet.
You're kind of far from the Tower.
I gather this isn't a random inspection.
It's not.
I want to talk about Andre Cooper.
You know, the young man whose partner shot and killed--
Yeah, I know who he is.
The kid's having a rough time.
Black cops are shunning him for not doing more.
The white cops are calling him out
for not backing up his partner.
Cooper was the valedictorian of his academy class.
I don't want his career to end before it starts.
Yeah. I get that.
Just don't know what you want me to do here.
Bring him into Intelligence.
I would think of it as a personal favor, Hank.
My team's handpicked by me.
You realize I could just assign him to Intelligence, right?
I do.
But you didn't.
Well, he's sitting in my SUV right now.
Least you could do is introduce yourself.
Look, I don't know what the deputy super told you,
but Intelligence is pretty unique.
I mean, there's only six or seven cops in the whole unit.
There's just not a lot of open positions.
Can I be blunt, sir?
This wasn't my idea.
She told me to jump in the car and take a ride.
So if she put you in a awkward position,
I apologize.
And as much as it would be an honor
to work in Intelligence,
I don't want any special favors.
What do you want?
To be in the game.
In the middle of it.
If you want to make a difference, do some good,
you gotta be on the streets,
in the community, talking to people.
It was nice talking to you, Andre.
For what it's worth, Sergeant,
I checked that pizza joint across the street.
- Okay. - Saw a guy duck back in
when he saw patrol coming.
Place went from open to closed real quick.
What did he look like?
Black. 40s.
6'5". Slender build.
Had on blue jeans, brown steel-toe boots,
a vintage Bulls Jordan jacket.
Vintage?
The red leather sleeves. They don't make those anymore.
Appreciate the heads-up.
Yes, sir.
Witness?
No. Grown man bitching about parking restrictions.
Listen, I want you to grab Kevin.
Check out that pizza joint on the corner.
I think the owner might know something.
All right.
Sorry, we're closed.
I'm not here for the pie, Bob.
I want to talk to you about the homicide across the street.
It's a damn shame about Roy.
What a world.
- You catch the guy? - No, sir, not yet.
That's exactly why we're here.
Did you see anything suspicious before or after the gunshots?
No, I was in the back.
We noticed gang tags on your doors.
That a problem for you? They've been harassing you?
- They're good customers. - Really?
Because three months ago, you filed a police report that
said two gangbangers roughed up one of your employees
and smashed out windows.
That was just... just a misunderstanding.
Bob, Mr. Roy was a good friend to me,
so if you know anything, you need to tell me now
because I'm not going to sleep until I find his killer.
I can't help you. I'm sorry.
I ain't no hero, brother.
I got a wife and two little kids.
You think of anything, call me.
My CI told me that Quincy Barrett
runs that neighborhood. He's got a strong sheet.
Distro, agg assault, armed robbery, intimidation.
- Whose flag does he fly? - Nobody's.
He's a lone wolf. From what I understand,
he recruits unaffiliated kids to deal dope
and shake down good business owners for protection money.
- All right. Anybody talking? - No one so far.
But it's pretty clear that pizza guy is getting harassed
or saw something.
He just doesn't want to get involved.
Well, we also know Roy was getting harassed.
OCD Lab dumped his phone,
and he's been getting threatening text messages
for about a month from a burner.
These are the most recent.
Two weeks ago, "Tick tock, old man."
Last week, "Time to pay."
And yesterday, "My gun's untucked."
All the messages are coming within the vicinity
of the hardware store.
And after Roy's murder, the phone was turned off.
Sounds like Roy didn't want to play the game,
so Quincy decided to make an example out of him,
send a message.
All right, so what else we got?
During our canvass, a witness told us
that they saw a beige SUV patrolling the block
for about 20 minutes before the shooting.
Had tinted windows. We did our homework.
Quincy drives a beige Escalade.
Okay. We catch it on any security cams?
No, he got lucky.
Well, it looks like his luck just ran out.
I'm gonna pull something up.
So this was captured on POD footage
across the streets from a car wash on Jackson
two hours after Roy was killed.
That Escalade's registered to Quincy Barrett.
And that guy, it looks like
he's only cleaning the driver's side.
All right. Anybody recognize him?
No, he doesn't look like Quincy Barrett to me.
- Too far for a facial rec. - Yeah.
Okay, so let's ID this car washer.
We gotta figure out a way to get inside that Escalade.
You find Roy's blood in there, it's game over.
No Escalade.
Hey, Jay, we're all set back here.
Copy.
Chicago PD. Open up.
Guy inside just dropped a gun into a red backpack.
- Not Quincy. - Guys, heads up.
Guy inside just hid a gun. Stay frosty.
Copy that.
Quincy Barrett.
The hell is this?
We got a report that your car was used in a hit and run.
We'd like to look at your vehicle.
Yeah. Well, good luck with that.
- What's that mean? - Someone stole it.
I don't know. Maybe whoever stole it
did that hit and run.
- Did you report the theft? - Nah, not yet.
But you know what? Maybe y'all can help me out.
You know, start looking.
Where were you yesterday afternoon, Quincy?
Y'all hear that phone ringing?
That's my lawyer calling,
telling me to keep my damn mouth shut.
Nice day, Officers.
Hailey. Hey, I got a male, Black, 20s,
exiting the building with a red backpack.
Yeah, that's him.
Could be the murder weapon in there. Take him.
- Copy that. - Hey, man.
Chicago PD. Can I talk to you for--
Slow down. Slow down.
- Yo, I haven't done anything. - Okay. Hands low.
Hands high.
Why you running?
- White cops scare me. - Yeah. What color am I?
Blue. Just as dangerous.
- What you got in here, man? - Nothing.
- Nothing, huh? - I know you leaving Quincy's.
What you doing? Washing cars again?
I don't know what you're talking about, man.
We were just playing video games.
Kev, yeah. It's just a gaming controller.
Like I say.
Can I have it back?
Off the car. What's your name?
- Damari Evans. - You got a license?
Where were you yesterday at 3:00 P.M., and why?
Midway Hospital.
My little brother had a seizure.
- Can I go now? - Go for it.
Damari, if I find out you had anything to do
with the murder of Roy Hill,
we'll see each other again, okay?
Okay, so that's Damari Evans and his younger brother, Theo,
at Midway Hospital.
This is the same day that Roy Hill is murdered,
and they are in that waiting room from 2:30 to 4:00 P.M.
And what time was Roy shot?
Shots fired call came in at 3:15.
All right, so Damari's his cleaner,
- not his killer. - Which would suggest
- Quincy did his own dirty work. - All right.
Were we ever able to track down this Escalade?
No. There's probably too much blood in there,
and he's hidden it somewhere.
All right. What else do we know about Damari?
Yeah, he's got one bust for distro, two agg assaults.
He's been in the gang database since he's 15,
and he lives with his little brother, Theo.
Okay, so Theo is a straight-A student,
one B-plus.
He has a severe form of epilepsy,
which requires a ton of medical attention,
and both parents are out of the picture.
Right, so he's the mother, father, brother,
- breadwinner wrapped in one. - Yeah, and that's good for us.
It means Damari's vulnerable.
Right, we jam him up,
get him to flip on Quincy to protect Theo.
We need to come at him as a big-time buyer.
But how?
Besides me, you guys are all burned,
and I'm pretty sure Damari doesn't want to sell to me.
- Good to see you. - All right. I'll catch you.
What you need, homie?
I'm good.
But you got company.
How's that?
You see that gray pickup down the block?
You see it? That man, woman?
Whiter than Christmas?
I'll bet a hundo they police.
Chicago PD. Let me see your hands.
- Yo, we ain't do nothing. - Put your hands up.
Shut up, turn around. Face the fence.
Before we pat you down, you got anything on you
- that's gonna stick us? - No, I do not, Officer.
I'm just waiting on my little brother.
Man, y'all can just keep on stepping. I know my rights.
Don't talk to me about rights.
I know you're selling, so where is it?
Back up, man. You ain't got no right to harass--
Calm down.
Come on!
He got you pretty good.
I told him to make it look real,
but not that real.
Should we take you to Med?
Good job, Coop.
It usually takes a few days before you land your first deal.
Yeah, well, you know it ain't nothing like running from cops
to bring brothers together, right?
This thing still transmit if I go into a basement?
- Yeah, half a mile radius. - Let me see.
- Let's see. - Here you go.
Okay.
So what does Damari know about you?
Name's Sean Hicks. From Auburn Park.
Went to Taft High School.
By the way, he tested me on the Taft mascot. You were right.
You tell him about your sick mom?
No.
Didn't think I needed to take it that far.
Felt like we were exploiting a private situation.
That's exactly what we're doing.
Damari's got a sick brother.
He's gonna respect you for taking care of your sick mother.
Gotta use any commonality we can find.
Look, stay on point, okay?
We're watching, but not too close.
And the bangers on that block, they got their radar up.
You catch a bad vibe, you walk.
- Right? - Yes, sir.
- All right. - Well, talk to me, man.
What high school did you go to?
I went to Bolingbrook High.
South suburb. A'ight.
You just make sure you take care of yourself in there.
Don't go in there talking about lacrosse or tennis.
You don't have to worry about that.
Why is that?
I was on the golf team.
Ooh, coming to get you, boy.
Don't think so.
Taste the carbon blaster!
Oh, that's cold.
Yo, you wanna take a run up against this punk?
Nah, man, I can't stay too long.
Gotta take Moms to the hospital.
Yo, what happened?
She got cancer.
In the lungs.
In chemo three times a week.
Yo, that's tough, bro.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Yeah, it ain't pretty.
Or cheap.
So you...
been holding down all the bills?
Yeah. Ain't got no choice.
I hear you, bro.
So how much you looking to buy?
Theo. Theo!
Theo, come on. Lay on your side for me.
Theo.
Just breathe. Just breathe.
The kid's seizing.
Come on, man. Just breathe.
- What the hell are you doing? - Calling an ambulance--
No, man! I got product here.
Look, he needs his medicine.
Just go to my room. It's on the dresser.
We're gonna have to call an ambo.
No, no, no. Just give it a minute.
I don't want Cooper to get burned.
Come on, Coop. Hurry up. Hurry up.
Inhale, buddy. You can do it.
Come on now.
Just breathe, T.
There you go. Breathe.
- You all right? - Good.
Yeah. He's gonna be fine.
- Right, Theo? - Yeah, I'm good.
Sorry. I didn't mean to scare you guys.
Yeah, well, you did.
Yo, no more of that, okay?
It's scary as hell, man.
Yo...
Yeah, we'll talk some more business tomorrow.
Yeah.
Hit me up if you need anything. For real.
All right, little man.
That was good work last night with Damari.
You kept your cool.
Sir, I thought Theo was gonna die.
Hey, man, we would never let that happen.
- Okay, good. Good to know. - Yeah...
Look, if things didn't stabilize quickly,
we would've stepped in, helped out.
Are you sure it's Quincy Barrett?
Bob, lock the door, stay in the back, and we'll check it out, okay?
All right.
That was Bob Hayes from the pizza joint.
He says Quincy is casing it right now in a silver Camry.
I got Hailey and Jay over there right now
doing follow-ups on Roy's murder.
Head over there, back them up. I'll loop them in.
- Come on. - Okay.
We know Quincy was driving a silver Camry.
Yeah.
It looks okay inside.
Kev told him to lock up, right?
Yeah.
Chicago PD.
Whoa! Chicago PD! Get your hands up.
Who are you? What are you doing here?
I'm Trent.
I just came in 10 seconds ago to get a pizza.
The door was open. I'm looking for Mr. Hayes.
Are you armed?
No! I didn't do anything. I just came to get some food.
- I promise. - Okay.
I'm just gonna search you for a second, all right?
Yeah.
All right. You got him?
Yeah, I got him.
Hang out in that corner for a sec, okay?
Body.
Hailey, it's Bob.
5021 George, I got a bona fide DOA.
3433 Wilson Road.
Hayes' Pizza. Roll a crime lab.
Copy that, 5021 George.
He took two to the chest, center mass.
One insurance round to the face.
- Cash register? - Untouched.
All right, so it was a hit.
Quincy knew he was a witness, tied it off.
All right, listen, we need evidence.
Let's get some boots on the ground now.
- Come on. - You got it.
- Coop. - Sir?
Just got a text.
Looks like Damari wants to meet up and do the deal.
Okay, good. Let's get it done.
Talk to Atwater. He'll set you up.
Sarge, you got a sec?
What's gonna happen to Damari?
What do you mean?
Say we arrest him.
He agrees to help us take out Quincy.
What kind of deal we talking?
Depends on how helpful he is
and how involved he was in the two murders.
If he does time, what happens to Theo?
DCFS will probably step in.
So we take one criminal off the street
and just create another?
Not sure that's a victory.
All right, listen to me.
We need to take down Quincy Barrett.
That's our focus.
That's the job.
Yeah. There he is.
Hey, man. How you doing?
- All good. - How's your mama?
She's good, man. Thanks for asking.
Yo, what kind of cancer she got again?
Lung.
Yeah, my aunt had that.
Yo, dawg, what you think about that investment idea
we talked about earlier?
Aw, Kev. Bro, you know I'm with you all the way,
but I don't like that one.
You don't like it?
Well, I don't think that that neighborhood's on the up.
What do you mean "on the up"? Anything can be on the up
if you get there at the right time and you put the work in.
So...I was able to get
100 grams, uncut.
Yeah.
It's all there.
Cool. Man, let's do it.
Yo, hold up. Hold up.
Man, it never stops, bro.
- What happened? - Theo's medical stuff.
He just had another seizure.
Principal took him down to the ER.
Sorry to hear that.
No, that's okay. They just cruising.
I spent 13 grand last year on medical bills.
- Can you believe that? - Damn.
No wonder why I gotta sell dope, man.
Yo, wait. Hold on. Hold on.
How about you go to the ER to check on Theo?
We'll do the deal later tonight.
No. What the hell?
- Come on, Coop. - What the hell?
Nah, man. It's cool. We can just bang it--
Nah, man. These cops is making me nervous.
Why risk? You know what I'm saying?
Yeah, let's hook up later, man.
All right. Bet.
What was that?
What was that? What was that?
We're two minutes away from making the arrest--
There was a patrol car out there.
If we got harassed,
- if they asked for my license-- - Andre.
That's why you backstopped.
You got a clean license, you got a clean name,
They couldn't blow your cover if they wanted to.
Yo, it just didn't feel right, okay?
So I made a call in the moment.
But we still good.
We're doing the deal later tonight.
Are you sure about that?
The hell does that mean?
That means you gotta worry less about Damari
and more about the families of the two dead bodies.
Roy Hill. Bob Hayes.
This job is hard.
Especially when you're trying to do right.
The more you care, it actually gets harder.
So if this isn't something that you can do,
if you don't think you can handle it, step aside.
But either way, we got jobs to do, and we gotta get it done.
That was his call, Kevin.
He was the one in play.
And Patrol was in the vicinity.
Okay, well, how about just ducking in the building
and keeping the deal going?
He's new. He's learning.
I understand that, but I think there's more to it.
- Okay. - He got a very soft spot for Damari.
We can't forget about what just happened last week.
He watched his white partner kill an innocent Black man.
He's got a lot on his mind,
and it's starting to worry me a little bit.
Okay, you make the call.
You want to pull him?
Sarge, Kev, I got something.
We picked off Quincy's credit card at a mini mart
20 minutes after Bob Hayes got shot.
We tapped into their security server
for the camera inside and out.
He walks in, buys a pack of cigarettes,
walks out, meets with someone in the parking lot.
Looks like he handed the murder weapon off to Damari.
Guessing his job was to stash it or dump it.
The question is, where?
- And the answer is in that phone. - Yeah, you're right.
We ID that cell number, we find the gun.
So, do you think Cooper can handle it?
All right. Get him up to speed.
Yo, man. You ain't gotta do this.
Nah, I got plenty.
Ding-dong over there, he eats like a bird.
Dig in.
It's the least I could do.
You saved me twice in, like, two days.
You're like a cop-sniffing dog.
All right, is this Damari just playing,
or he getting suspicious?
Twice in two days. That is a lot.
I mean, come on.
What do you think, Sarge?
My vote is suspicious.
Think we should pull him?
All right, we haven't heard the safe word yet.
Let's let it play for now.
Hey, I got good eyes.
Good ears too.
And I don't like police neither,
so I'm always aware of where they are,
who they harassing, so don't even trip.
Yeah, well,
there's plenty of them up in this neighborhood
sweating folks.
Always looking for problems too.
Used to.
I gotta admit, things are a little different now.
I know it's kind of fun, watching cops act all polite and nice.
Yo, they've been catching so much hell
that they scared of their own shadows.
It ain't like they don't deserve it.
I get you bro, but
it's not like we all choir boys.
You know, some of us
actually do break the law.
Hey, uh, you got a bathroom I could use?
Yeah, down the hall, to the left.
The hell you doing, man?
I was going to the bathroom, I saw the poster.
Had to be dude's first poster he ever did.
I ain't ever seen it before. But you know, my bad, man.
- I ain't mean-- - Nah, man, it's all cool.
I ain't uptight like that.
Cool.
Yo, grab your coat, man. We need to bounce.
Where we going?
Meet up with Quincy.
Yo, Coop.
Didn't we talk about this?
Do not travel, dawg.
What's wrong?
It's just, you didn't tell me we was meeting up
- with big boss man. - Yeah, he just texted.
You bring the cash?
Yeah. It's in my coat.
All right. Come on.
Yo, what's the matter?
You don't trust me?
Of course I trust you, man.
When they start asking if you trust them--
Then they don't trust you.
One more thing.
No cell phones.
Hey, Sarge, are we really gonna let them go mobile?
We don't really have a choice.
Copy that.
All right, 10-4.
Sarge, they're getting in Damari's car.
Yo, stuff the cash under the seat.
In case we get stopped.
Man, you is raw.
Man, where are we going?
Yo, stop asking so many questions, bro.
Just chill.
Come on, man. What's going on?
Move on. Move on.
- Come on. - Bro, you gotta get him.
Is this a joke? What the hell, man?
Come on, bro.
Hey, Sarge, we getting blocked by a garbage truck.
You got eyes?
- That's a negative. - I'll call it in.
Get this truck out of here. Get out of here!
We're losing the feed, Kev.
All right, we'll anticipate Cicero.
Maybe they're getting on the 290.
- All right, here we go. - You ready?
- Yeah. - All right. Let's go.
- Come on. Come on. Come on. - I lost signal.
Well, he's on his own now.
- This kid's on his own. - Yeah. Yeah.
Let's do this.
We got nothing? Nothing at all?
We got nothing. We got the BOLO going out
every five minutes. We got nothing.
- I just--I don't understand. - We told him not to travel.
Didn't we tell him not to travel?
- I know! - Come on, man!
We're gonna find him. We'll find him.
Damn! Forgot the bread.
Welcome to OnStar Emergency.
- My bad. - All good.
So this a normal thing?
Him wanting to meet up with the people you do business with?
I wouldn't say "Normal," but
he calls the shots.
So when he says meet, we meet.
It's the way it is.
Product in there?
Yeah.
Don't worry.
It's gonna be fine.
Definitely no cops in here.
Man, it kind of spooky, ain't it?
Yeah.
It feels like a place
where one of them horror movies take place.
You and me having fun, then boom.
Crazy dude in a clown suit show up.
Yeah, with a chainsaw.
Okay. Where is this kid?
Units on the Citywide.
We're getting a vehicle SOS distress signal.
Multiple attempts have been made to contact the occupants.
Anyone available to roll over to 420 North Belmont?
- Check it out? - 2322.
We'll roll on that job.
What kind of car are we looking at?
Black Buick LaCrosse. Four-door.
Illinois plate. William-7-Young-527.
- That's Coop. Let's go. - Smart move.
Okay, that means he's in trouble. Hey, hey, hey.
5021. Squad, that's our BOLO vehicle.
We're rolling on it.
5021 David, 10-4.
A few more years, man, and I'm done.
I'll have enough money to go legit.
Start that business I was telling you about.
Yeah.
I'm gonna make it big too.
I'll buy one of those mansions in the suburbs.
You know, on the lake?
Yeah, man. Sounds good to me.
And we'll go water skiing.
Then we'll cook steaks on the grill.
Man--
Sorry I'm late, fellas.
Oh, no worries.
Ah, so this the dude you been telling me about.
Yeah. Sean.
Where you from, Sean?
South Side.
Winter Park Apartment Complex.
- 18th and Woodbridge. - Cool.
Who you stay with over there?
I don't stay there now. Got my own spot.
33rd Street.
Uh-huh, don't it feel good to be on your own?
Independent?
Speaking of which,
you got any affiliations I need to know about?
I ain't linked up with nobody, man.
I always did my own thing.
So tell me, young brother,
how'd you meet my man, Damari, again?
It's kind of funny, actually.
Was walking down King Street.
Saw this white dude, this lady--white lady--
sitting in the car acting all nonchalant.
And I saw my man, Damari, on the corner.
Figured he might be doing some business,
you know?
So I gave him the heads-up. Thought they might be cops.
Sure enough, they were.
That's a good break.
Yeah.
He saved me in a pinch.
Then y'all became, like-- like best friends?
I don't know about all that, but
we cool.
Start talking about doing some business.
You know it's--it's kind of like one of them movies.
Right? You know, where the cute white chick
bump into the handsome dude?
He spilled coffee all over his dumb ass?
You know, they call that, um, serendipity.
Yeah, like a coincidence.
But, you know, the thing is, Sean, um,
I don't believe in serendipity.
You know, serendipity, it--
I don't know, it make me nervous as hell.
Nah, Q. Man, you got it wrong--
I ain't talking to you, boy.
No, so what is it about you?
What? You working off a case? You helping out police? Like--
- It ain't like that-- - Yo, I told you,
- keep your mouth shut! - It's cool.
It's cool.
I understand where you're coming from.
I ain't never been arrested.
So I ain't got no case to work off.
Yo, Q. He's straight, man.
It's all cool. It's not what you think it is, man--
Chicago PD!
Drop the--
Andre, are you good? You hit?
- Yeah, I'm good. - Call it in.
420 North Belmont.
Squad, man shot!
I need a ambo at 420 North Belmont!
Copy that. Ambo on the way.
Come on, Damari. Hang on, man.
Stay strong for Theo.
You're...
you're a cop?
Hang on, man.
- Just hang on. Hang on. - You're a cop.
Hang on.
Stop running!
Stop moving!
Stop! Moving!
Gun's clear.
Quincy Barrett, you're under arrest.
Get up.
You okay?
Any word on Damari?
Yeah.
He's dead.
It's not on you.
Not even a little bit.
He had a hard life. I get that.
But it was his decision to work for Quincy,
to sell drugs,
to shake down honest business owners, and cover up murders.
I mean, when you sign up for that life,
dying's a part of the game.
You done preaching?
Don't do that.
I'm not preaching.
I'm just telling you exactly what it is.
This ain't "Batman," Dawg.
The criminals don't wear masks. They don't act all crazy.
Some of them are smart, and they're charming.
They take care of their mothers, and their fathers,
and their uncles.
And their little brothers too.
You know, I get that.
But I feel like we could've done better.
I feel like we could've told Damari what was going on
and best thing, he'll cooperate.
We could've took care of Theo.
There's gotta be a better way to do this
without destroying innocent Black lives.
That's all I'm saying.
I mean, we had to put Damari into play
to get justice for Roy Hills and Bob Hayes.
Innocent Black lives.
There's not a easy answer to this problem.
But us being here is part of the solution.