And I just wanted to
touch base with you
one more time.
I'm not sure what you're asking.
I'm asking if there's anything
you would like to add
or modify.
No.
I stand by my original statement.
Yo, what's in the bag?
Nothing.
Hey, I'm police.
I asked you a question.
Officer Doyle had no probable cause
hopping out of the car and stopping Shawn Paige.
Doyle was the aggressor, not Paige.
That man was walking down the street
minding his own business.
So the two men inside of the recording studio
who shot and killed Doyle...
Doyle!
You believe they were acting in self-defense?
Yes, ma'am.
I need you to fight, Doyle. I need you to fight.
Okay.
Then I guess I need to file a motion to dismiss.
That's your call.
No, it's actually your call.
You were the only witness.
So if you think Doyle is to blame, there is no case.
Like I said,
I stand by my original statement.
It takes a lot of guts for a young Black cop
to take on the Chicago Police Department.
I'm right here! I'm right here!
I know what's been going on with Atwater past few weeks.
I got no idea what you're talking about.
Kenny.
Please don't make a jerk of me, okay?
We both know what you've been doing has gotta stop now
before someone gets hurt.
Like I said, I don't know what you're talking about,
but even if I did,
there's no way I could agree to that.
That kid Atwater broke the most sacred rule there is:
he snitched on the police
on a cop who died on the line of duty
with a wife and two little kids.
If that's not bad enough,
state's attorney's office just dropped the case.
The two punks that killed Doyle,
a Chicago police officer,
are gonna walk free.
Atwater did what he thought was right.
No. He crossed the line.
Blue wall is there to keep us together.
It keeps us safe.
It's a bible, our Ten Commandments.
You of all people know that, Hank.
If someone chooses to violate that code,
he's gotta pay the price.
Way it's always been.
Way it always will be.
You know, Lisa, I signed a statement
with the state's attorney.
Your husband will be exonerated.
I can't believe it.
I really can't.
It's the best damn thing I've heard in a long time.
It's good news for you too.
That means that lawsuit against the city just got a lot better.
Proves that cop Doyle was in the wrong;
your husband Shawn was in the right.
Thank you.
Glad I could help.
You know, brother, this city needs more people like you.
People who actually care.
Know how to treat people like people.
I got you, little homie.
Feel real sorry about your father.
He was a good man. He did nothing wrong.
Then why'd you kill him?
I'm telling you, I'm starting to get paranoid.
Like, for real.
Every time I see a cop, I get nervous.
I start thinking, my mind starts racing.
I told you I was literally on my knees
looking under the damn car. For what?
I don't know, but I was looking.
How many officers were in the car?
- What do you mean? - I'm just asking.
One. Why?
Well, if someone was gonna plant something,
I'm guessing, you know,
they would do it alone and leave their partner out of it.
You're saying that--
I'm saying that, you know, Doyle's crew, they play dirty.
Sorry for dragging you into all into this, Ruz.
This nonsense is starting to get to me.
Am I going crazy,
or is this actually happening?
- Hand me that rag. - What?
It's heroin.
What the hell?
Well, at least we know you're not crazy.
Damn.
Well, what's the plan?
You gonna inventory and write paper?
I don't know. I'm still thinking about it.
Did you get a good look at the patrol car?
You see V-tags, plates?
All right, we can pull POD footage,
scroll through the video. Who knows?
Maybe we catch this dirty prick actually planting the dope.
It's possible,
but these dudes are all over the place.
Doyle's probably got two cousins and an uncle working for IED,
which means no matter what we find,
the case still won't go anywhere, and you know that.
All right.
Well, you do what you gotta do,
but you remember that I'm here to help you, all right?
Any way you want.
Appreciate that.
Police officers will spend more time in the streets
and in the neighborhoods.
Hey, Deputy Supe's giving a speech.
You mean apology.
She's pretty much telling us
we're a bunch of unenlightened idiots.
I wouldn't go that far.
She's just telling us what we already know.
Police have to do a better job at deescalating.
Sure, but she doesn't have to be so disrespectful.
We're all trying our best.
Not good enough, Hailey.
It isn't.
CPD did not kill George Floyd, I get that,
but we sure as hell killed Shawn Paige.
So maybe we should just reserve our judgement,
listen to what the sister has to say.
Yeah, I'm not...
We will once and for all tear down the blue wall.
Nice to meet you, Sergeant.
- Nice to meet you. - I know you're busy.
I really appreciate you coming in here
to meet me in person.
Deputy Supe calls, you come.
Please, call me Sam.
You want anything to drink? Coffee, water?
No thanks.
You know, I've been here just two weeks,
and all I keep hearing is your name.
Hank Voight this, Hank Voight that.
By all accounts, you are one hell of a cop.
Well, that is very kind of you,
but I'm guessing you didn't call me down here to blow smoke.
No. I didn't.
I wanted to give you a heads up, cop to cop.
If you keep running your unit the way you've been doing
for the past seven years,
you're gonna be out of a job by Christmas.
Anything else I should know?
Yeah.
I'm on your side.
I want you to succeed, Sergeant.
If Hank Voight can change the way he polices,
if he can learn how to play by the rules,
the rest of the department will follow.
Look, thanks for the heads up,
but I gotta go if that's all right.
5-year-old girl just got shot.
Stay safe, Sergeant.
Ma'am.
Hang in there. You're gonna be okay.
We were walking back from the market,
and then I heard two loud pops,
and I saw Laura on the ground bleeding.
Okay, did you see the shooter?
No.
Did you see anything suspicious?
No, no, no, no, no. I just--
We were just walking, and then she got hit.
Listen, I need to be with my little girl right now.
- Okay, go. - Okay, what do we know?
Not much.
Jay and I heard the "Shots fired" call
come over the radio, so we rushed to the scene.
The little girl was bleeding out when we got here.
She got shot in the stomach.
Good news is, the ambo got here quick.
What happened? Robbery, drive-by?
Yeah, we don't know.
She was walking with her parents,
and then she got shot somehow.
Unfortunately, they didn't see much.
They heard two loud pops. Next thing you know,
their daughter's on the ground bleeding.
- So stray bullet? - Sounds like it.
All right, so start canvassing.
Talk to witnesses, pull PODs, surveillance cameras.
Find someone who saw something.
Thanks.
I hope Kev didn't think that I...
I was bitchin' about the Deputy Supe's speech,
not trying to minimize what happened to Shawn Paige.
I think he totally knows that.
He's just venting.
He's going through so much right now.
- I wouldn't worry about it. - Okay.
Sir, do you live around here?
Yeah? Did you see anything unusual?
Anybody with a gun, anyone arguing?
No.
- Did you hear gunshots? - No.
- How long you been out here? - About an hour.
You've been out here for an hour and you didn't hear
two gunshots that hit a little girl
right over there 30 minutes ago?
I already told you.
Look, we're just trying to get some information.
And I ain't got any, so get the hell out my face, bitch.
What did you say to me?
Come on.
Yeah, y'all racist-ass cops
ain't welcome around here no more.
Hey, man.
You see the shooting today?
Maybe hear gunshots about 30 minutes ago?
See an argument, fight,
car drive by real fast?
Anything like that?
All right.
No, no, no, what are you doing?
Hey, stop. What are you doing?
He just threw a beer bottle at me.
Let it go.
It's not worth escalating this.
That's Agg Assault against a police officer.
All right, they can film all they want.
- I don't care. - I do care.
I'm not risking my career over a damn beer bottle.
You let it go, okay?
- Okay, what do we know? - Nothing much.
No shot splatter, no shell casings,
no witnesses.
None that were willing to cooperate anyway.
I just talked to Med.
The girl, Laura Diaz, she's in critical,
but the good news is, doctors removed the bullet.
It's 9mm. It's with ballistics right now.
Not sure if it's connected,
but Laura's father was arrested for possession three years ago.
Also has some gang cards on file.
Looks like he runs with the Latin Players.
Maybe we were wrong.
Maybe it wasn't a stray bullet after all.
You're saying that I was the target,
and they hit Laura by accident?
No, what we're saying is,
we know about your affiliation with the Latin Players.
What the hell are you talking about?
Roberto, we're just trying to find the person
who shot your daughter.
We're here not here to investigate you.
We don't care who you run with.
I don't run with anyone.
I own a bakery in Little Village on 26th street.
I work there seven days a week.
We also know about your prior arrest.
I got pulled over by a cop for running a stop sign,
and I had two joints in my glove compartment, okay?
That don't make me no drug dealer, bro,
and that sure as hell don't make me no gangbanger.
Okay, it's our mistake.
But like I said,
we're just trying to find the person who shot your daughter.
So think hard.
Roberto, as difficult as this must be,
put yourself back in that moment in time
when you heard the gunshots.
Was there anybody around?
Anybody walking? Running?
Naw.
You see any cars? Motorcycles?
Bicycles?
I heard a car drive away, like, real fast,
but it was through the alleyway at the other end of the block.
All right, you remember the make and model, the color?
It was dark, man.
It was, like, black I think.
Thank you. That helps.
Yeah.
Listen, I'll do whatever I can, it's just...
go find this son of a bitch.
Okay, black car
drove off right after the gunshots.
Cool. Copy that.
All right, that's Halstead.
He's gonna pull more surveillance video.
- Okay. - Try to find a black car.
Good.
I heard they dropped the homicide charge
against those two bangers who shot Doyle.
It was a weak case.
Bangers or not, that night,
just two dudes minding their own business.
Yeah, look.
Kevin...
I know you've been going through a lot, okay?
But you gotta understand, these cops,
I mean, this is gonna rile them up even more.
The only thing they were hanging onto was that trial,
watching those two offenders get convicted of murder.
I get it, but that's their problem.
And like I've been trying to say,
those two dudes weren't really offenders.
Oh, come on, man, you don't have--
The charges got dropped.
Kevin, I'm trying to help you.
If you ever need to talk...
I'm good.
Thanks.
This security camera caught our masked offender
running down the alley.
Then an unknown male chases after him,
confronts him, they fight,
our offender draws a weapon.
I'm guessing that's our 9mm.
He fires two rounds, misses his intended target.
And it hits a 5-year-old girl
named Laura Diaz a block away.
The question is: where was the offender coming from,
and who did he rob?
Can you enhance that?
Is that a church?
Chicago PD. Anyone here?
Hello?
Police.
Hello? Jay.
Sir?
Sir, sir, it's okay. We're the police. It's okay.
You want us to call an ambulance?
- No. - Do you need medical help? You sure?
I'm okay.
All right, let's get you up, okay?
You got it? Come on.
- I'm okay, I'm okay, I'm okay. - All right.
You wanna tell us what happened?
Hold on. I need a drink.
That's the last time I stash money for a drug dealer.
That's for damn sure.
I'm not proud of keeping dirty cash,
but I won't apologize for it either.
I did what I had to do to keep the doors open,
give the people in this parish a place to come,
a place to pray.
Yeah, look, we're not here to judge or absolve.
We just wanna know what happened.
I was in here doing paperwork.
I look up. I see some guy in a mask
pointing a gun at me, telling me to open the safe,
like he knew I was hiding all this cash.
I did what he said.
I gave him the money, and he ran out.
But then I realized the dealer would think I was involved,
so I ran after the guy. I tackled him.
He tried to shoot me,
but ... Anyway, he ran away and drove off.
Well then, he drove off,
so who tied you up and beat you?
The dealer.
I called him up. I told him what happened.
Next thing I know, he's in my office punching me,
calling me a thief.
All right, what's the dealer's name?
A little girl got shot
'cause you were hiding drug money in a church.
So you need to start talking now.
Carlos, I don't care about you,
the cash, the priest, or the church.
I just wanna find the guy
who did the robbery and shot that little girl.
Now you ask me, we're on the same side on this thing, bro.
What are you saying?
I'm saying I'll find him, and then I'll put him in prison,
and I'm done.
You're free to do whatever you gotta do.
Okay, who else knew about the money?
Nobody.
No friends? Business associates?
They all criminals, man.
Why would I tell them where I hide my cash?
So you telling me only you and Father Allende
knew about the money in the church?
Yeah, that's why I beat his ass.
He's playing me like a fool.
No. His story checks out.
After the guy took the money, he ran out,
Allende chased after him, tackled the guy.
He turned around, got off two shots, almost killed the priest.
Got the whole thing on tape too.
Sound like an inside job to you?
So who else knew about the money in the church?
I'm telling you, man, I don't know.
All right, listen.
If you think of something that might be useful,
give me a call.
We got a hit on that black car?
Yeah, pulled video from a traffic cam
two blocks south of the church.
You run the plates?
Yep, it came back to a 2004 Grand Cherokee.
It's registered to a female Hispanic, 29 years of age.
She goes by the name Anna Salgado.
She lives at 6438 South Homan,
and she does have a sheet, boss.
Got pinched for a drug misdemeanor.
She also has a brother doing three years for a felony
and a daughter, seven years old.
Guess who the father is.
Carlos Infante.
The banger hiding his cash at the church.
Nice work. All right, bring her in.
I already told you.
I don't know anything about no robbery at no church.
We got a warrant for your phone.
We read all your texts.
Look, I know what's going on.
What's that mean?
It means that I know you and your baby daddy,
Carlos Infante, have been beefing about money
'cause he hasn't been providing for your daughter.
But you're a good mom,
so you took matters into your own hands,
took what you thought was yours.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Come on, Anna.
You and Carlos were together a long time.
You knew he was hiding money at the church.
Maybe he told you,
maybe you overheard him talking one day,
but either way, you knew.
Now we know you're not a criminal, we know that.
You don't know how to rob people.
You told one of your friends about this, right?
A friend came through,
did the robbery, took the cash,
jumped in your black Jeep, drove away.
Like I said, I don't know what you're talking about.
You understand a little girl was shot
about the same age as your daughter?
She's fighting for her life.
Now you tell us who was driving your car,
we can work out a deal,
keep you out of prison--
keep you at home with your little girl
instead of her growing up in foster care.
Now who was driving your car?
Somebody must've stolen it, or maybe--
Don't be stupid!
I'm done talking! I want a lawyer.
- How'd it go? - Didn't say a word.
Yeah, and for good measure, she lawyered up.
- You got enough to charge her? - Not even close.
Look, we do know that she's involved.
She tipped somebody off.
So let's get eyes on her. Set up outside her house.
Find out who she's hanging out with.
I'm not gonna lie to you, man,
I'm, like, a little impressed with this Anna girl.
I would've bet $1,000 she was gonna roll.
So that says what?
The shooter's gotta be her boyfriend or a relative?
Someone she cares about, right?
Someone she can't just snitch on.
'Cause I'm telling you,
Voight, he made her a hell of an offer.
No jailtime, gets to keep her daughter,
and this girl, man, she just...
Stayed stoneface. She didn't even flinch.
I get it, bro.
She's a hero.
Didn't roll on her homies.
What you talking about?
I'm just saying, if you wanna talk about it,
we can talk about it.
There's no point in dancing around it.
I don't actually know what the hell you're getting at right now.
- Now, come on, man, let's... - Kev.
Are you being serious right now?
Look at who you're talking to. It's me.
I'm not talking about you. I'm talking about this Anna girl.
She's a single mother; she's staring down a felony
and is keeping her mouth shut-- that ain't easy.
That's all I'm getting at here.
You did what you did, and I have no issues with it.
You sure about that?
Absolutely. Hear me when I say that.
Sorry, I--I just...
It's all right. It's all right.
My bad.
You got a lot going on.
Well, go home. Get some rest.
All right, I'll stay here for another hour or so.
I can set up the camera myself.
All right, all right, all right, all right.
- You gonna be good? - Yeah.
Kev, what'd you end up doing with the dope?
I dumped it.
I had to get rid of that.
Are you sure that was the right move?
It was the only move.
Just because people are marching in the streets
doesn't mean that the world has changed.
Cops are still blue,
I'm still Black.
In trying to explain the situation,
she echoed the same thing I've heard over and over again:
the George Floyd murder was the tipping point.
I agree.
We all saw that white cop with his knee on his neck.
Plus all the other stuff going on.
Again, the virus, the shutdown...
Hey, I'm police. What's up, guy?
- You ran the stop sign. - What are you talking about?
Sir, you ran the stop sign. That's the reason we pulled you over.
No, I didn't run a stop sign.
I guess y'all just bored?
Saw a brother driving a decent car,
figured you pull his ass over, have some fun?
Hey, take it easy. My partner said he saw you run a stop sign.
We had no idea if you were Black or white.
Step out of the car.
Look, I'm police.
My name's Kevin Atwater, badge number 52784.
I work with the intelligence unit.
Y'all can check whatever you want.
I said, step out of the vehicle.
Nah, I'm not stepping out of no damn vehicle,
but I will show you my badge nice and slow.
Okay, so y'all can--
Okay, look, fellas, I'm stepping out of the car.
Shut the door.
I'm shutting the door. My hands are high.
You see my star and my gun.
If you look in my left pocket, you'll find my ID.
He's telling the truth.
He's the police, Ron.
So what you a cop?
I got an anonymous tip
that a guy was selling drugs in this car.
What are you talking about?
The guy sold a kilo of heroin to a dirty cop in a blue Dodge.
You with Nolan's crew?
Well, search the car, Ron. Look wherever you want,
but you ain't gonna find a damn thing
'cause I already found the dope.
It was in the trunk.
Is this really what you wanna do,
Black man?
You wanted to see me?
Yeah.
Shut the door.
So I heard you got into a beef last night
with a couple patrol officers.
More complicated than that.
I'm sure it is.
One of Nolan's boys pulled me over last night
hoping to find dope in my car.
Dope?
They planted a kilo of heroin in my car.
Why didn't you tell me?
Didn't want to get you involved.
Okay.
So tell me, what's your plan?
Going to IED?
I can't prove they planted the dope
or that they're even harassing me.
So I'll just sit back and wait for one of these punks
to screw up and leave behind some actual evidence.
Don't really have any other options.
Sure you do.
Kevin...
The blue wall is a tricky thing.
It's not a person or an object. It's a code.
You never really see it.
I mean, it's there, but it's not there.
You understand?
It's like trying to fight a ghost, Kevin.
I know, Sarge.
I just wanna do this my way.
Okay, so where we at with Anna Salgado?
Not sure--I'm meeting up with Ruzek right now
to check out surveillance video.
Hit it.
You know these guys are pushing their luck.
- They need to know that. - I told you, I'm good.
- No. - It's over.
Are you gonna talk to this punk Gaffney,
or am I gonna talk to him, seriously?
Check it out.
All right, well, let's run it through facial rec.
Miguel Cortez, he's a career punk.
He's got five priors, two armed robberies,
two ag bats, one attempted murder,
six or seven drug charges.
- Hailey... - Yeah.
Pull up the surveillance video from the church.
Okay.
Is that Miguel?
Looks like him. Same height, same build.
- It's just not clear enough. - Yeah, but come on.
We all know it's him. It makes perfect sense.
He's dating Anna,
she's complaining about not getting child support,
she gets fed up,
she tells Miguel where the dope money's stashed at St. Angela's.
Yeah, and he grabs a gun and a mask.
He sets out to commit the easiest robbery of his life.
Exactly.
Hey, good news. After we ID'd Miguel,
we pulled video of his last known address.
Good.
That's Miguel entering his house
45 minutes after the robbery and shooting.
Same pants and shoes,
and he's carrying the same bag we saw in the other video.
So let's get a warrant. Scoop his ass up.
Right.
I've got up top.
Did you hear him?
Announce your office and hit that door.
Be ready.
Upstairs window.
We just got made.
Chicago PD!
Hey, put your hands on the table.
Hands on the table.
Ma'am, walk towards me. Walk towards me.
Keep your hands where I can see them.
Sit down. Put your hands on the table.
- Hands on the table. - Come on.
I got you. Go.
All right, it's all right.
Stop, put your hands on your head and walk towards me.
- Ruz, I got a runner! - Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
It's over, Miguel.
Get your hands up.
Now.
Be smart, man.
Put your hands up nice and high.
Don't make this hard on yourself.
You wanna die?
'Cause I won't ask again.
Hands behind your back.
Here we go.
We got about 50K in here, maybe more.
Best part is,
Miguel left it in the church collection bag.
The St. Angela's logo on it and everything.
Nice.
Book it into evidence, will you?
Copy that.
You talked to Kev about all this Doyle business?
A little. You?
I'm trying. He's shutting me out.
He's having a hard time, boss.
These guys, they're playing too rough.
They're just getting started.
He did what he had to do.
It's different for him. It just is.
You know, being a Black cop here in Chicago these days.
Can't be easy.
Go on in.
Ma'am.
We got a problem.
Kay, I don't know what you're talking about.
I just watched the bodycam footage of Miguel Cortez's arrest.
You kicked down the damn door without announcing your office.
That's because we got made.
I just spoke to the state's attorney's office.
They've determined the entry improper,
so all the evidence recovered is inadmissible.
Okay, look, I get it.
Nobody wants to hand out no-knocks these days.
We had a warrant to enter the premises
and apprehend the offender.
You're not hearing me.
You entered the premises
without announcing your office.
There were women and children in there.
It could've gone bad a hundred different ways.
But it didn't.
Like I said before, Sergeant,
I want you to succeed more than you know.
But the days of playing God are over.
The quicker you understand that, the better.
Right or wrong, there's nothing we can do.
All the evidence has been tossed.
You guys, I'm sorry. I saw the blinds move.
I don't know what I was supposed to do.
Adam, no, listen to me, you did the right thing.
What I'm trying to tell you is, it doesn't matter.
You get it?
The reality is,
no one's got the guts to stand up for police right now.
Not the mayor, not the white shirts in the ivory tower.
No one.
Get used to it.
Okay, so...
the only real evidence we have now
is that video of Miguel entering his house
carrying the bag.
Same bag he was carrying when he tried to shoot the priest.
Yeah, I get it, but try proving it's the same bag.
I mean, a black bag is a black bag.
We gotta start all over from the beginning,
build a whole new case.
So find more surveillance video,
new witnesses.
Meantime, I'm gonna talk to Miguel.
I can still let him know how much evidence we have.
For God's sakes, bro,
the collection bags are marked St. Angela's.
It doesn't get any better than that.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Your girlfriend told you about the money
because Carlos stopped providing for their daughter,
and honestly?
I don't even blame her.
I mean, that guy makes a lot of money selling dope.
Least he can do is break off a few grand
every month for his little girl.
I told you. I didn't do it.
You stole the money, you ran out,
the priest chased after you,
he tried to tackle you,
so you opened fire.
That's what happened.
You know, the fact that you were so close
and you missed,
that tells me you probably just trying to scare the guy.
But see, the problem is, Miguel,
the reason we're all so upset
is one of your bullets hit a 5-year-old girl.
She's fighting for her life right now at Chicago Med.
Chicago is a-- it's a dangerous place.
You confess to the robbery
and the shooting,
you can cut yourself a deal.
You understand?
But you wait, play the long game,
you try and take this thing to trial,
state's attorney is gonna nail your ass to a cross.
- I want my lawyer. - What is the matter with you?
Yo, I'm done talking!
Heard what happened with the search.
- Yeah, well, it is what it is. - New world.
Everybody's paying attention to the fine print all of a sudden.
- Where is he? - In there.
Mr. Diaz, what can I do for you?
You tell me you caught the person who killed my little girl.
You're saying...
She died an hour ago.
Oh, my God.
I'm--I'm so sorry.
Did you arrest the killer?
We're still working on that,
but the good news is,
we know who did it.
We just need a little more evidence, build a better case.
If you know who did it, isn't that enough?
Doesn't that mean you already have a good case?
Sometimes the law is complicated.
No, it's simple.
It is real simple.
So who killed her? Who killed her?
- Who is he? - I can't tell you that.
Who is he? Where is he?
If you don't take care of this, I will!
Sir, please!
No. My little girl is dead.
And I want that son of a bitch who killed her to go down,
- to pay for what he did! - So do I.
And I promise you I will do everything I can.
But it's, it's just...
Grab Miguel and put him in a cage.
Boss, you sure that's a good idea?
- Excuse me? - Sarge, I mean...
come on, things are different now.
I'll do what you need me to do--
Laura Diaz just died.
Five years old.
The prick who pulled the trigger's sitting right in there.
Doesn't matter.
Of course it matters. He killed her.
I know he did, we all know he did,
but we can't just drag his ass down to a cage.
We done with all that--
- Oh, yeah, says who? - Guys, let's not do this.
Says me.
You calling the shots now, Kev?
No, but I know we can't keep bringing people down
to a cage and beating they ass
because we think they know something
or did something. Those days are over.
You don't like the way I do business?
I'm not woke enough for you?
You feel free to get the hell out.
Well, Sarge, this is your unit.
I'm proud to work here,
but things have definitely changed.
That means that we gotta change too.
Yeah, you wanna be a Boy Scout?
You wanna be a Boy Scout!?
Maybe you should get yourself another job!
I'll tell you what, you're right about one thing--
this is my unit!
And in my unit, we do what we gotta do
to put bad guys away!
Whatever it takes!