.
- Police! Freeze!
- I wasn't at that drug house
to do a buy bust.
I was there
to score oxy for me.
- I'm gonna help
get you through this.
[phone ringing]
Hey, put her on the phone!
- What's going on?
- I think someone
just kidnapped my daughter.
It's Daddy, it's Daddy.
I'm here.
Eva, can you hear me?
- What are you doing here?
- Just give me
five minutes with him.
- She 18 yet?
She was good.
[both grunting]
- What the hell
are we gonna do?
- Hey, look at me.
Be honest, when
was the last time you used?
- Today.
Just a few hours ago.
- All right.
Antonio, listen.
We gotta get you out of here.
Take your gun.
Okay.
Now give me your phone and go.
It's all right.
I got this.
Now go.
It's okay.
Go.
- Yeah.
All right, put this
in your car.
- All right.
- The phone comes up,
you say Antonio left it there
at the beginning of the tour.
- Copy that.
- You arrive on scene.
You came around that corner,
through that door.
You witnessed me
and the offender
engaged
in a physical altercation.
- No, hold on. Hold on.
- Then you witnessed Rizzo--
- No, no, no, no, no.
- You witnessed Rizzo
go over the wall.
- No, no, no.
Boss, no.
- Hey.
You run downstairs.
You attempt to administer aid.
- No, no.
I won't let you
take the fall for this.
- He's unresponsive.
You determined he was dead
on impact.
- No. You're not doing that.
You can't take it.
- The phone.
Then body.
Then attempt to help him.
- They will bury you.
Okay? There is no way
that the department--
- We are not
having a discussion.
Adam.
I need to know right now,
are you with me?
- Of course I'm with you.
- Then you need to go.
Now. Go!
[distant sirens wailing]
[tense music]
♪
- Sarge, you good?
- Yeah.
- Call came in over the zone,
Intelligence in pursuit.
You boys need
a transport vehicle?
- It's over. The offender and I
got into an altercation.
He tried to disarm me.
He didn't make it, so, uh...
Do us a favor.
Roll the crime lab.
I need to talk to IRT
about an officer-involved
death.
Thank you.
- Sarge.
What's going on?
- Officer-involved death.
- Rizzo?
- You all should probably
get back to the district.
- Ruzek was involved?
Where's Antonio?
- I called him off.
- I thought he was
on his way here.
- He wasn't here.
All right, you can all
head back to the district.
I don't want any of you
logged in on the crime scene.
You understand?
- Hailey, come on.
Come on.
- You been through
one of these before?
- Yes, sir,
unfortunately, I have, yeah.
- I'll just remind you
that as IRT,
we're here to investigate
the behavior of the offender.
You understand?
You're not on trial.
- I understand.
- Can you tell me
in simple terms what happened?
- I was in hot pursuit
of the offender.
As I closed in I announced
my office several times.
I ordered him to stop.
He did not.
He was non-compliant.
He was violent.
He lunged for me.
For my weapon.
And, in fearing for my life,
I had no choice
but to defend myself.
- He wasn't armed?
- No, sir.
It was a physical altercation.
But weapon or no, I did believe
my life was at risk.
- You and your sergeant were
the only ones on the scene?
- Yes, sir.
- Are you injured?
I need a verbal yes or no.
- No, I'm not injured. No.
- Okay then.
Let's get some pictures.
You gotta piss and blow,
and then, hopefully,
if everything checks out,
that's the last
you'll have to see me.
- Copy that.
- But remember.
I'm the nice one, yeah?
When you get to COPA, they'll
investigate your behavior.
Be clear, be short,
and be dead honest.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
- All right.
- Hey.
You gonna explain
what's going on now?
Where's Antonio?
- Antonio's taking
some time off.
- Time off?
He was on his way there.
- Antonio is gonna be taking
some days with his family.
Ruzek is dealing with
an officer-involved
death investigation.
And that's the last
this team will discuss it.
- Sarge, is he--
- You never have to explain
something you didn't say
or hear.
Is that understood?
- It is.
But I wanna know if Antonio's
gonna be okay.
- Yeah. He will be.
He just--just needs some time.
We all okay now?
- Uh, sorry to interrupt
whatever this is.
There's been another
carjacking downtown.
North Side, broad daylight.
This time the victim died.
She was 18.
Brennan's requesting
you take this one.
- All right, you heard her.
Let's go do our jobs.
Hey, Trudy, um...
we're down two today.
Ride with me to the scene?
- Yeah.
- Hey, Wigand.
- Hey, Sarge.
- Same MO?
- Yeah, looks like it.
All the witnesses are saying
that there were two carjackers,
both of them masked and gloved.
It's just like
the other four carjackings.
You know, they waited for her
to step away from the vehicle
and then charged.
You know, only this time--
- She fought back.
- We've got
multiple witnesses.
They say the carjackers
moved fast.
She reacted to the violence.
- Okay, I'm gonna get forensics
to set up a tarp.
- Hey, uh, listen, I want
you to get her hands bagged.
Hopefully you'll find some DNA
under her fingernails.
Girl's parents been notified?
- Patrol's en route
to her house.
- I think you should take it.
Look, this thing's already
gonna be all over the press.
Don't want some rookie cop
confirming their kid's gone.
- Right.
- Thanks.
- Put out an investigative
alert
on the stolen vehicle.
It was a Lexus F type.
Seems like the carjackers
sped directly onto Lake Shore,
probably hooked up
with 94 or 55.
- Talked to a witness
who owns that shop.
Said there's security cameras
that look
directly at the scene.
- Go check it out.
- That's where we're headed.
- Detectives?
Camera feed relays
to my laptop.
I'm sure it caught
the whole thing as it happened.
Would have at least
seen the girl.
She...
she was right outside and...
they just...
- Ma'am, you don't have
to watch the footage with us.
- Thank you.
I'll just, uh...be in the back.
- All right.
- Jesus.
- You see that?
- Yeah. They're coming
from the L stop.
- Whoever they are,
they're smart.
They never look up
at the camera once.
But they took the L train
the whole way there.
We were able to trace them
back to the Red Line
and they hopped on
at the 47th Street station.
- Right. They paid cash,
so nothing to trace.
but I'm sending the footage
to the CTA workers.
- 47th Street station.
That's Canaryville.
47th Street's, like, two blocks
from my mom's house.
I got a real good CI there,
Mark Rollins.
Guy I grew up with.
He's working off
a home invasion case.
He's plugged in too.
Runs with Pat Kent's crew
and...
if these carjackers
are Canaryville locals,
Kent'll know about it.
- You know nobody
in Canaryville's gonna
willingly talk to us,
so we do need an angle.
- All right, so dig
into the pattern.
Find the nexus between time
and neighborhood.
And I want a detail posted
on every L stop above Jackson.
And uniformed patrol
sitting on 47th.
We don't let another one
of these happen,
you understand?
- Copy that.
- I'm assuming
it's not news to you
IRT wants you on a short leash.
So you visit your CI with me.
- All right.
- Let's go.
You have no idea
what you just did.
I mean, there could
be witnesses.
Cameras. They could have
caught you on PODS.
Phone records could indicate
Antonio was there.
- I know.
- There could be forensics.
DNA evidence.
- Boss.
- You're not getting
out of the car yet.
- All of that would be there
had you done what I did.
- And who the hell
do you think you are?
You don't protect me.
I protect you.
That's my job.
I'm the one who allowed
Antonio to be there.
This is on me.
From this point on,
you don't say another word
about this, you get me?
- Yes, sir.
- There's a single crack
in this,
this tips sideways,
we're all on the hook.
- Sarge, I did
what I had to do.
I don't know what you want.
- We buried Al six months ago.
- This is not that.
.
- Hey.
- Oh, hell, no.
- Mark.
- I said I'm not working with--
I'm not doing it!
I'm not working with you, man.
- Nice to see you too.
May I remind you
you still have a case
you gotta work off.
- Yeah, I've been working that
off for the last ten months.
You got me snitching
on the whole damn neighborhood.
You sent me those
narco cops last month.
- They were beat cops and they
had one question for you.
- They were idiots.
This is all, uh,
legally personal--legal--
- Would you just calm down,
all right?
We're not here
to search your stuff
and shutting curtains
and slamming doors in my face
isn't gonna stop us if we were.
- Sergeant Hank Voight.
- You brought your boss?
- What, you don't want
to work with me, either?
- Yeah, no.
No thanks.
- Well, see, I think you do.
'Cause I'm the guy
who can actually
get your whole file cleared.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- And what do I have to do
for you to do that?
- Inform on the carjacking crew
working out of Canaryville.
- What, are they boosting
Saturn twin-cams on 42nd?
I don't know any crews
jacking cars. Sorry.
- That so?
- Yeah, that's literally
what I just said.
- Okay.
Well, you know anyone
who might know?
Pat Kent?
- You gotta be kidding me.
- You inform on this one thing,
you get Pat to give us
something, and you're done.
All right? You're off the hook.
No more me, no more cops,
nothing.
- No.
No thanks.
- Okay, well,
consider your case still open.
I got a lot of friends
who'd love to talk to you.
- Okay. Fine, fine, fine, fine.
What do you--What do I
gotta do?
Just tell me.
What?
- You go in, you push Pat
for info.
But be smart, subtle.
Don't push too hard.
This phone is your wire.
We'll be outside listening.
We'll also be hacked into their
surveillance cam for eyes.
We can have a ghost
in there for you.
Someone under, you won't
even know they're there.
- Something funny?
- If one of the two of you
starts slinking
around Canaryville,
there's no way in hell
no one notices.
But I have a second idea.
Um, I don't even use a wire.
Right, yeah, so I just--
I go in and I talk
to a couple people.
I'll get you a little info
and...
you know, we'd all
be real happy.
- No, see,
I talked to Adam.
And he said he's known you
for, like, a long time.
And you're getting a wire.
- That's cute.
- Uh, this is up and running,
so I'm gonna
let everybody know.
- All right.
- Cool.
- How do you know Adam?
- We, uh...we grew up
around the block.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Took different paths, huh?
- No. No, not really.
You know...
it's only in Chicago
a kid like Adam
can grow up and become a cop.
Do you...
have time for coffee, or--
- Move.
Are you really okay
with all this?
- With what?
- With not knowing why Ruzek's
staring down the barrel
of an OID?
- I don't know if I'm okay
with any of it.
But I think the best way
to protect everyone
is to not talk about it.
- Hey there, Mark.
- Mark's here. We're up.
- Hey.
- You know we got police heat
all up on 47th?
- What the hell
are you talking about?
- The two cops in full uniform
sitting at the stop
like their asses are on fire.
- What the hell is he doing?
- Yeah.
- No idea.
- They're, like, a lick away
from pulling a stop and frisk.
Who the hell's
bringing the heat?
- I don't know.
- Someone should
probably find out.
- Yeah.
- You going
to Becker's tonight?
Valerie said she's only going
if you go.
- You want me
to talk to someone?
- No. It's good.
- Pricks apparently been
out there for, like, 12 hours.
- Jesus. We gotta be ready
to pull this guy.
- I know they're gonna
get bored.
Start pulling their weight
with pat downs.
No one's gonna wanna go in
with possession--
- It's fine.
I'll talk to Billy.
- Billy?
- Billy's been clearing?
- Clearing. Chop shop.
- Yeah.
- Did I not just say
it was good?
- Question.
How the hell are you okay
with the fact
that the girl
you want to screw
will only go to this
house party if I'm there?
[all laughing]
- She only likes you there
as a buffer, all right?
- I think she wants me there
'cause she likes me, Coop.
- She said she wouldn't
even kiss him
'cause it might ruin
their friendship.
- He's known her for
three days, what friendship?
- Ah, man.
- Wasn't quite
what we talked about.
- Yeah, are we done?
- This Billy's place,
is that Billy Cowan?
Owns an auto repair on 45th?
Guessing that's an
off-the-books chop shop?
- Crack team.
- I'll take that
as a confirmation.
Your COH.
That was a dumbass way
to press for info.
- No it wasn't.
Not when everyone in there
knows you've got their back.
- Yo, are you Billy Cowan?
- That's me.
How can I help you?
- Right here, buddy.
I gotta say, Billy, you do not
look surprised to see us.
He doesn't look surprised,
does he?
- Yeah, well,
that's because he knows
we're not gonna cause a scene.
Unless he doesn't want
to talk to us.
- Not sure how I can help you.
- Oh.
- Well, I think we all know
that there's a few ways
this can go down.
We can search the shop,
talk to people, get loud,
tear this place up
piece by piece, or...
- Or you can give us
something better.
- Trade up.
Name of the game, Billy.
- Who's dropping off
the luxury cars
you're chopping, Billy?
- I don't run
that kind of shop.
- Oh, okay.
5021 Eddie, we're gonna need
an assist
on executing a search warrant,
1432 West 45h--
- Look, I don't know any names,
all right?
- Yeah, no names?
Okay.
- What's that?
- I don't ask people
for their names.
- Billy.
You're trying my patience here.
- She's gonna need a name, man.
- All right.
All right, okay?
He drops off the cars.
I give him the cash same night
and clear them out.
I ain't got any of them here.
- He?
- I really don't know his name.
But I'm not a damn idiot.
I got contingencies
for if something happens.
- Of course you do.
- Our friend Billy
installed his own camera.
Said this is the guy
right here
that comes in
and drops the cars off.
Comes in alone,
drops 'em,
and Billy pays him cash
same day.
- Billy didn't know his ID,
license plate,
any identifying markers, so.
- That's the best shot we got.
- Yeah.
- All right, so we do it
the old-fashioned way.
Farm it off.
Every beat cop, CTA worker,
get every gang and tact unit
across the city.
If someone knows this guy,
that picture's gonna be
enough to spark it.
Hey, you can run it past Mark.
- All right.
- He should be around here.
Hey.
Hank, this is
Detective Tim Powell.
- Hank.
- Powell.
- Are you Officer Adam Ruzek?
I'm with IRT.
I'm taking over your
officer-involved death.
- Why the change in lead?
- Let's talk downstairs.
- Yes, sir.
.
- We did full forensics
at the crime scene.
Found some blood on the wall.
- Huh. Well...
as I stated at the scene,
there was a hell
of an altercation.
So it's possible Rizzo
was injured
before he went over the wall.
- Blood wasn't Rizzo's.
Unidentified profile.
- Huh.
- Just as a reminder,
you said at the scene
that you were not injured.
Photographs we took
confirm that.
- No, I didn't believe so,
but, you know.
It's possible.
- Okay.
So you have no idea
who could have left
the fresh blood at the scene?
- No, sir.
- All right.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- You are gonna talk to me.
- No, I'm not.
You have to stay out of it.
Please.
- I don't care what
we're supposed to do.
What Voight told you.
You have to tell me
what's going on right now.
And don't give me some of this
police loyalty,
blue line brotherhood--
- Stop. Stop.
You think those are things
I just believe in theory?
These are just nice words
I toss around?
- Adam.
Please tell me you didn't do
what I think you did.
Are you insane?
There are a thousand ways
this goes wrong.
A thousand ways you end up
on the wrong end of this.
If IRT came to question you,
that means there's
discrepancies in your story.
You are risking your career.
Jail time.
- I know.
- Your life.
For what?
Some half-assed notion
of loyalty?
- It is not a notion.
It's Antonio.
It's Voight.
It's our unit.
It's our unit...
and I'm gonna protect it
every time.
Every time.
That's who I am.
Why do you have
a problem with that?
- I don't have a problem
with that.
I have a problem with something
happening to you.
- No, you have a problem
with my damn ethics, Hailey.
You always have
had a problem with that
and I'm not gonna talk
about policing with you again--
- Listen! This has nothing
to do with police loyalty.
It has to do with you.
I care about you.
I care about you, and I...
- I could hear you guys
in the stairwell.
What the hell are you doing?
- Nothing. It's fine.
Sorry.
- You cannot be having
this conversation here.
And we're supposed to be out
securing an ID.
[door closes]
[somber music]
♪
[door opens]
- [sighs]
I thought we were done
with this.
- I'm not in the mood
today, all right?
I just need you to look
at a picture.
You know this guy?
- [sighs]
No, I've never seen him.
- You've never seen him.
That's the truth?
- Yeah. Sorry.
I don't know who that is.
- You're such a bad liar.
No, no, no.
Sit down.
- You can't force me to--
- I can if I don't believe you.
Who the hell is he?
Look, I get you don't want
to be here.
I get you don't want
to be doing this.
This is the last time, I swear.
You can't play
by the Canaryville code
on this one, Mark.
All right? This crew?
They beat a woman and then
they shot her twice.
And they left her dead
on the side of the road.
She was 18 years old.
So whatever you got
for this guy,
I don't think
it's got anything on her.
- I thought he was a good guy.
- He's not a good guy.
- Yeah, well, I don't know him
that well.
I don't even know his name.
I just--I've seen him around.
He, uh, he's from out of town.
Indiana, I think.
- Do you know
where he's staying?
- Some vacants off Pershing.
- That helps.
Hey.
Thank you.
- Hey.
- Anything?
- No.
Everyone's saying they've
never seen him before.
Uh, I'm gonna take
the last four houses.
Why don't you meet up
with Atwater and Burgess?
They're still working
Peoria Street.
We should expand the area.
- 2113 squad, we have
an on-view carjacking.
- Hailey!
Turn up your radio!
- Go, 2113.
- Two armed,
masked offenders.
Vehicle is heading
westbound on Harrison.
- 2113, that's
our patrol detail.
- 65 George Ida eight Charlie.
We're in pursuit, victim
is in the car.
Repeat, offenders have taken
the victim with them.
[tires squealing]
- Burgess, we got a carjacking
in progress right now.
Turn on your city-wide.
We're responding.
- Copy that.
- Westbound from Harrison,
in pursuit approaching
California.
- 5021 Henry, we're
plainclothes officers
joining the chase.
- Westbound from Jackson.
Copy, 5021 Henry, 1023.
2113, you have the air.
- Adam!
- 1133 squad, we've got two
units on California.
Mercedes approaching.
[tires squealing]
- Where are you going?
- Mercedes now westbound.
- I got him.
[suspenseful music]
♪
Hailey.
You good?
- Go.
♪
[tires squealing]
[tires screeching]
[gunfire]
- On my door.
- 5021 Ida, we got shots fired
at the police.
[exchanging gunfire]
We got him pinned down
in an alley
off of Jackson
and South Peoria.
- Agh!
- One down!
- One's on the move!
Let's go!
If there's anyone in the car,
open the doors,
keep your hands
where I can see them.
- Help me!
- Ma'am, is there anyone else
in there?
- No! Help!
- All right.
Come with me.
You're okay.
All right.
Come here.
Get behind me.
Just hold onto me, we're gonna
back towards my vehicle, okay?
You'll stay behind me.
You're okay.
It's all over.
.
- She's all right?
- She took a hell of a beating,
but she'll be all right.
Patrol detail rolled up
on the carjacking in progress.
Carjackers just
pushed her inside.
- The offender Upton
shot and killed.
He had an ID on him.
John Crawford.
He's a match
for the chop shop photo.
He lives in Canaryville.
- Hold on.
He's local?
- Yeah, born and raised.
His name pops
in the CHRIS system
right alongside Mark's.
- You gotta be kidding me.
Mark lied to me.
- Just go bring him in.
All right, tell me
we got a bead
on this second carjacker.
- It's in the wind.
We're tapping PODS.
Flooding the zone.
- And notify air one.
Have patrol start
knocking on doors.
This guy ran somewhere.
Let's find him.
- All right.
[soft music]
♪
- Hey.
You okay?
- Yeah.
- Go okay
with the shooting team?
- Yeah.
You can't let him do this.
Not after what happened
to Olinsky.
- I would stop right there.
Whatever this is.
The anger at me.
Difference of opinion.
Emotion getting the best of you
for a guy you're dating.
I would stop.
And walk right back
out that door.
- It's all those things.
And trust me,
I don't want to be here.
I don't want to be
risking my career
for a guy I'm dating.
But here I am.
He has my loyalty,
and I don't know
how to help him.
So I'm asking you.
- Hailey, I'm doing everything
I possibly can to help him.
Everything, but...
But at the end of the day,
it's gonna be his decision.
Not mine.
Not yours.
- Ah. Okay.
All right, all right--
thank you.
- Why in the hell
would you lie to me?
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- Mark, a woman just got
her face beat in
because of your sorry ass.
- I just told you,
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about!
- You don't get to play that!
Not today!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Hey. Sit down, Mark.
Sit down.
Thank you.
That's John's phone.
We pulled it off his body
at the scene
we just responded to.
The last person who called him?
You.
So you wanna try again?
- No.
I'm done now.
- Oh, you're done?
- Did you not hear
what I just said?
- Mark, you don't understand
what's going on here.
You're gonna get charged
unless you talk to us.
Tell us everything
that's going on.
You're gonna get charged.
You're gonna get charged
with your case.
with obstruction of justice.
All of it.
- Mm, no, I'm done.
- Mark, that's hard time.
- I'm not talking
to you anymore.
- Hank.
Can I see you a minute?
- Yeah.
- We've known each other
a long time, you and me.
All right?
- I'm done talking to you.
- Thank you for doing this.
- We don't have
to go through all that.
Trudy asked me
to take over the case.
I'd do anything for her.
But I have no
clear answer for you.
There's no surveillance
footage. No PODS.
We've yet to scrum up
a single witness.
And the blood on the scene's
gonna be a problem.
- COPA's first move will be
to file a search warrant
for Ruzek's blood.
- I know.
And it's not gonna match.
From there it's how far
COPA wants to dig in.
Listen.
File's still open.
I'm on lead.
I'd be willing
to make some changes.
You and Adam come in,
we sit down,
we rework the case,
the evidence.
You both tell me the truth.
We get a new story
on the books.
- I'll talk to Adam.
Thank you.
- Once COPA gets this,
it's out of my hands.
This is the very best I'm gonna
be able to do for you.
- Appreciate it.
- Thanks, Tim.
- This guy can really do that?
- Yeah.
And you're gonna do it.
- It's not that simple.
- Yeah, it is.
Yeah, it is.
Adam, you go to COPA,
I mean, things could go
way wrong.
It's an election year.
COPA ain't gonna be
taking it easy on police.
Just walk it back now.
Say it was me.
- Of course.
- Rizzo reached for your gun.
Listen to me.
I intervened, we got
into a physical altercation.
He went over.
Just put me on the hook.
- If I do that, then you're
standing right where I am.
Antonio's still at risk
of losing his job.
And you're at risk
of losing yours.
And if you go down, Boss,
the entire--
The entire unit goes down.
- I can handle this.
- How?
How could you handle it?
- Adam, if...
if you go to COPA,
I can't guarantee
I can protect you
if things go bad.
There's a price to pay
for this kind of loyalty.
You and I both know that.
I'm asking you
to take my help now.
Adam.
I mean, kid, I'm--I'm...
I'm begging you.
[somber music]
♪
.
- Mark still ain't talking.
Transit team is up,
but investigative alerts
haven't popped anything yet.
- Not much to go on without
a concrete description or ID.
- All right, so look into
every carjacking
within a two-mile radius
from where he ran.
Let's talk to mass transit
again too.
- Mark didn't just call John.
He made another call
a minute later.
To his brother.
This is Tommy Rollins,
Mark's older brother.
He's been in and out of prison
and in and out of Chicago
for the last decade.
His last known address
was in Gary,
but I looked
into his financials.
He used two ATMs
in Canaryville last week.
So he's here.
Tommy grew up six blocks
away from John.
Same elementary school.
- You get this intel
off the street?
- Yeah. I called two contacts.
I gave 'em one name,
they both filled in the other.
Tommy and John run together.
They always have.
- So...
Mark saw John's picture.
Figured his brother
was probably involved.
- He called Tommy to warn him.
- All right, I'll get
an emergency ping
and expedited warrant.
Let's gear up.
- Yeah.
[dramatic music]
♪
- What's going on?
- Ma'am, get back
in the apartment.
Close the door.
♪
- Chicago PD! Tommy, stop!
Hey! Tommy!
[both grunting]
Stop it or I'll shoot you
in the back of the head!
- Little Adam Ruzek
all grown up,
trying to be just like
his daddy.
- Long time no see, Tommy.
Get on the ground.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Get on the ground.
Stop moving, Tommy.
You think I won't shoot you?
- You don't got the balls.
- You want to play with me?
- Do it.
- Get. On. The ground.
- Adam.
Put your hands on your head.
Now get on your knees.
- You'll always be a punk.
[grunting]
- Put your hands
behind your back.
- Look what I found.
- You gonna take
a shot at me, Tommy?
Huh? Pull a gun on me?
- I don't get this.
- Yeah, well, I don't got
to talk to you, man.
- There's no way that you
could have possibly thought
that we weren't gonna catch on.
Do you even talk
to your brother?
- That doesn't matter.
- I mean, Mark,
he's been in jail
more than he's been out, man.
- What are you asking me, Adam?
Pretty easy to forget
where you came from, huh?
I wasn't gonna be the one
to bury him.
- These guys are here
to take you to County.
You're gonna be charged
with your original case
and obstruction of justice.
Sorry, man. There's nothing
I could really do.
- I get it.
- Get up.
- Hey.
I didn't think...
I didn't think this was gonna
turn into anything.
It sorta caught me off guard.
I should have told you.
I'm sorry.
- I get it.
And...
you didn't have
to tell me anything.
We're good.
And we're always gonna be good.
- Sorry to come over like this
and pull you out of bed.
This is all very domestic.
I don't think I've ever
been here before.
- Do you want a tour?
- No.
No, I just...
wanted to ask you a question.
- Yeah.
- You remember my first day
in Intelligence?
Al brought me in.
You were the first person
he introduced me to.
Then Voight.
- I remember.
- Well, I've always
trusted you.
And...
- That's not really
a question, Adam.
- Your buddy Powell.
He's all right?
- You can believe
what he's telling you.
- So I say that...
Rizzo went for my gun,
Voight...
got into an altercation
with him,
defended himself,
Rizzo goes out the window.
- Are you telling me
that's the actual truth?
- I'm just asking
what that truth would do.
- Uh...I think
COPA would...
file a search warrant
for Voight's blood
to match with the profile
on scene.
I think it wouldn't match.
And I think, given Voight's
reputation,
uh, COPA would dig in
with absolutely everything
they had.
- Hmm.
- But I also think
Voight's Voight.
And, um, chances are,
he could find a way
to survive it.
To protect all of you.
That's who he is.
- Yeah.
That first day,
driving into the district...
I asked Al, you know,
there was like, I don't know,
two dozen rookies
in the Academy.
So why'd he pick me?
- Oh, did he even answer you?
- Yeah, he did. He...
he told me he knew.
That I was already his police.
- [sighs]
[soft music]
♪
- We're here to investigate
your behavior
in the incident that occurred
December 5th, 2018.
Specifically any use
of excessive force,
police misconduct,
or any unlawful denial,
deception, or falsehood
in your account.
Is that understood?
- Yes, sir.
- All right, we'll start by
reading aloud your statement
given at the scene to IRT.
- "I was in hot pursuit
of the offender.
"Closed in on him.
"While chasing, I announced
my office several times.
"Ordered him to stop.
"He didn't.
"He was violent.
Non-compliant.
"He lunged for me.
For my weapon.
"In fear of my life,
I had no choice
but to defend myself."
Officer Ruzek.
Can you attest to the validity
of that statement?
- That's accurate, yes.
[wolf howling]