You know, every time we have a day off,
we just end up at O'Malley's.
Even doing the outdoor thing, that place has an aftertaste.
We gotta stop going there.
No, O'Malley's was a necessary evil.
I needed to play darts. I needed to win.
Even though I didn't do any winning whatsoever.
You still got that beer from last weekend?
No. I think I have the awful stout, though.
- That's it? - Yeah.
Yum.
Are you gonna want one of these?
Nope.
All right.
- We still watching that movie? - Yes.
All right. Gimme these legs here.
Okay.
Sorry. I'm so sorry.
I'm really not that sorry, though.
I hate this rug so much.
This is a stupid rug.
My rug would've fit in here much better.
You are never gonna put your ugly rug in my apartment.
I was gonna put my rug in here
and it was gonna be beautiful with the d¨¦cor.
So what's happening right now?
Are you gonna even pretend to clean it up?
Or just--just gonna leave it?
I wasn't even gonna pretend. It's fine. It's just a splash.
It's not a splash. My rug is soaked.
It's a splash.
I'm too comfortable. Come on.
And you're very warm.
You smell like O'Malley's.
So do you.
Like, uh, whiskey and smoke. Winter.
- I like it. - You like it?
Don't we know better than this?
Do we?
If not, we might be insane.
I've been trying to keep the beard a little soft,
so I got this oil.
- Let me feel. - No.
- It's beautiful. - No, no.
Thank you.
So is this part of our relationship now?
We're accepting that every six months or so,
we sleep together?
It'd be real right with me.
Yeah.
Or we could try the version
where we sleep together on the regular.
What version is that?
That would be called dating.
We already act like a couple.
Is it so crazy that we try again?
- Yep. - Why?
Because, uh, I think I know what I want now.
Fine.
I want all of it, Adam.
I want the proposal,
I want getting married in some bad banquet hall,
I wanna have babies, I want the job,
I want the mess, I want the whole thing.
- Kay. - Still wanna talk to me about dating?
Yes.
- No, you don't. - CPD assist requested by CFD.
Traffic accident, Astor and Scott.
Go ahead and answer it.
Pull the ripcord.
5021 Eddie. Two plainclothes officers responding
to CFD's request for backup.
- Will advise once on scene. - Copy that, 5021 Eddie.
Hurry, please.
- Hey, you need help with her? - He ran the intersection!
No, no, she's not why we called for the assist.
It's him. Something's not right.
- Is it a DUI? - I don't know.
Sir, please stay still.
Sir.
No. Those injuries aren't consistent with the crash.
No, none of it's consistent at all with the crash.
Whatever happened happened real recent, though.
Sir, can you look at me? My name's Officer Adam Ruzek.
Can you tell me who did this to you?
No, no, no, no!
I need you to stay still.
I'm okay.
Sir, you may feel fine, but you're not.
I need you to stay right where you are.
There's blood on the outside of the door.
- I am fine! - Hey, hey, buddy--
- You got him? - Yeah.
- You got this guy's name? - Yeah.
BMW's registered to a Jeff Trubin.
No priors, single, lives downtown.
Couldn't get anything. Guy's still unconscious.
Pretty brutal beating.
I mean, happened inside the car,
then maybe somebody dragged him out, beat him some more?
I don't know. Maybe it was a domestic?
Maybe it was a passenger?
This one doesn't really add up.
2261, can I get a direct mobile
to whoever is assigned paper at Astor and Scott?
Think I got a related incident.
Yeah. 5021 Ida.
We're held down at Astor and Scott.
I'm two blocks south from ya.
Got something strange.
Think you might wanna talk to this witness.
We'll take it.
Copy that. We're on the way.
Seems way too coincidental
not to be related to your accident.
He called 911 about 30 minutes ago.
All right. Hey, sir.
I'm Detective Halstead, this is Detective Upton.
Sir, you mind going through it again?
Yeah, sure. So, I was working right over there
and I heard some screaming, so I looked over
and I saw three guys go past wearing masks.
- Masks? - Yeah, ski masks.
They were runnin' like hell.
One of 'em had a crowbar.
Another was tucking something into their waistband.
A gun, I guess.
Then all of a sudden, a gray SUV came up.
They hopped in and sped away.
Then about a minute later, a blue BMW came speeding by.
A blue BMW?
I could see the driver. His face was really bloody.
What about the gray SUV?
Did you get a look at that driver?
- Get the plates? - No, I'm sorry.
All I saw were the kids in the masks
- and the side of the SUV. - Kids?
I mean, I didn't see their faces,
but by the way they're running, the way they were dressed,
the way they were screaming at each other,
I could tell they were kids.
Seemed like teenagers.
Caught a strange one.
The only witness was the guy that called it in.
And the victim?
Blood tox came back negative for drugs and alcohol.
The guy's still unconscious
but Med's gonna contact as soon as we can question him.
Okay, so what do we think happened?
Well, right now, we're betting on a failed carjacking.
Been a 40% increase in carjackings
in that neighborhood this month alone.
Perfect territory.
There's a through line from downtown,
usually pretty void of pedestrians,
meaning there's a hell of a lot of high-end vehicles
on a quiet street.
The victim was driving a $90,000 BMW,
and there was evidence of a beating
inside and outside the car, so they pulled him out.
So a new, young crew tries to jack Jeff's car,
things go wrong-- maybe Jeff fights back
or the kids get spooked.
Crew takes off, hop in their buddy's car
and Jeff tries to drive away.
We got a hit on the offender's car.
Gray SUV was clocked on PODs two blocks away.
Nice. You get an angle on the windows?
Can't see inside or see plates,
but I ran the car through our HOT file.
Gray SUV was reported stolen two months ago
by a Jessica Ramirez. Now, the kicker?
Jessica works at a DCFS center
with kids aging out of the system.
Teenagers.
Okay, that's good.
Why don't you guys check it out?
So your SUV was stolen from here?
Uh, no.
Well, I mean yes, it was,
but I had parked it around back in the lot.
And the kids here have access to it?
Sure. But really, anyone has access.
The lot's open to the street.
What, you really think just anyone took your car?
I don't know.
At this point, I kind of just assumed my car was gone for good.
Right.
Well, Jessica, look.
We're looking for a crew of teenagers
that were involved in what we believe to be
a pretty brutal attempted carjacking,
and they're using your SUV.
So I understand you want to protect these kids, but--
I noticed my spare keys were missing, uh,
after I called the police.
These kids, they have it rough.
I was just trying to give them a moment of peace, but...
my spare keys were in the drawer.
You know who might've taken 'em?
No, but I know the kids who had access.
A lot of names. 13 teenagers.
Be hard to find, too.
Kids that age out notoriously disappear.
Makayla?
Hi! Hi, you!
What are you doing here? What's going on?
- What's happening? - They took me here.
What's she doing here? What's happening?
I'm sorry. Are you...
Officer Kim Burgess.
We worked the Ward homicide case.
What's she doing here? Where's her guardian?
Where's--where's-- where's Kathy?
I'm sorry, I can't lawfully give you any details
of a minor's case without the correct authorization.
Understood, but clearly, I know Makayla,
and--and I know her social worker, Alanah.
You'll have to speak to Alanah, then.
Makayla, honey? Come on.
Hey, can we--
can I--can I--
Real quick. Real quick, Makayla.
Why don't you go talk to this nice lady?
I'll call Alanah,
and then I'm gonna make sure everything is okay, all right?
- I promise. - Okay.
Lot of reasons she could be here.
Yeah, I know.
Alanah's not answering.
Kim and Ruz, you got ears in?
Yeah. Go ahead.
Call came in over the zone.
On-view carjacking, three masked offenders.
Sounds a whole lot like our crew.
Jay and I are around the corner.
Call came from the intersection of Kostner and Wilcox--
Jay!
God damn it!
Help!
Help me!
Chicago PD! Stop!
Chicago PD! Get your hands up!
- Come on! - Come on, come on!
Three masked offenders fleeing on foot.
- Copy that. - It's okay.
It's okay, we got you.
Two of them are armed! They went that way!
Okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Two offenders heading westbound.
One broke off of gangway mid-alley.
Copy. Headed back your way.
Hey, police!
Medics took the victim to Chicago Med.
Had signs of a massive heart attack.
His name's Troy Wrightman, 62 years old.
This is his car.
Married, no children, no priors.
The kids that we saw fleeing--
looks like they were three males and a female.
Ruzek's talking to a witness.
Says he saw two kids rush the car.
Two? What happened to the third?
Don't know. Says he saw two.
Here's what's weird.
The kids ran off, they opened the doors,
they ripped the victim out, they beat him,
- and then they took off running. - So, what,
you guys got here and scared 'em before they can
- actually take the car? - I don't think so.
We got here right as the SUV was about to hit the alley.
Seemed like a getaway car.
You don't need a getaway car for a carjacking.
No.
Guy's pockets were rabbited. No wallet.
Maybe we're looking at a robbery crew.
Hell of a lot of trouble for a wallet.
Yeah. I don't know.
All right. Keep working the scene.
I mean, we got one witness. Maybe there're more.
Dig into this Troy.
Search that SUV top to bottom. Whole thing's evidence.
Yeah.
Thank you, thank you.
- Was that Alanah? - Yeah.
- Everything good? - Yeah, I think so.
I guess Kathy missed some school pickups
so the teacher had to call DCFS,
but now Makayla and Kathy are back together,
and they're offering Kathy extra support, so...
- That's good. - That's good.
Okay, where we at?
I connected with Med.
Our two victims, Jeff and Troy, are conscious,
but they're refusing police help.
They don't wanna talk.
We searched the SUV top to bottom.
We found 2 grand in cash
and six wallets with the IDs in 'em.
Upton and Atwater are chasing that right now.
Car's loaded with stuff.
It's like these are street kids.
They're living in there.
Maybe they use the car when it gets cold out.
Right. So we ran those profiles
of those other robbery victims from the six wallets.
Definitely a pattern.
- They're all men? - Yeah.
Three of the IDs have prior pops for solicitation,
so we ran the crime scenes with that information in mind.
First one is five blocks from a male stroll,
second one is two blocks from a corner Vice recently ID'd.
The kids are prostitutes robbing their johns.
Yeah.
Which makes sense why
our witness only saw two kids rush the car.
The third one was already inside.
They take the job, get into a car, go into a quiet place--
the other kids are there waiting to rush the car.
Explains our 2 grand in cash.
So the kids get tired of touching their johns,
find a new way to make money.
I mean, they're doing this to survive, right?
Well, let's run that DCFS list again with this in mind,
loop in Vice, hit every stroll and corner
young prostitutes frequent, any place street kids crash.
We just took their car and all their cash,
so they gotta know the heat's on 'em.
Let's find these kids before they get more desperate.
This case, the kids, the prostitution...
it's starting to remind me
of the case where we lost the baby.
Yeah.
Do you ever wonder if maybe
that's the reason we're even closer now?
Like, why we want to be together all the time,
why we act like a couple...
because of this terrible thing that happened to us?
Of course it is.
What?
That's not a good thing, Adam.
- Why not? - Because it's not real.
It's not closeness, it's just trauma.
- It's not real? - No.
- Kim, hold on. - Yeah.
You and I, we've always been us, all right?
- Then we were gonna have a baby. - Yeah.
So we fell in love with something together,
then we lost something together.
I mean, sometimes trauma just brings people closer.
Why is that not real?
Excuse me. We're with Chicago PD.
Looking for a few teenagers that might work this spot.
Can you tell me if you recognize any of these folks?
Wouldn't I be in trouble
if I knew there was hooking going on here?
Bro, I'd be impressed if you didn't know
there was hooking going on here.
We can make it harder on you if you don't talk, buddy.
- Him. - Miguel Reyes?
People here don't tell me their names.
When was the last time he was here?
- Now. - Now?
'Less he got a job.
Usually smokes on the corner by himself.
Thanks. I'm gonna circle around the block.
Yeah, sounds good.
Adam, I think I got eyes. Northwest corner.
And I think he's alone.
All right, copy that. I'm on the way.
He's running!
Chicago PD! Stop!
Adam, southbound on Normal Avenue!
Copy you. I'm headed back for you.
Miguel Reyes, put your hands up right now!
That's barbed wire.
Look around you. You got nowhere to go.
Let's go.
Okay, his name is Miguel Reyes, 18.
Just aged out of care two months ago.
Was removed from his home at age seven due to abuse.
History of complex trauma.
He spent the last decade shuffling through groups homes.
Had any priors?
Yeah. He's got one vandalism charge, but that's it.
Social worker said he's a sweet kid.
Just reactive. He's learned to fight back.
No current address, and besides an aunt in Georgia,
he's got no family. The kid's on his own.
Yeah. Let's do this.
All right, Miguel.
I'm gonna explain to you exactly what you're looking at here.
We know you were involved in a string of armed robberies
alongside three other teenagers.
Your last victim, Troy, he had a heart attack.
It almost killed him.
No one killed anybody.
But you're saying you were there?
No, I-I definitely didn't say that.
Miguel, you and your friends--
and they're your friends, right?
Started robbing people
so you wouldn't have to turn tricks anymore.
I can understand that.
But the problem is you robbed these men.
You beat them, you had a gun, you had a crowbar.
That's aggravated robbery with a deadly weapon.
That's decades in jail, okay?
So the best thing that you can do for yourself
and for your friends would be to cooperate with us.
No.
Right.
Miguel...
if you talk to us,
we can explain your story to the state's attorney,
you understand?
We'll tell 'em who you are, who your victims are.
You talk to us, we can help.
I've been helped by people like you my whole life.
I'm sure that's true.
I don't need any more help.
That I don't believe.
I'm not saying I did anything,
but they're not my friends.
They're my family.
So even if I did know something,
I promise I wouldn't ever tell either of you.
You think he knows we got nothing concrete on him?
It is all circumstantial.
We gonna need this boy to talk.
I say we release him.
He said it himself. Those kids are his family.
He's not gonna talk 'cause of them,
but he will go right back to them if he can.
He's got nowhere else.
Okay, so let's release him. Just keep eyes on him.
We'll bring 'em all in.
- Kev. - What's up?
Just--quick question.
What did you need when you were first raising Jordan and Vinessa?
Like, what kind of support did you need?
Everything.
Whole time I was...21. Drowning in it.
Yeah, I needed everything.
Okay, thanks.
I'm sorry to bombard you like this.
- It's okay. - Oh, good.
Okay, great, 'cause I just-- I don't know.
I wanted to let you know that I am here to help
however you need--babysitting, getting help with services,
- whatever you need. - I see my social worker.
I know that, I just--
there can never be too many people, right?
Okay if I say hi to Makayla real quick?
Maybe not the best time.
Sure, of course.
Maybe another time.
I just wanted to know that you're both doing okay.
That's all I--
Kathy, are you okay?
I can't do this anymore.
- What can't you do? - This.
I-I can't be a mom to her.
No, you can. You're doing great, and I'll help you.
I can't do it.
Makayla's with DCFS already.
Kathy, listen to me. You can be her mom.
You're capable, you're so much more than you know--
Just don't. Don't--don't do that.
She is unhappy. I'm not good for her, okay?
I've tried everything.
I take my pills, I go to work,
I see the social worker, everything, and I can't do it.
I understand. I--
My cousin would've never wanted this for her kid.
Makayla was the love of her life.
- She's the love of mine. - Okay, so what if I help you?
What? Who even are you?
I mean, what right have you to be in my home
telling me anything?
- Kathy, please-- - Go.
- Kathy-- - Get out of my house.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
- We lost Miguel. - What?
Kid's a flippin' jackrabbit.
He came straight here after the 21st.
He ducked in and out of,
I don't know, eight alleys, gangways.
I think he squats in one of these buildings on this block.
Yeah.
What's going on? You all right?
Not really.
- I think I made a big mistake-- - Whoa, there he is.
Miguel!
Stop moving.
Are you injured?
Help me. Please, this way.
You gotta tell us what's going on!
Hey, hey, listen! Hey! Slow down! Stop!
Slow down-- we can't help you
if you don't talk to us. Kim.
Run, run! Police! Run!
- Stop, stop! - I'll meet you there!
Get over there! Hands on the wall!
Where'd they go? Where'd they go?
Help her!
Kim, Kim!
- The girl. - Oh, my God.
5021 Ida, emergency. Roll an ambo to 1800 Kedzie.
I'm in a vacant on the west side.
Female down. Head trauma.
Got two male offenders fleeing on foot.
- Copy that. - We didn't do this! We brought her home!
What the hell happened to her?
Ambo en route.
- I don't-- - Miguel!
We needed the money, okay?
We were too nervous to do another robbery,
so she was gonna work a normal job.
- Who was the john? - I don't know.
- Who, Miguel? - He freaked out! He beat her!
- Who, Miguel? Who? - I don't know!
- I need a name, tell me! - I don't know!
House is clear. Where's my ambo?
What's her name? Give me her name.
- Lily. - Okay.
Lily, stay with us, all right?
I'm not leaving you. I won't leave.
- Come on, Lily. - You're gonna be okay.
You're not alone.
Both kids are in the wind, but they won't get far.
All of their belongings, last of their cash,
it's all here.
The girl, Lily, is being rushed to surgery.
Doesn't look good.
We still don't know who beat her?
A john. Ruzek's running the car outside.
It's probably his.
It sounds like the two kids drove Lily here
and then Miguel stopped talking, so that's all I got.
- All right, let's find something. - Yeah.
I found the other two kids' IDs.
Samuel Wilton and Michael Jeffries.
16, 17 years old.
Gun.
Car outside is a rental.
Links back to a Robert McKinney.
62, two priors for solicitation, one for a domestic.
I gotta think he's our john.
- You got an address? - Yeah.
- We got this. - All right.
Talked to Platt--she's gonna send two patrol cars
- to the house now-- - He broke both her cheekbones, her skull.
Take it myself.
Wait, what?
Send me the address. Kim and I are on the way right now.
One gsw, and guessing we're gonna
get some good prints lifted from that bar.
He's also got substantial scratching and bruising
on his face and arms. Signs of a struggle.
We're not sure. Looks like multiple offenders.
We're real close to a stroll. Might've picked someone up.
Lily. He picked Lily up.
Beat her, tried to rape her, and then a friend stepped in.
She's a victim on a case you're working?
No, she's an offender.
I'm gonna go call Voight.
I-is Lily okay?
She's still in surgery.
Miguel, you need to talk to us now.
- Tell me what happened. - No.
- Where are your friends? - I'm not an idiot.
You think I'm gonna tell you that now?
You told me that Lily was gonna do a normal job.
You and your friends were looking out for her,
but she didn't want to do it, so the john got mad,
- beat her, tried to rape her... - Stop.
- You heard screaming... - Stop!
And saved her! Miguel, that is self-defense!
And that is the kind of thing that we can prove!
Not after what we did! We robbed those men!
- We beat them. - I know.
That's what I'm telling you.
But without your friends confirming your story,
without you talking to us,
all I got standing in front of me
is a kid who brutally robs people,
who isn't cooperating,
who told his buddy offenders to run
after you killed a man together.
That's what the state's attorney's gonna see.
Come on, sit down. It's okay, sit.
Miguel.
Son...
You're already going away for the robberies.
I can't help you there.
But the timing matters.
You're a good kid who was dealt a bad hand...
And you played it wrong.
Miguel, you're still young.
This is still your life.
And you're gonna spend the next four decades
staring at concrete if you don't talk to me now.
Come on.
But my friends will have a chance.
- No. - No.
I mean, they won't.
He's telling you the truth
because the chances are we will find them,
and it's a lot harder to claim self-defense once you've run.
And let me tell you:
if they cross state lines, that's it, we can't help them.
You can't guarantee me that you can help now.
I'm all they have. They're all that I've ever had.
I need to help them.
No, you need to help yourself right now.
No, no. I'm not gonna hurt them.
There's a chance you guys don't find them,
that they'll have a shot at something.
I'm done talking to you.
Miguel.
All right, Miguel is not gonna roll on his friends.
So what do we have?
Ballistics did come back
on the 9 millimeter from the shooting at the house,
and it's match for the killing.
Forensics also came back as a match for the SUV.
We got three separate prints on the crowbar.
One of 'em is Miguel's.
All right, what do we have on Michael and Sammie?
Nothing yet.
We're up on buses and train stations.
We've got investigative reports out.
Yeah, I mean, we've been digging,
but they were in foster care for over a decade.
They got no family, no connections to anybody
other than each other. I mean, it's gonna be
tough to pinpoint where they're gonna run to.
We have enough evidence to charge Miguel on all counts.
Okay, so we start processing charges on Miguel.
Maybe once they feel real, it'll scare him into talking.
So that's it?
They're kids.
They were doing this to put a roof over their heads.
They've got these dream houses scribbled in their notebooks.
They're kids with no place to go,
a system that failed them.
Hell, they're robbing their johns,
and the answer is, "They can go to jail"?
That's the best we can do for them?
Look, I get it, but...
they did rob these men.
One of 'em's dead, and Miguel's not talking, so...
unless you got a better play I'm not thinking of...
I don't have another play.
Okay, so keep searching.
Okay?
Miguel's only chance is we find his friends
so they can corroborate his self-defense story.
- Let's go. - Hello?
- You confronted Kathy? - I went to offer help.
But it turned into accusations?
Well, I didn't mean for it to.
She filed a complaint.
Okay, is this--
is this really what we're gonna talk about?
You're Makayla's social worker,
and we're not gonna talk about Makayla?
You want this to have a clean solution.
Yes, I want this to have a solution.
Well, it's way more complicated than that.
It's also way more complicated than you falsely believing
that everyone here isn't doing their very best.
Yeah, well--I'm-- I know, sorry.
Kathy is dealing with mental issues.
Anxiety, depression.
If we keep Makayla in her care,
there's a thousand possible bad outcomes.
Kathy is telling us it's not best for either of them,
so we find an alternate placement.
- A group home? - For right now, yes.
What if Makayla came home with me?
I know you feel for her,
but there are so many ways to be there for a child
without fostering them.
She's a child who's just experienced trauma,
she's a Black child,
you're a cop with a very demanding job
who's white, who's single.
None of this is to be discouraging.
That's all fine,
but these are very real issues you need to think about.
Makayla deserves someone... committed.
It's just--you can't make a decision like this
in a moment when life seems unfair.
- Hey. Anything? - Nothing.
The kids moved last night,
and I don't think we clocked 'em.
Hey, uh, might have them.
Patrol car report of a stolen Chevy downtown around 5 A.M.
POD caught it. Two teenage offenders.
Physicals match Michael and Sammie.
There we go. We got a BOLO on that?
Patrol's actually got it in a truck lot on Ashland--
unoccupied.
That's gotta be them. We'll take it.
There's our Chevy.
Keys are still in the car.
- Hey. - Hey, how you doin'?
Morning. We're with Chicago PD.
We're looking for the two kids that were driving the Chevy
that's parked out front.
You recognize either of these guys?
No. Haven't seem either of them.
Got anybody else working here this morning?
- Just me. - Security cameras?
No. City might have some down the way.
You got none on the lot whatsoever?
No, sorry. Kids do come here to hitch a lot, though.
A lot of trucks move in and out.
Thanks very much.
Listen, I'm gonna go around back.
Yeah.
I'm gonna keep checking, but back looks clear.
Front, too.
We could pull the PODs nearby,
maybe grab whatever semi they hopped into.
We're hours behind them, Adam.
If they're smart, they'll keep switching trucks,
keep hitching.
Already gone.
Nothing on any PODs.
Yeah, nothing on traffic cams,
no security footage.
There's just every reason to believe
they already crossed state lines.
Process Miguel,
get out leads, messages on Michael and Sammie.
Look, chances are some state policeman will pick 'em up soon.
Okay, Miguel.
Patrol will be here in a few, transport you to County.
- What about Lily? - She's still unconscious.
It's too early to know the damage,
but they think there will be some.
- I can let you know. - Okay.
Miguel, when we were in that abandoned house,
when you told Michael and Sammie to run,
you said, "I'll meet you there."
Is "There" where you were gonna build a home together?
Where is "There"?
Your friends ran. They crossed state lines.
I told you before what that would mean,
what their chances would be.
They will be picked up by state police
who are looking for them.
I know you wanna protect them.
That's why you're doing all this.
I do, too.
So tell me, Miguel,
where is "There"?
They're in Iowa.
Yeah, I've got credible information
that our offenders are fleeing to Iowa,
so I've limited the investigative alerts
to your jurisdiction alone.
No, nothing down south.
No, no other BOLOs or alerts needed.
Yeah, Iowa. Thank you.
- You're still here? - Yeah.
I'm just finishing up.
Sorry we can't solve every case and save every kid.
You know, I never told anybody this,
didn't even tell Adam...
but a couple of months after I lost the baby,
I looked up that girl that I saved in the motel room.
Really?
Think I thought it would make me feel something.
Called her mom.
Said she hadn't seen her daughter in months.
She'd run away, and she was gone.
What would you think if I took Makayla in?
I think that would change her life.
I know I'm not her family, I know I'm a cop, I'm white.
I know these are real things.
You're right.
You are not her family and you are white,
so you're gonna be up against a lot.
I think I can do right by her.
Kim, you asked me what I needed before.
It wasn't about me, it was about what they needed.
I had to keep my family together.
Had to make sure that Vinessa and Jordan
didn't get stuck in a system
that I knew they couldn't get out of.
So, yeah, it was impossible.
We did need everything.
I just--
I was theirs...
you know what I'm saying?
I loved them, and that took care of the rest.
And if you got that, you'll be good.
- I was coming to find you. - Yeah?
Hey, do you wanna get some dinner?
Before you say yes, I want to tell you
that I'm gonna turn off our radios as a preemptive strike.
That way, you'll have to talk to me.
Kathy gave up her parental rights.
No. Why?
Because she loves Makayla and wants what's best for her.
- But where's Makayla gonna go? - With me.
Really?
Like, on a temporary basis?
Well, for now, but Alanah's working on it.
There's a lot of red tape, logistics, but it's possible
it could become a more permanent situation.
- Like you fostering her? - Yeah.
- Really? - Yeah.
Okay. Have you thought that through?
I mean, what would that even look like?
- I don't know. - Kim?
Adam, you can say whatever you want to say.
It's not about what I want to say, it's just, I mean--
that's a lot, you know?
You know you can't replace what we lost.
I'm not trying to.
I feel something for this kid. I do.
- I feel close to her. - I understand.
But just yesterday, we're talking about trauma
and you told me how that's not real, right?
Right. Well, what if you're right?
What if it doesn't matter?
I know that this might change what we have,
you know, what we can have.
Kim, that's not why I'm saying any of this.
It's just not.
I'm always gonna be in your life.
That's not gonna change.
It's just this is, like...
I'm a little worried that this is a reaction,
that you just can't stand the idea
of seeing another kid lost.
Hey, you.
So I know all this has been pretty weird, probably, right?
Look, this might be another big, weird change,
but I was thinking, if you're okay with it,
that maybe you could come home with me.
You know, we could be like a family
and take care of each other-- if you're okay with it.
Okay.
Okay, all right, okay.
Just hop on in.
Hmm, this thing.
- You want me to... - Is there--yeah.
Why don't you do it and I'll just--I'll watch.
All right, you're all set.
I'll be seeing you both very soon.
- You guys have fun. - Bye, Alanah.
Just you and me.
Yeah?