.
[bright tones]
‐ Hey, Sarge?
Is here good for this stuff?
‐ Yeah, there's good.
‐ So how long you been
volunteering here?
‐ Eh, since it started.
About six months or so.
They used to build
farm equipment here.
They used to make things
in Chicago.
But then the plants closed
and all those jobs‐‐
‐ Yeah, here we are.
It's great for these guys
though, right?
‐ Yeah.
Man, you wouldn't believe
what we found
when were clearing this out.
Needles, all that.
No wonder the city
gave it to us for free.
But, you know.
Safe space,
place for kids to learn
how to grow things
straight from the ground.
It's a big deal.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
That's ready
when I say it's ready.
‐ Copy that.
‐ Anyway, I want you to help me
to spread some manure.
‐ Aw, crap.
‐ Turkey crap, to be exact.
[static burst]
‐ 22‐21, units on a city‐wide.
‐ Saved by the bell.
‐ We're getting
multiple calls of shots fired
in the area of 4000 Avers,
North Lawndale.
No further at this time.
‐ Four blocks, left on Avers,
couple blocks down.
‐ All right, thanks.
‐ Yeah.
‐ Copy that.
5021 George responding.
[suspenseful music]
5021 George, I'm on scene.
I'm at 4400 Avers.
‐ There.
‐ Okay,
how many gunshots you hear?
‐ Four, maybe five?
‐ You see anybody run out
or anybody with a gun?
‐ No, sir, I heard voices and
then shots and then nothing.
‐ All right,
could you go back inside?
Stay away from the windows.
‐ Okay.
5021 George,
offender possibly still inside.
‐ 10‐4, 5021.
2923 are en route if you
want to stand by for backup.
‐ 5021 George,
I'm going dark.
‐ Copy.
♪ ♪
‐ Come on...
[crying]
‐ Are you okay?
You okay?
All right, listen.
You stay here, don't move.
It's gonna be okay.
All right?
♪ ♪
[baby crying]
Oh, my God.
Hold on, hold on.
Stay behind me.
Come on.
Let's go.
[tense dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ [sobbing]
No, no, no!
No, God, no!
God, please!
Take me!
No, no, please take me!
[sobbing]
[desolate music]
‐ It looks like
a dope hit gone wrong.
Kids weren't
supposed to be inside.
I think the offender
kicked in the door
and he just stumbled across
the kids by mistake.
‐ Covered his tracks.
‐ Yeah.
In the living room
I found the two local kids,
David Tatum and Aaron Powell.
They were both
shot in the head.
Everybody was done
at close range.
A third kid made it.
He's uninjured.
‐ Yeah, they're taking him
to Med to get checked out.
‐ All right,
did he see anything?
‐ He was taking a pee.
He was in the bathroom
the whole time.
That's what saved him.
It's where I found him.
Talked to Patrol,
he said that he heard the shots
but he didn't see anything.
Um...guy guarding the door
is ID'd as Rayford Godfrey.
He's a Hustlers food soldier.
I think he died immediately.
Guys on the corner said that
Ray was soft for the kids,
so he probably just let them in
to play video games.
‐ Are those the bangers
you talked to?
‐ Yeah.
[exhales deeply]
West Side Hustlers.
This is their joint.
It's a stash house, flop house,
et cetera.
‐ Mm.
‐ Shot caller's
around the block.
His name's Kareem.
He's willing to talk to us.
‐ Well,
we're running point on this.
So neighbors, footprints,
barking dogs,
the means, the ends,
we run it all down.
All right.
PODs, Shot Spotters?
‐ Not on the block.
‐ We'll expand the perimeter.
♪ ♪
‐ These people need answers.
We are gonna give 'em to 'em.
♪ ♪
All right, Jay.
‐ Look, knock down doors,
whatever you need to do, okay?
This is real.
‐ Kareem, this is my sergeant,
Hank Voigt.
‐ Never had no sit‐down
with no cop before.
‐ I won't tell a soul.
We need to talk about
what happens now, Kareem.
‐ Man, this is not‐‐
‐ Peace, Pete.
‐ What happened today
typically requires
a certain response from you.
‐ One of those babies
was my nephew.
‐ I'm sorry.
And I can't even imagine
that feeling.
But I need time, Kareem,
to do this by the book.
And that's not for me or you.
It's for this neighborhood.
'Cause we need to be able
to walk back in here
and tell these people,
"We got 'em."
‐ We know what
the alternative is.
That's not gonna
bring those kids back.
‐ Let me ask you something.
You trust me?
‐ I don't know you.
‐ Exactly.
♪ ♪
[chuckles]
You ain't got forever.
‐ I don't need forever.
Wait a second, I'm not done.
This whole thing‐‐
it started out
as a burglary, right?
So we need to treat you
like the victim of a theft.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
When someone gets robbed
we trace the stolen goods
and whoever's got the goods.
‐ Oh, hell no.
[scoffs]
‐ You want me to tell you
what was up
in that stash house?
What was taken?
‐ Stolen.
From your criminal enterprise.
Yes, that's correct.
‐ This is entrapment, man.
‐ I look like I give a damn
about making a drug bust, huh?
♪ ♪
Just give me what I need
to do my job.
All right, here's what we got.
Crystal ketamine,
400 grams packed up in jabs.
Two handguns,
a semiautomatic rifle,
roughly 23 grand in cash.
‐ It's in small bills,
sorted in bundles.
‐ They have any idea
who did it?
‐ No, not yet.
So let's look at rivals,
recently released
violent offenders,
potential anniversary
retributions, all of that.
‐ We're on it.
‐ What do you think
of this guy?
‐ That's the closest
camera angle we got.
In an alley two blocks away,
and it's a minute after 911
got the first shots fired call.
‐ And it looks like
he's running
north towards Homan Square.
‐ Uh‐huh.
You run this guy?
‐ Yeah.
Nothing on facial rec.
‐ That's not nothing.
Kareem said that
the stuff the guy lifted
was in a green
military‐style duffel bag.
‐ All right,
so let's press for an ID.
Canvass the neighborhood.
Talking about Lawndale all
the way up into Homan Square.
I realize
it's a fishing expedition,
but it's what we got for now.
Sir.
‐ Sergeant.
[clears throat]
Hank, this case
is an utter mess.
We got two dead kids.
Heat's already coming down
from City Hall.
‐ We're aware of the urgency,
sir.
‐ Well,
I got a proposition for you.
You know I'm a data guy.
‐ Served you well.
‐ Could serve you well.
Hank, this stuff I'm into,
it's not the competition.
What you do,
boots on the ground,
that is our bread and butter.
All I'm trying to do is
turn the lights on a little
brighter while you do it,
put another tool in your bag.
And we can take that photo,
we can run it through
our new facial rec system.
It's beta.
It'll be off the books
but it is powerful.
And it works, I've got three
arrests already with this thing
and they are airtight.
‐ Yeah, well, my guys already
ran facial rec, no dice.
‐ Yeah‐‐no, this is
a completely different thing.
This is what comes next.
Centralized database.
That's our stuff plus FBI,
State Department, ICE, DMVs.
That is 600 million images
all filtered through
precision biometrics,
locality‐sensitive hashing.
I know it's a lot.
But, Hank,
the ACLU hates this thing.
So do the bad guys.
That tells you
everything you need to know.
‐ This is going
to be the bridge
from mapping faces
to mapping behavior.
We're gonna be able
to read emotions,
whether people are experiencing
joy, fear, jealousy.
‐ Holy crap.
You can read that emotion?
‐ Here he is.
With 99.64% certainty,
Marcus Jerome West, 27.
‐ Can you map 765 Polk?
‐ Okay.
It is a half a mile
from the scene.
That's where he was running to.
‐ Home.
‐ First pinched at 16.
Rap sheet is long.
Drugs, burglary,
gun enhancement.
He's indexed
in the gang database.
Known associate of 312 Orion.
‐ 312.
I believe that's a squat
out in the projects.
It's not our jurisdiction,
but I can confirm that,
Sergeant.
‐ Okay.
‐ Okay, so this guy's
got a lot a long sheet.
Theft, drugs, guns‐‐and
he's a documented gangbanger
affiliated with a crew
that works
in the shadow of the Hustlers
and aspires to bigger things.
‐ That sounds right to me.
‐ Look‐‐I like the gadget,
but it's upside‐down.
I mean,
it's handing us a suspect
before we've got a case.
We got no evidence,
we got no motive.
‐ I just handed you your guy.
‐ This thing isn't even
online yet.
It's not official.
I can't get a warrant.
‐ Hank, it's Chicago
and my brother's a magistrate.
I will get you a warrant.
‐ Sarge,
we got two murdered kids.
Let's go get this guy
before he's in the wind.
‐ All right, so let's do it.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Let me know when to go.
‐ Go.
‐ We're ready.
‐ Move up.
I got West.
He's going out the window!
♪ ♪
‐ There.
5021 Henry, we're in pursuit
of a male black,
tank top, sweats,
westbound 1500 block
of West Polk.
♪ ♪
[sirens wailing]
‐ Stay down!
‐ Spread your arms out!
‐ [shouts]
‐ Stay down, don't move!
‐ 5021 Henry,
offender in custody.
‐ [groans and grunts]
♪ ♪
.
‐ Look at him, Marcus.
Look at him.
‐ I don't got a clue
what you're talking about, man.
‐ Right, right, right.
‐ More importantly,
neither do you.
‐ So you didn't
kill those kids?
But you were two blocks away
60 seconds after it happened?
You're carrying a bag
of drugs, guns, and cash.
And you're running home?
‐ That ain't me, man.
‐ Where'd you stash the bag?
‐ I'm telling you, man.
That ain't me!
‐ No, what you're telling me is
you don't know what you were
doing when this went down.
Where you were,
who you were with.
So if your conscience is clear,
why'd you run?
‐ Why'd I run?
‐ Yeah.
‐ From the cops?
[laughs]
You know, till you said that
I thought we was vibin', man.
Felt like you can
really relate to my life.
Poor black man in Chicago
and all.
‐ Don't go there with me.
‐ Like you would understand.
'Cause you would know.
Poor black man in Chicago‐‐
cops bust your door,
you run.
Whether you did something
or not.
You run until
one of three things happens:
You get caught, you get away,
or you're dead.
♪ ♪
Because this train right here,
it's always on time.
♪ ♪
You call it running.
I call it self‐defense.
♪ ♪
‐ It is with heavy hearts
that we come before the Lord,
praying for direction
and discernment.
The scripture says,
"Weep with those who weep,"
and so here we are,
all together.
These boys belong
to the world now.
Their lives were not wasted.
And because of their sacrifice,
someone is going to get up,
step up, stand up,
and become
a part of the solution.
Amen.
all: Amen.
‐ Listen,
we got a car wash going on
in support of the family,
in support of these boys,
and so please
take advantage of it.
‐ I was wondering if
you could help me out, bud.
‐ Have you guys
seen him before?
‐ You ever seen this cat, man?
‐ No? None of you?
Seen him?
‐ No, sir.
I don't know him.
‐ You sure?
‐ Never seen the dude.
He did it?
‐ So we doing this here?
‐ I'm just paying my respects,
bro.
But yeah, here.
Kids die,
decorum goes out the window.
‐ Look, I'ma be real with you.
Your time is running short.
See all those people in there?
That's a lot of pain.
They need justice.
And a lot of them,
they don't expect it
to come from you;
they expect it to come from me.
So.
‐ All right, hold on a secong.
Why don't we double it, okay?
‐ Long as you understand
you're buying a clean car and
a proper burial for those boys.
You ain't buying no good will
and you ain't buying
no time neither.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ We got 31 hours left to
charge this guy or he walks.
‐ We can't let that happen.
‐ No kidding.
I stuck my neck out
on this thing
and we don't even have a case.
‐ We know this is the guy,
100%.
So just let me go in there,
I'll break him.
I'll get a confession.
‐ Okay, get it done.
‐ All right.
All right.
Get up, Marcus.
‐ Can I go now?
‐ No, it's over.
‐ What's over?
‐ I got three witnesses
that put you on the block.
‐ Man, they're lying!
That ain't me!
‐ Look, I don't think
you meant to kill anybody.
You were dope sick.
You were looking to score.
You stumbled across these kids.
There's only one way
that can go down
and it was probably
the worst day of your life.
‐ No, man!
‐ Look, I wish I could
take that away from you.
I really do.
I wish I could but I can't.
♪ ♪
‐ [sniffles]
I'm a junkie, man.
A tweaker.
Yeah, I've done lots of
stupid stuff to feed my babies.
Lost it all.
More than once.
‐ Yeah.
It's a disease, Marcus.
‐ I ain't no angel
but I ain't no killer either!
♪ ♪
And I ain't gonna
tell you otherwise!
No, sir!
♪ ♪
So you do what you gotta do.
‐ Okay, I will.
♪ ♪
‐ This is a good play.
Some folks,
you keep 'em here
their whole 48, it feels like
somebody's just asking them
a couple of questions.
But you sweat a guy in County,
things change real quick.
[exhales deeply]
Ever since this broke, I can't
stop thinking about those boys.
Playing video games,
just looking for a little fun.
‐ Yeah.
‐ [exhales deeply]
I wish they'd come
to the garden instead.
Maybe I missed them.
‐ Sarge, you can't blame‐‐
‐ Maybe we all did.
Hey, Jay.
Nail this monster, okay?
♪ ♪
‐ This ain't right, man.
You're holding me on a murder
I didn't even do.
You know what comes next,
right?
Word always gets out
in the joint.
‐ You have an alternative.
‐ Like what?
‐If you told me the truth right
now, I'll take you downstate.
Be a lot less heat for you.
‐ I've told you the truth,
every stop!
‐ All set.
Signature here.
‐ Keep an eye on him.
‐ Walk‐in customer.
♪ ♪
‐ You let me know
when you're ready to talk.
‐ It ain't me, man!
I've told you it ain't me!
♪ ♪
.
‐ Oh, yes, sir.
I do understand.
All right,
we've got 11 hours left
to make our case
against Marcus West.
We got him sweating in County
but all we got
is a surveillance photo
from the alley near the house,
which the State's Attorney
is going to toss
because the facial rec system
we used to get it
isn't even on the books yet.
So where are we at
connecting West
to gang activity
in North Lawndale?
‐ We're gonna keep digging,
boss.
‐ Good.
DNA?
‐ The volume's overwhelming.
The whole West Side's
been in and out of that house
for years.
They're shoveling
as fast as they can.
So far, no hairs, no fibers,
no blood
putting West inside that house,
but I'm on top of it.
‐ Have we tossed West's
apartment yet?
‐ Top to bottom.
‐ No cash, no drugs, no dice.
‐ We'll find it.
‐ How about we do what we do,
hmm?
Evidence, motive, means.
Stick to our rules,
build a case.
A witness, a print.
‐ Hank, there's a problem.
Marcus West
was attacked in County.
‐ He was stabbed seven times,
but that's not
the most pressing issue.
His head injuries are so severe
that we had to induce a coma,
shut down brain function.
It was the only way
to minimize the swelling.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
‐ Is he gonna make it?
‐ I think so.
Got what he deserved, though.
Almost.
‐ Do everything you can
for him.
Everything.
♪ ♪
‐ Inmate log from County?
‐ Yup.
Complete with pictures.
Nothing jumps out.
68 of our best and brightest
in lockup with West last night.
You can eliminate
the frat boys from DePaul,
but other than that.
‐ You gotta be kidding me.
♪ ♪
You lied to me, Peter.
‐ How's that?
‐ You told me you didn't know
who Marcus West was.
You know exactly who he is.
‐ Had these
outstanding warrants
for three years now.
Come on, man.
Listen to this BS.
Criminal trespass and
displaying fictitious plates?
‐ So after three years it's
just weighing on you so bad
you just had to
turn yourself in.
‐ Come clean.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
You think you can just
come and check into jail
like it's a motel
so you can get to Marcus West?
‐ Something happen to him
in here?
‐ Yeah, something happened.
♪ ♪
‐ Huh?
‐ Sergeant, Marcus West
is in really bad shape.
‐ All right,
anything from County?
‐ No, Ruzek's
interviewing guys inside.
Nobody's talking.
Sarge?
Did I‐‐
‐ Did you what?
‐ I just wanted
to make the case so damn bad.
Did I go too far?
‐ Hey, we got two dead kids
and a city that needs answers.
We're on the clock
and dying on the vine.
‐ That's why I jammed him up.
‐ Yeah.
Listen to me‐‐hey.
You are a good cop
with a good heart.
It was the right play,
you hear me?
Right now we gotta make a case
against Marcus West
before he wakes up
and it has to be tight.
Come on.
Hey.
See if Patrol missed anything.
I want you to scrub this case
from the top, you hear me?
Start with
talking to the kid again.
‐ Yep.
‐ Hey, give me something.
‐ Well‐‐
[exhales deeply]
we pulled the supporting docs
from the gang database listing
and there are a couple things
that labeled West as a 312.
He's friends with this cat
named Reuben Jones
who lives over in Orion Courts
and the gang database had
this picture from Instagram.
It showed Marcus and Reuben
throwing up the same sign.
‐ Orion Courts
is only a half mile
from the heart
of the Hustler's turf.
They get bigfooted
around the Hustlers every day.
‐ Reuben Jones'
most recent offense
was for moving ketamine.
‐ And as you know, Sarge,
it's the same drugs stolen
during the murders.
♪ ♪
‐ So this whole thing
could be 312 Orion
planting a flag
trying to get in the game.
‐ Right.
Yeah.
‐ All right,
let's run it down.
‐ Right.
♪ ♪
‐ How you doing?
‐ Hey.
‐ Reuben Jones?
‐ Oh, who that?
‐ Chicago PD.
[dramatic music]
Now, I ain't come here
to arrest you, dog.
Hey!
♪ ♪
‐ [grunts]
Get up!
Run again!
‐ Don't do that.
That's not a good idea.
I told you
I wasn't going to arrest you
but you want to
do it the hard way.
You got cuffs?
‐ Yeah.
‐ Hey, get yo' ass up.
‐ The street life
take discipline.
This wasn't never
gonna be life for Marcus.
Marcus is a user
and he steals.
And on top of all that,
he ain't even good at it.
‐ So if Marcus West
isn't in the gang,
how do you know him?
‐ We grew up together.
You know, trick or treating,
birthday parties,
little league.
Garfield Park Green Dragons.
Y'all ain't never heard of us?
‐ Nuh‐uh.
We saw you, though.
‐ Bro, y'all trippin'.
Y'all know where we at.
Man, that's Orion Courts.
It ain't no gang thing.
It's a neighborhood thing.
‐ Okay, talk to me.
‐ All right,
bro moved away a few years ago
when his mom's passed.
But he always around.
You know the main reason why,
though?
A/C.
We got it, he don't.
Man, when it get hot,
he always around.
Matter of fact,
I just seen him the other day.
He was over there passed out
snoring on the couch
like a chainsaw.
Probably hit that weed,
had him out like a light.
‐ Wait.
What day was that?
‐ Hmm.
‐ He's been through so much.
He just went through this
with the officers.
‐ I know, but not like this.
We need to go over everything
in detail.
Any little bit of information
can change everything for us.
‐ This is a chance
for Noah to be a hero.
‐ I can do it.
‐ Hey, Noah.
I'm Kim.
I was just reading what you
told the Patrol officers.
Let's start from where you
went into the bathroom, okay?
Okay.
So you go inside
and you close the door
'cause that's what you do
when you pee, right?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Okay.
‐ And that's when you heard
the bad guy
kick in the front door, right?
‐ No.
‐ What do you mean, no?
‐ So the kid did hear
the door get kicked in.
‐ Yeah, but not until after.
‐ After he heard the gunshots.
‐ If the guy's
already in the house,
why did he kick the door in?
‐ Because he let himself in.
Look, he popped the guy
watching the place.
Stumbled on the kids who
weren't supposed to be there.
He kicked in the door
on the way out.
‐ For show.
‐ Make it look like a break‐in.
‐ If this was an inside job,
are we saying
we got the wrong guy?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
‐ Look, whoever did do this,
we know he knew those kids
and those kids knew him.
So he's probably in the
Hustlers and close to Kareem.
‐ Got something, Sarge.
POD footage from Orion Courts
the day of.
‐ We got Marcus West
walking to his buddy's house.
‐ And he's still in there
at 3:00 p. m.
♪ ♪
‐ Yeah, Marcus West.
‐ Why wouldn't he
just say he's there?
‐ He was doped up, Sarge.
‐ And probably
protecting his buddy.
I mean, Reuben Jones has
a couple outstanding warrants.
‐ Oh, my God.
‐ Jay.
He's gone.
Marcus West.
He didn't make it.
He's dead.
♪ ♪
.
‐ Come on.
Your fancy software‐‐
it didn't work, Derek.
You gave us the name
Marcus West.
‐ With 99.64% certainty.
‐ He wasn't the guy?
‐ No, he wasn't the guy.
‐ Sorry about that.
‐ Sorry?
‐ I told Crawford
this thing's still a year out.
Six months, maybe.
We're still running the code,
algorithms.
And sometimes
this kind of thing happens.
You get false positives.
It's rare but it happens.
Mostly to black people.
‐ What?
‐ The code was written
by white engineers
who designed it around
predominantly white
facial features
and tested it
on their white friends,
so it's less precise
if you're black.
And here's the really bad part.
Darker your skin,
worse the problem gets.
‐ You don't think that would've
been useful information for us
before we go and use it
on a dark‐skinned black man?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Marcus West
didn't kill those little boys?
‐ We think
the killer's an insider.
Remember the Hustlers?
‐ All right,
let me get this straight.
You drag West in,
you interrogate him,
you don't have
enough evidence to charge,
but you book him
into County anyway.
‐ Detective Halstead
was convinced
he killed those two boys.
So yeah, we held him
for the full 48 hours.
‐ So why book him into County?
Why not hold him
at the 21st District?
‐ Come on.
We do that all the time.
As you know,
County's got a way of...
encouraging people to confess.
‐ Oh, yeah?
But I assume
all the other times
an innocent man
didn't end up dead?
An innocent black man?
Jesus Christ.
All right, I‐‐
I'm gonna shoot straight
with you here, Hank.
The optics on this,
not so good.
White cop playing cowboy
jams up an innocent black man,
throws him into County
for a crime he did not commit,
and‐‐
I mean, someone's gonna
pay the tab on this.
I mean, my money's on Halstead.
‐ Really?
That's funny,
'cause my money's on you.
You're the one who told us
to rely on
this fancy computer program
that gave us the wrong guy.
I mean, you staked your claim
on a technology that's no good
at identifying black people.
That's on you, not Halstead.
♪ ♪
‐ Well, I'd say we're all
in a pretty bad place, Hank.
I mean, you're gonna
apprehend the real killer
and then everybody's gonna know
that an innocent man is dead
and they're gonna want
heads on pikes.
Let me ask you a question.
I mean, you got a play here?
♪ ♪
‐ All right, it's not Kareem.
He's the boss, he's not
gonna steal from himself,
plus one of these dead kids
is his nephew.
‐ Right.
Okay, so then
that leaves these four.
They're the only ones who knew
where the drugs and cash
were being held right?
‐ Right.
‐ So which one of them
is cold‐blooded enough
to murder two little kids?
‐ That guy.
"Prophet."
Every step, he's been
throwing up road blocks
trying to keep us
from the truth.
First time we met, he told
Kareem not to talk to us,
said we're
trying to entrap him,
even though it's
their people got killed.
That's my gut, anyway.
‐ All right.
Well, how do we prove it?
♪ ♪
‐ We know your boy
Peter Dupree killed Marcus West
in lockup.
‐ And I told you from the
start‐‐I got people in pain,
hungry for action, grown men
with minds of they own.
‐ All those dudes in lockup,
it's hard to imagine
no one saw anything.
‐ Miracles.
They do happen.
‐ Yep.
That they do.
Here's the thing, though.
Marcus West didn't do it.
I just wanted to let you know
as a courtesy.
And we are still on it.
And we are getting close.
[cell phone chimes]
‐ I appreciate the info.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Yeah.
Uh‐huh.
‐ Walk with me.
Listen, I didn't want to
lay this on the big man but...
we've been doing some thinking.
I mean‐‐
[scoffs]
I mean, who kills a kid, right?
I mean, even in our world.
There's only one reason someone
kills those kids in there.
It's cause they
know who you are.
I mean, you don't think
any of your boys
do something like this, do you?
Someone from your gang?
[suspenseful music]
‐ No way.
We like family.
‐ Oh.
Well‐‐
it's a theory
and we gotta run it down, okay?
So I'm coming to you man‐to‐man
and I'm telling you, we are
gonna be knocking on some doors
and I want
to knock on yours first.
Listen‐‐
I just want you to show
your boys how to act, okay?
There's no show.
There's no guns,
no kicking in doors.
So just be polite, okay?
Just be part of this.
I mean,
we want the same thing, right?
Then we'll be out of your hair.
♪ ♪
‐ No problem, man.
Partners.
♪ ♪
‐ Okay, Prophet's inside
221 South Tripp.
Assessor's office has the owner
listed as Olivia Jackson.
‐ That's the same last name.
‐ Yeah.
Hold on,
I've got LexisNexis cooking.
Bingo.
This is his sister's house.
‐ Here he comes.
Prophet's coming out.
♪ ♪
‐ Hey, he's got the bag.
‐ He's on the move.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
‐ Yeah, he's coming our way.
♪ ♪
‐ Everybody sit tight.
‐ Sarge,
we can end this right now.
‐ I said stand down.
♪ ♪
‐ All right,
he said stand down.
♪ ♪
‐ Street's clear.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
‐ It's all here.
We got it.
♪ ♪
.
‐ Appreciate it.
‐ We found the real killer.
‐ Good.
And not good.
So was it an inside job?
‐ Number two guy
in the Hustlers.
Named Randolph Jackson,
goes by Prophet.
Got him dead to rights.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
‐ So how do we do this?
‐ Well...
Not exactly what they teach you
in the academy,
but it's a way out.
♪ ♪
For all of us.
‐ [clears throat]
♪ ♪
‐ You alone?
‐ This ain't that movie.
♪ ♪
Easy.
‐ What's this?
You punking me?
♪ ♪
How the hell
did you get this?
‐ I stole it.
‐ You stole it?
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ From where?
‐ Prophet.
‐ Prophet?
‐ All I know is I saw Prophet
carrying your bag of belongings
from his sister's house.
Stashed it in some car
near an alley.
You ask me,
I think Prophet
ordered that hit
on Marcus West at County, too.
♪ ♪
So I think about now
you gotta ask yourself...
♪ ♪
Is he capable of killing
two nine‐year‐old boys?
♪ ♪
‐ So what happens to Prophet?
‐ That's your business,
isn't it?
♪ ♪
You trust me now?
‐ What's up, man?
‐ What up, Prophet?
‐ Hey, hey‐‐
[grunts]
♪ ♪
‐ We have identified
the man responsible
for the execution‐style
killing
of three people
in North Lawndale,
including
two nine‐year‐old boys.
♪ ♪
Perpetrator
has been identified as
Marcus West.
Mr. West had an extensive
criminal record.
Multiple counts of burglaries,
narcotics, weapons.
And he was located
through the use
of a cutting‐edge
facial recognition system,
one we hope to take city‐wide
in the next year
after some fine tuning.
Data‐driven policing.
It works.
And it works in a way
that the people of this
great city can believe in.
Now, after he was
taken into custody,
Mr. West was assaulted
by rival gang members.
He was placed into
a medically‐induced coma,
and, despite the dedicated work
of medical professionals,
he succumbed to his injuries
and he has been
pronounced dead.
He was 27 years old.
The CPD is confident
in its information
and in this investigation.
And this case
is considered closed.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
‐ Did you do
what I think you did?
♪ ♪
‐ Jay‐‐
for once in your life,
just let it be.
♪ ♪
.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[wolf howls]