I stand by my original statement.
Officer Doyle had no probable cause.
Atwater snitched on the police.
Every time I see a cop, I get nervous.
He's gotta pay the price.
Blue Wall is a tricky thing.
- Step out of the vehicle. - Look, I'm police.
Is this really what you want to do?
Black man?
It's gotta stop now before someone gets hurt.
You--you kidding me? You know it's 6:00 A.M.?
Yeah, I got work in the field.
What even is all this?
A new security system.
Cameras on every door,
sensors all over the house.
Right. What?
Maybe the beatdown was the end of it?
- Or the beginning. - Look, bro, come on.
Maybe the white cops will finally realize
that they're the racist pricks
on the wrong end of a revolution.
Revolutions ain't ever that fast, Jordan.
I'm not gonna be driving my car so much.
What else do you think they're gonna do to your car?
If anybody's here that shouldn't be, you let me know.
Clean this up, all right?
You good, Kev?
Yeah...
- I think they locked me out. - Meaning?
The system's not letting me in.
My radio doesn't work.
I don't have any access.
What happened?
They jumped me.
Did you see their faces?
Their faces were covered. There were no cameras.
They didn't say a word. They were smart.
- Okay, let me find them- - You can't go to IAD.
I'm guessing they've already got an open case on me.
Nolan has men inside, so we can't trust that.
And I have absolutely nothing on them still.
Which is why I'd go elsewhere.
I appreciate that,
but this is what we knew was coming.
Kev, there are ways--
Sarge, we already talked about this.
And I already talked to the team.
I can handle them. I'm good.
Okay.
Well, come on. We caught a case.
Sergeant Voight.
911 call came in about eight minutes ago.
- What was the call? - Injured female.
A male caller reporting his friend hurt.
Patrol arrived, entered, found a deceased female.
- Okay. - Male caller inside with her.
Sir, the male inside is Billy Braddem.
- As in Alderman Braddem? - It's his son.
- The ex-cop, right? - Yup.
- Talk to me. - She was already stiff.
Died hours ago. Probably around 2:00 A.M.
Kid won't move. He's high out of his mind.
You want us to help her, you need to let her go.
- Found him like this? - Yeah.
Listen to me...
- Or I'll have to remove you. - I got it, we got it.
- Kev. - She needs help.
I can hear her breathing.
Hey. Billy, I'm Kev. Can you look at me?
She's breathing.
I can hear her too. I can hear her.
I'm gonna step closer so I can hear her better,
but I need you to let her go.
Here. Set the knife down.
We wanna help her.
So just put the knife down.
You gotta work with us.
Billy, listen to me. Just like that.
there you go. There you go.
Yeah, we're good.
All right? We just wanna help her.
- We're gonna help her. - I love her, I love--
Come on, okay, okay.
Please help her, please.
The victim's IDed as Isla Sherman,
18 years of age.
She's got a few priors for drug possession as a juvie,
but other than that, I mean, she's a bit of a ghost.
It looks like she was an addict.
No LKAs in years other than the place that she died.
- You locate the family? - Yeah.
I tracked her mom down to Arizona.
She was surprised Isla was still alive actually.
Written her off as dead a long time ago.
- Won't be claiming the body. - And what about Billy?
Oh, with him, I had to do some digging.
Alderman Braddem never mentions Billy in his stump speeches.
Kid's never one of the sons
standing behind him at the podium.
He's got no public traces.
I did find him logged as a patient
at more than a dozen rehabs, though.
Yeah, his school records are a mess.
I mean, this kid's been in and out of a different school
every year since he was 14.
So we think Braddem kicked him out of the house?
Yeah, I mean, that would be my guess.
I can't figure out his relationship to Isla, though.
Friends, boyfriend, maybe they just use together?
I'm scouring social media--
She's been waiting for you for over an hour.
We're halfway to that being her permanent office,
so could you, please?
Yeah, I'm back.
Deputy.
Have you got any baking soda in your office?
I don't.
- One of those stain pens? - Sorry.
That's a shame.
I read your crime scene report--
You wanna know if I know the Alderman?
I'm just guessing where this is headed.
The answer's no, I've never met Alderman Braddem.
Okay, because this is one of those instances
where CPD must enact equality in law enforcement.
Sure.
Meaning absolutely zero Blue Wall
or preferential treatment for an Alderman's son.
Yeah, lucky I never met the man.
- I won't be protecting his son. - Okay, great.
And I'm still gonna ask you to press murder charges ASAP.
You know, questioning an offender who's not coherent--
Is better than affording an offender
an extra 12 hours before questioning.
- To get sober. - Or to rehearse.
Look. We're gonna treat his kid like any other offender.
You take his blood, you document his tox,
question him, and charge.
Asap.
You know, we don't have to go 12 rounds every time.
I'm gonna give you an order. That's my job.
But we can be nice.
Can you see this?
I can.
Is it see-through?
It is.
Okay. Deputy Miller.
Hey, Billy.
Billy, look at me.
Look at me.
I'm Sergeant Hank Voight with the CPD.
Hey, Billy.
Do you remember me? We were just downstairs.
We just talked.
Boy, this kid's got no short-term memory whatsoever.
I don't even think he knows where he is.
Billy, do you know why you're here?
Isla?
- Where is she? - She's dead.
Can you tell us what happened to her?
Hey, Billy.
Billy!
The way we found you with the knife,
this is a bad situation, do you understand?
- Do you think I killed her? - I do.
All right, this death looks like
what we call a crime of passion, Billy.
Like a fight broke out, something went wrong,
a knife was grabbed from the kitchen.
I didn't kill her. The--the man killed her.
Okay, the man. What man?
The man in the apartment. He killed her.
- Who was he? - I don't know.
Can you describe what he looked like?
He was white.
He was in his 40s. He...had green eyes.
He was wearing a suit. White shirt.
Blue tie with red stripes on it.
He had this voice like...
It was really light.
And like he was telling a story.
Like he knew what he wanted to say, and...
You ever seen this man before?
Can I see Isla?
She's dead, Billy.
I just wanna see her again.
Please, just...
tell me where you put her.
You ever hear a suspect description that detailed?
No. Maybe it's the high talking.
That detailed?
Or telling his own story.
I just feel like you gotta be some amount of "Here"
to come up with that, and whether it's true or not,
it seems like he believes it.
And he asked to see the body.
That's not normal offender behavior.
Addicts' behavior doesn't always
match their truth, though.
They know how to lie.
I suppose he could be feeding us a fake suspect.
I don't know.
And we're not gonna know more until he's sober.
Well, he gave us another suspect.
Let's run it.
You really wanna wait to charge?
Until we know he's guilty, yeah.
There's really nothing that would indicate
there was a third person in the apartment.
We got two sets of takeout
and beers surrounding two chairs.
- Two sets of the works. - Not much here.
This place is tiny.
I know, I really don't see
how somebody could be hiding out.
And the blood splatter indicates just one offender.
TV was on at the time of death.
Yeah, Forensics hasn't dusted this room yet.
They are expected to rise based on positive...
We just wanted to circle back,
make sure Patrol didn't miss anything.
You see anything unusual? Any visitors?
- The car was unusual. - A car?
All right. What car is that?
I don't know. It looked blue, maybe?
2:00 A.M., it just sat out there wasting gas.
Headlights blaring through my window.
Did you see anyone in the car,
or anyone enter or exit the apartment?
No, just the car. I took my dog out.
By the time I came back, it sped away,
but it sat out there 20 minutes.
Why didn't you mention this to Patrol?
No Patrol ever came by. I've been home all day.
Nobody's talked to me.
She died, didn't she?
- That young girl? - Yes, ma'am.
She seemed like a good person.
Seemed like she tried real hard to be happy.
I don't understand. Where is my son?
- Sir, your son's upstairs. - Upstairs.
You've got him in a box? You found him high?
Yes, sir. He was high.
You're questioning my son without a lawyer
while he's high.
Are you kidding me?
Why the hell is he upstairs without a lawyer?
- Listen, I'm happy to talk-- - I am gonna have your badge.
- I'm just doing my job. - You won't be for much longer.
I will tear you apart in front of the media.
And I know who you are. I know how you police.
Alderman Braddem.
Deputy Superintendent Miller.
I want to see my kid. I need to be in there.
And I will help you do that, just not in the hallway
and not while raising our voices.
Right this way.
I'll speak to you upstairs.
McKenzie, you just came here to watch?
That was clearly leaked to Alderman.
Well, it doesn't matter how. We're here now.
Tell me we got something.
I confirmed a blue Sedan outside Isla's apartment
around the time of death.
Caught it coming and going.
Matches the witness' time frame,
but there's no POD outside of Isla's.
So the car turns into her block,
I lose it, and I catch it leaving 20 minutes later.
So we can't confirm the plates
or that it was even outside of Isla's.
It's possible somebody exited the car,
went into the apartment, but we have zero way to prove that.
- Hey, I think I got something. - Okay.
TV was on in Isla's apartment last night,
so I followed a feeling, and this was playing
during the time of death.
Was first indicated in the city's loop, and has--
White male, 40s. Grey hair, green eyes.
Blue and red tie. Suit.
And a voice like he's telling a story.
Can happen during trauma.
Brain's wires get crossed, latches onto the wrong thing.
I don't think Billy has any idea what's real.
Over 12 hours on an open and shut scene,
and now we've got an ex-cop Alderman
in the 21st, meeting with his son's investigator.
- You disobeyed a direct order. - Because it wasn't real.
If I give you an order, it's real.
No, not if you don't tell me why you're giving it to me.
That kid was found holding the murder weapon
- laying next to the dead girl. - I'm aware.
And yet, you haven't charged him.
What if that kid in there were Black?
Would you be ordering me to charge ASAP?
'Cause I think if that were an 18-year-old Black kid in there
with no rich family, no politician father,
you wouldn't be pressing me to charge
until I had the whole of it,
until it felt right.
But he's white, he's privileged,
and you're damn scared the media's gonna
hand you your ass your first month of work.
I don't care who his father is.
You do.
All right.
You take the full 48 if you need to.
I'll make sure you can have it.
No.
No, it's not possible. It was real.
I-I know I was screwed up, okay?
But--but I'm clear now.
Maybe...maybe it wasn't this man.
- Fine, but someone was there. - Billy.
Are you sober now?
Okay, understand this. We got about 32 hours
till we have to either charge or release you.
I didn't do this!
That, I don't know. What I do know is
your father and your lawyer are downstairs right now,
and I'm obligated to bring your lawyer up here.
My dad's here?
And he brought his whole team of lawyers?
He thinks I did this.
No. No, you know what? I...
I don't want his lawyers.
I don't want his help. Go ahead. I-
I know there's a form I can sign.
You're declining representation?
Yes.
I don't know what happened.
I don't remember, but I didn't kill Isla.
So go ahead.
Ask me whatever you want.
The first time Billy entered rehab
was a month shy of his 14th birthday.
My dad, he--he wanted to help me, fix me.
Rehab, military schools,
religious camps,
some shaman that tried to starve it out of me,
but none of it worked.
Then I met Isla at a meeting.
And unfortunately, Isla didn't have
the money or the father that Billy had.
No rehab--just possession charges, shelters.
She was totally alone in all this.
Isla quit going to meetings.
You know, she thought she was good.
For some reason, she thought I was good too.
That we could do it together.
Just her and I.
We tried.
And it worked.
- So you were sober until-- - Last night.
We had a year.
It's hard to confirm sobriety,
but it does look like Isla's life changed.
So this is her before.
She seems to have a pretty small circle of friends.
Most of her posts are about drugs and parties.
And then, right around the time that Billy says they met,
a new set of friends, lots of photos.
She looks happy.
Also around that time, she opens a bank account.
Gets a job, the apartment.
I think they really did change each other.
Now take me through it one more time.
- Last night... - Isla texted me.
She said she was bad.
That's all. I knew what she meant.
It's what we would do if we felt like we were coming apart,
itching to use.
We'd talk each other off the ledge.
She asked you over?
All right, so we're still running towers,
but it looks like Isla texted Billy at 6:45.
He called her back two minutes later.
- Arrived at her place at 8:00. - And they were alone?
According to Billy, nobody else in the apartment.
Just Isla and the drugs.
She already had the heroin on her?
Yeah, she had a black duffel bag.
Dope was already out of it.
Then we used.
We drank.
A year of sobriety gone in a second.
And then, I can't really remember it all from there.
I know we were together in the kitchen.
Okay.
And then, I was in the bedroom.
I woke up to voices.
Someone was mad at her. A man.
- I could see someone there. - Okay, what were they saying?
I don't know. I just...
I woke up again.
She was on the ground, wet and bloody.
I-I tried to help her.
I think I pulled the knife out.
Once he's high, we can't confirm any of it.
There's no black duffel bag at the scene.
No reports from neighbors hearing any arguing,
no signs of forced entry.
Right, so what about the knife?
If he pulled it, Forensics should be able to confirm it.
No, we're dead there.
Forensics ruled the knife inconclusive.
Blood and prints were contaminated.
So what else we got?
Not much.
We can't confirm anyone was inside the apartment besides Billy.
Here's an odd thing, I ran Isla's cell phone.
Everything matches with Billy's story,
except for when she texted him to tell him she felt bad,
she was all the way out in Lake Forest.
Lake Forest? She has connections out there?
Billy never mentioned anything,
but the phone tagged her location.
- She was definitely there. - All right.
Good. Let's run with that.
Go. Come on.
I'm so sorry. Nobody was here.
I don't even know anybody named Isla.
Okay.
Well, have you seen any cars in the area since yesterday?
- Anything unusual? - No.
This place is pretty much the definition of ordinary.
I'm sorry.
What's with this hidden camera here?
It's probably just a kid's toy, or--
No.
- It's a hidden security system. - I just rent the property.
Hadley, you're gonna stay down here with me.
Come on.
You smell that?
Acetone.
What you got?
Clear.
5021I
5021 Ida,
I got a confirmation on my narcotics call.
Gonna need backup and Forensics
- to 163 North Sheridan. - Copy that...
About a million dollars worth.
I'd say.
Jordan?
Jordan.
Jordan, why are you calling me from the landline?
What?
Our security alarm just went off.
- All right, well, go. - Are you sure?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. - Jordan, I'm on my way.
Jordan, where you at?
They said it's probably tripped.
- Let me see your phone. - What, why?
You said that it was burning hot
and that the battery was dying, right?
They bugged you.
Bugged?
There's static on this line too.
They bugged both phones.
- Who bugged us? - Shh.
What?
The cops.
- Give me your phone. - What?
- They ain't bugging me, man. - Give me your phone.
They ain't bugging me. Okay, okay.
All right, all right, all right.
- Stop, man, stop. - Sorry, Jordan, but they were in here.
They've been playing with me all day.
I know what's going on-- know what's going on...
Kev, security said this happens all the time.
I know exactly what's going on. They're cops.
You don't think I know what they're doing?
Kev, Kev!
They were in here. They were in here.
I know what they do. I know what's going on.
I know what they do.
- What's up? - Look,
they accessed the side window.
And I don't have a direct image,
but I do have a partial on this black SUV.
Can't tell whether this is a cop car or not,
and I can't make out this guy's face.
Well, we could add more cameras.
Man, they gotta be feeding this to IAD,
trying to find some dirt.
They're working every angle, ain't they?
Hey, Kev, maybe...
we need to find a way out of this thing now.
What you mean?
Nolan and McKenzie are third generation police.
I mean, there's gotta be some sort of deal that they'd take.
- Oh, and you talked to Voight? - No.
Your dad?
My dad? What the hell would I talk to my dad for?
Third generation. Ain't this what y'all do?
Kev, they are coming after you, okay?
If there's something that we can give them--
Huh, give them? I'm not giving them anything.
I did nothing wrong.
I told the truth. They jumped me.
Four against one. Kicked my head in.
Then broke into my house, where I live, where my family lives.
We still got a case. Still got a clock.
- Get anything on Hadley? - No.
She claims she's never been in the basement before,
doesn't even have a key.
It's all a lie, of course.
She knows exactly who the drugs belong to.
She lawyered up.
Bag house is on bad paper.
The owner registered it to a bogus LLC.
All right, so me and Kev are gonna run all that past Billy.
Meantime, you get Hadley into holding.
Who is she?
I don't know, okay?
I don't know this woman.
I've never seen her!
I-I told you everything I can remember.
You're telling me you can't prove it.
Did Isla ever mention a Hadley?
Ever tell you where she scored her drugs?
I've told you everything I can remember.
- I can't-- - Hey, Billy.
Billy, I know you're feeling the pressure right now.
All right, because we are running out of time--
You think I don't wanna remember?
Okay, well, just calm down.
Okay, you can take this. You can handle it.
My body feels terrible.
I-I feel like I'm losing my mind.
I know, but this is where you fight, okay?
This is where you fight, okay?
Okay? All right, all right, all right.
Now, you don't know Hadley. That's fine.
What about the drugs?
What about the heroin?
- The tag. - Okay.
- The tag. - The insignia?
- Yeah. - Okay, what about it?
Yeah.
These bags of dope, they were in the black bag.
She had a lot of them.
Wait, you're saying that she had
more than just a few grams?
Yeah, the black bag was full of these bags.
Guys, I made a connection. Check this out.
This is Tim Rollins. He's 36 years old.
He's got a history of violence, two priors for drug possession
with intent to distribute in Indiana.
Now, Hadley has calls, Venmo requests,
and social media hits with this guy.
So does Isla.
And her social media is loaded with pictures
of the two of them right up until when she met Billy.
Ex-boyfriend. The drugs are definitely his.
Isla knew it. She was itching.
She went back. She stole the drugs.
Bring him in.
Blue Sedan.
It's been cleaned. Bleach.
Jay, Hailey.
We dropped an anchor on Tim's place.
We got a blue Sedan freshly scrubbed down.
It's the exact match to the car
idling outside Isla's apartment.
Copy that. We're nine minutes out.
We'll hold anchor until you arrive.
Tim Rollins.
Stop!
Chicago PD!
- I'ma go around the back! - Copy.
5021 Ida in foot pursuit. Westbound alley towards Bell.
Offender is male, white. 6'2" in blue jeans.
I need patrol cars off Bell and Waveland.
I need containment right now.
Copy that, 5021 Ida.
We will send units in your area.
5021 Ida, I need an ETA on that backup!
- Watch out! - 5021 Ida,
units not responding.
Do I have containment or not? Where is everyone?
Negative. No one in route.
Dispatch, do I have cars coming? Where the hell is my backup?
I lost eyes.
Adam!
Adam? 5021, 10-1. 10-1,
shots fired. Officer down.
Roll an ambo to the west alley of Bell.
Where is he? Where is he? Where is he?
He's gone, he's gone.
You--let me get this off.
Ah, I'm good, I'm good.
Shut up. You don't know that.
- It didn't go through. - I know.
Rollins kept going. You should go.
No, no, it hit your rib.
You breathing all right?
I'm fine. The wind's just knocked--
Ruzek, where you at?
It's good, bro. The vest took it.
- What the hell happened? - Hit the ribs.
I shouldn't have taken the corner.
- Patrol never rolled. - He's good.
They're not rolling with me. I'm sorry, bro.
- It's all right. - I'm good.
He's good.
No, you just got shot 'cause of me.
It's not on you, Kev. You're good.
He just got shot. He just got shot.
- Who didn't respond? - Kevin.
I know it's on your radar.
- Who didn't respond to the call? - Kevin, I am looking into it.
I'm going to question every officer--
Who was it?
There were three patrol officers in the area and four tact guys.
Who were the tact guys?
Right now, every one of them has plausible deniability--
Of course they do. Who were the tact guys?
McKenzie was one of them. Kevin, come on.
Kevin, no. Kevin, please...
Really?
This is what we're doing? Letting cops get killed?
- I was making an arrest. - Ruzek got shot.
I couldn't roll on a call. Back the hell up, man!
You feel good, huh?
Coming at good cops 'cause I told the truth?
I'm not coming for you.
You just wanna watch officers bleed out in the dirt--
- I said I ain't coming-- - Yeah, you woke now?
I gave you your answer. Now back up!
I ain't backing no damn where, coward.
You're still protecting your racist ass buddy?
Not here, man.
You take a breath. It's us.
- Take a breath. - He's giving orders.
I'm good.
You think any of us wanna be doing this?
The world of police is burning down.
You think patrol cops wanna be coming for you,
risking their jobs?
He's giving orders.
We got a lead on Rollins. We gotta go.
I know you feel it.
Nolan's still got the department.
You'll never see them, never prove it.
This is how they do it.
They make you scared of your own shadow.
This is how they break you.
We got Rollins entering the Wilson CTA stop
two minutes after your 10-1 call, Ruz,
and then exiting again at Belmont.
Rollins has a cousin that lives two blocks from Belmont.
Great place to hide out.
Hey, Adam.
- You okay? - I'm good.
All right, we are not relying on Patrol this time.
We secure the location
and contain the perimeter ourselves, understood?
- Let's do it. - Let's go.
Come on. Let's go.
- Back's secure. - Copy.
Tim Rollins, Chicago PD. We have a warrant to enter.
I've got movement in the house--go.
Kev, Adam, he's heading your way.
- Stay down! - Stay there!
Yeah, yes, stay down.
Offender in custody.
Confirm, Hailey.
We got you. We got you.
- Okay. - All right, let's go.
Let's go. Get him up, get him up.
This the gun you shot my partner with?
- Get up. - Get him up.
Let's go.
I'm sorry, bro.
You got no reason to be sorry.
You do know I got you, though, right?
We all do.
You're not alone.
Yeah, I'm 10 minutes out.
Hey, if you want me, then come get me.
I could take whatever you got.
Not sure what you're talking about.
Well, come for me, not my unit,
good cops that don't got nothing to do with this.
If I'm the one you want, then come for me!
You know I did the right thing!
"The right thing"?
Is that what you think you did?
You're the hero who crumpled the Blue Wall?
Doyle was a gladiator cop that killed--
Doyle was a dead man!
He was already killed, and then you killed him again.
You left his children with a dead father
they gotta be ashamed of, and for what?
You're standing exactly where you were.
Blue Wall's still all around you.
I'm gonna keep coming for you
in any way I want
until I have your badge.
Evening.
Heard you closed the case.
Congrats.
Really?
It's professional courtesy.
All right, I read it in the management book.
It's supposed to build trust.
Do you like me now?
Look, I know you didn't get me 48 and protection for free.
Can we just cut to the part
where you tell me what you want?
I gave you 48 because you were right.
Look, I get it.
You look at me, and you see everyone that came before me:
Kelton, Woods, Brennan.
You know their file is still up at Ivory?
- They hated you. - They didn't hide it.
- I'm not them. - They all said that too.
I'm sure they did, but I'm just here to do a job,
a job that I am very good at.
I'm something new, Hank.
Part of the new world, huh?
Yeah.
Chicago's an old city, Sam.
It is.
You should get that. Go ahead.
Today was fun.
The fight's always the good part.
It's the only way you really see people.
Voight.
It's starting to get cold.
Yeah, I know I got two options.
Let you make some deal for me, or I hand over my badge.
Well, I can't have you in my unit, Kev.
- Not if-- - I know.
Not if I'm jeopardizing cases.
Or I'm risking team's lives. I get it.
So let me help you.
I already talked to Nolan. Listen.
The deal would be I put a beef on your record.
Official complaint.
I mean, it would tie you down.
It means you'd never make detective,
never leave my unit.
It's a brick,
but Nolan would stop coming--
I'm not taking that.
Then you're not gonna be a cop anymore.
Maybe I don't wanna be a cop anymore.
I'm constantly looking over my shoulder.
I'm mad
every hour, every minute, every second.
I'm mad at Nolan, I'm mad at you, I'm mad at Ruzek.
I'm mad at every white cop
that feels like they can make a deal for me.
And every cop that's done this job the wrong way,
which means I'm mad at myself.
I'm so mad, I don't even think
I can do the job the right way anymore.
Then do it different.
Do it different.
That's the win. You get to do it different.
- And Nolan skates? - Nolan.
Nolan, the way he polices, he's not gonna last another year.
Then what's the point of giving him a damn thing?
Because it's not a new world yet.
It's just not.
So we just wait for the whole world to change
and just pull me up?
What would you do?
Voight?
In my skin, with this world, would you do that?
Me?
No.
I'd say you are a good cop.
And you're a good man, Kevin.
And you ask me, as soon as you're not one anymore,
they're winning.
Kevin, I...
Listen, I'll back you no matter what you choose.
But the question is, what do you wanna do?
Nobody's home. I already checked.
I wouldn't wanna scare your family.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
I'm a cop too. Nobody saw me come in.
- You're gonna kill me? - No.
I'm gonna tell you our way out.
Well, that's not how this works.
It is if I take the third option...
where I give up my badge a different way.
Where I sue you
and I sue the Chicago Police Department...
where I detail the harassment, the intimidation,
the kilo of dope you planted in my car,
the officers who pulled me over,
the break-in at my house,
the beatdown.
The innocent cop you let get shot,
the fact that you ordered other officers to do your bidding--
You might need some sort of evidence.
Yeah.
But do you really think all those men
are gonna stand by you?
When I rip you limb from limb in front of the media?
When I give up my badge, my job, and my life
to stand on the podium and call you a racist?
When every member of my team backs me?
When I march in the streets with your face on my poster?
When I come for your job, your pension,
your house, your name?
All while you're still living?
While your three sons watch?
I don't wanna give up this job,
but if you keep coming after me,
any member of my unit, or any other cop,
I promise you
I will give it all away.
I will make it my job to come after you.
And I will destroy you.
Pass the ball, bro. Pass it.