Oh! Someone's had a big off.
Renault made contact there with Haas.
That was a terrorist attack.
He just turned into me, mate.
Yeah, they're not getting very
close on the walk back there, are they?
The midfield this year has been
one of the most thrilling battles
we've had in a long time.
There's millions of dollars to play for.
And all of it's really boiled down
to just two teams...
Renault and Haas.
It's old Europe
versus the New World.
French royalty versus raw American power.
If Haas beats us, it would be a disaster.
I think it's a great fight.
We're ready to go to war.
This battle for fourth place,
it's brilliant and brutal.
He pushed me off the track.
their drivers don't get on.
Magnussen
on the inside with Hülkenberg.
Magnussen just ran me
off the track. What a cock!
Once again
the most unsporting driver on the grid.
-Suck my balls, mate.
-Very good, man.
It's a tough rivalry.
Renault
really don't wanna be beaten by Haas.
It's a mighty, mighty fight.
Racing, in America, it's in the blood.
NASCAR, IndyCar, it's a long history.
At Haas F1, we want our drivers
to have that same American passion.
You ready for this?
I have no idea. We'll see.
How's it going?
You'll have fun.
What's the worst that can happen?
- Piece of cake.
- We've got the ambulance ready, so...
This kind of team
works for me,
'cause some Formula One teams go racing
with money
and other, you know, Formula One teams
go racing with their heart.
Haas is clearly one of those teams
you don't feel like you're racing
for commercial reasons.
-So, is the car ready?
-Yeah.
Do you know what to do?
Yeah. Flat out.
Haas F1 is the first
American team in more than 30 years.
When we started it,
everybody told us we would fail.
"Why should you guys in America succeed?"
Whoo hoo!
It's not easy to put together a team
and make it work.
Kevin Magnussen's really got
the bit between his teeth.
Haas rise to the occasion once more.
Haas have done that in NASCAR.
Now in our Formula One third year,
we're already fighting the big boys.
-  Sensational from Haas!
- Awesome!
Boy, I need a... drink.
I don't know what I need.
You just have
to drive like that again this weekend.
Are you gonna give me a rub down?
Uh, no.
We're deep in the heart of Texas,
the Circuit of the Americas.
It is the United States Grand Prix.
Whoo! USA! USA!
And for Formula One's
only American team,
isn't it great to be back home?
Grosjean! Grosjean!
Haas have had
a really up and down season.
At the start,
you had Romain Grosjean really going
to pieces in the early races in the year.
But he's found his form
and come back on song.
Grosjean comes home fourth.
Whoo hoo!
Now both drivers are secured
for another season into 2019.
Everything seems
to be coming together for them.
They're confident.
They're hungry to fight.
But coming into Austin,
it really is a massive one.
If they can maintain the great performance
that they've shown over recent races,
they might just be able
to put one hand on that fourth place
in the championship.
What's the general vibe
around the team at the moment?
What's the atmosphere like?
Yeah, the atmosphere is great.
The team is going well.
Very much looking forward to the race.
And I'll just try to bring
some good points back home
and a great show for our fans.
It's very satisfying.
This year, we've got a really good car
for the first time
coming in a home race.
And, you know,
Austin is a great place for us.
We're gonna see a lot of Haas T-shirt,
cap, you know, and flags.
Whatsoever we can see on the track.
So, we're here for the the fight
with Renault, ready to go to war.
Because you wanna fight Renault,
of course.
Yeah, that's the big target.
I think it's a great fight
and it's a great challenge for us.
Yeah, you are fighting Renault, who
is a huge car brand all over the world.
So, how do you see this fight?
Well, you're right.
You know, Renault's a huge brand,
but they're not the biggest brand
in the United States, I can tell you that.
All, uh... regimes come to an end
sooner or later.
For Haas to finish fourth
in only their third season would be...
uh, frankly it would be--
it would be unbelievable,
because the team they're up against
Renault... is one of,
if not the biggest auto manufacturer
in the world.
They have a wealth of experience
in not just competing in Formula One,
but winning world championships.
It is however, at the moment,
a midfield team
trying desperately to rebuild itself.
And in the balance of where we are
from a competitive standpoint right now,
Renault lost their momentum
and they need to get it back.
Renault seem to have stalled a bit
in terms of their point scoring of late.
They're still hanging on
to fourth place, but only just.
Eight points separate them
from their American rivals.
And if their recent form
is anything to go by,
it's not looking good for the French.
Oh, no.
Nightmare for Renault.
And that's Nico Hülkenberg into the wall.
Where are Renault
at the moment?
Because it does look as though it's been
a bit of a struggle the last few races.
Well, we are where we are. I mean...
But in terms of the true form
of the team, though,
you were looking so strong
in fourth and now... it's not ideal.
Um...
What has happened?
Oh, the Renault goes wide.
Is he gonna try and launch?
Oh, no!
The Renault's made contact there.
Carlos Sainz is out of this race.
We are fourth. That's the reality,
but it is a very tough midfield.
And since Barcelona,
they've been a faster car than us,
really, so, uh, that's worrying.
Renault, at the moment,
is in a very tricky situation.
I think if, if Haas beats us,
it would be a disaster.
I think we all know how important
that fourth place is for Renault.
I think we all feel it inside the team.
We feel the pressure.
What you have to understand about Renault
is that they've invested millions
in their pursuit of the top three teams.
That means there's a huge amount
of expectation on them,
not only from their shareholders,
but from the whole of France.
Renault's connected to the French people.
It's a partly state-owned company.
Um, so it's a huge responsibility,
so you don't want to mess it up.
This year, fourth is very important to us.
We need to show to the world
that our ambition to become a top team
and fight with the best is credible.
I just hope you see
it's a stepping platform
if we want to join the top three.
But coming in to Austin,
it's difficult to hide the fact
we've lost confidence.
Proper music, huh?
Welcome to Texas.
Bleh.
When the weather is like this here,
it's like...
Let's talk a little bit
about the threat of Haas. Have they...
Haas? Who are they?
I've never heard about them.
They're just
this other little American team.
-There is an American team?
-I think so, yeah.
Did you know?
I'm Nico Hülkenberg.
I'm 30 years old from Germany
and I drive
for Renault Sport Formula One team.
Well, the atmosphere could be better.
It's challenging. Everyone realizes that.
Um... many things didn't go
the way we wanted them to go.
But we have to focus on what is ahead.
It's all about the race.
The race is the only thing that counts.
Nico Hülkenberg!
You're famous!
Hello. How are you guys?
Wait, how much races did you win?
- None yet, unfortunately. Yeah.
- Oh, wait, really?
How are you famous?
-Wait, you didn't win any?
-No.
Do you have a good mindset?
Do you think you will win?
It's not so easy. It's very hard
to achieve, you know.
So, how many races
have you ever won?
Quite a few.
- Microsoft! I wanna play games.
- But in Formula One, not so many!
- They're disappointed.
- This Sunday!
This Sunday, I'll try. I'll go for it.
Expectations, you know...
I've had to deal with them all my career.
My personal expectations to myself
are probably higher than anyone else.
This is what I've been dreaming about
and worked towards
since I am eight years old.
Nico...
Nico Hülkenberg has been viewed
as this champion-in-waiting for a decade.
Phenomenally successful in junior career,
but just never achieved what everybody
thought he would in Formula One.
This is a guy who now holds the record
for the most races without a podium.
Oh, dear. Boom!
Front wing just fell off.
That is dreadful luck.
Hülkenberg goes off the track,
losing his left wheel.
Hülkenberg, for the second year
in a row, is out of this race.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, ooh!
He is frustrated.
He is frustrated, having been,
most of his life, a midfielder.
All of these years spent
without podium, without wins.
I mean, no, Nico, given the right car,
is capable of being world champion.
He is world champion material,
there is no doubt about that.
I'm getting older,
but, you know, I still have
that aim and the goal
to become Formula One world champion
and to win races.
I wanna-- You know,
I will keep going and not lift off
till I have achieved that.
And now with Renault, you know,
I have a team and a partner,
because believe I can.
But first we have to get
to that fourth place.
And beat Haas.
Ladies and gentlemen, Gene Haas.
It looks like an incredibly competitive
weekend for your boys.
Yeah, our competitors are just
pains in the butt.
- Yeah, but--
- So you just get out of the way.
Are you optimistic?
Renault's having a bit of a wobble.
-What do you think?
-Yes.
Correct.
Thank you. Thank you.
Coming into race day, there'll
be a massive feeling of excitement
in the Haas F1 camp.
They might have been underdogs earlier
in the season, but they're not anymore.
Remember, they've got a Ferrari engine,
and the way they've developed this car
during the year
has now made them much faster
than their French counterparts.
You would really have to say
that this race is theirs for the taking.
We all know that we're
in the fight for fourth.
It's getting tight now. For sure,
Renault will try to win it as well.
I'm confident
with the performance of the car.
Just keep focused, do what you're doing.
Do not change anything.
Just do always-- get to the best,
and, uh... we will finish fourth.
You know, a lot of people wouldn't have
given us any chance to achieve this.
Renault has got three or four times
the amount of people we have got.
More than double the budget we have got.
But I think Renault has realized
that, at the track, they cannot beat us.
Hey, you know, Kevin,
you'll get a chance to beat Nico as well.
That, I think, means a lot to him.
There's a bit of history
between Magnussen and Hülkenberg,
and part of it stems
from Magnussen's own history with Renault.
He used to drive for that team
and felt Renault didn't have enough faith
in him to try and keep him.
He was replaced by Nico.
So, Kevin Magnussen's
definitely had a point to prove.
It's going to be a dirty race.
Kevin and Nico don't get on... at all.
Magnussen just ran me off the track.
How can I-- How can I say?
It's-- It's a tough rivalry.
When it comes to racing, he's just nasty.
And what he does is just, you know,
ruthless, being an asshole, basically.
It's no secret.
I can't wait to beat him.
It's a big target for me, personally.
You know, it is what it is.
A lot of people say Kevin
is the bad boy of Formula One.
But he's a pure racer.
He fights for everything.
He doesn't leave anything behind.
You know, he would never give up.
And he can be
one of the best in Formula One.
So, it all comes down to this.
The outcome of this race
could transform the fortunes
of one of these teams.
On the grid,
Renault and Haas are side by side today.
Who's got the fastest pace?
Who can show what they're made of
when it really matters?
We've been
very neck-and-neck the whole year.
But I feel like this is the chance
to actually prove which of us
is better as individuals,
as racing drivers.
Radio check, mate.
Radio check.
Track temperature was 29 degrees.
You're just sitting there,
you know, waiting.
It's so fucking intense.
You feel, like, your heart, you know,
pumping, "boom, boom"
and it feels like it's kind of
in your mouth.
At that moment, you just need to function.
Everything that
I've worked towards in my career so far
has come purely down to this moment.
Very good start indeed
by Nico Hülkenberg in the Renault.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Into turn one...
Oh! There's contact.
Carlos Sainz going wide in the Renault.
Fuck! Come on!
Fuck.
Oh! Grojean's hit Leclerc.
Leclerc's spinning. Grojean's got damage.
No!
Oh.
Fuck! Front wing.
Box now. Box now.
We have our first retirement
and it's the home team, Haas.
- Too much damage on Grosjean's car.
- Oh, that is such a shame.
Sorry.
Lap one and Haas
are already a car down.
You think this cannot happen.
It's just like realizing
that there was a big opportunity
and you cannot make it right again.
I was just thinking,
"Please, not again."
I was really trying to be careful,
but of course, when it's your home race,
you want to do well.
So, maybe I pushed too hard.
You're talking about, "Maybe I brake
two-tenths of a second too late."
But at that speed, it's about ten meters
and ten meters means
that you have contact or not.
I apologized to all the team.
Obviously, not what we wanted
in the fight with Renault,
and, you know, the most painful
at that point
is seeing that Renault,
I think they were sixth and seventh.
A big gap for Kevin to, uh, close.
There's more contact.
And another car spinning off.
Wow!
You're doing a great job, Nico.
Grosjean out of the race.
Magnussen is P-10.
You know, you need to
be really focused in that moment.
You might have a good start,
but Kevin is quick.
He's always gonna be
a serious, you know, threat to us.
Stay positive,
stay positive. It's a long race ahead.
With one driver...
sure, it's more difficult now,
but in racing, you never give up.
In situations like this,
you race hard, you know.
Kevin Magnussen
turning it up a notch.
If he wants to catch those Renaults,
he's gonna have to fight his way
through that midfield.
All the responsibility
is on you...
and I'm not willing
to make any compromises.
Fucking hell.
They're just really slow.
Keep on pushing, Kevin.
-Go on, mate.
-Go on.
Kevin Magnussen
is closing the gap.
But with both Renaults
in point-scoring positions,
Haas have a mountain to climb.
Sainz was after the curb
on turn one, you know?
So you think Sainz got
an advantage by doing this?
It's a big advantage to them.
Can you please have a look
at the start of Sainz,
because he apparently cut
the corner totally,
you know, to get an advantage.
What were we supposed to do?
The Renaults were in front of us.
We cannot sit back and just see,
"Oh, maybe we get lucky
and they retire
and then we get the points."
No. You need to go
and attack at that point,
because there's nothing left to lose.
Carlos, we have a situation.
What?
Carlos has a five-second penalty
for going off the track.
You could not script this moment
if you sat down at the start
of the season and you tried it.
Ah, what a shame.
Carlos Sainz, at the moment,
is up into seventh place.
When he comes into his pit-stop,
he'll have to stay stationary
for five seconds.
I couldn't believe it.
I was thinking,
"Why? Why? Why? Why?
And how is it possible?"
A five-second time penalty.
He'll serve it in his pit-stop.
This will cost him time and could cost him
and Renault an awful lot of points.
We were in a good position.
Five seconds...
it feels like forever.
With Sainz held up in the pits,
Magnussen is able
to get ahead of him.
Yes!
The Haas driver is
giving it everything.
And into the pits comes
the other Renault of Hülkenberg.
Standby, Nico.
Unbelievable.
What a turnaround for Haas.
Magnussen has made it up to sixth place.
- Oh!
- Yes!
Great job.
You are pulling away from Hülkenberg.
Magnussen is in front, right?
Magnussen is in front.
Now is the time to push
as hard as you can.
Push like hell.
The battle for best of the rest
has come down to these two drivers,
these two rivals,
these two men with everything to prove.
Hülkenberg on a very good lap.
Yeah. He's picking up the pace now.
We're under threat.
Hülkenberg chasing down Magnussen.
This is a massive scrap.
They are both pushing
to the absolute limit.
Oh, no.
We've got a problem, Nico.
You are losing
a little bit of performance.
So, look after the rear tires.
Annoying.
Right rear
is not looking very good.
I think it's got some light blistering
in the middle of the right rear tire.
Fuck!
And Magnussen is starting to pull away.
-  Fuck.
-  Sorry, Nico.
The pace is slow.
All of a sudden, the car has problems.
You're like, "This can't be true."
Some one thing was wrong
in a split second
and everything is, you know--
everything is suddenly much harder.
Losing the rear more and more now.
Magnussen has boxed.
Twenty seconds, 20 seconds.
So Magnussen
has been called in for his pit stop.
Hülkenberg has a chance
to regain his advantage.
Hülkenberg retakes the position,
but with the Renault's rear tire problems,
can he hold onto it?
We need to fight until the end.
Keep on pushing.
You just have to focus on yourself.
You know, our battle is probably gonna
go down to the last lap.
It's gonna go down to the very end.
Will Magnussen catch Hülkenberg?
How many laps to go?
Eleven laps to go.
Give me everything.
I need everything.
A very dramatic final few laps.
Can Hülkenberg keep going on these tires?
Seven laps to go, Nico.
Gap to Magnussen
behind you is 7.3.
Oh! Locking up there.
Hülkenberg's in real trouble.
Tires are struggling.
Hang on, Nico.
You know,
if you do a mistake, it's gonna hurt you.
You're doing a great job
in the circumstances, Nico.
Just need a few more laps,
you're doing a great job, mate.
I think we're fucked.
You might be in front,
but you're burning through your tires.
And you can see,
you know, the defeat is coming.
You think about all these times
you have bad luck in your career.
I can't really lose much more.
But fortunately...
not this time.
Whoo!
Hülkenberg crosses the line
ahead of Magnussen.
Somehow, he managed to hold on.
Absolutely brilliant, Nico.
That was beautifully judged there.
Thank you very much.
Thanks, mate.
The Renault
crosses the line in sixth.
Those points should be enough to ensure
Renault take fourth
in the Constructor's Championship
this season.
Making Renault best of the rest.
Wow! Thank you.
How are you doing?
You know, I needed that.
You know, it was
really important for myself,
for my own confidence, you know,
and I just, like...
You feel free suddenly again, you know?
You got all that weight from your chest,
from your shoulders and...
a very great feeling.
What Hülkenberg did in Austin
really is a huge moment for Renault.
Not only do they win
best of the rest for 2018,
but they keep that dream alive
that they can and will be
world champions once again.
Fucking hell.
You know, it's embarrassing.
During the last laps,
I thought it would be fine.
But we've lost-- lost out.
We just gotta, you know,
take that on our shoulders
and try and do better next year.
You know, I believe we can do better.
Fuck. Fucking hell!
I'm afraid to get off the fucking pitwall.
Fucking hell.
You sit there, like, beaten up
on your seat and just think,
"How did we do this all wrong?
We should have done better."
Everybody in Haas wants to do better.
I don't know.
Maybe it just wasn't our time.
Thank you.
Do you think, next year,
you're gonna have more races like that?
Well, of course.
We want to close the gap
to the top three teams.
You know, it's, obviously, a challenge.
Of course, everybody
is working and pushing hard for that.
Thank you.
I think Nico, with his talents,
evidenced by his performance in Austin...
it shows that there is some things
that doesn't work right now
in Formula One.
You can't have a driver like Nico
not on a podium.
Thank you.
He's world champion material.
He deserves a car
that can match his skills.
And I just hope that one day
we can see that in action,
because he deserves it.