So, this is the helmet
that I will race
in this year's Italian Grand Prix.
The best feature about this helmet
for this weekend
is thatI will be able to take my mask off
as soon as I'm wearing the helmet.
- That's it.
- Okay.
We cannot be too funny
considering the performance after Belgium.
- Says who?
- We. Because...
I think you should be funny
if you look at our performance.
So, is that the credo for this weekend,
"Don't laugh"?
- No!
- No jokes?
Enzo Ferrari said,
"Ask a child to draw a car
and they'll color it red."
I think
that's all you need to know about Ferrari.
It's everyone's understanding
of what a racing car is.
Formula 1 is synonymous with Ferrari.
They're the oldest-standing team.
Arguably one of the biggest brands
in the world.
They're the most iconic team in Formula 1.
A lot of drivers' dream is
to drive for Ferrari.
Seven World Championship titles.
Ferrari enjoys a status
that no other team holds.
They use that to its strength.
Not again!
But sometimes it bites them.
Ah, it's so frustrating!
We are outperforming Ferrari.
Oh, come on!
They aren't as competitive
as they normally are.
Ferrari have Leclerc 13th,
Sebastian Vettel 14th.
I'll hang in there,
but you know that you've messed up.
The Ferrari engine power
is just not there.
Charles Leclerc absolutely plumb last.
The feeling of Ferrari right now
is one of huge question marks.
What a miserable season.
Will they ever regain
the form of old?
I know what it feels like
to be running a team
when you're in the shit.
But I didn't have a whole lot of sympathy.
It's going to be a disaster.
Um, can we talk a little bit
about the season so far?
It's been pretty difficult, right?
Um...
Why?
We don't have that much time
and, uh, yeah, to be honest...
Next question!
It's a very speedy hello
from the fastest circuit of them all.
We're here in Monza
for round eight of the Formula 1
World Championship in 2020.
It is the Italian Grand Prix.
Grazie.
Netflix again? Oh my God.
From where do you fly? LA?
No, I fly JFK.
I fly Charlotte, JFK, JFK, London.
I come private if you want a lift?
- Where do you leave from?
- Guadalajara.
Their rooms
can't be smaller than ours.
Ferrari had bad seasons
in the past, as well as this year.
Yes, we are in a difficult moment,
but Monza is a very historic Grand Prix.
Obviously, being in Italy,
it's, uh, the one which counts.
- Is everything okay?
- Yes, fine.
Let me say,
you may lose a season,
but if you are winning Monza,
at least you have saved your season.
I am going to read out
some of the media questions.
- Yes.
- This is a question from Vanzini.
What is the key word right now?
What do you suggest?
Well, the same as always.
No, I think determination is better.
Yes, I would say
we have a lot of determination.
- More than usual.
- Yes.
Certainly, we understand
that it's a very difficult moment,
but I think
that the frustrations we've got, um,
we need to transform that
into determination.
- Ciao.
- Buongiorno.
Buongiorno. A difficult weekend
for you to arrive back here in Italy.
How do you keep the expectations realistic
for this weekend?
Uh, certainly, uh,
we know what we need to improve.
I think there is no doubt.
What's important is to stay focused
and really to try to work very hard
and to transform any frustration
into determination.
You feel for Ferrari,
going into their homeland
with nothing to show.
They have to try and find some redemption.
They have to find something
to pin this season on.
Do you think
it will be a bit like last year?
Hopefully,
it's got as bad as it's gonna get.
I think it will be a mess.
- Looking good?
- As always.
Uh, can you just
turn upside down your mask?
This is not to be filmed,
but you got "Ferrari" upside down,
which is okay,
but maybe at best to put it...
- There you are.
- That's better?
- The filter.
- Yeah, the filter needs to be...
They are tricky.
Okay, now, first of all,
welcome, everybody, to Italy.
Uh, now, first point,
please wear your mask all the time.
As usual, this is really important.
Mask? No mask?
My name is Sebastian Vettel,
racing for Scuderia Ferrari.
No mask.
Wow.
Brave.
No mask.
Don't look at your mobile
during media activity.
I'm telling you this
because the media have come up to us
saying, "Don't do it,
you know, it doesn't look good,"
so just be focused on what you're doing
and please don't look at your mobile.
That's four post-races
that I'm not speaking at all.
I'm watching the phone,
but don't have any questions.
I know, but it doesn't look good.
Hi, I'm Charles Leclerc,
driving for Scuderia Ferrari.
Um, I have a contract
until 2024 with the team
and I started in Formula 1 two years ago.
Even if you're not talking,
you should show interest
in what Sebastian is saying, so, just...
I am showing interest.
But he is repeating, uh, the same...
It's always the same question,
so I know the answer.
Okay, okay, but still.
Wait another ten years,
then you'll see.
There's no hope for you on this.
Okay.
Uh, now, the first point, Charles...
I think that Seb is
a very experienced
four-times world champion,
but I think even for Seb,
it's always a continuous learning process.
Charles is very young.
He is very fast.
He is very consistent.
He is good in battling,
defending, attacking.
So, in order to develop our team
for this season,
there is not a number-one driver
in Ferrari.
Hello.
Morning, Charles and Seb.
How are you guys?
Good, thank you.
Right, let's get cracking.
We've got some brilliant fans here
who, uh, are dying to...
- Hello.
- The connection has gone.
- Really?
- Yes.
Uh, cut Zoom.
- Go out, okay? Go out of Zoom.
- The problem is the connection.
- But to make this work.
- It's coming.
- Hello!
- Is it better?
Yes. For now, it looks good.
It's a difficult year
for Ferrari.
Not just on track, also off track.
Amazing modern technology.
Okay, Esther, go again.
What was your question?
Okay, so, Charles,
when will you launch
your clothing collection?
Oh! Uh, well, at the end,
for now, it's on standby.
Uh, it's something I really wanted to do
and it's something that I think
I will keep in mind for the future.
- What's the collection?
- It was like full clothing.
- Like, a full collection.
- Ah. He's not allowed.
That's why it's not happening.
'Cause we have a... We have a partner.
So, he was told off.
I... I... I'm not supposed to say that,
but I'm leaving at the end of the year,
so I can say what I want,
you know?
It is clear that I will not be
a part of this team beyond this year.
I was surprised when I got the call
that the team does not want to continue.
Seb has been with us
a few years already.
I think we all love Seb
because he's part of our family,
but, uh, we felt the necessity to,
to look ahead, to look forward.
It's like trying to create foundations
for our long-term future.
For Ferrari to announce so publicly
that Sebastian Vettel's leaving the team,
I think, is a clear state of intention
of what they want for the future.
Charles Leclerc.
That's a pretty toxic environment
for a man
who's a four-times world champion.
Would it make you insecure?
For sure, it's tough.
Obviously, I care a lot about the sport.
It's a big part of my life
and therefore, you know,
I asked myself a lot of questions
about what I want to do in the future.
I think
that Sebastian
was left very hurt
by the way in which his departure
from the team came about.
The fact that the negotiations
hadn't been anywhere near as lengthy,
shall we say,
as we'd been led to believe.
I heard
that telling him so early
would have created a lot of difficulties.
But I think whatever were the concerns
people were raising
were the wrong concerns.
Ferrari!
Ferrari! Ferrari!
Ferrari is just special.
It has always been special for me.
Go on, Charles!
From being a child,
I was always looking at the red car,
and, uh, it has always been a dream
to be a driver for, for them.
- Hey, guys.
- Thank you, Charles.
You're number one, bro!
Over winter, Ferrari gave
Charles Leclerc a contract extension,
the likes of which had never been seen.
Go on, you're the best!
Not even Schumacher
got a five-year contract extension
and Charles did,
which shows just how important
Charles had become to their future.
- Did you sleep well?
- Very well.
Well, it still feels amazing
to know that, um,
I have the longest contract
in the history of Scuderia Ferrari
and to know that we will be working
for such a long time
and to be building
something special together.
Go on Charles, Ferrari!
Hello, thank you.
- Go on, you're the best!
- Kick his ass!
Hi, guys. Thanks.
Hello. Hi. I'm sorry.
- Let's see what today has in store.
- Let's see.
Now,
from the Temple of Speed,
Monza's national autodrome,
it's time for Qualifying
with 20 of the best drivers in the world.
Today, Red Bull hope to interrupt
an endless stream of pole positions
for the German team.
And Ferrari are simply hoping somehow
to find their way into the top ten.
Expectations are difficult to have
this season
because it's unpredictable, the results,
but it is a very special race for us,
so, uh, we have to do well.
But yeah, it's not going to be easy.
Morale is tough, obviously.
The team is certainly not on a high.
But I think everybody's trying
to do their most
to make sure
that we still get the best out of the car.
Qualifying's important.
It determines
your starting position on the grid.
The fewer people that start ahead of you,
the fewer people you've got to overtake
to win on Sunday.
Don't send me
in too much traffic.
Copy.
This is the two Ferrari cars.
Seb overtook me.
I don't understand
why I went out in front of him.
Was he not meant
to overtake Charles?
Was Charles meant to be ahead of him?
Have Ferrari got things
a little bit mixed up?
All happy families down at Ferrari.
Mode charge. Mode charge.
Track is clear behind.
There's a pressure
on Charles Leclerc's shoulders,
the man, of course,
who was on pole position here last year.
- The car is so hard to drive.
- Copy. Understood.
We aren't doing well on the long runs.
So difficult.
Ah, fuck's sake.
At the moment, you are P11.
We are so slow.
There's nothing Leclerc can do.
He doesn't have enough prancing horses
down the front straight.
Charles Leclerc across the line.
Only 13th on the grid.
Thirteen, unlucky for some.
Best I can do.
The best I can do.
The real concern is
that's their true pace.
Any cars around me?
No, we are in a good slot.
Hamilton 3.3 in front.
Constant speed 200.
There was a chance
to do better here.
For info,
there's a big traffic jam out there.
Let's talk about it after.
Look. This is the kind
of traffic we were hoping they'd avoid.
If you need
to overtake people, we will.
A similar queue to that
you had on your way back from holiday.
Vettel can't fight back.
The Ferrari engine power isn't there.
Is there a gap I can get through?
Too much traffic.
It will be mode push
for last corner. Mode push.
What is going on out there
on this Saturday afternoon?
Sebastian Vettel,
he's in the bottom five at the moment,
crosses the line in a few moments,
Sebastian Vettel.
Uh, we see Vettel pitting.
He's pitted.
He's not going to improve his time.
Ferrari just weren't ready.
What has happened to them this year?
Shit. What a mess.
And the big headline news here at Monza
is that Sebastian Vettel
is knocked out in qualifying.
It's Ferrari, P17.
- I guess that's it.
- Yeah, it is. P17.
Not quite the Ferrari
of old here in Monza, is it?
Thirteenth and 17th on the grid.
Ferrari's worst fears in qualifying
have been confirmed.
How frustrating is it that
you win from pole position here last year
and then down to this position?
That must be heavy for you.
Yeah. I mean, it's tough
because once you do a good lap
and then you do P13, it doesn't feel good,
and, uh, yeah, I mean,
it hurts even more once it's at home,
but it's a reality at the moment
for us, unfortunately.
Seb, you didn't finish your second run.
No.
I was in the middle of the mess,
so there was no point to do it.
Yeah.
That's what it was, a very short day.
You can call it frustration,
but at the end of the day,
on power, we are probably worse off
than we were last year
and the unsatisfying,
most unsatisfying bit
is that you didn't get
to prove to yourself,
"Okay, what could I do today?"
You know, how close to the top
or how far up could I have gone?
- The pole's above your head.
- What?
You have a mic above your head.
But yeah, it's not easy.
I don't know how it will be tomorrow.
- Well, yeah, look at Vettel.
- Yeah.
He didn't do the last lap.
It's okay, they can't read our lips.
No, but be careful,
you have a mic above your head.
We missed many opportunities.
Certainly the pressure was there.
Obviously, the car is not as good
as we would have wished.
I think Seb's got
some difficulties with the car.
Lack of confidence.
And Charles' car was not performing.
No grip, so, you know, difficult
to really be fast around the lap.
So, we had a poor quali, very poor.
It's a tough time for Ferrari.
There's been a lot of mudslinging,
a lot of accusations
regarding the "secret settlement."
I was wondering how you cope with that?
Honestly, I think
there is a lot of bullshit around it.
- Yeah.
- A lot of rumors.
It's very simple. There have been never
a breach of regulations.
Leclerc's on the inside,
Hamilton goes onto the gravel,
and you can hear the cheers from Monza.
The Ferrari fans loved it.
Ferrari came out of the break last year
firing on all cylinders.
Charles Leclerc won
in Spa. He wins in Monza.
They basically built a car
with a rocket ship in the back of it.
Ferrari coming on strong
in the second part of this season.
They were going so fast
that nobody could quite believe it.
Vettel is going for it.
The Ferrari's speed is giving Hamilton
a lot to think about.
Ferrari have won three races in a row.
Well, we highlighted certain things
to the FIA, together with Mercedes,
that... that we felt
that they should be looking at.
The other teams couldn't work out
exactly how or what,
but they knew something was up.
All of a sudden, in Austin,
we got rumblings of a technical directive
all about fuel flow coming from the FIA,
which is basically a rule clarification,
that says you can, you cannot do this.
I tell you who's on their back foot,
you've got to say Charles Leclerc,
just trying to get a handle on this car.
Let me know
if you can faster, question.
I don't think I can.
And then no power.
Vettel can barely keep up,
he's so slow down the straight.
How was that?
Shit. Uh, that's how I call that.
I really don't know what happened.
I think there was really something weird.
Ferrari is coming under fire
because allegedly, they have been
gaining an advantage with their engine.
The other teams are not happy about it.
They did conduct an investigation,
came to a conclusion,
reached a settlement with Ferrari,
but aren't disclosing the details of that.
We were surprised
at the statement from the FIA.
We're pushing for full disclosure of that.
The FIA haven't found the team guilty
of any specific wrongdoing.
Are you disappointed then
that they didn't clear the team?
I trust my team
to do the right things
and we trust the FIA to do their job.
I fully trust my team
uh, and I trust the FIA
for making sure everything was okay,
so for me, yes, it's, uh, it's done,
and now I look to the future.
They don't have the power
that they had before, that's clear,
and they don't seem
to be in a happy place at the moment.
From the outside,
not knowing why the deal was secret,
it looks like Ferrari had
an unfair advantage
that the FIA took away.
People say,
"Why you don't change engine supplier?"
I think that is not what I call reality.
Going forward,
we are staying with Ferrari,
even if, in the moment it isn't...
I mean, uh, uh... easy
They helped us a lot in the beginning,
so now, we need to help them
and be loyal and...
and a little bit patient.
When you look
at the relative performance
from last year to this year,
I think it's self-explanatory.
Some team principals
have suggested
that the 2019 car or engine wasn't legal.
Honestly,
I don't think there is much to add.
The point is closed.
This is a beautiful day in Monza
as we prepare for round eight
of the Formula 1 World Championship.
I'm having a romantic conversation
with my girlfriend. You can't record this.
You have to go back to 1984
as the last time two Ferraris
started outside the top ten
at their home Grand Prix.
Test Vettel mic.
Test, one, two.
I want to see how far I can dig.
- Yeah. Okay, cool.
- See what we get.
2020, for Sebastian and Ferrari,
it just hasn't quite clicked,
it hasn't quite meshed.
Okay. Okay.
We can see you now. Perfetto.
There is no way
that a Ferrari should be 17th...
They are coming from there.
They are just there now,
so if you want to film them...
...or that Sebastian Vettel is...
that far off.
Seb's a four-time world champion
and one of the most ruthless,
brilliantly effective racing drivers
that I've ever seen.
How are you?
- Good.
- Good. Good.
You don't lose that ability overnight.
Seb, um, I think
you're a very morally guided person.
I think you have a good heart
and a good direction.
Well, I think you have to
have your principles, so I think, uh,
yes, as much as I want to succeed
and I want myself to have success
rather than others,
I play by certain rules.
And, you know,
one of those rules are I have to be fair,
and if being successful
means that I have to break these rules,
then it wouldn't feel right.
It's like cheating, in the end,
and you are cheating yourself, so...
Do you think everyone
plays to the same rules that you do?
I can't answer.
Take control of it yourself.
- Should be your decision.
- Yeah.
- You know?
- It is.
- You're still young enough.
- Yeah.
Seb leaving Ferrari,
what's going on there?
Just take a moment to pause.
- And then come home.
- Exactly. All right.
See you later.
Yeah, it's, I'm sure,
a question that you'll be asking him.
Sebastian Vettel is out of a seat.
He has nowhere to go.
Up and down the paddock,
everybody was trying to work out
what was he gonna do.
Would he leave Formula 1?
Would he find another team?
Sebastian is
a great personality who, uh,
shaped the last ten years in Formula 1.
Simply the fact that Sebastian's available
is worth the discussion.
Frankly,
I'm good friends with Seb.
I knew him
from before he was a Formula 1 driver
and, uh, for a very long time.
He's still a young man and very talented.
It'd be, uh, a shame
not to see him on the grid next season.
I remember Sebastian Vettel,
when he was driving for us,
came from more than 40 points behind
to beat Fernando Alonso
to the 2012 World Championship.
We don't write anything off.
Literally anything can happen.
Let's hope
he doesn't lose motivation.
Yes, we need to keep him focused.
As a team principal,
my challenge certainly is
make sure that the external comments
are not affecting the morale of the team.
It was a very difficult quali.
Uh, I understand...
the disappointment of the people around,
but more important to stay focused.
Okay. Back of the grid.
And radio check.
Yeah. One, two, radio check okay.
Ah, it's not the first time
I started at the back of the grid.
I believe that there's always a chance.
Sunday, when you stand on the grid,
even if you're not in a great position,
you never know what happens.
If you are racing in P10
and the nine cars in front of you retire,
you win the race.
Ferrari's not so good
in the straight.
- Unbelievable!
- Fucking hell.
And radio check, Charles.
To be honest,
I think it would be a mistake
for me to put extra pressure
because I'm driving for Ferrari.
Radio check. Can you hear me?
What I have to do in this situation
is to try and maximize what I have.
Radio check.
Whoa. Wasn't plugged in.
No problem.
When I close the visor,
I try to extract all of those thoughts
to be 100% focused on the goal.
I think emotion was going up.
The pressure was there.
No doubt.
Because we knew
that Monza was important for us.
And we're underway
for the Italian Grand Prix at Monza.
Great getaway for Lewis Hamilton.
Up to second place goes Carlos Sainz.
Bottas down to third.
Charles Leclerc is losing a position
to Kimi Räikkönen.
Alex Albon getting it
all wrong in that first chicane
and losing places as a result.
Charles Leclerc on the inside
of Kimi Räikkönen, looking for a gap.
That soon disappears.
Any feedback on the starts?
You are P13. P13.
Lap five of 53.
Hamilton's lead is three seconds
over the McLaren of Carlos Sainz
in second place.
Here's Vettel.
Russell, 0.7 behind.
Copy.
Sebastian Vettel
who's still down in 17th, under pressure.
DRS enabled.
Vettel does not have DRS.
Yeah, copy.
And we are very hot
on the left-hand side of the brakes.
Rear left.
Russell, 0.5 behind.
Distance!
Here comes George Russell.
Vett has smoking from behind.
I'm not sure if he's dropping oil.
- Something wrong, the rear left.
- Copy.
You need to cool down the rears
if you can.
They've got a problem with the car.
They've got Russell
trying to get past him.
Vettel can't slow it down!
Brakes failed. The brakes failed.
Brakes failed.
Oh God!
Brake fire.
The brakes are on fire.
No more brake pedal.
Brake line exploded.
I can bring the car back if you want.
We're always in the middle
of any crisis.
End of the day for Vettel,
who's leaving Ferrari
at the end of the season.
His last race as a Ferrari driver at Monza
and he's out on lap eight of 53.
A torturous Italian Grand Prix
for the Scuderia.
They'll hope this is as bad as it's going
to be for them at their home ground.
For Seb,
it has been certainly frustrating.
It's the most important race of the season
and I think that
whoever is a Ferrari driver,
the dream is to win in Monza.
And it is lap 24
of this Italian Grand Prix.
Ferrari is passion
and you can feel it.
It's just unbelievable
and you don't get that
anywhere else on the grid.
Gap to Räikkönen in front, 0.6.
Copy.
It's our job now
to get back to, uh, to winning.
Leclerc's putting Räikkönen under pressure
behind Antonio Giovinazzi
He's got past Räikkönen.
He might clear two Alfas
in about 300 meters here.
And he does!
Charles Leclerc picks off Räikkönen
and picks off Giovinazzi as well.
Fantastico!
Leclerc may have lost speed.
He hasn't lost any bravery
and commitment, has he?
Confidence in Formula 1,
I think, is everything
because if you are not confident
in your car or your abilities,
then you are going to struggle.
We need to close the gap.
We need to close the gap now.
We are not where we expected to be.
We are not where we want to be.
Try to maximize full throttle.
I'm...
I'm struggling, guys.
But still, my goal is the same,
to try to put the car on its limit.
Are you okay?
Charles? Can you hear me?
Ah...
Fuck!
It was very extreme.
I can remember everything
apart from the hit itself.
I think there's a bit of a blackout
for a few seconds.
The hit was pretty hard.
Everything happened,
uh, very, very quickly
and then, unfortunately,
puts all our hopes to the bin.
I'm sorry, but I...
Honestly, I struggled so much
with the balance.
Fuck!
Sorry.
Copy.
Main thing is that you're okay.
And go to P0, please, P0.
Leclerc hauls himself out of the car.
It was a long way through the corner
for that to be a brake problem
like Vettel's.
Let's see what did happen.
He's on his own
coming into the Parabolica.
And he just lost it on the power
on the hard tires,
and driver error.
What a horrible, horrible
Italian Grand Prix for the Scuderia.
How bad a result
was this for Ferrari?
It was one of the most horrible weekends
they've had in a very long time.
It's a huge fall from grace
for Ferrari
because this is a team
that should be fighting Mercedes
and yet, they cannot compete with anybody.
It was a difficult weekend
which concluded even in the worst way.
Obviously,
we are all unhappy and disappointed.
It's poor, obviously,
where we are,
especially here, for our home race.
It's probably a blessing
there's nobody in the stand.
We are very united.
I don't think
there are even tensions inside the team.
There are no shortcuts in life.
We are in this position
because we probably deserve to be.
I think
that I can feel the team behind me.
Very committed.
Now, it's down to us to...
to prove that we are capable.
Welcome
to the second Italian race of the season
and a milestone in motor racing.
Ferrari's 1000th Grand Prix.
And they're preparing
to celebrate in style.
Ferrari has been always there
since the very start.
Never stopping since 1950
when the F1 started.
I think whatever difficulties
we've got at the moment,
it's important to celebrate
because we are celebrating
an entire history
and a fantastic milestone.
And if you've got such a history,
somehow you are special.
This is Ferrari's 1000th race.
The party, the displays.
They are a huge, huge corporation,
making millions of pounds.
This is the time to shine.
As the sun rises
on a beautiful Tuscan morning,
news that Sebastian Vettel
has signed for Aston Martin.
Seb, we understand you didn't even
put pen to paper until last night.
For me, it was important
that I sign up for something I believe in.
Today, it's been announced
that I'll have a seat,
I'll be on the grid next year.
I'm looking forward to a new challenge.
I'm a competitor,
so if I wasn't convinced
that I can be competitive
with Aston Martin,
I think, uh, you know,
life is treating me far too good
uh, to drag on and to keep suffering.
Bonjour.
Okay, well, of course,
the big news we all know now
that Sebastian has a seat and a team
for next year and beyond.
And beyond?
- Big news this morning.
- Good.
Good to have you around.
We have done a post for you, saying...
Yeah, I saw, thank you.
Yeah. Thank you, Silvia.
No, not "Thank you, Silvia,"
it's all of us.
Now, uh, in terms of the, um, timing
of the announcement, Sebastian.
We had quite a lot of people say,
"Sebastian, you know,
announced this on this day,"
and everything.
Of course, we believe it was triggered
by last night's announcement from Perez,
which came out so late.
It was obviously a last-minute thing,
so this is our position when we get asked.
- Yeah. It's the truth as well.
- Okay.
The timing probably tells you everything.
He probably couldn't have picked
a more inappropriate time...
...for the team,
but I guess he was pissed off.
So, on my side,
I have, uh, um, some Information
about Saturday evening,
the event that we will have in Firenze.
It's mandatory, guys, to be sharp
because we will have a lot
of important Ferrari family guests there,
so we cannot really be late.
It kind of takes the shine
off Ferrari's big celebration,
but it puts the focus back on Sebastian.
I think Sebastian Vettel feels
that with Racing Point,
which will become Aston Martin next year,
he can build this team up
to be incredible.
The future now is very exciting.
My number one ambition is
to be at the front of the grid,
fight for something worth fighting for
and have fun and enjoy.
I think
Ferrari has always proved
to be capable
of reacting to the difficulties.
Uh, we know that we need
to turn that into determination.
We are still investing in the future,
committed to creating solid foundations.
My job is to help the team.
Miracles don't happen in Formula 1,
so we need to stay focused on what we do.
I believe that if we continue to work
step by step in the right direction,
we'll manage to be
in a much better position for next year.
Ferrari is a legendary brand.
Ferrari have always been part
of motor racing.
Ferrari is somehow unique,
and Ferrari is a family.
And being a family,
somehow, it's a passion.
We are a great team
and we will develop the right car.
That's what makes me confident
that we can certainly do better
in the future.
The big news of the week is
that Ricciardo is on his way to McLaren.
Is Cyril talking to you yet?
With the breakup, I am emotional.
It's like being dumped by a girlfriend,
but she hasn't moved out the house yet.
Pierre's confidence
has completely transformed.
I wanted to prove myself
as a driver.
I deserve to go back to Red Bull.
Fuck yes!
Haas's problems continue.
In a season like this,
small mistakes have big consequences.
If you're not good enough,
you will be spat out.