Welcome to the season finale.
It's the Abu Dhabi Grand Prix.
I can't believe
you've recovered so quickly.
Yeah. Me too, man.
Only just made it.
Lewis Hamilton is back.
He's tested negative for COVID.
It's been a year like, like no other.
The World Championship record is equaled.
Lewis Hamilton
is a seven-time champion of the world.
I think what we've done as a team is...
It's very special.
It's seven consecutive
Constructors' Championships for Mercedes.
If you're gonna take on Mercedes,
you've gotta be firing on all cylinders.
Oh dear. That's Max Verstappen.
- Fuck!
- Something broke.
Max Verstappen is out
of this race and out of the car as well.
You need to see that gap reduced.
Can Red Bull put down
a marker for next year?
And who will prevail
in this epic battle for third?
We're in a very good position.
It's gonna go down to the wire.
Who wants it more will probably do it.
The battle for third in the Constructors',
it's absolutely incredible
that we should be
at the last race of the season...
'Sup?
...and still have
this massively important fight.
I think we've got a good plan.
It's all coming together.
And now it's going down to the wire.
We have come to the final
of the pre-practice sessions in 2020.
The battle
for third is Racing Point...
The key is
I don't want to overheat the tires.
...Renault...
It's gonna be hot again.
I think 30 degrees or something.
...and us.
All right,
let's fucking win this thing.
It's a game where you want
to make the most
of other people's misfortunes,
but, uh also realize that, at any point,
things could happen to you.
If anything, we thought Racing Point
would be quite convincingly third,
so we brought a very good fight to them.
And we knew it was gonna be
a very tough fight with Renault.
You think
we should be competitive there?
I've never been so...
probably excited about finishing third
in a championship before.
It's been a hell of a battle.
I mean, at times,
Racing Point's been third,
McLaren's been third, we've been third.
It's gonna be tight,
but all we can do is focus on this weekend
and end the season on a strong note.
That's, uh, you know, the hopes.
To fuck shit up in
all the good ways possible.
That's what I'm hoping to do.
On board with Daniel Ricciardo.
Nice job, mate.
Two or three more laps like this
would be great.
Okay, this is about my pace now.
Very classy performance.
He's absolutely flying.
Yeah, I think 'cause I'm, uh,
I just have amazing natural abilities,
uh, I'm the epitome
of human high performance...
Daniel Ricciardo
is having a very good final sector here.
It's just hard.
It's just hard to be humble.
It's really hard!
I'm just kidding.
Daniel Ricciardo
absolutely aces the final sector
and goes second fastest.
I honestly feel
I'm getting better each year.
There's things I'm still...
internally, I know I'm doing better,
even if it's controlling the pressure,
controlling the emotion.
It's also experience, you know. It's...
it's my tenth year, I think, in Formula 1
and I'm at that,
probably at that nice balance now
where I've got, still got the desire
and the, let's say, the will
to push the car to the limit,
but I've also got now the knowledge
and experience
of being a tenth-year driver.
Is that a podium, boys?
Is that a fucking podium?
It's a fucking podium!
He's here. Woo!
- Mega, man, mega.
- Oh!
Daniel Ricciardo
comes home in third place
and gives Renault their first podium
since Malaysia in 2011.
A fucking podium, Daniel!
Thank you!
Well done.
Every single lap
that we see Daniel performing,
a moment of uh,
of joy and satisfaction, of pleasure,
but at the same time,
it's negative emotion
because we also measure what
we'll be missing, what we'll be losing.
It feels like
the first podium again.
The joy and, uh, the feeling was missed,
so yeah, I'm very happy.
For him, it was so important
to make the point and to show
that until the last lap of the last race,
he will be loyal to his decision
that he made a few years ago.
I'm sorry, but yeah,
it's... it's not complete.
It's not over yet.
So, we made the bet.
It was if I get a podium,
uh, he has to get a tattoo.
I probably threw it out there because
I've got more than a tattoo or two.
I was like, "Why don't you get one?
Do you have any?"
He goes, "No."
I was like, "That's it. Tattoo."
So he was like, "Okay."
Well, you know what,
if we do a podium, I'll do a tattoo!
- You've got to.
- I can't... It's not...
We've achieved the achievable
and it's time to get it done.
Have you done this one before?
- The buffet?
- No.
- For lunch?
- We had it for dinner, it was cool.
It's good
to get something healthy, eh?
Sometimes, I give up, I'm like...
It's the first time I didn't
check the dessert menu.
- Says the Dyson!
- What's that book?
One of the boys gave it to me
to give to you. Look.
There's some
of the most, like, horrific tattoos.
- Oh my gosh!
- It's for Cyril!
Oh no!
I've never seen someone so excited
to get a tattoo, so...
That Homer Simpson one's awesome.
Have you seen the Judge Judy one?
I spoke to him the other night about it.
He reckons he's gonna get it on his ankle.
- Yeah.
- That's the most painful spot!
- But I think he feels it's like... Yeah.
- It's hidden.
We can pass this on to Cyril.
It's the worst tattoos.
I was not betting
against my own luck,
I was not betting against my own team,
and I'm extremely happy
to have to honor this... this obligation
now that we've done this podium.
Oh, yeah, a bit of sun!
♪ There you are looking at me
On the elevator... ♪
Fruit platter?
For you?
Thank you.
No, it's not for him. No, no, no.
It's for us.
No, leave it here.
I am the athlete.
I need to hydrate.
What do you mean
he's a very important person?
- He pays.
But leave it here.
Yay!
So, battle for third,
we are behind our friends there
in Racing Point.
A few more than Renault
and a few more than Ferrari.
- Thank you.
We've gone all of a sudden
from being the underdog
to having a chance
to win that midfield battle.
We are doing a good job
of making it to the points with both cars.
I think it's time for...
There you go.
With Carlos's podium last season,
a lot of people saw him as,
you know, the driver within the team.
That hit me hard because it's something
I'd want more than anything,
but then it switched, I think,
quite heavily, as we came into the season.
I started the year with a podium,
then a lot more people saw me
as being able to deliver when I need to.
How's it going, dude?
I'm quite sore after, um...
- Golf?
- After golf.
- Are you?
- Yeah.
- What kind of golf were you playing?
- Men's golf.
We're very tight
in the championship.
I think, you know, before the last race,
we were split by one point. I was behind.
Now, I'm one point ahead.
- What do you play off, 12?
- Uh, 16.
- Carlos is pretty good.
- Yeah.
We want to beat each other,
but we also
need to do a good job for the team.
We don't have one driver doing really well
and one doing not well.
We're pushing each other,
and, uh, I think that's why
we're probably the closest pairing
or closest teammates on the grid
consistently in qualifying and races.
Gonna be tight.
- Gonna be tight.
- Yeah.
Racing Point
have been third best the whole year.
We'll miss Carlos.
We've enjoyed our time racing with him,
but, you know, we're... we're excited
and, uh, in a couple of races' time,
we'll be, uh, thinking
all about, uh, Daniel and... and Lando,
and hopefully,
that'll take us yet to another level.
I wanna know what Daniel thinks
when he drives it.
What he brings, you know,
why everyone says he's so special,
why they say he's a better driver
than the majority of the grid.
Learning from him,
you know, a multiple race winner,
a guy who's worked
with multiple different teams and so on,
I just look forward
to that next chapter of the story.
Welcome to the Yas Marina circuit.
It's time for one final blast
around the track
ahead of the Abu Dhabi Grand Prix.
It is the last qualifying of the season.
Renault have been quicker
than Racing Point and McLaren all week.
It's a Grand Prix
for which pole position is crucial
and the last five races have all been won
by pole position here.
A tenth and a half
covers the top four.
It's very much Red Bull versus Mercedes.
Something is changing
a bit for a Mercedes team this evening
that have been one and two
in qualifying here,
uh, for the last six Abu Dhabi Grand Prix.
So, pressure then,
on Daniel Ricciardo of Renault,
just to get into Q3.
Also pressure on Lando Norris' McLaren.
As we watch Lance Stroll.
Can he get into Q3?
That'll do nicely.
Lewis, then, really treating his tires
extremely kindly on the out lap.
Hamilton crosses the line.
He's back on pole position.
Who can deny him now?
What about Max Verstappen?
He's gone best of all
in the middle sector.
He was only a tenth down in the first.
Max Verstappen's taken pole
in the season finale.
Pole position.
That's a statement.
- Excellent job.
- Yes!
Come on, boys! Come on!
Well done, Max.
Mega lap. Well done!
Ah, this feels good.
Well done, boys. Amazing. Amazing.
Great lap by Norris,
powering his way.
Gets to about 200 miles an hour.
P4. Get in.
Fuck yeah!
Nice.
Daniel Ricciardo
can't get into the top ten
and he misses out by just four hundredths
of a second to his teammate.
That's a shocker.
I fully expected him
to clear the bar and get into Q3.
Both Renaults are out.
Lance Stroll takes
eighth place on the grid, sadly for him.
That's going
to make Racing Point uncomfortable.
You know, I want to do well,
so I... I'm frustrated,
but overcoming tough times
and getting through them,
that's something that, um,
I've improved at as I've matured.
Fucking surfing!
Nice one.
I look back and there's been
quite a few, uh, highlights this season.
It's great when you do well.
I was on pole a few weeks ago.
Here comes Lance Stroll.
Stroll crosses the line
and he does go pole!
1:47.7.
It was just
such an amazing achievement.
Yes, boys!
Let's go!
You dream about things in the sport
and one of those things
is to stand on the podium,
to win a race,
and, you know, to be on pole.
Brad, I wanna hear you say it, mate.
That's pole position!
I wanna hear you say it!
That's pole position, Lance,
pole position.
Let's go!
I love my job.
Lance did a great job
putting it on... on pole,
which just shows what talent, uh, he has.
And then after that, in Bahrain,
we scored a significant amount of points.
Sergio Perez comes home
to win the Sakhir Grand Prix!
And it's the first ever
double podium for Racing Point as well,
as Lance Stroll takes third place.
Well done, Lance.
P1 and P3 for the team.
Well done, guys.
But...
...you know, sometimes, um...
you love the sport
and it just don't love you back.
Here comes Dani Kvyat
down the inside. Oh, there's contact!
Massive accident.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Definitely wasn't a normal race
after that happened.
There's Sergio Perez.
Oh, puffs of smoke!
That's Sergio Perez
very much out of this race.
You know, it's racing.
Some weekends are good
and some weekends are bad.
For sure, it sucks.
Uh, none of us were happy
walking away from that race,
but I'm still learning.
I think we learn every day.
You catch that six-meter wave?
- You were killing it out there.
- Yeah.
I definitely wanna work
on my consistency, get better
and, you know, be there more often.
Um, I just turned 22, so,
um, I do see myself getting better,
hopefully.
As we bring to an end
the Formula 1 season in 2020,
17 races and 3,249 racing miles,
it is down to this
to decide who gets that third spot
in the Constructors' Championship.
There are
a fair few million reasons
why you'd wanna fight for third
in the Constructors' Championship.
It's not just about pride.
It's big bucks. Big, big bucks.
Racing Point are ten points ahead
of McLaren with one race to go.
That's an easy swing.
I would have said a few races ago,
it was Renault.
However, McLaren are the ones
that are right behind us.
Arguably, Racing Point have been
the third-fastest car of the season.
Anything less than third
in the Constructors'
could be seen
as a failure.
We're on this journey
to get back to the front of the field,
and we've been ninth, sixth, fourth,
and here we are, fighting so hard
to finish third in the championship.
Renault's
a bit further back in the race for third,
12 points behind McLaren,
who are in turn
ten points behind Racing Point.
Given all the water
that's gone under the bridge this year
between Racing Point and Renault,
there's no way Cyril wants to lose third
in the Constructors' Championship
to that team.
Racing Point this season,
uh, clearly, uh.
no one was expecting a team of this size
to... to be operating at that level.
So, clearly, finishing, uh, on that podium
of P3 for the Constructors'
would be, uh, quite something for us.
It's a race
that could just conjure up anything
and you can feel it,
the pressure in the air.
With a ten-point lead
over underdogs McLaren,
Racing Point must be favorites.
And in his last race for the team,
only a fool would bet
against Daniel Ricciardo and Renault.
- This is what it's all about, Tom.
- Yeah.
Normal start.
Let's have a good race.
I think we can pull it off.
All right. Whatever happens today,
thank you for everything.
Fuck some shit up.
Give everything.
Yep. Thank you, boys.
Fifty-five laps.
Everything we got.
And for the final time,
we're racing in 2020.
Verstappen ahead of Bottas.
Norris getting a good start,
but behind Lewis Hamilton.
Into the first real big braking zone
we go.
Daniel Ricciardo on the Ferrari
at the hairpin
and he's got himself
ahead of Sebastian Vettel.
Currently,
your pace is faster than anyone up to P4.
Understood.
Here comes Lance Stroll.
Two points in it at the moment
between McLaren and Racing Point,
now that Lance Stroll has moved up
into seventh place.
Sergio Perez still right at the back.
I'm losing power.
I lost the fucking engine again.
I'm off.
That is absolute heartbreak
for Perez and the Racing Point team.
You're fucking kidding me!
What could that do
for the team's ambitions
to finish third
in the Constructors' Championship?
- What happened?
- Perez engine failure.
That's what I want to hear!
Go on, Carlos!
Daniel Ricciardo in fifth,
stayed out and got track position.
- Car behind is Norris.
- Okay.
We should naturally be quicker
than Ricciardo ahead.
Yeah, confirm.
This is looking really good.
A good bet for fifth place, McLaren.
202 points as it stands at the moment
will be taking that third spot
in the Constructors' Championship.
Nice job.
Stroll, the one remaining
Racing Point car left in this race.
Ah! Brakes are shit!
Big lock-up there from Stroll.
We've got a tire problem.
We have no traction.
I'm trying to brake, but I lock up.
You can understand
Racing Point's concern there.
Pierre Gasly
has gone down the inside of Lance Stroll.
He's gone past the Racing Point.
They did touch as Gasly went through.
It's unbelievable how bad we are
at maintaining temperature.
Stroll's gonna have to look out behind him
because Esteban Ocon's catching
at a rate of knots.
Verstappen, starting from pole,
he's led every single lap of the race.
As he rounds the final corner,
the checkered flag's in sight.
Verstappen wins the Abu Dhabi Grand Prix
and rounds off the season
in perfect fashion
for himself and for Red Bull.
Norris crosses the line to finish in fifth
and his teammate Carlos Sainz,
home in sixth position.
Yeah!
Daniel Ricciardo will be seventh.
Awesome job.
Thank you.
Ocon is really hustling
the Racing Point now
in the battle for ninth place.
Ocon has DRS.
Brad, leave me alone.
Go!
Yeah!
Esteban Ocon left
his good work right until the last minute.
It's gonna be Esteban Ocon
to finish in ninth place.
Yes!
Until the end there.
Oh, well done, mate. Good effort.
Stroll couldn't score the points
that Racing Point wanted and needed.
Oh, fuck.
Thanks, guys.
That was a nice way to send it off.
Thank you, Daniel.
And, uh, we look forward
to racing against you next year very much.
Thank you.
We can have a beer tonight.
Two.
Congrats, everyone.
- Lando, great job.
- Great job, Lando!
- Cheers, Zak.
- Yo, dude!
We all know you would've won
the race, but, you know, we did our best.
Great job!
Woo!
Well, luck is,
uh, definitely a part of sport.
I think you create your own, uh, luck
by working very hard
and having great people.
I think this year, there's more
hard work and grit and determination
that's gone into it,
which is another step,
a lot more money for the team.
Getting that third spot's part
of that story I'm trying to make
with McLaren.
Getting back to that, winning races
and winning championships again.
We only did it in the last race,
so it was close,
but, um, as long as we improve some races,
my engineer does a better job, um...
...then I look forward
to another season next year
where we can hopefully do a bit better.
Come on, man.
Congratulations.
Leaving a team, moving on,
I think kind of breaking any relationship
is... is never easy.
I look back now,
and I look back at the start of 2019
and where we are now
and yeah, we really did build something.
I'm stoked that we can part ways
knowing that it was...
it was a really nice two years.
Daniel is a fantastic driver.
I cannot not love Daniel.
I love Daniel. We all do.
Everyone's life has sort of...
uh, these moments where you know
you should be doing something
and waiting and pushing,
but procrastinating a bit.
Daniel is the one that has pushed us
into doing the changes.
I'm not convinced we would have done
those changes without Daniel.
Credit to Cyril, he actually called me
'cause he obviously,
he really wants to honor the bet.
And I said, "With lockdown, the way
Europe is at the moment, it's difficult,
so it'll probably have to wait
'til next year."
Who's paying? You paying or I'm paying?
He gets to choose a design
and I think he's done that,
and I get to choose the size and location
and I've done that also.
Not too visible.
But a Mike Tyson thing, no.
I guess the base of it
will be something quite traditional
and then maybe
with, like, a little bit of, uh,
a honey badger involvement in there.
But I don't wanna make it too,
like, cheesy or anything,
but it should also be something
that maybe he looks at and giggles,
uh, for... for the rest of his days.
We should have come third,
but it's not easy to do.
Next year,
our driver line-up is, uh, Lance
and Sebastian,
four-time world champion, a veteran.
We wanted to bring in a driver
who had the experience
of working with world-championship teams.
To have a young,
up-and-coming driver
with an experienced driver
is the right thing to do,
and who better to learn from
than Sebastian Vettel,
who's a four-time world champion?
Lance can learn from Seb
and, uh, and hone it
such that he too, in the future,
can aspire to become a world champion,
so I think we got a great combination.
Next year,
Lawrence has big ambitions for the team.
Any moment, guys, be ready.
Aston Martin is coming in,
a great name for Formula 1.
Ultimately,
it's all about contract performance
and there's a lot that goes into that.
And that's what Lawrence wants to do,
that's what we're gonna focus on
in the next two, three, four, five years.
Good morning.
The heart and soul of this company
started with its racing.
This is the factory
where the cars are built.
And then, to support its racing,
built the most luxurious
bespoke automobiles.
- Looks really good.
- Yep.
So, it was natural
to be able to take Aston Martin
and align it
with these great bunch of guys
that is currently today Racing Point.
It's, I believe, the most exciting thing
to happen in Formula 1 in decades.
- That's a great color.
- Yep.
Aston Martin are seen
as the British Ferrari.
That link with James Bond,
that 1960s chic.
It's very, very cool.
You get so excited,
seeing all this luxury product,
bring Formula 1 to market it
and put it on track next year,
it's very beautiful.
This is where we have our design center.
Marek Reichman,
our chief creative director,
and his people...
Hello, Marek.
...are about to show me the visuals
of what our cars will look like
for next year on the grid.
- How's it going?
- Good. You?
Yeah, good.
What we have developed
is a very modern green color,
which has a dichromatic effect over it.
What does that mean?
It means
it really sparkles in the sunlight.
That's spectacular.
This looks like it's going faster
standing still.
Yeah. Exactly. Yeah.
We gotta make sure it's fast on the track.
That's great.
So, if there's been a lot of jealousy
on track of our performance this year,
there's gonna be a lot more jealousy
from our competitors
when they see
how good and quick we are next year.
It's a difficult year.
When the pandemic started, we didn't know
if we were gonna be still here or not
and we needed to do tough decisions
about the drivers.
Thank you to all of you and thank you
for the time we had here with Kevin.
There is obviously ups and downs,
but that's life.
- All right, Kevin. This is for you.
- Thank you.
Next year, we'll have Mick Schumacher.
This year,
he was first in the F2 Championship.
Mick Schumacher, Michael's son.
- This is the race helmet from 2012.
- Thank you. It's such an honor.
I really appreciate that. Thank you.
- And Nikita Mazepin.
- Yeah!
His father has come
to invest in the team.
It's a family which loves racing.
That is what, uh, Nikita loves
and what his dad loves.
For the future Haas F1 team,
I need sponsors, uh, uh, to survive.
I'm very happy to have him on board.
I'm really excited to start
as soon as possible in 2021.
Now we've got a lineup of young drivers,
which is great.
Carlos did very well through the 2020,
and he's bringing
some know-how and experience.
He will fit very well with Charles.
Both young,
but already experienced drivers,
so I think
it's solid foundations for the future.
The plan for 2021
is try and take off where we left off.
We've beaten Mercedes at, arguably,
one of their most dominant venues.
It wasn't a lucky win.
It was a pole position
and a straight fight
against the two Mercedes.
Mercedes produced the most competitive car
they've ever done this year.
They are the benchmark currently
in Formula 1.
They have dominated the sport
for the last six years.
To beat them,
you've got to be at the top of your game.
We got ahead of them
by the end of the year.
It took a monumental effort,
but we've demonstrated it's possible.
With Sergio and his experience
alongside Max next year,
it's achievable.
We've just got to do it over 23 races
rather than over one race.
We've been unbeatable again in 2020
as a team
and, um, it doesn't happen for no reason.
Time after time after time,
Mercedes create
an absolute monster of a machine.
I think, when you reflect
on the seventh consecutive title,
you have that moment of satisfaction,
but that passes quickly.
You think about the next race
and you think about the next year,
what you need to do
in order to stay competitive.
There is no sense of entitlement
or complacency within the team.
Breaking news:
Toto Wolff has signed up
for Mercedes for another three years.
I've led this team now
for seven years,
which means traveling to all Grand Prix.
I've spent 250 hotel nights last year.
More than 700 hours in an airplane.
And you start to ask yourself
how much longer can you do that?
But on the other side,
I'm a co-owner with Mercedes of the team.
I'm not gonna walk away.
Especially if you like to keep an overview
of what's happening.
So, in a way, you need to decide
whether you want to be on the dance floor
or on the balcony
and I'm on the dance floor at the moment.
But one day, I'd like to be on the balcony
and oversee the whole situation.
I don't think we're done yet
with seven titles.
There's more to come.
This year has been
about more than just racing.
Relax.
I can't breathe, my face.
What are you on?
I can't breathe!
What happened with George,
it brought up a lot of emotion.
All of a sudden, things that have been
suppressed over my lifetime
bubbled to the surface.
And I was like...
I can no longer stay quiet.
Every Black kid in the world will,
at some stage, experience racism.
It's just a fact.
When people call you names
and the N-word's thrown around,
you're told to go back to your own country
when you're in your own country.
There are literally millions
and millions of people
who will have experienced
much, much worse,
and that needs to change.
I had it so many times.
In the past years,
I've had racist names being called to me,
but lately, um,
if anybody has said anything to me,
I just ignore them.
I was just eight years old.
For someone to look down
at a young eight-year-old
and tell them they're not gonna
achieve anything in life,
they must be in a really bad place.
As Lewis began to win,
the fact that he was
the only Black face on the track
became an issue.
My dad would always tell me,
"Tread carefully.
Be careful what you say."
We don't get involved with, um, people
who have problems about whether we win
or whether... what color we are.
We go out on the track and we do our best.
What's it been like for you
to be the only Black Formula 1 driver?
Sometimes I wonder why.
Why me? Why am I the...
the only Black driver that's come along
and had the ability,
not only to get in the sport,
but be at the front of it for so long?
That's okay.
I mean, I've been built for this.
People probably don't...
...won't know
that I grew up, like, on my dad's couch,
so we didn't have any money.
I remember the struggle.
I remember how hard it was for my mum
with the multiple jobs she had
to keep a roof over mine
and my two sisters', uh, heads.
I remember how it was for my dad
to keep me racing.
So, I... I know
how hard it was.
And then, on top of that,
that other struggle
with acceptance and not fitting in,
that's all bubbled up into,
hmm, you know...
created the beast, I guess,
that you see on the track.
Lewis Hamilton wins!
Hamilton has more wins
than any other driver
in Formula 1 history.
The way I'm wired,
I... I don't really have a filter.
I say what's on my mind
and I'm not always too bothered
about upsetting someone
if it's gonna make a difference.
And the winner, Lewis Hamilton!
What I think this year's shown was
when you do have that success,
what are you gonna do with it?
I'll be damned if I'm gonna win
all these championships
and have all this success
and not, um, use it to make change.