- Okay.
- I can do this.
Bit higher.
Took to season 3 to get a board.
Professional. We haven't done that before.
- Roll cameras.
- Oh shit, that's bright.
- Can I say it in Spanish?
- Yeah!
Do I look athletic?
Dynamic? Intelligent?
Never held one of these things before.
Only see it in the movies.
Drive to Survive: Season Three,
my one and only take.
Action.
Yes, boys, come on!
- Big accident.
- Fuck!
If they're good enough,
they swim, they survive.
If they're not good enough...
Let's crush them.
Formula 1 racing
is very much like war planning.
Hamilton is the race leader.
Oh, that's a spin!
- Box, I lost the frickin' wing.
- Yeah.
And that's Bottas.
Bottas has put it in the wall!
Fuck! How is this possible?
A tough day at the office?
No, it was a total crap,
shit, awful day at the office.
- Looks dangerous.
- Looks angry.
This is the worst experience
I've had in any race car.
Last year,
this is roller coaster.
There's contact!
We've got two fucking idiots
driving for us. This is not acceptable.
We will make changes.
Hope you get it fixed.
You tell me.
- Nice. Big smiles.
- Who's your favorite driver?
Uh...
Whoever's winning for us.
Oh!
- Gasly makes a mistake.
- Fuck, no!
We've decided to release Pierre.
We're gonna remove that subject
and put you in place.
I fully deserved the seat.
The new driver lineup for McLaren.
For me, a new year is a new start.
Where's the fucking boot?
I'm working
more than anyone else in Formula 1.
It will show itself on track.
- Vamos!
- Waa!
- Yes!
- Wow!
I could see him being with McLaren
for quite some time.
Send it!
Last year,
I took a gamble and switched teams.
I feel a real responsibility
to push this car.
Let's fucking have it, boys.
A massive engine problem
for Daniel Ricciardo.
With Renault,
we haven't achieved what we wanted to.
I don't work this hard
to not see the checkered flag.
Once again, Ferrari on Ferrari.
What the hell?
It's both of them! Both cars out.
Competing against the best,
that's one thing.
Trying to do it with Ferrari
is, uh, is another one.
Hell yeah, let's do it!
Ooh... Spicy.
Mate, that pink suit photo
is terrible, bro.
How does that one pass?
Mate, look at my face.
What is that?
Can you scroll down?
It looks like he's taking a shit.
Show your eyes!
It's always hard
looking at yourself.
- Especially wearing a pink suit.
- Yeah.
I don't really give a shit.
I know what I look like, but...
Hi.
So how's it going?
Good. We're just on our way to the track.
With your traveling, you have been
wearing a face mask, haven't you?
Mum, it's cool.
Apparently, if you drink Corona,
it builds your immune.
It was never my favorite beer,
but I'll drink it if I have to.
Good morning,
and welcome back to Formula 12020.
Live from
the Circuit de Barcelona-Catalunya,
with the 2020 Formula 1 season
just around the corner.
Go away.
Everyone to the bridge.
All of you guys get down there, please.
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
All right, guys, find your marks.
You'll see 'em written there. Find your
marks and stand next to your teammates.
Lauren is gonna do a couple of pullbacks
between the center of all you guys.
So what we want you guys to do
in this moment
is really picture your goals for this year
and what you're attempting to accomplish.
Picture them and visualize them,
so when this comes across,
they see you all genuinely really caring
about what we're talking about, okay?
Is everybody ready? And action!
Pre-season testing
is the first opportunity
to get the 20 greatest drivers
in the world on track
before the season begins.
Everyone, reset your look.
Look back at camera, please.
Right at camera. Look tough.
Amazing. Thank you.
You can really sense the start
of the new season is almost upon us.
All right, everybody start walking.
Start walking!
Come. Come. Start walking.
And that means new drama,
new conflict and new possibilities.
And killed it.
You guys are good.
Thank you, guys. You can go.
- Thank you, everybody!
- Thank you.
- All right, man. Have fun.
- See ya, mate.
And there she is,
ladies and gentlemen, the C39!
What a year it's gonna be this year.
2020 pre-season testing
is nearly underway.
The teams, the cars, the drivers,
undergoing some final preparations,
waiting for that green light.
There's always an excitement
and anticipationabout the testing.
Because it's, it's everything
starting to come to life.
The hype is there.
The past, the hope.
With a new season, what comes with it,
it's just this fantastic feeling.
It's where
you have the first proper test.
Against competitors,
but also against yourselves.
There is a buzz.
There's always a buzz,
and everybody's happy to come back.
Keen to see the performance
of the various teams and drivers.
But you never...
You never kind of know what to expect.
This year, there's a genuine sense
up and down the pit lane
that this season
might not be business as usual.
The team that everyone's talking
about this year is Racing Point.
And their billionaire owner,
Lawrence Stroll.
There's a lot of intrigue
as to exactly what's been going on
behind their garage doors over the winter.
All right.
You're gonna walk me through
what we're proposing for this season.
Lawrence Stroll,
he has stature, he has a presence
that really commands your attention.
Fifteen minutes
for the whole thing.
Lawrence is a, uh, force of nature.
You know, I've worked previously
with owners that were billionaires,
but they didn't have the goals
that Lawrence has.
Hi, Lawrence.
He brings funding,
but, uh, he also brings, uh, expectations.
You got me till 12:30.
Fire away.
Uh...
I thought we would start with, uh, Simon
to present where we are
and, uh, where we will soon be.
Thank you.
So we, uh, the latest direction
is we've commenced an eight-week period
now of intense engineering.
There are two major areas that we're
looking at, and that remains on target.
We're trying to get that ready
for the end of the year.
So we're now
really going to drill into that,
and we'll be able to come back to you,
Lawrence, with some news.
Sure.
My name is Lawrence Stroll.
I am the chairman.
At the end of 2018, Force India
was at the height of its financial crisis.
The Force India Formula 1 team
has gone into administration.
The team has survived
with a consortium of investors.
The consortium is led
by billionaire businessman,
Lawrence Stroll.
There were a lot of people
who were very concerned
whether they'd have a job,
how their children would go to school
or their mortgages
or doctor bills were gonna be paid.
We acquired a team
that was fourth on the grid,
with a considerably smaller budget
than our competitors.
I really thought
this is a tremendous opportunity
in something
that I had a lot of passion for.
So our targets remain
business strategy, contract cost,
uh, and planned development.
We have, um, very exciting
and ambitious growth plans,
and I believe
we can go from strength to strength.
- And that will bring lap time?
- It will.
I've always won in the businesses
I've run. I plan on winning here.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
- We're done?
- Yeah, we're done.
Lawrence is a big character
who made an instant impact
the second that he first entered
a Formula 1 paddock.
He's serious.
And he's investing his wealth
in that team.
The only question mark is what
his plans are to take the team to the top.
After the consortium
came in and bought the team,
there was a change in the driver lineup.
In comes Lawrence's son,
Lance Stroll.
Well, my dad and I have
a pretty good relationship, I'd say.
You know, we go way back.
Yeah.
He bought me a go-kart
when I was six years old.
He's supported me
throughout my whole career.
and introduced me to the sport
at a very young age.
A lot of people think
Lance Stroll's always had it easy,
given that his father's
one of the most successful businessmen
in the world.
But you don't win championships
just by being rich.
You gotta be talented, you gotta be quick.
There is a very fast driver
underneath that helmet.
What makes me
as good a driver as I am?
My commitment.
My commitment is what makes me
such a good driver.
I'm willing to go above and beyond
to tick every box.
Cool.
Have you heard anything?
All I heard is
Mercedes is gonna be quick.
- We can be strong this year.
- We nailed it this year.
- Yeah.
- No?
Time will tell.
This season, people are buzzing, you know?
You can feel the energy in this building.
I see smiles, and, uh,
you know, I see, I see a vision.
We're ready to take it on.
The outbreak centers
on the city of Wuhan.
Although person-to-person transmission
has been confirmed,
it does not, thankfully, spread easily.
- What are we, five minutes away?
- We are indeed.
- Yeah, so the launch we've got at 2:30.
- It looks good? You've seen it?
- Yeah. The car looks great.
- I can't wait.
So I think... Lawrence is there.
- He arrived?
- Yeah.
- Lance?
- Yep.
With him? Very good.
Hello. Hello. How are you?
- It's definitely pink.
- Hello.
- How are you?
- I just want to have a quick look.
We've done a lot of work over the winter,
preparing this year's car.
- Well done.
- Looks all right.
- Amazing.
- It's well done.
- Yeah.
- Really, really good.
Last season, we were seventh,
coming off of a... a difficult year.
This year's season, Lawrence says
he wants everything to be six-star.
Looking very dapper, Otmar.
I bought this this morning. All this.
- Can you do up your button?
- No.
- All right.
- I look like a stuffed sausage.
I'm not new to the team.
I've been there for ten years.
- The car's good in the simulator.
- Looks good.
We got a lot of work to do
to set up though.
- Yeah.
- Oh, there's...
When you get new ownership,
um, you've got to manage that situation.
It's highly likely when ownership changes
that the, uh, senior management changes.
You have to finalize it before we leave.
- I gotta leave with Lance...
- 4:30.
- 4:30, wheels up.
- Okay, four o'clock.
- I gotta finish the prospectives tonight.
- Let's finish it.
Good. I gotta be in the car at 4:00.
Very good.
You know, job security can be
a bit precarious within Formula 1.
He'll want to see results in 2020.
So now,
ladies and gentlemen,
it's the moment we're all waiting for.
It's time.
The new Racing Point 2020.
We've just seen the new
Racing Point car for the first time.
How's it look?
Hopefully it drives as well as it looks.
I look forward to testing in Barcelona.
You won't be able to miss us
out there on the track.
- Thank you.
My heart and soul
and passion are going into this.
You always want to be better
than your competition.
So you always look above.
You don't look down.
2020 pre-season testing
is nearly underway.
The teams, the cars, the drivers,
undergoing some final preparations.
You can hear the engines firing up.
And we're waiting
for a green light. Let's go for it!
- You're clear from traffic behind.
- Okay.
Daniel Ricciardo, off to a flying start.
Pre-season testing
is the first chance the teams have
to see if what they've spent
all year designing
is actually gonna work
when it gets onto a racetrack.
- Last year the car felt good here?
- Yes.
So you think if we're slow here
this year, we're all right?
Don't go there. No, no.
Sometimes,
the cars work exactly as planned,
and it's smooth sailing.
True to form, Hamilton
to the top. He's on a screamer, isn't he?
But that only happens very, very rarely.
Oh, and he's spun! He's spun it.
Jesus Christ.
- He's grinding to a halt.
- Yeah, dropping out.
Jump out. Yes.
Not ideal.
Second failure for Williams.
And, for the drivers,
it's a huge challenge.
Big spin for Vettel.
They have just three days each
to get to grips with the car
that they hope
will be taking them to race victories
and potentially world championship glory.
Decent lap there
from Carlos Sainz.
That McLaren's not looking too bad
at the moment.
I'm always excited
to go into a new racing season.
There's so many unknowns.
We have such a great history in the sport.
When I joined, uh,
the team was very much, uh, struggling.
But we finished fourth last year
and, uh, we'd like to close the gap.
We've got, uh, two outstanding drivers.
One very young and, uh,
pretty new to the sport in Lando Norris.
You know, Lando could be
one of the future stars of Formula 1.
Normally, when I do warm-ups,
I get too tired before I get in the car.
I do nothing
and then my warm-up's on the out lap.
It's what an out lap's for.
A warm-up lap to warm me up.
Four...
I don't think this is, uh,
as action-packed as Carlos' warm-up.
- It's more chilled, you know?
- Cool. Anything else you want?
No. A lie-down.
This is Lando's second season
in Formula 1.
Zak wants McLaren to be a new version
of this incredibly successful team
that we all know.
There's a lot of faith
being put in a guy who's still so young.
Okay, Lando. Drive straight out.
Yeah, confirm.
Expectations will be higher
on Lando this year.
For himself, from the team, from the fans,
'cause he's, he's not a rookie.
Lando Norris,
in an F1 car for the first time in 2020.
Wait for it.
Okay, Lando. Give it everything.
Yeah, confirm.
Scenario seven. Scenario seven.
Looking really fast.
Really pushing that car to its limits.
Coming through the final corner
to complete the lap.
Lando Norris. A 1:24.981.
He's gone fastest.
OK, Lando, fastest lap.
Well done.
Awesome job, boys.
I like to stay in the shadow, and,
when it's time,
jump out and shine.
I'm looking forward to getting
behind the wheel for the first time.
With Racing Point,
the car that left the garage on day one,
in terms of its color scheme,
looked very similar to the one
that was released to the press.
But the car itself
had undergone some dramatic changes.
It was
quite familiar
to everyone in the pit lane.
Radio check, loud and clear?
Track is clear.
When the Racing Point
came out of the garage,
I think everybody's jaws dropped.
It was, shall we say,
very inspired by last year's
championship-winning Mercedes.
I think a lot of people
in the paddock thought,
"Hang on. What's going on here?"
You're good to go. Go, one.
Go!
Stroll now. Here we go.
That fucking Racing Point
is quick.
Yeah, there's something a bit weird.
OK, Lance.
Keep pushing. Keep pushing.
He's gone fastest in Sector 1.
He's the fastest in Sector 2.
They look phenomenal.
It looks like it's going to be the fastest
lap of the day, and of the test.
- Fastest car on track..
- Nice one, guys.
It's mind-blowing.
It's worth remembering
that there are the rules.
You have to design and build your own car.
Now, the closer that car is
to one that's gone before,
especially if it's one
that absolutely dominated
the previous season's world championship,
the more people are going to ask questions
as to whether that's entirely fair.
And, most of all, whether it's legal.
You may not have been looking
at the numbers. We were.
But being around the same pace as Ferrari
can't be bad.
No. But, uh, yeah, it's early days, so...
We'll see. We'll see.
How is it, every time we ask
you or Sergio about the pace of the car,
you can't wipe the grin off your face?
Sun is shining. We're in Barcelona.
Could be worse. Life's good.
Reckon they've leapfrogged you?
Difficult to say.
I don't wanna comment too much.
I mean,
it looks like a Mercedes, that's for sure.
I don't know how... what the idea
and the process is behind it.
It's almost a,
uh, an identical replica.
I think the question,
the bigger question is, is it allowed?
I think it's, it's a bit surprising
they weren't maybe
a little bit more discreet.
Is it something
that has been designed by your team?
Is it something that's been copied?
I think it's very easy to agree
that we need to put a light on this story.
So there is no reason to delay.
What we've done over the winter
is, uh, is completely legal,
and we took inspiration
from the fastest car on the grid,
but it's no different
than what other teams do.
For sure, there will be
quite heated discussions going on,
because, if it was copied,
that's, in my opinion,
not legal.
Formula 1,
it is a political nightmare,
and everyone does have their own agendas.
Thankfully,
I leave that to Otmar to get on with,
and distance myself from it
as much as I can.
And, uh... I'll leave it at that.
This will be a very interesting season.
Let's see how this all plays out
in the first race.
Finally, everybody, it's here!
Welcome to Australia.
Round 1 of the 2020 season.
Other sporting events
may have been canceled by coronavirus,
but Formula 1 bosses insist
that this race is going ahead.
The Netflix crew.
It's still too early in the season
to abuse you guys.
Give it, like, another week.
I think Australia
is always super exciting.
- Hello, Lando. Good luck.
- Thanks very much.
It comes with a high degree of pressure.
You get a lot of anxiety.
Coming out of winter testing,
you can't underestimate the competition.
First race.
I gotta go this way.
It's a great spectacle, Melbourne.
There's a bit of sour grapes
about this year's car.
If they saw what they saw,
but we weren't quick,
you think anybody would've complained?
Probably not.
And in the meantime, uh,
we gotta get prepared for a race.
Straight down the middle. Lovely.
Clack, clack, clack, clack.
- It says, "Kills coronavirus?"
- It kills coronavirus?
- Why don't we just gel our whole body?
- I know.
The key stuff
is gonna be coronavirus.
Uh, I know the team's working,
uh, very hard every day
to put the right measures in place.
Starting with a full-on face gas mask.
- Mm.
- You get zipped up.
Focus.
Ladies.
- Are you excited?
- Yeah.
- Are you?
We all look so depressed to be racing.
Have you seen?
- For him, he looks quite happy.
- Yeah.
This corner is notorious
for dipping your wheel off.
What are your general thoughts?
- Gonna struggle into turn one.
- Yeah?
I can't remember that last year.
- I remember talking about one and three.
- Yeah.
Australia was my first track
last year in Formula 1.
It was my most nerve-racking race
in my life.
I'm gonna be, like, here, on the grass.
Did you see the onboard of Verstappen?
- Yeah.
- He is literally here.
Yeah. I'm gonna be more than that.
I would love to say a podium
as a target to have.
Turn 11.
This is genuinely one of the ones
I couldn't think of much to say about.
- Flat.
- Send it.
There's always a possibility
something can happen.
So the latest rumor we heard,
there are three or four
people in the paddock
with suspected coronavirus.
- Really? Whoa!
- Suspected.
Shit! Fuck. We're gonna be,
like, put under quarantine.
But I guess the thing is
if those people actually have it,
then the whole paddock will have it.
The opening race
of the Formula 1 season in Melbourne
still looks as though
it's going to go ahead,
despite two members of the McLaren team
having shown some coronavirus symptoms.
Could you sign that for me, please?
Sorry, they don't let me
touch any pen that is not mine.
I don't know what can happen.
You just gotta smile and wave.
Man, I think this paddock's gonna
just, like, implode from coronavirus.
One of our mechanics had symptoms.
He described what he was feeling
and, uh, that doesn't sound good.
Now, we're getting tested.
We're very nervous.
I think people are scared.
This situation, this is about the health
and safety of your entire racing team,
the other racing teams,
the fans, the officials.
We have no idea what's gonna happen
in the... in the future.
What if they ask, "Do you think it's right
that we're racing this weekend?"
I'd say, um,
"Absolutely, it's a risk."
"But at the same time,
if we take the right precautions,
I see no problem with it."
And, ultimately, it's a matter for...
Formula 1 and the FIA.
Yeah.
Microphone. It's been cleaned.
Is it right
that a member of your McLaren setup
had to be isolated because of coronavirus?
The fact that he's isolated
doesn't mean he has coronavirus.
Only time will tell.
If one of your guys
went down with this virus,
would you still race?
I think I'd still race.
Uh...
But... Yeah. I would still race.
Um...
And are you worried in any way about this?
About the virus?
Um, I mean,
I'm worried if I get it, of course.
- Stay well, Lando.
- Sorry?
Stay well.
- You too.
- Thank you.
What's that?
- The US have closed their border.
- Have they?
The NBA season's done.
- No way!
- Whole season.
- Yeah.
- When did they do this?
All of a sudden,
everybody's hearing whispers about,
"Oh, someone's being tested."
There's a lot of different opinion.
I think it comes down to a 50-50 split
of those who are in favor of continuing
and those
who just want everything to stop.
Welcome to our first
drivers' press conference of 2020
ahead of the season-opening
Australian Grand Prix on Sunday.
Let's open this up to the floor now.
Alex Kalinauckas, Autosport.
A question for Lewis.
Um, regarding the coronavirus situation,
are you comfortable
having traveled all the way to Australia
and are you satisfied with what Formula 1
and the FIA have done so far?
Um, I am really
very, very surprised that we're here.
For me, it's shocking
that we're all sitting in this room.
Um, so many fans here already today.
Um, yeah,
Formula 1 continues to go on, and, um...
So, no, to your answer.
If we could
take our next question, please.
Lewis, you've been outspoken, where others
maybe have not dared to be, about corona.
What do you think is the reason
why this race is still going on?
Why are we still here?
- Cash is king?
- Cash is king.
Uh, I... Honestly, I don't know.
I can't really add much more to it.
Strong words from Lewis Hamilton.
Lewis Hamilton made
his feelings pretty clear, cash is king.
Not impressed
that the race, at the moment,
is still going ahead.
Anyway, nobody has an official statement,
so we're waiting.
Like everything
with this coronavirus scare
around the world,
information is coming at rapid pace
and it's changing,
quite literally, every minute.
That's what the...
They said four Haas people
have gone into the hospital.
The moment that one gets coronavirus,
this is killed.
Gone. Boom. Out.
In the last few minutes,
it's emerged...
...that a McLaren team member
has tested positive for coronavirus.
Got a phone call from,
uh, our team manager
to say that we'd had a positive case.
Suddenly, this situation has blown up,
with a McLaren mechanic testing positive.
Our position is we should race.
Keep testing,
and if the situation develops further,
um, you know, review it in 24 hours.
I definitely don't want us to go ahead.
I don't think we should.
We, uh, really looked forward
to racing in Melbourne.
And, from a team perspective,
we still wanna race.
There's another development
from Melbourne.
Authorities have confirmed that...
Thank you very much
for your patience.
For us, it was an easy decision.
Ultimately, we are out.
It has just landed.
A joint statement
between the FIA, Formula 1
and the Australian Grand Prix Corporation
that this Grand Prix has been canceled.
- It will not take place.
- Uh, unbelievable.
The Australian Formula 1 Grand Prix
has been canceled.
This weekend's
Australian Grand Prix has been canceled.
- The Australian Grand Prix...
- I want my money back!
We'd appreciate it
if you would make an orderly exit
towards the tram stations.
Thank you.
Disgusting.
It's disgusting for everybody here.
- Cash is king! Cash is king!
- Why aren't we allowed in there?
Can you summarize,
in a few sentences,
what happened the last 24 hours?
Uh, it's obviously frustrating.
When we arrived in Australia,
the intention was to go racing.
The important thing now is
to make sure that we get
all members of staff home safely.
Not to Bahrain?
No. I think it's fairly inevitable,
if we're not racing here,
we won't be racing in Bahrain.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you. Thanks. Thanks.
Formula 1
without races doesn't exist.
At the end of the day, we're dealing
with people's livelihoods, their jobs.
Their way of earning a living.
Plenty of question marks
now remain over the season.
Seems like it will be
a huge, long-term issue.
Everything is in uncharted territory.
I don't know
if our sponsors are gonna stay around.
I don't know if fans
are gonna be able to attend events.
Uh, I don't know if Grand Prix
are gonna be able to be put on,
which gives us the revenue
to build race cars.
Lights out and away we go!
Australia's gone, China's gone,
Vietnam's gone, Bahrain's gone.
Smaller teams,
uh, will be... will be struggling.
So there is indeed a genuine risk
for the sport and for Formula 1.
We could potentially lose
a number of teams here.
As an independent team,
are we actually going to survive this?
What happens from here?
I'm sorry, you will have to wait.
You're way too hot.
That's just the way I am.
We were finally able
to have a Grand Prix.
The stakes have never been higher.
I look forward to seeing Toto.
Hopefully give him a harder time
this year.
Fuck, again!
The big story remains Racing Point.
We're not fighting
a level playing field.
They're dragging our name through the mud.
I will not accept this.
The car is so hard to drive.
Fuck!