- [kisses] Say "love you."
- Love you.
Bye.
[in sing-song voice] Silverstone...
I love Silverstone. I just love it.
I think there's something incredibly
spiritual almost about Silverstone.
It really holds a very special place
in my heart.
I want to have my ashes
spread at Silverstone.
You know that, don't you?
[Jonathan] I do now.
- I thought I told you.
- [Jonathan chuckles] No.
[both laughing]
I think Dad does as well.
Over my childhood,
I really understood how famous my dad was,
and how big Williams was.
It's just been the venue of so many
historic moments for our team.
That was our heyday.
[crowd cheering]
Dad's always been my hero.
Dad's got two laps to try
and convince you to come to Williams.
[all laughing]
[Claire] He is Williams.
I don't wanna disgrace the Williams name.
I don't want Williams to fall apart
under my watch.
We have a fighting spirit,
and it's really being put to the test,
but I can tell you it's 100% back.
Ladies and gentlemen, please put it
together for Claire Williams.
[crowd cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
- That's like it. You got that?
- [man] I did.
Lovely. Thrilled to bits.
- [kisses]
- You're the best.
- [Frank] Bless you, Clairy.
- [Claire] See you later.
- Silverstone.
- [Claire] Yeah.
I'm deputy team principal,
which has really turned into
de facto team principal.
My dad's taken a step back
in the past few years,
and so really, I operate
as the team principal.
Morning, Gwen. How are you doing?
I'm responsible for making sure
that we've got the right people
in the right jobs,
with the right equipment to do those jobs.
And to make sure that this is a great
environment for people to work in.
I'm very protective over it.
Obviously, it's very close to my heart.
I'm sorry I didn't make it down.
It was a busy day yesterday.
Was it? I was looking forward
to you coming down. [chuckles]
[Claire] Williams is
in a very difficult place at the moment.
Last year was pretty horrific.
We just got it wrong.
We designed a bad race car.
And we've gotta fix it.
[man] Jack. Okay?
- That was all of it.
- It's not your lunchbreak, as usual.
- Jeremy settle down.
- [Jeremy] No, it's not.
[Paddy] I actually found you
doing some work.
[Jeremy and man] Whoa!
[Jeremy] Straight in there, on Netflix.
[Paddy chuckles]
- [Jeremy] Thank you, Paddy.
- [Paddy chuckles]
[man] It's gonna be
Paddy's comedy special.
[Jeremy] Yeah.
My name is Paddy Lowe.
I'm Chief Technical Officer
for Rokit Williams Racing.
[Jeremy] There's no pressure
when Paddy is looking.
One of the biggest challenges is the one
that we face at the moment,
which is to take Williams back
to the front of the grid,
where they have been in the past.
We brought Paddy in from his
extraordinary successor, Mercedes.
Trying to breathe new life into Williams.
Rear is all ready to go.
- Pretty much.
- [man] Pretty close, yeah.
Paddy was the one who came up
with active suspension at Williams,
back in the 1980s.
He was the tech genius
that was responsible for so much
of Williams' glory years.
[Paddy] Those days, a garage was quite
an oil-stained, concrete sort of place.
Now, very flash places with glossy floors
and sophisticated equipment.
So, a very, very different world.
Thank you.
[Claire] He's an incredibly clever
individual,
and he has really stripped
everything back to basics.
[Paddy] We made a lot of changes
to how we developed the car.
Changes within the team,
changes within our technical approach.
So, we're optimistic that we've made
some good improvements.
[man] We are just connecting
the ERS pack up,
getting ready to fire up
the FW42 for the first time.
We're positive about this car,
but I was last year as well,
so hopefully, we've learnt.
[engineer] Okay.
[Paddy] I wanna see a feeling
within the team...
that the team has turned a corner
and moved forwards...
and capable of winning championships
in the future.
[drilling]
[drilling continues]
- [Paddy] So we get the year I hope.
- Yeah.
[George] So, should we do a race?
We'll do a quick corner.
I mean... I'm doing quite enough.
- [laughs]
- [Robert talking indistinctly]
Paddy simulation.
Oh, this is good.
It's not just back at base
that Williams are making changes.
They've got two brand new drivers
for 2019.
[Claire] Are you ready for the
professionals to come and kick your ass?
- [man] So, we having a race, are we?
- [Claire] Yes.
[Robert] We give you the advantage.
How many laps?
- [Claire] Shut up, "how many laps."
- [all laugh]
[Claire] "How many laps?"
- Do you know who pays your wages?
- [all laugh]
[Claire] Christ.
Our driver lineup's wonderful this year.
I'm so happy.
I was really clear around what we wanted.
I can't even see the car.
- It's right...
- Oh, yeah.
[Claire] Robert and George
are two quite different personalities.
George is, I think,
a one-in-a-million driver.
He rarely puts a foot wrong.
- Oh! [chuckles]
- Hey!
Man, come on.
- Who's the yellow one?
- That's me.
George Russell, hotly tipped,
Mercedes youngster,
Formula 2 champion. Really exciting guy.
[commentator] He can see
the checkered flag. George Russell wins!
[Claire] He's fought his way up the ranks.
Some pretty senior people in F1
who know what they're talking about,
there's a lot of talk that George
is a future world champion.
- Have you won?
- [Claire shrieks]
- George!
- [George] Sorry, Claire.
- [Claire] That's really unsportsmanlike.
- [George] I know. Right.
I'm George Russell.
I'm racing for Rokit Williams Racing.
For me, it's a dream
to be part of Formula 1.
I've lived my whole life
wanting to become an F1 driver.
Out of the hundreds and thousands
of people who've tried, I'm one of 20.
And that's... Yeah, that's incredible.
Oh, my God, my eyes are going weird.
- You're surprisingly not... [chuckles]
- Oh!
Something's gone wrong.
- Yes!
- [laughs]
- I'm surprisingly what? Not bad?
- You're surprisingly not... Oh! [laughs]
Can't believe you said that
I'm surprisingly not that bad.
Oh, no.
This is all we did at home
when we were growing up. Oh!
Robert's at pole. Robert's at pole.
[Claire] I wanted Robert in the car,
'cause I wanted a driver that was able
to understand the issues with the car.
Robert had seriously impressed us
over the course of last year,
as our development driver.
I'm Robert Kubica, I'm from Poland
and I'm racing for Rokit Williams Racing.
It is strange to be back in Formula 1
after more than eight years.
[Will] Talk to anybody from go-kart
all the way up to Formula 1,
Robert was one of, if not the best.
[crowd cheering]
Robert was the one they feared,
the one that they knew
could and would make it.
He was supposed to go to Ferrari
to join Fernando.
That was supposed to be the dream team.
My career, unfortunately,
changed quite drastically.
In 2011, I suffered
a big accident in Italy.
I suffered a lot of injuries.
The crash was so bad
that it nearly severed his right arm.
The fact he can control a Formula 1 car
is incredible to all of us.
It's a huge thing for Robert to come back.
It is the Hollywood story.
It's one of the great sporting comebacks.
To be back is a dream.
[Claire] He's a bit like a dog
with a bone.
He will push and push and push
until we fix the issues with the car,
and he is not shy in telling us
what those issues are.
- My finger's hurting.
- [man laughs]
They signify everything that
I've always wanted in a driver lineup.
Oh, yes. I'm still in the...
- Am I still in the lead?
- [man] You are.
[George] Oh, no! [chuckles]
[man] Claire wins!
- Did I win? Did I?
- [man] You win.
- Mentally, I'm destroyed now.
- [laughs]
That's better.
Everything is focused on getting your car
to that first day of testing.
[Claire] Would you...
There are a few bits of printing.
Would you mind just printing them for me?
It's a letter.
Thank you very much.
This is car build week.
Mike, I'm on my way down.
It's gotta go on Saturday night,
and everything has gotta be on it.
Everything's gotta be ready.
Doesn't that blue look nice?
- [man] Yeah.
- I can see...
- Have you seen your team kit yet?
- Yeah.
- [Claire] Do you like it?
- It's really nice, yeah.
[drilling]
[Claire] People just think we have a car,
and it goes around the world
to every race.
A few guys change the tires on it,
and that's about it.
You have to depressurize,
so they both can get through there.
So we can get this all the way down.
[Claire] These cars
are extraordinarily complex.
There's 20,000 parts
that we're manufacturing ourselves.
[man 1] How many of these have we got?
- One for the moment?
- [man 2] Yeah, we're not gonna scrap it.
[man 1] No, no, no.
[Claire] When you are an independent team,
when you are a team
on a budget the size of ours,
it's an extraordinary challenge
to actually get your car to testing.
[man 3] The rear end is on there,
and the rear end
is actually structurally complete.
The mirror idea is a real winner.
Haven't heard that word for a long time.
- [man 3] Yeah.
- Jesus.
- [man 3] And it's...
- [Claire] New wing mirrors.
They could be the reversal of our fortune.
- [man 3] Yeah.
- [Claire] Something so simple.
[man 3] We are a very, very long way
behind having a finished car here
before we go to the test.
Massive challenge at the moment
is the delivery of diffuser.
[Claire] What's the issue
with the diffuser?
- What's the holdup on that?
- [man 3] Um...
The complexity of the parts
are delaying the delivery.
And we've got a host
of components which
We've got an issue with
the front bell crank
pivot shafts are not finished.
The pin for the tower bracket
we've somewhat lost track of.
These are for bigger problems that...
We haven't even got any wheel nuts
to hold the wheels on.
Have we not worked it out yet?
- [man 4] We're still digging into it.
- [man 3] Still digging into it.
[woman] Meeting with Mike and Nicky.
Did you say tomorrow?
[Paddy] No.
I need to speak with them today.
- Okay.
- [cell phone rings]
Hello?
Yes, speaking.
It's not all on schedule at the moment.
Uh, we have had a number of slippages.
There are 101 different issues
with the car that weren't expected.
They're all being dealt with,
and, inevitably, that means that things
can take longer than was planned.
Re-machine the holes? Change the dials.
But we will get to the test.
We always do.
- [Claire] Everything's all right?
- [man 1] Yeah.
[Claire] Still smiling?
- Yeah.
- [man 2] Good.
[Claire] It's in better shape
than it did yesterday.
Yeah. It's just frustrating,
the little bits of rig parts.
[Claire] Yes. Yes, I know.
It will be an extraordinary feat
if we make this on Monday, right?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- [Claire] Which we're gonna.
Yeah. We are.
- I'll leave you to it. We will.
- [man] I hope so. Yeah.
- See you later.
- [man] See you.
[indistinct chatter]
[Will] There are only eight days
of pre-season testing...
to put your car on track, figure out
what works, figure out what doesn't.
To be as ready as your rivals
once you get to the first race
of the year.
The big news really today is the fact
that Williams will not run today
and they won't run tomorrow, either.
The car isn't ready yet.
It was a huge shock.
With only eight days
of pre-season testing,
every second on track counts.
Missing half a day,
missing an hour is huge.
You don't miss testing.
[Claire] I'll take that one with me.
- [man 1] This one?
- Yeah.
- [man 1] And the other one?
- [man 2] This one's coming on this side.
They need to be very safeguarded.
- [man 2] I think I broke it.
- [Claire and man laughing]
- It's a million man-hours, right?
- [Claire] Yeah.
That is a lot of blood, sweat
and tears in there.
Realizing the car isn't going to be ready
for winter testing brings out disbelief.
It was like, "Are you kidding?
How did this happen?
How did we get to this point?
How do we protect the damage
that this is going to do?"
I was... I was incredibly angry.
Get these bits to the garage
'cause they need to start working on them.
They're gonna have their work
cut out this morning
getting all those bits on the car.
It would be so nice
to see it out on the track.
It's not been a good few days.
I'm hoping that when people
see it on track today,
everyone will have forgotten about it
and hopefully will bring us
a bit of performance.
And to have George and Robert,
it's really exciting.
I can't wait to see those guys
get in the car for the first time.
It'll be really nice.
[Will] It's not unheard of for parts
to be flown out last minute,
but when team management
are flying out with them,
you get the impression
it's pretty drastic.
[Claire] Here you go.
How you doing? You all right?
We've got your bits.
[Will] At times like this, you can't look
to the boys on the factory floor.
They're doing as much as they can
with the equipment at their disposal.
It has to go higher.
The ultimate question is
where does the buck stop?
Does it stop with the person appointed
to head that technical direction
and the ultimate design of the car,
or does it fall to the person
who made that appointment?
Whose head's on the block?
[Claire] Are you all right?
[Dave] Yeah.
It's just nice to see
the car in the garage.
Christ.
If we could've had it three weeks ago,
we'd be laughing.
Hi, Claire.
Hindsight, Dave, is a wonderful thing.
Hi, Paddy. You all right?
- How was your flight?
- Fine.
- [Paddy] Early?
- Yeah, it was early.
Got all the bits with you?
Got the bits. Yeah.
They're out at the back. Yeah.
[Claire sighs]
It happens
when you get out onto the grounds.
[Claire] Yeah.
All right, let's see those bits.
- Hi. You all right?
- [woman] Yeah. You?
- [Claire] Yeah.
- [woman] Good.
Yes. All good.
[reporter] But what has been
the reason of the delay?
We're not going to be discussing
those issues in public.
It's not ideal.
Um, this is not the situation
that we wanted to find ourselves in.
Particularly after last year.
We wanted to come out strongly.
That's one of the hardest parts
of the job,
when you're feeling down and you feel
like you couldn't be kicked anymore.
I'm getting a kicking at the moment
from every angle.
We're not just disappointed, but it's...
It's embarrassing not bringing
a race car to a circuit.
[Paddy] I don't need anyone else
to give me a hard time.
I'm my worst judge, let's say.
The bottom line is
we didn't do the right things.
We have many difficulties at the moment.
Lots of challenges to face.
I suppose it's part of my makeup
to not reflect any sense of panic.
I'm an engineer,
so problems are objective.
They're not emotional things
because emotions don't get us anywhere.
[engineer] You good?
- [George] Yeah. Ready for it.
- [engineer] Yeah?
Been ready for three days, mate.
[George] It feels like...
- This is how we normally do things.
- [George laughs]
We just leave it late.
Well, you can see there's a little bit
of a crowd around the Williams garage.
The good news for them is they have
finally got their car sorted out.
So, Williams up and running,
but a lot of questions being asked why
they initially missed the first two days.
[Paddy] Very large rank.
- [man 1] Sorry?
- Very large rank of media in here.
[man 1] Well, it's the only time
you've spoken in days.
[Claire] Yeah, we'll do that.
[Paddy] Work to do.
[man 2] Paddy, what happened?
Why was the car late?
Um, that is a very, very
complicated matter and I...
Frankly, I don't even know
the answer because it's...
It will take a lot of
investigation and analysis.
In general, the thing that
has got us out is the, uh...
The sheer quantity and complexity
of parts you have to produce
to make a Formula 1 car these days.
[Will] I spoke to Paddy over testing
and he refused to take responsibility.
You're either responsible or you're not.
So, you gotta take it on the chin.
And he kind of refused to do that, so...
[clicks tongue] See you later, Paddy.
[reporter] There have been some
big developments at Williams.
With immediate effect, Paddy Lowe,
"has taken a leave of absence from
the business for personal reasons."
[interviewer] Can we talk
about Paddy at all?
[Claire] There's no point
wasting that energy,
focusing on something
that's been and done.
You gotta move forward.
Formula 1 moves fast.
We gotta start racing
and that's where it really matters.
- Okay. Bye, girls.
- [Claire] Kisses. Can I get kisses?
- Bye.
- [Marc] See you later. See you later.
Girls, go inside before you get cold.
Have a nice breakfast.
- Bye, monkey.
- [Claire] Okay.
I've got butterflies in my stomach.
I always get them driving to Silverstone.
I wonder what George and Robert must
feel like going into this race weekend.
[Marc] I don't worry, necessarily.
I just worry that we can keep it.
That's really important to me.
Yeah.
And I'm fed up with drivers.
Buggering off, leaving us
to go somewhere else.
We nurture all this talent
and then they get to go off...
- They get their success somewhere else.
- Yeah.
I want to be the one
that gives a driver a good car.
Formula 1 is not easy.
Sometimes, I think to myself,
"Christ, when is it gonna get easier
and what more do we have to do
to close that gap down to the midfield?"
We're here in this sport
because we love racing.
We do not love being
at the back of the pack.
- Good morning!
- [George] Good morning.
Are you gonna get near
the podium this morning?
I will do my best,
but I can't promise anything.
- [woman 1] Of course he will.
- [George] Thank you.
- [woman 2] Good to see you.
- [man] Drive well.
Thank you. Likewise.
Nice to meet you.
Overall, it's not been ideal at all.
I mean, obviously, you dream of coming
into Formula 1 and winning races.
That's the dream.
[sighs] Morning.
Morning.
Just driving around on my own.
No one in front of me,
no one really behind me.
[man] Are you gonna race next year?
Can't tell you that.
- Sorry, I have to go.
- Go.
- I'll see you later.
- [woman] Go.
[George] Obviously, I want more.
I want to be a world champion.
I'd love to be in Lewis' shoes, you know.
In a car, firstly, capable of winning
almost every single weekend,
and performing to a level
that he performs week in, week out.
But I believe I'll get there one day.
I believe I'll have that opportunity.
[reporter] Difficult to show
your potential
when you're always
at the back of the grid.
No, it's not difficult at all
because the people
who will make a difference in my career,
the top people at Williams,
the top people at Mercedes,
they know exactly how I'm performing,
even if the result isn't
exactly the same every week.
So, I have no concerns with that.
Cheers, thanks.
[Will] George is on the Mercedes
young driver scheme,
so that means he has, at least in part,
his future assured.
I'm late for something, guys.
Cheers. Thank you.
The air condition's calibrated so
that the most power goes in my room.
- That's why the race took their team off.
- [woman] That's probably true.
- It's not true.
- [woman chuckles] I know.
[Will] Toto Wolff as head of Mercedes
has always been very impressed
and has always spoken
incredibly well of George.
Whether that means George will make it
into the big Mercedes team?
Only time will tell.
But it's certainly on George's radar.
It's really nice to see
the Mercedes junior program
- has come back to life.
- Yeah.
And we're taking the most potential
young guys, and here we go.
Firstly, Mercedes are the number one team
in Formula 1 and have been for so long.
They were the guys
who invested in my junior career
and ultimately really helped me
to make the step into Formula 1.
[Toto] It's very rare that a rookie
wins the F2 season.
So, he won the F2 season,
- and now we have a problem.
- [man] I saw it last year.
[all chuckle]
- He's gonna be a future world champion.
- [man] I know.
That's what some of my colleagues...
- [Toto] They say that.
- [man]...told me earlier this year...
- When you put me in your car, Toto.
- [Toto] Yeah.
That's the... [chuckles]
[Toto] That's the trick.
- Yeah.
- [laughs]
[announcer 1] Welcome to
the historic Silverstone Circuit
for the British Grand Prix.
[George] I am a rookie.
I don't have experience,
but I'm deadly serious,
and when it's got anything to do
with making me go quicker,
I'm definitely incredibly serious.
I need to work my socks off
to justify why I'm in Formula 1.
And show my true colors
that I can be a team player
and really build this team
through the tough times.
[Claire] George very much encapsulates
a Williams spirit.
He's got that, you know,
"I'm gonna just get on with it."
[announcer 2]
Last car approaching the grid.
[Claire] I'm so pleased that he's joined
Williams at the start of his F1 career.
And all I hope and pray is
that he is with us for a long time.
[engines revving]
[commentator] Everybody cleanly through
the first corner at Abbey.
It's the Williams bringing up the rear.
[George] It's all over the place.
Understeer is atrocious.
These brakes aren't improved.
We're gonna have to stop.
It's getting to the point of danger.
Struggling a lot.
Do we really need to leave me out here,
overtaken like this?
Hit me.
[Marc] Stay out. Stay out.
[George] However. Come on.
You don't wanna risk anything.
Car's all over the show.
[commentator] Lewis Hamilton wins
the British Grand Prix for a sixth time.
What a performance from him.
[George] Still quite incredible for me
how you can finish a lap,
it feels like one of the best laps
you've ever done in your life.
Still, in the scheme of things,
incredibly fast, but these guys
have just got something more.
We need to sort this out.
We really, really need to sort this out.
In my previous years, I had one target,
and that was, you either put it on pole
or win the race.
I'm driving around in 19th position
week in, week out and...
I don't wanna be there.
[Claire] I'm sure he's frustrated
by some things
that we haven't been able
to action fast enough.
I wish for both of them that
we'd given them a better car this year.
- It's pretty brutal out there.
- [George] Yeah. I know. Tell me about it.
[man] Frustrating, isn't it?
[Claire] You've gotta take the small wins
to make yourself feel good every so often.
Okay. We beat Vettel.
[laughs]
- Yeah. Exactly.
- [man] Yeah.
Yeah. We did.
You're not spraying champagne
each and every weekend.
Only one team can do that.
Only one driver can do that.
[George] It's just a joke at the moment.
I've never been
so inconsistent in my life.
You look at my lap chart,
you think I'm a bloody rookie or whatever.
I felt like I was driving very similar
lap after lap, and it was like a yo-yo.
I felt like an idiot.
We need to seriously pull our fingers out.
[man] Okay. All right.
We'll see what we can do about that.
Good job. Well done. Well done, thank you.
[Frank] No real point.
[Claire] No. We were only lapped once
which makes a change.
Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
[Claire] Certainly,
I feel enormous pressure
whether I'm good enough to do this job.
The pressure is there
because it is our family business
and I took this job on
for a very particular purpose,
and that was to protect a legacy.
- Is that it?
- [interviewer 1] All good.
- Yeah?
- [interviewer 1] Yeah.
Okay.
You didn't ask the last question about,
"Has Williams got a future
or is Williams going to be in trouble?"
- [interviewer 2] I didn't?
- No. [chuckles]
[interviewer 1] She didn't...
I was thinking when I read it, I was like,
"I am not answering that question."
And then I was thinking about it
and I said,
- "Maybe I should answer that question."
- [interviewer 2] Do you wanna answer it?
- You can.
- Yeah.
[interviewer 2] I was told you didn't want
to hear it because you shouldn't.
- I don't wanna...
- [Claire] No.
[interviewer 2] Make you answer
something you don't wanna answer.
You can ask me. Ask me the question.
[interviewer 2] So, is there a danger
that if this goes on,
- it could be the end of Williams for you?
- [Claire] Yeah. Okay.
Williams isn't on its way out
just 'cause it's had a few...
A couple of bad years.
We're fighters,
at the end of the day, at Williams.
That was what we do.
We will fight
whether we're winning the championship
or we'll fight
if we're losing the championship,
and we will continue
to fight in this sport
for many, many years to come.
You're Netflix?
Not anymore. Fuck you, Netflix.
[crowd cheering]
[man 1] This is where
I'll have my single life.
This is the no-go zone.
[man 2] What do you think you did better
than Pierre Gasly to grab his seat?
[chuckles]
[man 3] What the hell is he doing?
If I get knocked,
I try to knock even harder.
[man 4] Very hard
to keep up with that man.
- [yells indistinctly]
- [screaming]
[man 5] This is the best day of my life.