Let's just touch on Azerbaijan.
How pissed off were you that day?
Very.
The two Red Bulls go through.
Ricciardo fends off Max Verstappen.
We talked about it
before the race.
Both drivers had nodded in agreement
that they'd give each other space.
If you're Christian Horner,
you are not enjoying this for one second.
Verstappen is in no mood whatsoever
to yield to his teammate.
They have crashed!
They've gone into each other!
It was a low point, and I made my feelings
very clear to both drivers.
Fuck!
That's 25, 30 points
we've just fucked away there.
We were fighting for positions, but,
yeah, of course, you never want to crash
with your teammate.
I was sure of what happened.
You know, I was sure
that I wasn't the cause of it.
I was kind of made to feel guilty.
This year, I'm gonna be out of contract,
and I think, "What am I gonna achieve
doing one more year with Red Bull?"
You know, I could be happier...
having a fresh start.
- Bernie, Flavvy. Come here.
- Come on.
- Bernie, come  here.
- Bernie.
-Go on, back you go.
-He got kicked by a donkey yesterday.
Come on.
Look what we've got.
Look who's here.
- Max and Daniel.
- Yeah.
They are very similar to a couple
of donkeys on occasion.
Sometimes they love each other,
and sometimes they butt each other.
In fact, managing donkeys
is sometimes easier than...
managing drivers.
All these drivers,
they all have slight insecurities,
like any great sportsman.
Life has been made difficult at the moment
because we've got
this exciting emerging talent
in Max Verstappen.
Max isn't yet 21,
so, I think that they're just drivers
at different stages in their career.
By the time we get to the August break,
I'm going to be ready for some time off.
Yeah.
It's gonna be an important year
for Daniel in his career
because he's very much at a crossroads.
We'd love to extend the agreement
with him, but, do you know what?
If he doesn't want to be here,
that's Formula One.
It's-- It's a big boy sport.
So, what's coming up
in the next few races?
- Um, Monaco, next race.
- Is this one of your favorites?
Yeah. Be good to see Max
get a result.
Yeah.
So, they want an answer
from us as early as possible.
Who's out of contract then?
-Uh...
-Well, Lewis is going...
Lewis, Kimi, and Valtteri.
If Valtteri has a bad year,
how long are they gonna give him
before they make a decision about
-whether they want to keep him?
-Yeah, exactly.
Since joining Red Bull,
it's the first time I've ever had
to look for another contract or kind
of been in a position to negotiate,
to have discussions with other teams.
What's being weighed up by us now
is whether or not we make one
of those tactical moves somewhere else,
and the question is obviously, "Where?"
I guess the only thing
on my mind is get results now,
because the better I do, the better offers
I'm gonna have probably from other teams.
I obviously want to be fighting
for the World Championship.
Based on things as they are right now,
Merc and Ferrari would be there.
They're two obvious candidates,
but, you know...
anything can happen.
Yeah.
I don't really want to rush right now.
While Red Bull Racing are nowhere near
the competitive force that they were
when they won four
world championships in a row,
I think that pales into insignificance
when you see where Williams are
compared to where they were
at that same point in time.
Birdie.
Vroom, vroom, vroom.
Goes faster than our car.
You didn't hear that, Nate.
So, I am Claire Williams,
and I am the deputy team principal
of the Williams Martini Racing team.
Arms up. Ah, good boy.
Aw.
Williams is everything to me.
It's been in my family throughout
my whole life.
Started by my dad, Frank Williams,
back in 1977.
So, we've been racing for 41 years now.
It became an enormous success story
of the eighties and nineties...
winning 16 world championships,
114 races,
and all as a small, independent team
started by a boy with a dream
when he was very, very young.
My youth was spent
helping out around the team.
So, it really is everything.
It's a big part of what defines me.
But I do believe
since I took on my job back in 2013,
the world in which we operate
is a very different place
to when Williams first started.
They were up in third in 2014 and 2015,
but they've slowly been slipping back
and that's a hard thing to turn around.
We face
much greater competition.
We face much more
challenging circumstances
in which we have to race
and operate our team.
But sport's not supposed to be easy.
Winning isn't easy, and that's why
it's so amazing when you do,
because you deserve it,
and at the moment,
we don't deserve to win.
We've got to put the work in
if we're going to change that.
In just five years, they've gone from
fighting for pole positions and podiums
to scraping to get off the last row
of the grid.
You know, there's always a lot
of criticism, but you can't listen to it.
You just have to keep going
and believe that what you are doing
will make changes.
Now Williams are going to be getting to
the stage where they're trying to work out
if there's an ingrained problem
they need to change
Do they need to change
their whole outlook?
Um, this car
has not been performing as we'd expect.
The first few races, we were literally
the slowest team on the track.
I've been given
a wonderful opportunity,
and I only agreed to do it
because I thought at the time
that I could help
turn the business around.
To be very clear, we aren't going down
that road of a B-team.
Any of you that know me well would know
that it would be over my dead body.
You will never read in the press
that Williams has
turned itself
into a junior team or a B-team.
I've got this whole history
that I need to protect.
If, under my watch, that were all
to go horribly, horribly wrong,
it would be my fault.
Monaco looks like
it could be a painful weekend.
The car is clearly
the slowest in the field,
and more than just Formula One fans
watch Monaco,
because it's bonkers.
Monaco is
my favorite race on the calendar.
It's the most...
Monaco's the big one.
It's where all the glitterati are.
You've got the boats...
the harbor...
the celebrities.
It just exudes money,
glamour.
It's just a lot of cool shit
in a small space.
Monaco is Monaco.
It's the oldest race on the calendar.
It's the prestigious one.
So much heritage. So much history.
It's an absolutely incredible sight.
The cars roaring
round the circuit at fantastic speed.
The track
is the same that it has been
for pretty much all 76 Grand Prix.
All the greats have raced
and won in Monaco.
Fangio,
Graham Hill,
Ayrton Senna.
The pressure and the prestige
that goes with that race,
if you come out on top,
winning that Grand Prix,
it's bigger than anything else.
From a Red Bull perspective,
they'll have targeted this
from the very start the season.
Their car will be suited
to the Monaco Grand Prix circuit,
but Daniel will want to stand out,
because they've seemed to be putting
more and more weight
behind Max Verstappen for its future.
Well, Max has got
that sort of magic dust around him.
He's the next generation coming through.
I like that one.
That is ridiculous.
Yeah. How much do you think
that boat costs?
One point eight.
One point eight?
'Cause I've been
on that one in, uh, Ibiza.
Oh, yeah?
Honestly, you lose yourself on the boat
like compared to like...
You have to call other people like,
"Where are you  on the boat?"
Well, it's like a cruise ship.
My name is Max Verstappen,
driving for Aston Martin Red Bull Racing
in Formula One,
and I'm also
the youngest Formula One winner.
So, I live in Monaco. For me, it's just...
like I'm at home really.
Just a bit busier.
We are used to, like,
a hotel during a race weekend, so...
You have to do your own
clothes washing?
No. Luckily, my mom is here, so...
What would it mean for a driver
in Daniel's position
to know that this kid
who's come in as the young buck
is promised more than he's on?
That's gonna hurt.
I mean, look,
they've invested a lot in Max.
One thing that Red Bull love to do
is create headlines, break records.
If he could be the youngest ever
world champion,
that's-- that's a dream scenario for them.
There's clearly gonna be
tension within the team.
They're both fighting, in a sense,
for number one status.
Verstappen has the contract in place.
Daniel's looking for a new one...
and that will be playing on Daniel's mind.
Max is clearly one of the big names
of Formula One for the next ten years,
but Daniel is still
hugely important to Red Bull.
I just want you to know that
there are no number one drivers here.
You know, nothing would give us
greater pleasure than to see him...
achieve the world championship
in one of our cars.
Whatever he says,
I don't believe that's the relationship,
and I think Max is
their chosen star for the future.
And I hope he feels he's got...
you know, he's got
a huge amount of support in the team.
You know, there's no pressure
to have the youngest world champion
or anything like that.
If they really want me,
they need to put something awesome
in front of me and snap me up.
Thanks!
- Super.
- Thank you. See you on Friday.
- Thanks very much. See you later.
- Thank you so much. See you on Friday.
I think Monaco's going to be
a very tough race for us.
I hope that our little cars
get through it in one piece...
-and we get some points.
-Yes.
If we don't start scoring points,
that gap's just going to widen to a point
where we're not in the mix anymore.
We'll finish tenth.
No one wants to come last in any sport,
but particularly so in Formula One.
And it's all to do with money.
There's a sliding scale of payments,
and being bottom means
they get the smallest slice of pie.
The Ferraris, Mercedes,
they're all spending, you know...
north
of three, four hundred million dollars.
But our budget at Williams
is somewhat smaller than that
at about 125 sterling a year.
To win in Formula One, you need...
you need money.
This sport requires
financial help,
and that financial help
has to come from somewhere.
I'm Lance Stroll. I'm 19 years old,
and this is my second season
with Williams Martini Racing.
Yeah, I think
it's no great secret
that Lawrence has made an investment
based on his son having a seat.
And I don't think it can be underestimated
the impact that that can have.
Wait. Oh, yeah. All right.
But I also have to believe that he has
the best interests of the team at heart.
I know I'm born
with a silver spoon in my mouth,
but I've seen
paid drivers in the past not deliver.
But when I look at my rookie season,
I've proved a lot of people wrong.
Finishing on a podium,
starting on a front row.
Those are all big achievements,
if you ask me.
I strive to be the best I can be.
This is all the same, right?
This hasn't been resurfaced.
Well, supposedly, it's from seven
all the way around to 15.
Yeah, this one...
- has caught out a couple of people.
- Yeah.
Lawrence is a businessman,
and you don't keep throwing your money
at something that's not working for you.
So, for as long as the team provides
the basis for his boy to be able
to show what he can do,
then you can see him
still being a part of it.
But the second that doesn't happen,
you can be sure he's going to take
his money somewhere else.
This year with Williams,
on and off the track,
has been a frustrating experience.
I'm not gonna lie.
Yeah, there's, uh...
hopefully better times ahead.
It's the team's last chance
to get their cars set up right
ahead of qualifying this afternoon.
You know, we've got a good package here.
The drivers are in great shape.
You know, they both enjoy this track.
The car looks super...
Daniel, how does it feel...
...to work yourselves
back into this championship?
- Still some unfinished business.
- And you've come here to win?
To make the difference,
you have to risk it a bit more.
- Red Bull are the favorites.
- The favorites, do you feel as such?
I'm just looking forward to get started.
Our car works well in Monaco,
because Monaco has
the least straights of the year,
which means horsepower isn't everything,
so therefore, we're able to compensate
with a great chassis
and give the drivers confidence
they can run up close to the barriers.
They can extract that lap time
from the cars.
If you're Red Bull right now,
you really want to see
Max Verstappen win this race,
because you've invested in him.
You've put your faith in him
for the future,
but it's so hard to overtake.
You've got to do it in qualifying,
and that means pushing
to the absolute limit,
and that's why Saturday
is spectacular here.
I've always come
into Monaco fired up.
It's the most difficult circuit
on the calendar.
It's the circuit with
the most smallest margin for error.
I think a race win
is definitely possible here in Monaco.
I've been...
I think, driving a lot better.
I've been in qualifying
really strong compared to Daniel as well.
I'm feeling good.
Finally a chance to see
if Red Bull really are in fighting form
as Max Verstappen heads out for practice.
Max Verstappen makes his way
onto the track.
This will be a good indication
of what he'll be able to do
come qualifying this afternoon.
Well, Max has got that sort of
magic, beautiful driving style.
It is a tough track.
It's always, you know, bumpy, low grip.
If you have a little slide,
you can end up in the wall.
Max Verstappen
on the fastest lap of the session so far.
You won't meet any driver
hungrier than Max Verstappen.
He wants to be fastest on every session,
every race. It's fantastic.
Oh, someone's hit a barrier.
It's Max Verstappen.
One of the favorites for pole position
later on this afternoon
has absolutely clobbered the barriers.
You just think, "Fuck it."
He was just pushing too hard, too soon.
He made a silly mistake.
Red flag for a Red Bull.
It's a red flag.
Stay to the left-hand side.
It's parked to the right.
He's given his team a massive
repair job to get that car ready
for the qualifying session.
It is painful,
because if it has a bad outcome...
you are even more angry.
You've got a pretty small window
of time of about two hours
to get the car turned around
and into qualifying.
I've got confidence in the mechanics,
but there's nothing guaranteed.
Max Verstappen's chips
scattered right now.
What are the odds of his car
making qualifying after his earlier crash?
Arguably, the most exciting
qualifying session of the season
is here in Monte Carlo.
Qualifying today, very, very important.
Lance Stroll in the Williams
heading out for his session.
Loud and clear.
Thank you.
Showing Luca on the radio.
-  Loud and clear.
- Thank you.
See how he goes this afternoon.
Lance struggled moving around a lot
in the seat in the first session.
He was moving around too much.
So, anyway, they've tried to fix it.
-Tell me that was fixed.
-It hasn't happened before.
-No, it's the first time all season.
-Okay, well, let's hope it's a one-off.
They think the belts
were just getting loose all session.
Okay. All right.
Let's hope it's a one-off then, Lawrence.
Target for now, plus 30 seconds.
Taking temp out of the rear.
It's quite busy into the corner now.
Everybody on slow laps.
The fricking headrest is loose.
-Fucking hell.
-It's okay.
Just fix it.
Okay, we'll do it next time around.
Okay, Lance. We need four tenths,
and we need a twelve nine
to get through, okay?
I'm really suffering with traction
and all those kind of things.
Oh, this is on the edge now.
Too much understeer, guys.
It can't go quicker like this.
And that's a 1:13.3
for Lance Stroll.
Another disappointing performance
for Williams.
They'll be starting towards
the back of the grid on race day.
Breaking news from Red Bull.
Max Verstappen, one of the favorites
to take poll this afternoon
out of qualifying
before he even gets going.
We managed to get the car turned around,
but, unfortunately,
when firing up the engine,
suddenly we saw a big oil leak
from the gear box.
There was no chance then
to make the qualifying.
He's a very, very fast driver.
We know that. That's not within any doubt.
This place bites hard if you abuse it,
and unfortunately, there's no more
brutal lesson than what he's just had,
so, uh, you know, I'm sure that he's
smart enough to hopefully learn from that.
All Red Bull's hopes now rest
with Daniel Ricciardo.
Can he beat Ferrari and Mercedes
to start in pole position on race day?
Lewis Hamilton is flying.
Here comes Vettel.
Okay, mate. Currently P1...
Six tenths quicker
than everyone else at the moment.
- So everyone's slow behind?
- Yeah, everyone's slow behind.
Hülkenberg behind is slow.
Räikkönen also slow behind him.
Grid position is everything.
If you drive in the middle of the road
in a race,
it's almost impossible for the car behind
to be able to overtake.
So, the intensity of qualifying
becomes even more important.
The streets of Monaco
are so tight.
Everything's coming at you so fast.
Max Verstappen watches on.
He can do nothing.
You are now quickest by two tenths.
Okay.
Sebastian Vettel has taken
front row at the moment as we go on.
This is gonna be so close.
Daniel Ricciardo, he was on pole,
of course, here in 2016,
crosses the line
now you're going to the one-tens.
What a lap!
Pole by a country mile.
Whoo hoo!
And that is pole position.
Nice job, mate.
Fuck, yes!
Delighted for the pole,
but we should've had two cars up there,
and, uh... it's frustrating to not have
both cars on the front row of the grid.
All right, that's 50% done.
Let's finish this shit tomorrow.
Until I lift that trophy
and feel that weight,
um, I won't be completely satisfied.
I don't think Daniel's putting
a foot wrong at the moment.
If the team have got
question marks in anybody,
it's why they've spent
so much money on Max.
Max put it in the wall
trying to prove to the world
that he was quicker than Daniel.
And he sacrificed his entire weekend
for what? For nothing.
Daniel is starting to stand out
as the more consistent
and the more stable option
that Red Bull have got.
So if Daniel then delivers again here
and Max misses
another opportunity to win,
you wonder if doubts will creep in
at Red Bull about whether
they've put their money
behind the right driver at this stage.
In percentage terms,
how confident are you of keeping him?
Um, it's always difficult
to put a number on these things,
but we're very, very happy with Daniel.
He does a great job in the team.
He's a popular member in the team,
and there's a desire for us
to retain him for next year.
This is what it's all about
when it comes to motor racing.
There is one place to be today,
and that is here in Monte Carlo.
Daniel Ricciardo in pole position.
Sebastian Vettel in second.
And because of his disaster in qualifying,
Max Verstappen will start
right at the back in last place.
Max, how are you doing this morning?
Not so good.
If we could get points
on one car,
that would be a great achievement,
but if we could get both cars,
even better.
If there was a huge great pileup
at the start of the race
and our cars just went through,
one can only dream, can't you?
Ten less than P3.
The waiting sucks.
I just want this race to start already.
I feel, this year, with the car we've got,
you know, since 2016,
it's my best chance to win.
Basically the win was taken from me
through no fault of my own.
Got the first pole position of my career.
I had a comfortable lead.
Daniel Ricciardo is looking
set to win the Monaco Grand Prix.
Okay, Dan, now box this lap,
please. Box this lap.
The team called me in,
and I come in the pits,
and there's no tires there.
And it's like a shit show.
They haven't got
the tires ready. The tires aren't ready.
The pit stop, instead of being
three seconds, it was more than ten.
Ricciardo is sat there, waiting.
I come out the pits,
and literally see Lewis just come past me.
Hamilton now leads
after a pit-stop that saw
Daniel Ricciardo sat stranded
waiting for his tires.
So, I lost the race.
Right now, I don't want to hear it.
I don't want to hear anything. I, uh...
I want to get out of here, to be honest.
This one hurts a lot.
2018. This is my time.
It's my fucking time.
If he can go and win this race
and beat Max,
that tells Red Bull that they need
to put their faith in him,
but that might not be his main priority.
He might think, "I need to show myself
as a great opportunity for another team,
a Mercedes or a Ferrari."
The 2018 Monaco Grand Prix.
It is time to get down
to the serious business.
As we count down
towards the start of this race...
The driver can make
the difference around this track.
The story so far, Daniel Ricciardo
in the Red Bull,
has dominated the whole weekend.
Every single practice session,
every single qualifying.
Verstappen had the chance for pole,
but it's 20th and last for the Dutchman.
What can Ricciardo do
from the front of the grid?
Will good fortune shine
on Williams
with Lance Stroll in 17th place?
The grid is cleared in Monaco
with Daniel Ricciardo on pole position.
It's a tense moment
as the lights go on.
Vettel is trying to attack
into turn one!
But he's not quite close enough.
Ricciardo leading, but Vettel is
very, very close to the back of him.
The gap behind to Vettel, one point one.
So far everything feels all right.
Max Verstappen's already gone past
Grosjean and Magnussen.
Is he gonna try and launch one?
He is, down the inside. On Lance Stroll.
- Nice move, Max. Well done.
- Yep.
With this pace, he can just
keep picking these off one by one.
Lance Stroll
fighting with Leclerc.
Oh, a bit of contact.
What's the problem with the car?
Something happened.
I think the front wing is damaged.
And so it's a front wing change
and the tires.
Daniel, you're doing
a really good job, mate.
That's really good stuff.
You just need to keep it smooth.
I got it, buddy.
Ricciardo still leading
Sebastian Vettel.
And box, Daniel, Box. Box.
Box this lap.
Remember the pit-stop
that cost him victory here in 2016.
Yes, boys.
Ricciardo relieved
that that pit-stop went okay.
Yeah, no problems
this time around for Daniel Ricciardo.
He's still smiling this afternoon.
Let's keep it focused, mate.
Keep it focused.
Verstappen gets
a really good exit. He's gonna go for it.
Of course he is. He's Max Verstappen.
Yes! Whoo!
Verstappen moves up
into ninth place.
Ricciardo seems
to have a problem.
And you can see it,
slowing down dramatically.
I see trouble brewing.
I'm losing power.
Let me know if I can do something.
Fail one fail. Fail one fail.
This could totally change the race.
Will it get better?
Negative, Daniel. Negative.
The MGU-K failed.
That usually means the engine is screwed
and it's 99% you have to retire the car.
The minute Daniel Ricciardo
makes a mistake,
Sebastian Vettel is all over him.
This is like a moment of defeat.
A moment of helplessness.
Part of you just wants to rip
the steering wheel off and just throw it.
How is this happening?
How long can Daniel Ricciardo
keep Sebastian Vettel behind him?
Can he keep him behind him?
I know it's hard,
but keep it focused.
Yeah, I got no power though.
To finish first,
first you have to finish.
Lance Stroll is two laps
behind the race leader now.
The brake pedal's
going really, really long.
Concentrate on turn 19.
I don't understand.
It's ridiculous.
What's the point in even racing now?
Stroll's just struggled
with the car all weekend long.
I tell you what,
it never rains, but it pours.
For Williams at the moment,
it is pouring.
Vettel now pushing harder.
Ten laps of focus. Ten laps to go.
This problem that
Daniel Ricciardo's had for so, so long
is still being managed.
It was just totally intense,
because he couldn't get beyond sixth gear,
'cause there just wasn't the power.
You gotta feel for him
in that cockpit at the moment.
His nerves are gonna be
shredded to pieces.
Keep putting pressure. You're doing well.
Head down till the end.
He will make a mistake.
It's out of your control.
But then you think, if I start playing
the sad story, then it's not gonna help.
There are three laps to go.
Daniel, you're doing
a really good job, mate.
Very impressive.
I'm thinking, "We're leading
the Monaco Grand Prix.
I don't care if this engine goes bang."
Yeah, we can win it.
So, let's fucking win it.
It's a big lockup for Vettel.
Can he get it stopped?
Just about.
Stoffel Vandoorne isn't
in the battle for the lead,
but he's come out between
the two leaders after his pit-stop.
Is this believable
what this guy is doing?
I would imagine Ricciardo
is starting to smile
just that little bit more.
Ricciardo starts his final lap.
You can't deny,
he really does deserve it this weekend.
Today at Monte Carlo,
it's redemption day for Daniel Ricciardo.
Daniel Ricciardo, you are our hero.
Un-fucking-believable.
Yes!
To see your car and driver
cross the line first
is like no other feeling in the world.
It's very difficult to come
to terms with when you're not winning.
We haven't won a race now
for nearly six years.
That's a long time.
When should I go,
"Actually, do you know what?
Maybe I'm not the right person to do this.
Am I good enough to do it?
Do I have the capability?"
There they are. Wanna hold it?
Oh, here you go.
Wow.
It's the most
proudest parents in town.
Oh!
-Oh, well done, you.
-Thanks, mate.
- Oh, you did. He did. He did.
- That was class.
I'm not sure whether the price
has gone down or up.
-Amazing. Amazing.
-Unbelievable.
He did
an unbelievable job today, eh?
Well, you know, it's just really painful.
It'll come.
You know. So, be happy
for your teammate today.
- Yeah, yeah, sure.
- Celebrate with him.
You know how this business is.
-It's up and down.
-Yeah.
I should have won that race,
and seeing the whole team happy,
it's hard.
Because you're standing there,
you have to try and smile and be happy,
'cause the whole team's happy, but--
Yeah, for me, it was definitely
the worst moment
and I was really not happy.
I could literally...
break down
the whole Energy Station by myself.
I was so thrilled,
because I knew what it meant to him.
Yeah.
It was the best.
Yeah!
I want to be
the best in the world,
and I believe I've got the talent
and I've put in the work.
Without getting arrogant,
certainly gonna have some--
some serious offers on the table.
Yeah!
Comments from Red Bull
involving the engine
has been a step too far.
The red line crossed.
That is a big, big issue.
We've been paying to fly in first class,
but ended up with an economy ticket.
We need to see that people respect us.
The relationship
with Cyril's been difficult.
Every single race win
that Red Bull had was with Renault.
He's an emotional guy.
You never know what you're gonna get.
Crunch time.
And it means a lot
to be racing against Red Bull.
We need to make a decision.