[Christian] Ah! [chuckles]
Ah!
We've got Rice Krispies on the dog.
It's like a chimp's tea party, isn't it?
Can I have some poached eggs, please?
When you get the chance.
What's your favorite car, Mol?
[Olivia] A digger!
[Christian chuckling] A digger? A digger!
She's coming, everyone, hide!
[shushes] Monty, get down! Get down!
[chuckles]
- Hey!
- [Christian] Hi!
[Geri] Hey! Hi, darling!
- No, I haven't seen the children.
- [children] Hey!
- [Christian chuckles]
- [Geri] Hey!
Mommy!
[Monty] Go!
[Geri] Hi.
[Christian] Right.
- Who's your favorite driver, Bluey?
- Lewis Hamilton.
[Christian] You're winding me up now,
aren't you?
You're winding me up!
Who's your favorite driver?
Sebastian.
Sebastian?
Who's your favorite driver?
- [Bluebell] Please say Max Verstappen.
- [Monty] Max.
- Oh! We got a Max fan.
- [Bluebell] Yay! [chuckles]
And Daddy.
[Christian] And Daddy.
Daddy's not the driver, though. So...
[Geri] Christian,
who's your favorite driver?
Who's my favorite driver?
[Geri] Come on, tell the truth.
[Christian] Well...
I don't know...
Uh...
Who is ever winning for us.
[Christian] Last season,
we lost Daniel Ricciardo.
Did I say his name right?
- [interviewer] Ricciardo?
- [woman] Riccardo.
- Is it Ricar... Riccardo or...
- He only drove for us for five years.
- [man laughs]
[woman] Yeah.
- So, Riccardo?
- [woman] Riccardo.
Yeah, we lost Daniel Ricciardo.
For us, that was slightly unexpected.
All right, good, that's great.
[man 1] Remove the smile.
Be a bit more intense.
[man 2] Couple more. Hold it.
Thanks, Max. Okay.
[Christian] Max is
arguably the hottest property
in Formula 1 at the moment.
[man 2] Little bit more
smile with your eyes.
Yep. There. Good, that's great.
So, we had to think long and hard
about who would be the right teammate
for Max Verstappen.
[man 2] Pull your helmet back
a little bit if you can.
- [Christian] It's a tough gig.
- Nice. That first look up.
Money. So good.
[Christian] Looking within our own
talent pool, to step into that seat,
Pierre Gasly was the obvious candidate.
[commentator 1] That's Pierre Gasly.
He's come fourth for Toro Rosso.
[crowd cheers]
[commentator 2] That's one of the greatest
Grand Prix finishes.
[all cheering]
[Christian] Product of
the Red Bull Junior team,
he stepped up into the lead team.
[Pierre] Coming to Red Bull
was a really special moment.
I tried to stay calm...
even though inside me, there was, like,
so much fire and I wanted to explode.
[man] Nice. Big smiles.
[laughs]
[Max chuckles]
Oh, here he is. [chuckles]
I didn't see you. You good, man?
No, I was like,
"Why are they laughing at me?"
[man] I'm sorry, Pierre.
We didn't mean to laugh at you.
- [Pierre] Money. Money, money...
- [man] Money in the bank!
[Pierre] Hello.
Who the fuck are you? [chuckles]
I'm Pierre Gasly. And you?
[Christian] Now, Max is extremely
impressive for a 21-year-old.
[all cheering]
[Max] Yes!
[Christian] Race winner,
what a debut. Fantastic.
At the Barcelona race in 2016,
winning on his debut.
[commentator] Well done to Max Verstappen.
[Christian] Eighteen years of age.
But don't underestimate Pierre Gasly.
He's a great talent.
What is your earliest memory
of racing each other?
[both chuckle]
[Max] You know what
I'm going to say, right?
You know what I'm gonna say.
- 2010 La Conca.
- [Pierre] Yeah.
- [both laugh]
- [Pierre] You fucking bastard.
Wow. So, the story was,
I had to start every heat...
Six heats on Friday and Saturday
behind Pierre.
- [chuckles] But...
- How many... How many times...
How many times did I push Pierre
off the track in the first corner?
But this is actually
my first memory as well,
like, really fighting...
Fighting each other.
[Christian] The biggest question mark
we have is,
"Is he gonna be up to the task, delivering
at the kinda level of Max Verstappen?"
Monaco's the big event of the year.
Morning.
Last year was a fantastic race for us.
Winning the Grand Prix.
So there's that pressure.
Everybody's expecting to see the Red Bull
cars near the front of the field.
Good morning, gents. Hi.
Good morning, Nige.
[indistinct chatter]
[Max] What do you think?
- Looks sick! [chuckles]
- [Max] Nice! [chuckles]
[Pierre] Monaco is really something
that gives me goosebumps.
There's no track in the calendar
that is that challenging for us drivers,
so, it's a mental challenge.
Max is one, if not the best driver
on the grid at the moment.
So, it pushes me
because I know it's possible
to achieve these kind of performances.
[indistinct chatter]
I think what is the most important
is that we get the best out of each other
and that's, at the end of the day,
the best also for the team.
[Christian] Of course, both drivers get
exactly the same equipment.
[indistinct chatter]
You are measured directly
against your teammate.
[man and Pierre speak French]
- [in English] You good?
- [man] Yeah, you?
[Christian] And we need both of those cars
scoring as many points as we possibly can.
[Christian] You all right?
Are you driving today or not?
- [Pierre] Am I driving?
- Are you driving this morning...
- [Pierre] Yeah.
- [Christian] Okay.
- So, we're just hanging out.
- [both chuckle]
Just make sure the car looks like that
at the end of session.
[Pierre] Yeah, definitely.
[Christian] Pierre Gasly. His career at
Red Bull Racing got off to a bad start.
He crashed twice in pre-season testing.
Did close to €2 million worth of damage.
That knocked his confidence.
And Monaco is a track
that is all about confidence.
For Pierre, that just
makes life even harder.
[Pierre] The car pull is good.
[engineer] Lift your pace now.
[Pierre] Okay, copy, it's good.
[engineer] Excellent, Pierre.
[Pierre] Oh!
- Fuck!
- [commentator] Gasly makes a mistake.
A cold shiver down his back,
I'm sure, now.
[Christian] Ouch.
[engineer 1] Did you see how close
he came to binning this one?
- Yeah.
- [engineer 2] He caught it quite well.
- He caught it nicely!
- Yeah.
[engineer 1] Yeah, fortunately.
Then needed to come in
and change his underwear, I think!
[engineer 1] I reckon he did, too.
[Pierre] Where I lose a lot is, uh...
the chicane.
- [Christian] Yes.
- [Pierre] Yeah.
At the right-hander,
you seem to come in...
- Later.
- ...later. I see you taking a later apex.
Yeah. And then after, I'm also slower,
so I go on the gas...
And then you got a bigger turn...
- For the left one. Yeah.
- ...for the left.
[Pierre] Yeah. For sure...
It's wrong.
I don't need anyone to tell me,
"That's what you need to do."
Because the target they set me
is lower than the one I set to myself.
That's the way I work.
[Christian] Right, usual street race.
- Don't be a hero.
- [Pierre] Yeah. In the first lap.
- In the first fucking lap.
- [Pierre] Yeah.
Okay?
- Just go with the track.
- [Pierre] This should be good.
[Christian] The circuit's
going to be horrible.
- Just keep building up.
- [Pierre] Yeah, I know.
All French drivers go well here.
It's almost compulsory.
- So, it'll be all right.
- [Pierre] Yeah.
[Christian] Formula 1
is all about pressure.
We need Pierre to deliver
week in, week out.
The expectation is you gotta perform,
and I think, if he can do that here,
that'll just give him a lift in confidence
and set him up nicely for the races ahead.
[man cheering]
[engineer] Thirty seconds.
[Pierre] Okay.
[engines revving]
[Christian] Take care.
[David] And the Monaco Grand Prix
is go!
Bottas tries to cover up Verstappen.
It's wheel-to-wheel.
Bottas just squeezes ahead.
So, it's Hamilton, Bottas, and Verstappen,
the top three.
[commentator] There's Pierre Gasly.
Down in seventh.
[Pierre] Monaco, it gives you
so much adrenaline.
Being as fast as you can,
but without losing the concentration,
otherwise you're in the wall.
Your level of focus is just so high.
You switch to a different mode.
Unconscious.
You do based on your feeling,
you just switch to a different person.
[engineer] Keep doing this pace.
[Pierre] Okay.
[all] Oh!
[Martin] Leclerc's hit the barrier!
He's got a right rear puncture.
Pieces of Ferrari everywhere.
- [engineer] We've got safety car.
- [Max] Safety car.
[engineer] Safety car.
Keep your dash posted.
Max, box and confirm, Max.
Box pit confirm, mate.
[Max] Yeah.
[commentator] So while the track
is being cleared,
the drivers dive into the pits
for a change of tires.
Who's going to come out first?
[Martin] Oh!
[David] Verstappen looks like
he's ahead of Bottas.
He is ahead of Bottas.
[commentator] The Red Bull team
have gained a position in the pits.
[David] Verstappen now in second.
[commentator] Pierre Gasly in sixth place.
Four places behind his teammate.
[engineer] Pierre,
keep looking after your tires.
Let's get this car home.
[Pierre] Okay, copy.
[engineer] This is good, Max.
Keep the pressure up.
- [Max] How many laps to go?
- [engineer] Ten laps remaining.
[David] Verstappen is really taking
the fight to Lewis Hamilton here,
the championship leader.
[engineer] You can overtake Hamilton
and drive off into the distance.
[Max] I'm trying to.
[engineer] I'll leave that with you, mate.
Come up.
[Lewis] Those tires
aren't feeling too good, huh?
Left front is dead.
[Bono] Okay. Copy, Lewis.
[engineer] Come on, Max.
Keep the pressure up, mate.
[Martin] Verstappen smells a victory here.
- Go on, Max!
- Go on!
[Lewis] Tire doesn't want to turn.
These tires are dead.
We need to hope for a miracle.
He's on my ass.
I think I'm in big trouble, guys.
- [engineer] Okay, Max, last lap.
- [Max] Yeah.
Thread the needle.
- [engineer] You got this.
- [Max] I'm trying.
[David] Here goes Verstappen!
Oh! They've made contact!
[all] Oh!
[Max] Shit, shit, shit.
- [engineer] That's a good effort, mate.
- [Max] Ah!
[David] Hamilton wins
the Monaco Grand Prix!
[engineer] You drove
like a lion today, Max.
You gave it everything.
It was so, so unlucky.
- Really unlucky. You drove your heart out.
- [Max] Yeah!
We deserved more.
[engineer] It will come. It will come.
[David] Pierre Gasly
with a fifth-placed finish in the end.
[Pierre] Thanks, boys. Was good.
The car was really super-fast.
[Christian] So, Pierre, obviously,
he got a decent result in Monaco,
but he was nowhere near
the pace of the lead group.
Being a really competitive guy,
I want everything to be perfect.
Coming into a new team,
new people around me...
You need to be patient,
but it's also difficult at the same time,
because I want this to be at 100%,
I want this to be at 100%.
I want myself to be at 100%.
I just want it to come straightaway.
[Will] It's incredibly hard for Pierre.
When you line up alongside Max Verstappen,
even your best day
is gonna look like failure.
[Christian] Formula 1
can take over your life.
Come on, then.
We're going to go see the helicopter.
[indistinct chatter]
[Christian] For me, this year is busy.
Obviously, my wife's busy with
doing her stuff as well.
Give us a hug.
- [Monty] Bye, Daddy, take care.
- See you later.
[Geri] Bye, girls.
What? Do you just want one of me?
[Christian] Come on, Geraldine. You'll be
late for your own fucking concert.
- Bye!
- Stop right now, thank you very much.
- [Geri] Thank you very much.
Somebody with a human touch.
Not...
- Hey, you!
- Always on the run. Gotta slow it down...
- Always on the run. I've got that.
[Christian] Pierre, it's going to be
a make-or-break season for him.
He will be putting pressure on himself
because he will, obviously, be looking
to gauge himself against Max.
And inevitably, the media will be
looking at, "How does he compare?"
- Hi, there.
- Ready?
Right.
If he can find that confidence,
he's a very capable racing driver.
Whether he's at Max's level,
I don't honestly know.
Only time will tell if he's capable
of running at the front in Formula 1.
I'm knackered.
- [Geri] Yeah?
- [Christian] It's a big weekend.
[Geri] Mine is like having to do
12 Monacos in the space of three weeks.
Yeah, and you get... You get
one or two weeks off between each...
I've gotta do it, like, one,
then day off, another two.
Actually, I've gotta do three in a row.
Just saying.
[whispering] I work harder. [chuckles]
[crowd cheering]
[engineer] Pierre, pick up your pace.
[Pierre] Yeah, I'm trying to.
Gasly is poor.
Right. But he's losing four-tenths...
...in the last two corners.
It's like...
Which, I think, you or I could do.
[Christian] His pace looked quite a bit
off his teammate.
- Okay, mate. Just keep building up to it.
- Okay. Yeah.
The more you relax, the faster you go.
- [Pierre] Exactly.
- [Christian] Yeah?
Pierre spends an awful lot of his time
looking at data.
Too much so.
He's not driving on instinct.
At this level, you can't do that.
He needs to stop screwing his own head,
measuring himself against Max,
and let it flow.
[commentator] It's a beautiful day
in Montreal.
A spectacular setting
for the Canadian Grand Prix.
What a thrilling race we have in prospect
here this afternoon.
[engineer] Radio check.
[Pierre] Radio okay.
[Will] There's a frustration
that's building within the team.
That's a big pressure on young shoulders.
The difference that marks the greats out
is how they deal with
the big pressure moments.
They embrace that pressure
and it's those high-pressure moments
that you get found out at.
[Pierre] I'm feeling confident.
Things are gonna work out,
and then, you will see.
[breathing heavily]
[David] It's Sebastian Vettel that leads
from Lewis Hamilton and Charles Leclerc.
Ricciardo is ahead of Gasly.
[engineer 1] Close up to Ricciardo.
[Pierre] Okay, copy.
[engineer 1] Push, Pierre. Push.
[David] Gasly starting
to come under pressure.
- Come on, come on.
- Come on!
[engineer 1] We cannot keep doing this.
Push, Pierre. Push.
[Pierre] Yeah, I'll try to.
[engineer 2] It's a good start, Max.
Take your time.
[Max] Okay.
[Max] I still need to gain
six, seven seconds, right?
[engineer 2] You're about three and a half
seconds shy at the moment.
Now press and hold the overtake button.
[Max] Okay.
[all clapping]
[Max] What I like about racing
is driving on the limit
of what you can do as a person,
but then, also, being so close
to the ground and being that quick,
overtaking and stuff.
Just confidence...
feeling...
and rhythm.
[David] Here's Verstappen.
He's up into sixth place.
[engineer] Push, Pierre.
Push, Pierre.
[David] Pierre Gasly is behind
by quite some margin.
[engineer] Close up.
Close up. Get past him. Quickly.
[Pierre] Argh!
[David] Lewis Hamilton wins
the Canadian Grand Prix!
[commentator] Max Verstappen charged up
from ninth to finish fifth.
But his teammate, Pierre Gasly,
slid backwards to eighth.
[Christian] Pierre, I forget the car
that he was stuck behind,
but there's nothing dynamic
about the drive.
We want the drivers to be heroes.
If he crashes a car, trying,
if he's going for it, I don't care.
What we don't wanna be doing is finish
in sixth or seventh or eighth or ninth.
That has no value to us.
[chuckles]
Honestly, I remember
that weekend so, so much.
[Jean-Jacques] The first Grand Prix,
Formula 1 of Pierre,
for us, it's, uh...
it's very, very amazing.
[Pierre] It's always fantastic
to have my parents around.
I don't really see them
so much anymore, you know.
I left home at 13.
All the time, I was in racing and karting.
[in French] I really want to win
everything. I want to win every year.
[crowd cheering]
[in English] It wasn't easy for my family.
They gave everything they had.
And they have been through
difficult situations just to support me
and try their best
to make my dream happen.
[in French] It's Pierre's first
karting all-in-one suit.
He was only nine
when he started competition.
It is very precious to me.
He wore it all weekend.
He only took it off to go to sleep!
[in English] So... Okay.
I've spent only one and a half years
in Formula 1,
and of course things are not perfect.
But Max, he does the job perfectly,
always extracting everything
from the car, so...
I just need to use that
and use the experience and the talent
he has to develop myself even quicker.
[Christian] The Red Bull Ring.
It's our home race.
[crowd cheering]
[Christian] We have a home crowd
and huge expectations that go with that.
[announcer] Max Verstappen is here!
[journalist] Red Bull has a reputation
for being rather ruthless
with drivers who don't perform
at the level of their teammates.
Are you sort of worried?
No, not really. I think at the moment,
it's clear, you know.
No one is happy and I'm the first one
not happy with the performance.
Um... And then, yeah, that's not pleasant
and no one is happy about it, so...
You know, he's just getting a headfuck
at every race at the moment.
Confidence then gets hit
and becomes self-perpetuating.
And the pressure just builds
and builds and builds.
[indistinct chatter]
[man] They ask you a question
and sometimes you go on a bit.
You know, they can only ask
so many questions. So, you know...
So if you give a concise answer
then you're helping yourself.
[Pierre] Yeah.
[music playing]
How do you cope with this situation?
With the rumors
that you will lose your seat on...
- Yeah...
- Yeah, you're smiling,
but that's not a fact of smiling.
[Pierre] I don't have anything to say.
You know, rumors...
All the media, like, some of them,
I'd just like to tell them "fuck off,"
because some of these things are not fair.
You know, a lot of people
try to break your dreams.
You gotta stay strong mentally
and keep going.
Thank you.
[man] Fuck! That wasn't easy.
[Pierre] Yeah.
[man] You all right?
[Christian] He's shown flashes
of real speed.
That's what you're capable of.
Now, it's a matter
of brushing himself down,
ignoring all the negativity
that he's getting
and to see if he can actually
realize the potential
that we know and still think that he has.
It's now down to him
to turn this situation around.
[crowd cheering]
[engineer] Max, let's get it done.
Let's do it.
[Max] Yeah. I hear you.
[crowd cheering]
Come on!
[commentator 1] Verstappen
making it look easy out there.
Next up, Räikkönen.
[crowd cheering]
[commentator 1]
Verstappen now up into fifth place.
[Max] Yes, boys. Come on.
[engineer] Yes, boys, indeed! Nice job.
[engineer] Pierre, get past him quickly.
Get through.
[commentator 1] Oh! And Gasly is
struggling to find a way past him.
[engineer] You can't stay there, Pierre.
Increase your pace.
Max, come on, mate.
[Max] All good.
[David] Max Verstappen is up
into the podium positions.
- And they absolutely love that!
- [crowd cheering]
[David] Max Verstappen manages
to clear Valtteri Bottas.
- Come on!
- [Max chuckling] Yes.
[engineer] Well done, Max.
[David] And he is back up
to second once again.
Verstappen.
There is no stopping him today.
[commentator 1] Pierre Gasly could well
be lapped by his teammate.
[crowd cheering]
[commentator 2]
There's the blue lights flashing.
Warning him he's about to be lapped.
[commentator 3] The leader, Leclerc,
is behind, Max right behind him.
[commentator 4] Gasly is duty bound
to get out of the way.
[David] Charles Leclerc
leads the Austrian Grand Prix.
Max Verstappen behind him.
[engineer] All right, this is game on.
Game on.
[man] Come on, Max!
[David] Leclerc goes off the track.
Max Verstappen!
[crowd cheering]
[cheering]
[David] He leads the Austrian Grand Prix!
[crowd cheering]
[engineer] Mate?
[Max] Yes, boys! Come on. Yes!
[engineer] Absolute class of the field.
Awesome.
[David] Verstappen wins
the Austrian Grand Prix.
[Christian] Amazing!
Amazing! Fuckin' hell.
- [Newey] We needed that one.
- [Christian] Yeah!
[Max] Whoa, mate! [laughs]
Oh, God, great job, boys.
[crowd cheering]
[all applauding]
[engineer] P-seven, Pierre.
Max, one.
Pierre?
[Pierre] Congrats to Max.
I screwed it up again.
[Christian] Max, you drove a mighty race.
You are the man.
I mean, what a race.
We're so proud of you.
[Max laughs] Two in a row, Christian,
at home.
Not too bad.
[Christian] Amazing. Honda's first win
as well, absolutely amazing.
[Max] Yeah, amazing job, guys.
[all laughing]
[Christian] Hey!
Great job!
Very, very good.
[Yamomoto] Super, Max.
Yeah, super.
[crowd cheering]
Oh, my God, that was epic.
Amazing.
[cheering]
[Christian] Suddenly, things are coming
alive for us and we're fighting.
You know, the momentum is with us.
[announcer] And now, Verstappen!
[imperceptible]
[all cheering]
Congrats.
I'm fucking fast, but at the moment
I'm so fucking slow.
Just got to find, like...
The right thing for me.
But I think there were still
some positives today, but...
I pushed too much at the beginning
when I was behind Räikkönen.
I pushed too much,
then after I caused a blister.
- Made things worse. But...
- [Christian] Yeah.
- Yep.
- That was...
Not great, but...
Max wins, so at least we know...
- We got a good car.
- [Christian] We have a good car.
You know, it's hard on Pierre,
it feels like we've given him
a huge amount of time,
a huge amount of effort
to try and make this work...
Congratulations.
[Christian] And...
he was promoted into that drive...
prematurely.
You know, I can't keep
making excuses for him.
You know, if they're good enough,
they swim, they survive.
If they're not good enough...
The question is, who is the right guy
to be partnering Max Verstappen?
- This is the living room.
- [Sophie] That's the dining room.
Dining room.
[man 1] Red Bull's an impatient machine.
The question is, who is the right guy?
[man 2] It's such a dangerous sport.
Holy jeez.
He would have given his right arm
to be in your position.
[man 3] He aced that one brilliantly.
- Can you win this weekend?
- Yeah!
[man 4] Whoa!
- [man 5] We'll speak later.
- You can occasionally kiss if you want.
Showtime.