Netflix are a real bunch of cunts,
aren't they?
I would love for them to play that.
They're not gonna play that.
[Michael] All right, let me get a coffee.
- [Daniel] I'm gonna do a bit of a squat.
- What do you want, an espresso?
[Daniel] Yeah.
[Daniel] Last year, I took a gamble
and switched teams.
Everyone was like,
"Why are you leaving Red Bull?"
A lot of people asking questions.
- [Michael] You know that expression...
- Go fuck yourself. That one?
[Daniel] Obviously,
I spoke to a few teams.
There was definitely talks with McLaren.
[driver] Fucking stupid.
Unbelievable.
[Daniel] But I guess the truth is
I hadn't seen enough to convince me
that it was gonna get better.
[Daniel] With Renault, I saw the momentum
they've had since 2016.
And they've had a really strong 2018.
That was a big attraction for me.
I looked at their plan
and when I kind of had everything
on the table in front of me,
the Renault one encouraged me
and convinced me more.
I took a chance.
But also, they made a big gamble
signing me.
[engine revving]
[indistinct chatter]
[woman in Spanish]
Carlos, would you like some ham?
Do we all want gazpacho?
Yeah.
- Would anyone like wine?
- [man] I want some.
[Carlos in English] I've been coming
to Mallorca since I'm zero years old.
[woman] How awesome.
It's very Spanish way
just to spend summer break
with your cousins, with your uncles,
grandparents, your sisters, your family.
[laughing]
Here, everyone is totally relaxed.
[man in Spanish] It's very good, folks.
- How do you like it, Auntie Carmen?
- Very good.
It's definitely very good.
[Carlos in English] Every professional
athlete needs their own time,
where you can actually relax a bit
and disconnect from the outside world,
and work, basically.
But 2018 summer was a bit different.
[man in Spanish] Come on!
2018 was a bit of a weird season
for Carlos 'cause he...
drove for Renault.
By June, July, all the silly season
starts with a driver's market.
[announcer] And the knock-on effects
of Ricciardo moving to Renault
mean Carlos Sainz will lose his seat.
- [man 1] See ya.
- [woman] Bye.
[man 2] Bye.
[Caco] We got a call from Cyril saying,
"Look, we just signed Ricciardo.
That leaves you out of the team."
[in Spanish] Where do we find more fish?
In or out of the platform?
I think the inside area.
[in English] I was hurt that the Renault
car that I had been driving that year,
it was so easily taken by someone else.
[Caco] We didn't really know
what was gonna happen in the future.
[Caco in Spanish] I'm ready.
[Carlos in English] My main scare
was not staying in Renault,
it was staying in Formula 1.
For me, it was 100% like,
"I need to have a seat.
I will have a seat."
[Caco] It was quite intense
'cause we were always on the phone,
always on the email,
speaking to all the teams.
[Carlos in Spanish] I'm not going to fail.
[Caco in English] But then, suddenly,
things started to fall in place.
Why not take the challenge and go for it?
[Caco in Spanish] Well done.
[Carlos] Great. Now we have one.
[announcer in English] Three, two, one.
[announcer] Big thanks
to the new driver line-up for McLaren.
[all clapping]
[Carlos] It's a great honor to be here.
It's something special,
so I really want to thank everyone.
[Zak] We got to know
Carlos moved very quick
and very happy to have him
as a McLaren Grand Prix driver.
[Zak] Everyone in here
works unbelievably hard.
Everyone has contributed to this race car.
Collectively, us, as a group,
we're gonna all get back to where
I know we should be, can be,
and have been.
And I hope to do it soon.
[Zak] 2018, I don't think
we designed a very good race car.
[man] We are out of the points.
[Zak] So, by the end of the year,
we were about
the eighth, ninth quickest team.
[man] Fucking stupid.
[announcer] Not another problem
for McLaren!
[Zak] We wouldn't have put Carlos
in our race car
if we didn't think he was extremely fast.
So, even though he was only 24 years old,
he's done a lot of Grand Prix,
and so he's got a great blend
of youth and aggression,
but yet, you know, mature.
That's what we really need
to get back to winning races.
[Zak] Hey, guys.
Where are we going?
Down or are we walkin' around?
- [woman] Straight down.
- [Zak] Straight around?
[woman] Yeah.
What did you guys do
in the Renault launch last year?
[Carlos] It was nothing special.
Nothing too...
[mutters] Not what you expect?
To be honest, no.
- Not as much...
- No.
...fanfare?
Definitely not.
- Looks good.
- It looks really good.
[Zak] Get me one of those. I'll take two!
[Carlos] Yeah.
It's year by year?
Yeah, by year, yeah.
[Carlos] It's unbelievable.
The first time I went there,
the first thing that came to mind was
how these guys cannot be winning.
McLaren last year, they had probably
one of their worst seasons in Formula 1,
if not the worst.
Hey, guys.
Shall I practice my entrance
like yesterday?
[man] The Ronaldo one?
[woman] Do the run and jump.
There's the car.
[laughing]
[Zak] Our goals for 2019 have to be
to take a step forward.
We had to make a lot of changes,
which we did.
You know, now we've got two great drivers
in Carlos Sainz and Lando Norris.
And he gets along with Lando very well.
They're very competitive with each other,
but in a healthy way.
High-five everyone, please.
- Please high-five everyone.
- [Lando] Imagine if I get left hanging.
- Mic check.
- That would be a good start
to our season together.
[Lando] I'm not ready.
My heart has started beating.
[woman] Shall we do a picture?
It's a big risk for Carlos,
moving to McLaren...
and not just because
of McLaren's recent troubles.
If he can rebuild that team,
I think it would do his reputation good.
But if it doesn't work out for him,
he could get buried
by the entire experience.
[man] Ready in 30 seconds.
[Carlos] You always have doubts.
You wonder, "Well, what if McLaren
are still 17th, 16th fastest?
What's gonna happen with me?"
People are gonna start
forgetting about me.
[man] Ten, nine, eight,
seven...
[Carlos] But for me,
a new year is a new start.
Then really try to forget
about the doubts.
[all clapping]
[commentator] On the shores
of the Caspian Sea
are the streets of Baku,
the capital of Azerbaijan
and round four of the Formula 1
World Championship of 2019.
[Carlos] I'm trying to smile.
Show positivity.
- [woman] Radiate positivity.
- Radiate positivity.
[Zak] Well, I think, you know,
Carlos's first couple of races,
he's had... bad luck.
The results have been a mixed bag.
Tonight, we'll be celebrating, 100%.
Hey, guys.
[Lando] Nothing happened.
If you get a podium, will you jump in?
[Carlos] If I get a podium,
I don't know what I'd do.
Actually, it's time to turn things around,
even if it hasn't been my fault,
just make it happen, you know,
just whatever I need to do, just do it.
[Daniel] All right.
Which way is it?
[crowd exclaiming] Daniel! Whoo!
[woman] I love you!
[Daniel] I love coming here.
[woman] Thank you!
[Daniel] Baku is a high-speed
street circuit.
[announcer] Danny Ricciardo!
This track creates just amazing racing.
It's so intense.
But, really, with Renault,
so far in the season,
we haven't achieved what we wanted to.
This season has been probably
the most challenging...
experience in my career so far.
[commentator] And Daniel Ricciardo,
losing his front wing going into turn one.
[Daniel] Everything just cut out.
[Cyril] Every single race weekend,
something happened to us
which had a negative impact
on the results.
[commentator] Daniel Ricciardo's Renault
career hasn't started that well, has it?
- Pidges?
- Do your pidges and your thoracics.
First couple of races this season
were, you know...
not the way I wanted to start,
you know, my account with Renault.
[Michael] Get some speed.
Get into appropriate intensity.
Nice, mate.
[Will] Moving teams is always tricky,
particularly when they've spent
so much of their career in one place.
I think Daniel knew that moving to Renault
would prove to be a challenge.
But I don't think he anticipated
these early races
would be as hard as they've been.
[commentator] It's time for Qualifying.
An hour of flat-out driving
on the streets of Baku.
[Simon] Okay, at the moment,
you're clear from traffic behind.
[Daniel] Okay.
[commentator] This is it.
He's got one lap to shine.
[Daniel] How're we looking?
[Simon] You're currently P11,
five hundredths from Norris.
[Daniel] I'm still not there yet
with this car.
Everything is different to the Red Bull.
The brakes, the throttle,
the feeling on the pedal.
It's everything.
All that being said,
it's still a race car.
You can drive it,
still nearly with your eyes closed.
But to drive it on the limit
and to really gel with
and understand the car,
that then takes a bit more time.
[commentator] Ricciardo crosses the line.
And it says 12th fastest.
Slowest of the 12 drivers
that we have had so far.
[Simon] You're P12.
[Daniel] Sorry, I lost the rear
quite early in the lap.
[commentator] Ricciardo doesn't seem as
confident on the brakes of a Renault yet
as he did in a Red Bull.
[Will] Daniel Ricciardo's
one of the best drivers in Formula 1
and a proven race-winner.
But that's not a silver bullet
for a car that in and of itself doesn't
have the capability of winning races.
I still know
I can get a lot more out of it.
There's still some areas I can improve on.
For sure.
[commentator] Here's Carlos Sainz,
still yet to score a point for McLaren
so far this season
and looking a bit on the back foot
coming into this qualifying session.
[Carlos] I think it's one of those
situations in this sport
where you're comfortable,
you're feeling great at the wheel,
but there's just one final thing,
which is a result.
[Tom] Okay, Carlos, you are currently P12.
It's not a good lap.
[Zak] Even though we knew
Carlos was very quick,
anytime a new driver gets into your car,
they need to prove themselves.
[Tom] Okay, mate, we finished P11.
For fuck's sake.
Fuck.
So frustrating.
It's so fucking frustrating.
[Will] You know, some drivers move
to teams and they excel,
and then you see them
sometimes move to teams
and then fall short of expectations.
[Carlos in Spanish] Bad luck, man. Shit.
- [man in English] Thank you.
- [Daniel] Thanks. No worries.
Ricciardo, I thought that was not...
I think that qualifying session
was not good.
Yeah, you should've thrown
some banana peels at my rivals.
Yeah!
Totally.
[Daniel] It's nearly a year
since I had a podium.
And it feels like it's been a while.
I felt like my best
was good enough for 12th place.
It's obviously not where we wanna be,
but Baku is crazy.
Anything can happen.
I've had massive highs and lows here.
2018 was one of the big kind of
controversial moments of that season.
[all clapping]
2017, I won the race.
So, I've certainly had
all sorts of emotions here.
Hopefully my experience pays off tomorrow.
[commentator] Daniel Ricciardo,
he is the lead Renault now
and having a better day of it.
Yes.
[man] Nice job.
[Simon] P10.
[exclaims]
[commentator] Now here comes one McLaren
on another, Carlos Sainz on Lando Norris.
Sainz is now the lead McLaren.
[commentator] Pace is looking very strong.
Get Magnussen out.
[Daniel] Nice one, mate.
[Simon] Okay,
next car on the road is Kvyat.
3.5 ahead.
[commentator] Daniel Ricciardo
has got himself up to eighth.
[Simon] Four tenths
quicker than Kvyat ahead.
[Simon] You gained nine tenths on Kvyat
that last lap.
You have overtake available.
And you get DRS on Kvyat now.
[Daniel] Understood.
[commentator] Here comes Ricciardo,
king of the late brakers.
Can he do it to Kvyat?
No! He's off!
[Simon] No.
[commentator] This is costing him
a lot of time.
[commentator] And he's... Oh!
He's just reversed into Kvyat.
Things go from bad to worse
for the unlucky Renault team.
[Daniel] I didn't see him.
[engine revving]
Something feels loose.
I'm gonna box.
[commentator] Ricciardo's gonna
have to retire, I think, from this race.
[Simon] Switching off.
Switching off, please.
[Daniel] Sorry, guys.
[engine revving]
[Tom] Okay, Carlos,
that's Grosjean in front.
So, Carlos, this is good so far.
This is good.
You're P7, there's two laps to go.
And this will be the last lap.
That's the chequered flag. Well done. P7.
[Eric] Come on, boys! Yes!
Finally off the mark.
[in Spanish] Good.
- About time.
- About fucking time.
[Caco in Spanish] Long time.
First points of the year for him.
Seventh was a good result.
Yeah, the feeling was a bit of relief.
[Caco in Spanish] Solid, man, very solid.
[woman in English] Yeah.
It always felt like a long time coming.
[laughs]
[Zak] That was good, better.
Needed that.
Good work, guys.
- [in Spanish] How are you?
- [in Spanish] Good.
[Carlos] Baku was exactly what I needed.
A bit of a good result, you know,
to get my system going.
[man] Smile.
[all laugh]
[Carlos] And a bit of a relief that...
"Bad luck" you call it?
I call it "things not going towards me"
ended there.
Unlucky, mate.
[Daniel] Obviously, I feel embarrassed
and I feel like an idiot.
I felt like
I had a bit of a responsibility
to give everyone a smile Sunday night.
And it just turned into shit, basically.
I'm feeling like the smallest guy
in the whole of F1, so, yeah.
To be honest, as soon as I went off,
I just was like, "Reverse!"
Do a circle, no?
No, I didn't see him.
I didn't think...
[Cyril] I think he gave himself just
one lap to overtake him
and made a bit of a brave maneuver,
which didn't work.
So, frankly, it was
another embarrassing moment for Daniel,
but for the whole team.
[Daniel] This sport definitely still has
the ability to rip your heart out
from one day to the next.
And this year, it has for me.
Living with your mistakes,
that's a tough one.
That's why you've sometimes
got to look at it
from a different perspective.
That's why I choose to come here,
spend some time staring at palm trees
and blue skies to reset my focus.
It's like 33 degrees today,
so get some sun, play a bit of basketball.
The basketball's in here, right?
How's your game gonna be today?
I don't know, mate.
This would start me off strong.
- [both laughing]
- Shit!
He's on today.
[laughs]
[Daniel] With Michael,
we have a good relationship.
Kobe.
Trainer, performance coach,
whatever the title is.
- Sink that long one.
- [both exclaim]
I'll go a bit closer.
Try to get my confidence up.
[Daniel] That's it.
It's definitely
not just physical training, you know?
And you need a friend
because we travel so much together.
Someone you can really open up to,
someone who's happy to hear my shit
after a long week.
[Daniel] Feed me.
[Michael] We met, I think,
when we were around 11 years old.
And we've been friends ever since.
[Michael] Let's go do a bit of a stretch.
See if you can touch.
Just forget the camel toe here.
[Michael] Daniel is obviously a joker.
- You're way off. You're touching nothing.
- I can feel something on my bum.
[Michael] Yeah, it's not the ground.
But there also is Daniel Ricciardo,
the racer.
He is definitely a serious competitor.
Loosen up those hips.
It's extremely important
to be in the right head space
when you jump in that car,
so the psychological factor's huge.
It makes a big difference
come race day, for sure.
[Daniel] The whole Red Bull thing,
I discussed the move with Michael.
The choice, looking at McLaren,
and I'm not bitter towards,
you know, McLaren for doing well
because it was my decision.
McLaren look quick, mate.
Carlos is just...
He's been good.
Cheers, cunt.
I feel like we've been quite unlucky,
but it is what it is.
Yeah.
Yes, I'm angry at myself,
'cause I'm always like, "I can do better."
Mate, there's no point dwelling on it.
I think your attitude's been good, mate.
You've just been fierce,
you've been competitive.
Take it as it is
and just keep working, keep building.
Try to build some more points
in Barcelona.
Yeah, exactly.
I know it's not gonna last.
[Michael] Yeah.
- [Rupert] There he is.
- [Carlos] Good morning.
[Rupert] All right, mate?
How are you? All good?
- [Carlos] Good. You?
- Yeah, good.
Is the bell still not working
or are you just ignoring me?
[Carlos] It's going to rain, yeah?
It could rain.
It's pretty much been doing that nonstop
the last few days.
- When is Sam coming?
- Welcome to the UK.
Thank you.
[Carlos] Moving to the UK was...
it was a bit of challenging myself.
It is probably the toughest of the things
to leave family, friends,
girlfriend behind.
[Carlos] We go for chicken fajitas?
It's cold.
I knew McLaren
was gonna need me in the UK.
We had a lot of work to do.
Who is doing the guacamole?
[Rupert] I'm doing the guacamole, mate.
[Carlos] You know for guacamole,
you need lime.
Ready?
Where's the fajita mix? It's not here.
I'm gonna be depressed.
It has to be here.
Excuse me, do you have
special fajita sauce, El Paso style?
He's really keen on.
- [Rupert] Here we go, mate.
- You have it?
I'm sorry to break this to you.
They might only have their own brand.
No. Then we need to go somewhere else.
Thank you very much. Nice to meet you.
[woman] And you.
[Rupert] It's not hard
to find the car, is it?
[Carlos] No.
[Rupert] Where does the shopping go?
Where is the fucking boot?
You must have a smaller bag, no?
You carry it. Come on.
[Rupert] It's my job, right?
[Carlos] Morning.
- [man] All right, mate?
- Yeah, good, you?
[Carlos] How many people
are attending the performance review?
Many drivers have asked me,
"Why do you spend so much time in McLaren?
Are you forced to go there?"
The way I apply the brake pressure.
[man] Yes.
A little smooth application
instead of being a bit more punchy.
[Carlos] People underestimate
the relationship with the engineers,
how important it is.
Yeah, we're going just now.
Thank you, mate.
[all chuckling]
It will show itself on track
and then it will pay off.
[Carlos] Hola.
- All right, mate?
- All good?
- Good.
- How's it going? All right?
[Rupert] Does that feel too tight?
Monday to Fridays in the UK,
I'm sleeping well, eating well,
training, dieting
and I need to focus a lot in that.
[Rupert] And again.
As a coach, you're trying to
take them out of their comfort zone
to basically ensure
that when they need to get in the car,
that they can perform at their best.
Carlos is always really looking
at ways that he can improve himself.
[Carlos] That will give me the confidence
to go to a Formula 1 track.
[Rupert] Slow it back down.
Knowing that I'm working
more than anyone else in Formula 1.
[commentator] In the battle
for king of the midfield,
McLaren now have a surprise lead
over troubled Renault.
- [Michael] Get in the zone, mate.
- [Daniel] Yep.
[Michael] You ready
for a bit of a dogfight?
[Daniel] Good man, fuckin'...
[Michael] Good, man, fucking right.
So am I.
All right, let's do it.
[Daniel] As far as, you know,
our midfield battle goes,
Carlos has been a bit luckier at times.
So, that creates
a bit more tension in the rivalry.
I put a lot into this
and I don't travel around the world
and work this hard
to, you know, not see the chequered flag.
[Daniel] This is my moment to really
go out, when those lights go out,
and be as good as I can be.
Let's race hard.
May the best man win.
[Carlos] My period in Renault
is totally closed
and I don't see that yellow car as my car
and someone else driving it.
I want to prove to McLaren and Renault
that, of the midfield,
I am the strongest driver.
I don't think anyone is better than me,
but Daniel thinks he's the best.
We all think we are the best.
Out of all these battles
that are happening here,
I want to be on top.
[Tom] Okay, Carlos, radio check.
[Carlos] Yeah, radio's good.
[Tom] Copy, that's loud and clear.
[Simon] Radio check. Radio check.
[Daniel] Let's fucking have it, boys.
[Cyril] Let's go for it, Daniel.
[announcer] Ten seconds.
- [crowd murmuring]
- [engines revving]
[commentator] We're racing in Barcelona.
Daniel Ricciardo off to a good start.
Sainz keeping out of trouble
into turn one.
[Tom] Good, Carlos. Good job.
Pace is okay. Pace is okay.
Ricciardo looks quick.
Keep him behind if you can.
[Simon] Carlos is struggling on pace
at the moment.
[Daniel] Okay, they've
definitely got more speed.
[commentator] Ricciardo trying to
get past Carlos Sainz.
Sainz moves to the inside
to cover off Ricciardo.
He knew an attack was coming there.
[Tom] Good, Carlos, good job defending.
Try and keep him behinid.
[Carlos] I'm trying. I'm trying.
[Simon] Gained nine tenths on Carlos
in that last lap.
So, overtake is available.
[Daniel] Understood.
[commentator] Ricciardo is squeezing
everything out of the Renault now
to try and get past Carlos Sainz.
That's Ricciardo through!
[Carlos] Fuck me.
[commentator] Renault have
overtaken McLaren.
[Simon] Nice one, mate.
You're doing a good job, mate.
[Daniel] Okay. I'll box this lap.
[Simon] Okay, understood. Boxing.
[Tom] Box now. Box now.
[Daniel] Ugh.
[Carlos] We did it one behind each other.
And the first lap was gonna be all about
trying to get past Daniel again.
[Simon] Watch out for Sainz behind you.
He's also just left the box.
[Daniel] Understood.
[Tom] Gap to Ricciardo now 1.9.
This is good, Carlos.
Better than him, we're in good shape now.
[man] That's better.
[Caco] Renault is struggling.
[Tom] Right, let's go and get him, Carlos.
[Simon] Sainz in your DRS.
[commentator] And the roles are reversed.
Sainz back ahead of Daniel Ricciardo.
[in Spanish] Come on!
Yes!
[Carlos in English] Come on, boys! Yes!
[Daniel] He caught up to me so quickly.
I really couldn't do much else.
[Simon] Okay, still a long way to go.
Let's stay focused.
Must get back into a rhythm.
[Tom] Good, Carlos, good job.
[Carlos] That overtake move from Daniel
gave us the confidence.
After that moment, I said,
"Maybe we can attack a bit more."
[Tom] Okay, Carlos,
that's Grosjean in front.
[commentator] Sainz is in the points,
but hungry for more.
[Carlos] I had a heavy contact.
It was a heavy contact
[Tom] Copy.
Pressure's okay at the moment.
[Caco] They were side to side.
He cannot turn in like that.
[commentator] He's just got time
for one last go at Grosjean.
[Caco] Come on!
[in Spanish] Come on!
Good!
[Carlos laughs]
[Tom in English] That's a great job,
Carlos. Great job.
[commentator] Carlos Sainz
is up into eighth place.
Well done, mate.
[man] Well done. Well done.
[Caco] Yes!
[Tom] Yes, Carlos, get in.
Great job, mate.
[Simon] And that's P12.
Sorry, man. Tough one.
[Daniel] Yeah, understood.
It's really hard to stay close with Sainz.
Sorry, guys.
[commentator] Carlos Sainz,
another finish in the points
and giving his grandstand reason
to get on their feet.
[Carlos] Bravo! Bravo!
That was fun.
[man] Thank you.
[Carlos] I always said it.
You know,
I think it was more a matter of time.
Deep in myself, I knew
what I needed to do to be quick.
[Rupert] Well done, mate.
Good job. Well done.
I have a feeling that McLaren knows
what they are doing
and I'm gonna trust it.
[in Spanish] Give me a high five.
[woman in English] Yay.
Well done, fucking amazing.
- [Zak] That was good.
- [man] Good race.
Good job, guys.
[Zak] Carlos has been very impressive.
I like his aggression, I like his speed.
[Carlos] Thank you, guys.
Cheers. Thank you very much.
[Zak] He hasn't put a wheel wrong.
And I can see him being with McLaren
for quite some time.
[Daniel] I was a bit frustrated
with how the race panned out.
Yeah, I've had a few battles with Carlos,
but the McLarens have turned it on
and they've certainly been
our kind of midfield target this year.
They've got a pretty good car.
I need to be smart
and use my strengths as a driver
to kind of work around
maybe some of the weaknesses in the car.
I expected myself to get it quicker.
[Cyril] You know,
there is no real question mark
about the capacity of Daniel
to be a strong driver.
I feel that the team is ready for Daniel.
We are ready for that partnership.
We just need to work harder
and give him a better car,
so that he can bring the team
to a different dimension.
[man] Formula 1 racing
is very much like war planning.
Let's crush them.
Yes!
Body's feeling sore, heart is racing.
[exclaiming] Fuck! How is this possible?
[man] It was a fucking shit day
at the office.
[Christian] Come on, Geraldine,
you'll be late to your own concert.
Hello. Who the fuck are you?
[man] Pierre Gasly
got off to a horrible start.
[Pierre] Fuck!
[man] We will give Alex Albon a run.
It's like an F1 car on steroids.
[upbeat music playing]