[interviewer] Welcome.
- Good.
- [interviewer] Yeah.
[interviewer] Can you introduce yourself,
tell me what you do?
[Binotto] Okay.
I'm Mattia Binotto.
I'm working at Scuderia Ferrari,
team principal, managing director.
[interviewer] So, have you got Netflix?
No.
- [interviewer] No?
- No.
- So, you haven't seen Season 1?
[commentator] And there's a problem.
Massive accident!
Wow!
[audience gasps]
[Steiner] Last season...
[commentator]
What a performance from Haas.
[Steiner] ...it was up and down.
[commentator] It's Grosjean!
[all] Oh!
Fuck. We fucking look like
a bunch of wankers.
But we made a big step up.
[commentator] Haas get their best-ever
finish in Formula 1.
Woah!
[Brown] At McLaren, I don't think
we designed a very good race car.
[commentator] Another problem for McLaren.
And Zak Brown, not happy.
[Williams] 2018 was a pretty horrific year
for Williams.
[man] What's the point in even racing now?
[man] Very successful drivers
started with Sauber.
[commentator]
Leclerc is driving a brilliant race.
[Leclerc] Yes, yes, yes!
[commentator] Charles Leclerc
will be joining Ferrari next season.
[commentator] The Red Bulls
are really going for it here.
[Horner] This is the best driver pairing
that we've had in our history.
[commentator] They have crashed!
[Ricciardo]
I was kinda made to feel guilty.
[commentator]
Daniel Ricciardo leaving Red Bull.
He's going to Renault.
[Abiteboul] You need a driver
and an engine.
[Abiteboul laughs]
[Horner] Yeah.
[Abiteboul] With Daniel,
we have a strategy and a plan.
[Ricciardo] I just needed to get out.
[commentator] And the knock-on effects
mean that Carlos Sainz will lose his seat.
[Sainz Jr.] See ya.
[commentator] It has been
a brilliant year.
[Horner] Mercedes is very much
the benchmark.
[commentator] Lewis Hamilton,
a five-time champion of the world.
[Horner] One chapter closes...
[Hamilton] We have to focus
on what is ahead.
[Magnussen]
We just gotta try and do better.
I feel like I've been here before.
[dramatic music playing]
[upbeat music playing]
[man] Yeah.
- [Williams] Hello. Are you all right?
- [Abiteboul] Bonjour.
- [Abiteboul] Netflix.
- [Horner] Yes, of course.
[Horner] Are you guys back
for a second series?
- [woman] Yep.
- [Horner] Holy fuck.
[Norris] There's only one answer.
[Verstappen] I was sweating.
I was like, "No way. No way."
Down here, where you
and the drivers will be on the boat.
- [Williams] Yeah.
- [woman] Think they're gonna
go up the river a little bit and then...
Wave like the Queen?
[chuckles] Wave to the crowds.
[Williams] Hello. Hi.
[man] Whoo! Hello!
[woman] Hello, Melbourne.
Welcome to the very first
Formula 1 season launch.
Who wants to see their favorite
Formula 1 drivers here tonight?
[man] The drivers of 2019
Formula 1 World Championship field
- are about to arrive on the boat.
- [all cheering]
[woman] Drivers have arrived.
And I can spy Sebastian Vettel.
I can see Daniel Ricciardo as well.
[man] Daniel!
I'm Daniel Ricciardo.
I am driving with the Renault F1 team.
I'm from Australia and I'm good looking.
[woman] Look, here they come.
George Russell. Lewis Hamilton.
[fan] Lewis, you legend!
I'm Lewis Hamilton
and I race for Mercedes-Benz.
- Shit, is that what it is?
- [man] Yeah.
- [man] Just say Mercedes-AMG.
- Yeah.
[man 1] Hey, the Hulk is here.
[man 2] Verstappen! Max! Max!
[Horner] Well, we're all here because
we love racing, we love competing.
In many respects, it's my life.
Outside of my family, it's the most
important thing in the world to me.
[woman] Hello, darling,
I have a present for you.
[Horner] This is my 15th season
leading this team
and I'm as excited going into this year
as I've been about any other years.
[crowd cheering]
[woman] If you want to,
otherwise I'll do it.
How is life?
Good, beginning of the season
so your dreams are still alive.
So far so good.
[Magnussen]
The first race in Australia is awesome.
You know, you're excited to get back.
I guess it's like, in spring,
when they let the cows out
of the houses and they go crazy.
[crowd cheering]
My name's Toto Wolff.
I'm the team principal of the Mercedes...
[in German] How do I say it?
Um...
[man] Valtteri!
So, my name's Valtteri Bottas.
I drive for the Mercedes-AMG
Petronas Motorsport.
[Wolff] Like with everything in life,
you have to be passionate
about what you do.
For me, personally,
it is about being able to add
a sixth consecutive championship.
That hasn't been done before.
[crowd cheering]
Where is he?
[crew] I'll send Sebastian
when he gets here.
Here he is. No, he's here.
I'm Sebastian Vettel.
I'm driving for Scuderia Ferrari.
Well, obviously, I'm here
because I love racing, love my job,
the goal and ambition
is to be successful with Ferrari,
and whilst doing so,
we enjoy and have a lot of fun.
[woman] Right.
Let's go down to the audience.
Who's got a question down there?
Put your hand up.
Here we go.
[man] My question's for Guenther.
After the race this year, do you aim
to look like wankers or rock stars?
Hopefully, rock stars.
- That was a good question.
- Good question.
[Steiner] Thank you for the question, sir.
A lot of people know what
happened to us last year in Australia.
[commentator] Kevin Magnussen has pitted.
We had two failures on the pit stops
and we retired both cars.
[commentator] And who's that going slowly?
It's Kevin Magnussen.
[commentator] And by the looks of things,
one of those wheels
isn't attached properly.
[Steiner] Stop the car, stop the car.
[commentator] Romain Grosjean pulling over
in the other Haas!
[Steiner] We fucking look
like rock stars, huh?
Now, we are a fucking bunch of wankers.
Hopefully, we can make up for it
and that would be a good revenge.
[Hamilton] Each season is a journey.
It's 21 races, 21 countries.
On the road with us at Mercedes,
there's nearly 100 people
that are moving from city to city.
It's quite an incredible journey
in trying to win a world championship.
And one I'm looking forward to.
We are doing pretty well.
We are in front of Alfa,
in front of one Ferrari.
Going to Melbourne, it's too early to say
who is good, who is not good.
I'm not counting out anybody,
I mean, we are all in for it.
Comparing with other cars,
it's always difficult the first days.
Only the racetrack will tell.
[Horner] It's not really
till you get to Melbourne
that you absolutely know
where your starting point is.
It's the first time
everybody pulls down their pants.
And you see what you've got.
[woman] We'll all do it together,
please, thank you.
[reporter] First, how does it feel
to be here with a different team?
[Ricciardo] Yeah, new team,
fresh start, fresh season,
but I still have
the same expectations for myself,
and to deliver, and to be the best I can
with the car I've got,
but also, I feel a real responsibility to
try and push this car further up the grid
during my time here.
When I signed with Renault, a lot
of people probably didn't understand it.
And maybe some still don't.
No worries.
[Buxton] No one saw it coming.
- Thank you very much.
Good luck for tomorrow.
[Buxton] It was a massive, massive shock.
- Any chance?
- Sure.
Right up until about a week
before it was announced...
Christian Horner was absolutely,
100% sure Daniel wasn't gonna go anywhere.
[Horner] When he rang to say,
"I'm leaving to go to Renault,"
first of all, I thought it was a wind up.
He couldn't really give me any reason.
But with Max Verstappen as his teammate,
my assumption was that
he was running a little bit from a fight.
[Ricciardo] I, personally,
wasn't running from anything.
I still want to achieve the world title.
And to do that,
I just felt like I needed a change.
[Driver] See you later. Take care.
[Ricciardo] Bye.
[Ricciardo] Once I signed on
the dotted line last year,
moving to Renault,
working with new people...
- Daniel.
- A pleasure.
[Ricciardo] ...it just increased every bit
of motivation and passion I had.
I'll just wave to everyone.
Good morning!
- [man 1] Good morning!
- [man 2] Morning.
- [man 3] Welcome.
- Thanks.
[Ricciardo] For sure, there,
I felt a bit of love.
- Sup fellas?
- [man] Hey.
That was the coolest thing.
I noticed that straightaway,
everyone's just like...
Welcome.
[Ricciardo] I wanna do great things here,
and I wanna feel like this is a place
where I can, A, obviously be happy...
- Welcome home. You okay?
- Yeah.
[Ricciardo] ...but, B,
become a world champion.
All right, this is it.
It's happening.
So, that's really all I'm here for.
[Ricciardo] What's going on?
Hiya.
[Abiteboul] So, welcome.
It's your office?
Yeah, it is, yeah, yeah. So, I think...
We believed in him, um,
but also, he believed in us.
Um, it was a special moment.
[indistinct chatter]
So, this is...
- Race base, right?
- This is race base, yes.
- This is all the machining area.
- Okay.
So, I'll be working here?
This is this my desk?
- Yeah. This is where you'll sit. Yeah?
- Yeah.
And you can watch
the gearbox through the glass.
Cool.
[Abiteboul] For Daniel to join us,
he was confirming our project was an
exciting project for him to be a part of.
You know, I saw the momentum
they've had since 2016,
and I think there was just pressure
to continue that for '19.
It sounds busy,
so I like the sound of that.
[laughs]
Oh, I gotcha.
What we've done so far
is P9, P6, P4 into the championship
over the last three years.
So, I guess natural expectation
that the next step is P3.
Sorry, dude. Dude!
Excuse me.
[laughing]
Let's hug it out.
That's like the greatest,
greatest band ever.
Definitely.
Respect.
[laughs]
[Ricciardo] If we, at Renault,
produce an amazing car
and really get ourselves clear
of that midfield,
and get in the fight
with those top three teams.
Ultimately, we want to latch onto
Ferraris, Mercedes and Red Bulls.
Okay, so, let's give a big round
of applause to Daniel.
Please, thank you!
[all cheering]
[Ricciardo] A first podium
with Renault, would...
Well, I've thought about it.
I've certainly thought about it, but...
[crowd cheering]
[Abiteboul] Welcome, Daniel.
[commentator] It's been a long wait,
but we're back everybody.
Welcome along to the first day
of the Formula 1 season.
We're here in Melbourne,
it's practice one.
[engine accelerating]
[mechanic] Hello, how are you,
how have you been?
- When did you get here?
- Monday afternoon.
[Hamilton] The ultimate goal is to win,
but we have to optimize this car.
We have to get this machine to perform.
It doesn't just perform on its own.
And the championship, it could be closer,
I really won't know until we get
to that first race, to be honest.
- How are you?
- I'm good. All good?
[Horner] Mercedes are a very
well-oiled machine.
[Wolff] Hey, ladies.
You okay? You good?
They are, without a shadow of a doubt,
the favorites going into this year.
And they will be
an incredibly hard nut to crack.
[mechanic] So, the brakes, we need to go
and check that with George.
Sounds good.
[Wolff] Has everything with the setup
been okay with you?
Yeah, yeah, everything's been good.
Fire-up's gone all right. So far, so good.
- [Wolff] No dramas?
- [mechanic] Nope.
Engine running good, running well.
[Wolff] We have brought ourselves
in a position that we
are the ones to beat.
[Hamilton] Radio check.
[crew] Your radio's loud and clear, Lewis.
[Wolff] A critical part is to manage
your own expectations.
Not feel a sense of entitlement to win,
but stay modest,
not looking back because at the start
of the season, all points go to zero.
[crew] And Lewis, one minute.
[Binotto] Last year,
we were a disappointed second.
[both speaking in Italian]
[Binotto] We are all very convinced
on what we wanna achieve.
But again, it will take time.
The competitors are very strong.
[technician] Before turn nine,
upshift early
closer to when you go full throttle.
[Horner] Well, Ferrari have dominated
pre-season testing.
They will be blisteringly quick.
[crew] Radio check.
[driver] Copy.
[Binotto] All the emotions are growing
because the car has to be
reliable to finish first,
but we are working on that.
[indistinct chatter]
- You all right?
- [Verstappen] Yeah, good.
Please, can it look like that
at the end of the session?
- Good.
- That would be nice.
Keep Olly, he's losing
a bit of hair these days.
He doesn't...
He doesn't need it accelerating.
[man] It's all ready,
whatever happens, we're ready.
[Horner] Max very much moves into
the driver to lead the team.
He started to select
another gear last year.
And he has this growing following,
this growing intensity around him.
[Buxton] Ever since
he signed for Red Bull,
Max has been the team's shining star.
Team management has said
that they want to turn him into
the youngest world champion
in this sport's history.
So, competing with that, for Daniel,
was always going to be tough.
[interviewer] Will you miss Daniel,
racing him?
Daniel's in the paddock
and he's still racing Formula 1.
So, I won't necessarily miss him,
but I'm just looking ahead
to the ones we have to beat
and those are Ferrari and Mercedes,
not Renault.
That's the target.
You know, if you see
that helmet in your mirror,
he's not gonna be there for long
and he's definitely gonna have a go,
and it's reminiscent of
the greats in the past.
He will not give up
and will give it absolutely everything.
[Verstappen] Well, for me the aim
is to become a world champion
and, of course,
it's always better sooner than later.
In 10, 15, 20 years' time,
if I would look back and I see third,
I'm not really interested.
But, personally, I'm only there to win.
[Horner] We gotta deliver to retain him.
He's got an agreement with the team
that if we don't fit the criteria
by the summer break,
which is top three
in the Drivers' Championship,
then he's a free agent.
And there's a lot of teams in the paddock
that would like to sign up Max Verstappen.
Our intention is to provide him with a car
to be able to challenge
for the world championship.
[announcer speaking Japanese]
[engine accelerating]
[crowd cheering]
[announcer speaking Japanese]
[announcer] Please welcome.
[Horner] Coming into 2019,
the biggest strategic decision
that we've had to make
was walking away from Renault and taking
on a largely unproven engine in Honda.
Well, the missing link for us
the last five years
has really been the power unit.
Um, you know, we went from winning
four double world championships.
The last five years
have been difficult for us.
[Horner] We're totally taking
a risk on Honda, you know.
You know, we've gone to the casino.
We've put all our money on one number.
[announcer speaking Japanese]
[Verstappen] It's not like some
other sports where it's just yourself,
which can make the difference.
If you don't really have
a car where you can fight with,
then you can't really show
how good you are.
At the moment for me,
it's very difficult to say what we can do,
because you don't know.
Nobody knows.
[Horner] The reality is Red Bull
make an energy drink worldwide.
Formula 1 is a platform
to promote and advertize it.
[commentator] Max Verstappen!
[crowd applauding]
[Horner] If this new relationship
with Honda doesn't work,
if we lose Max Verstappen,
then you'd have to question Red Bull's
long-term commitment to Formula 1.
[commentator] Time for qualifying.
[engine accelerating]
[commentator] Let's see the cars blast
around the Albert Park track.
It looks an absolute picture
in the sunshine on this beautiful evening.
[Buxton] Formula 1 hands out points
for the top ten drivers,
with the winner getting 25,
second, 18, third, 15.
Then it rapidly tails off.
So, if you're finishing lower than fifth,
you're not really scoring the points
that a top team needs
to fight for the championship.
All you can do is get into the midfield.
[Grosjean] To be fair,
everyone in the midfield
can be a good driver, you know.
Can be Renault, can be McLaren,
Alfa Romeo, Toro Rosso, or even Williams.
You never know, you know.
- [engineer] Radio check, Romain.
- [Grosjean] It's good, brother.
I insulted. No, I don't insult you.
I insult him.
[Steiner] A small team.
I compete with big manufacturers.
We know that our opposition,
they have got bigger budgets.
They've got more resources,
but it's not all about that.
We stand up to them
and I'm not afraid of them
because we're actually
not afraid of anybody.
[Steiner] You know we are going
into our fourth season.
I think we will have a good year again.
It's a joy to work with you.
With some of you. Not with everybody.
Where's Romain?
Nothing to say. Good.
Yeah, I need somebody to pick on.
It's normally him. He's used to it.
[Steiner] We rock a little bit
the establishment...
[laughing]
[Steiner]...which I think
a lot of people like.
Let's go and see the car a moment,
guys. Let's come over.
[Steiner] The doubters will be
always out there.
What do you think, guys?
Good, little bit different, huh?
Hopefully, it's fast.
I don't really care about what they say.
You have to cut out
the BS from these people
because they've all got an opinion,
but they don't do the job.
Romain, the last time a black and gold car
was on the grid,
it finished on the podium with you, yeah.
So can you repeat this, yeah?
- [Grosjean] No pressure. No pressure.
- [Steiner] Yeah, no pressure...
Well, we went bankrupt as well.
We are not bankrupt. We are not bankrupt.
You know, we're not bankrupt.
Anyway, not yet.
Depends how many cars
you destroy this year but, so...
That was going to come.
[Steiner] It's time now
to get on the podium, huh?
[Grosjean] I see.
[Steiner] Are you upset now with me?
This was a joke.
[rock music playing]
[music continues]
[commentator]
Lewis Hamilton on pole position.
Romain Grosjean starts sixth for Haas,
ahead of Kevin Magnussen.
[Steiner] If it stays like this,
we are fine.
[commentator] Daniel Ricciardo,
the Australian hero.
What can he do from 12th?
[commentator] What of Red Bull?
Can they take the fight
to the reigning world champions?
[Gasly] Radio okay?
[Verstappen] Radio check.
[crew] Copy, loud and clear.
[commentator] Just moments to go before
the start of the Australian Grand Prix.
[commentator]
It's lights out and away we go!
[engines accelerating]
[commentator] And Daniel Ricciardo losing
his front wing going into turn one.
[commentator] There's a Renault
front wing missing.
They didn't even get past
the end of the pit lane.
[Ricciardo] Has it come off completely?
[crew] Affirm.
Yep, has come off completely.
Boxing this lap for nose change.
[Ricciardo] Understood.
[commentator] A fairly troublesome start
then for Daniel Ricciardo.
[commentator] And Ricciardo
running plum last.
[crew] Okay, let's find a rhythm now.
It's going to be a long one.
[Ricciardo] I've picked up
a pretty big vibration.
[crew] Okay, Daniel.
We're going to box this lap, please.
We have an issue.
We're gonna retire the car.
Sorry about that, mate.
[Ricciardo] Sorry it didn't work out.
[commentator] That is a very,
very disappointing end
to one of his happiest weekends
of the season.
[engine accelerating]
[engineer] Okay, Romain,
let's keep pushing,
keep pushing and pressurizing other cars.
[Grosjean] Okay.
[commentator]
Grosjean goes down the inside!
[engine accelerating]
[commentator] Haas think
they've got a very fast car.
[Grosjean] Yeah, told you
the car was good. Fuck yeah.
[crew] Okay, Romain, let's push
as hard as we can.
Good job, dude. Good job.
Box, Romain.
[Grosjean] Okay.
[engine whirring]
[commentator] Oh, no.
Not another pitstop drama
for Haas in Australia.
[crew] We're still in this fight, dude.
[Grosjean] Okay.
[crew] Okay, dude,
so you are around 1.5 seconds quicker
than the cars ahead.
We will catch them so let's keep going.
[Grosjean] I'm losing the breaks.
What's the situation, brother?
[crew] Stop the car, Romain.
Stop the car where you can.
[car crashes]
[Grosjean] Fuck!
Ahh! Fucking stupid, fucking stupid.
[engine accelerating]
[commentator] That's a shame.
He's done a great job this weekend.
[Steiner] Fucking hell.
[commentator] It's Mercedes one and two,
Ferrari three
and four, Red Bull fifth
with Max Verstappen.
[engine accelerating]
[whistling]
[crew] How much pace
do you think you've got in you?
[Verstappen]
I can easily pick up the pace.
[commentator] It's time to see
the real speed of that Honda engine.
[commentator] Into the pits comes Vettel.
And all of a sudden,
it's game on for Red Bull.
[crew] You just focus on getting Seb.
[commentator] Cheers from the crowd!
You can hear them
as they see Verstappen's that much closer.
[crew] That's Vettel ahead of you.
Keep pushing.
[Verstappen]
We are definitely catching them.
[crew] Game on.
[Verstappen] Ah, yes.
[commentator] And there's Kevin Magnussen.
With Grosjean out of it, all hopes at Haas
fall on teammate Magnussen.
[Magnussen] Whatever position
I'm fighting for,
I only have one setting
and that's maximum.
[commentator] Whether Kevin Magnussen
can hold off the Renault behind.
Magnussen defends his place.
[crowd cheering]
[commentator] You know what I've really
missed in the winter?
Max Verstappen going for some overtakes.
We start the final lap of this race.
The whole car was coming alive.
We seemed to have really good power
compared to the others,
so I could basically just push flat out.
[commentator] Max Verstappen
is going for it here.
Max Verstappen moves up into third place.
[crew] Yes, mate!
[commentator] A brilliant
Australian Grand Prix!
[commentator] It's Valtteri Bottas who
wins the Australian Grand Prix.
[commentator] Hamilton across
the line in second.
Max Verstappen, for the first time ever,
will stand on the podium at Albert Park.
[crowd cheering]
[commentator] Ferrari finish fourth
and fifth, chased by Kevin Magnussen,
best of the rest, in sixth place,
putting Haas top of the midfield.
[crew] Chequered flag, Kevin,
chequered flag.
P6. Perfect race, man.
Perfect start to the season.
[Magnussen] Whoo-hoo! Ah!
Great job, boys. Great job, man.
[all applauding]
[crowd cheering]
And they're finished!
Well done!
- Very happy, happy.
- First podium!
Thank you very much, thank you.
[crowd cheering]
[Verstappen] I'm not a dreamer.
I want to achieve.
I think everybody had
a lot of question marks
about the partnership
we were starting with Honda,
but I believe that in the future,
we can win world championships again
like the past.
[crowd cheering]
- Good one.
- Good job. At least one.
- 50% better than last year.
- Yeah.
[chuckles] Getting there.
One more year and we're there again.
[Steiner] It's such a mix of feelings,
but in the end you go away,
you make sure everyone is motivated
for the next race and you keep on going.
[Grosjean] It's one of 21,
and they're all part of one championship.
The car is performing well. I feel good.
So, I'm ready to tackle the 20 others.
They actually showed your start.
They showed your start on the screen.
It's frustrating.
Your launch was awesome.
[Ricciardo] It's a bit
of a kick in the guts
because it's just not
the way I wanted to start.
It does get you down.
But the positive and the flip side is that
there's still so many races left,
so it's not like it's the last race
of the season
and you've got no more chance
at retaliation.
[Steiner] We are not going
to vote on this.
If somebody opposes to that, I sack them.
I wasn't even watching anymore.
I couldn't give a fuck.
[man] It's gonna be a gearbox change.
Do you think we can do it or not?
[crew 1] Two minutes to go.
[crew 2] What happened?
They hit each other.
[crew 2] Fuckin' idiots!
[Steiner] I've had enough of both of you.
You let the fucking team down.
I don't need you here.
- [man] Hello?
- Who the fuck are you?
You should have thrown
some banana peels at my rivals.
- Can you win this weekend?
- Yeah!
[Horner] If they're good enough,
they swim. They survive.
If they're not good enough...
[commentator]
Verstappen goes off the track!
[Sainz Jr.] I'm working more
than anyone else in Formula 1.
[man] We're gonna remove
that subject and put you in place.
[Wolff] Let's crush them.
May the best man win.
[upbeat music playing]