I lost it.
Fucking hell! No!
Last year was probably
the hardest moment of my life.
I had the Red Bull demotion.
I got moved from Red Bull to Toro Rosso.
Alex Albon,
after just 12 races in Formula 1,
has now replaced Pierre Gasly at Red Bull.
It was a really horrible and...
and difficult time for me to go through.
Yeah, of course, I got a lot of shit.
Did you get any advance warning?
Well...
Pierre was demoted
in a very public fashion.
You're surprised by
the decision. Do you believe it was fair?
In 2020,
I feel I'm a more complete driver
and probably performing
at my best level at the moment.
Alongside Lewis Hamilton
and Max Verstappen,
Pierre Gasly is...
...undoubtedly
the driver of 2020 so far.
I deserve to go back to Red Bull.
And that's the target, yeah, that's clear.
Is it the jacket with the trousers
or the jacket with jeans?
- Whatever.
- My jeans are good. Don't touch my jeans.
Okay, that's nice.
I think this is gonna go great. Look.
Get this.
Yeah, that's right.
- Oh my God!
- Here he is.
Who is this wild animal?
It's actually good, the weather now.
Yeah, when the sun's out,
it's getting much hotter.
Yeah, but you're hot all the time, right?
- No.
- When I get close to you, you get hot.
No, not really. Somehow... somehow not.
Not anymore.
"Not anymore"
means at some point, it worked!
Of course, yeah.
AlphaTauri is the new name
for Toro Rosso.
It is a solid midfield team.
Its only reason for existing
over the past decade
was as a Formula 1 school
for Red Bull's young drivers.
Pierre's confidence
since going back to AlphaTauri
has completely transformed.
Pierre Gasly closing in.
They go side by side.
Fuck yes!
Sensational for AlphaTauri.
Now, can Gasly keep his foot in?
He can, to get past the Ferrari driver.
Yes!
Ah, yes!
That feels nice.
Good job, Pierre. Amazing race.
But every driver that races at AlphaTauri
doesn't see their future at AlphaTauri.
It's a team where you prove your worth
to Red Bull Racing.
For me, it was good to be back.
Suddenly, I understood how to drive again.
This is a bit small, no?
Of course, the car is not as competitive
and, as a competitive guy,
you always wanna be in the fastest car.
My goal will always be to be
in that Red Bull car in the top team.
As long as I'm competitive,
as long as I'm pushing,
opportunities will come
and... and that's just my... my spirit
and mentality at the moment.
Welcome to Spa-Francorchamps,
located deep in Belgium's Ardennes Forest,
one of the oldest Grand Prix circuits
in the world.
On this Friday morning,
it's Free Practice one.
Hello, Netflix.
I'm totally not smiling right now.
The scene of controversy a year ago
when the Red Bull team
dropped Pierre Gasly
from their second seat.
Yeah, exactly.
- Here he is.
- Morning.
It's very tough going back to Spa.
All these memories come back.
But I'm not someone gives up.
What's the plan?
To do the interviews
and the first one is Jennie Gow from BBC.
- Yeah.
- We'll do it by phone.
Now, Pierre,
we all remember the events
of Spa last year.
Obviously, getting demoted from Red Bull.
Why is it that you are
so much more comfortable
in the AlphaTauri team?
You seem happy,
your results speak for themselves,
versus that Red Bull second seat,
which is always one that's uncomfortable,
I think, for everybody that ever takes it?
I don't want to go
into too much details about that,
but they gave Alex the seat last year
because he had some decent results,
um, and... and hopefully, the...
um, yeah, for the... the coming years,
it's gonna be decided
on the same, uh, on the same criteria.
But at the end of the day,
I'm not the one deciding.
I think Formula 1 is highly personal,
highly political,
so, when it comes to Pierre,
he has a massive point to prove.
Unfortunately, I've just had to
have one of the dogs put down, so...
Oh no!
It's horrible because
they become such a part of the family.
The mood I'm in, I tell you,
ask me about Pierre.
It's exactly one year ago
when Red Bull swapped the seats
between, uh, Pierre Gasly and Alex Albon.
Would you say it's impossible
to have, one day,
Pierre Gasly back at Red Bull?
He's obviously, uh, back in
and doing a good job in the AlphaTauri
and of course, we monitor his progress.
To drive for Red Bull,
this team is all about delivering.
Obviously, we have a lot of information
on how he's performing and developing.
Pierre's driven some good races this year,
but he's also shown dips as well.
Ça va?
Pierre wouldn't have had
the chance to be in Formula 1
without Red Bull.
And the reality is, when you get there,
if you can't cope
with the pressure and scrutiny,
you're never gonna make it
at the highest level in... in Formula 1.
I feel people
are gonna critique my shaving.
You know, I've got
that kind of like puberty fluffy beard.
- You're an aggressive shaver.
- I'm an aggressive shaver.
I've never been taught how to shave,
so, um, if anyone wants to sponsor me,
Gillette...?
Gillette or Nivea.
Nivea aftershave.
I would say, based on your ability
to grow a beard,
aim for the aftershave products
as opposed to the actual shaving products.
Last year, I was very much
a schoolkid on my first day of school.
How do you get in this place?
We're not even halfway
through the season yet,
and I still feel very...
very new to the sport.
Alex's performances
so far in 2020 have been good...
...but not great.
Everyone at Red Bull would have expected
at least a podium by now.
Right. Let's see what we've got.
We're working very hard
with Alex at the moment
to try and find
the confidence in this car that Max has.
The car hasn't been easy this year.
Arguably,
it's been a harder car than last year.
And he's up against Verstappen
who is just in unbelievable form.
How's the balance, Alex?
This car feels very nervous
into turn one.
It just feels like I'm sliding
from entry to exit.
- Like the tires are gone.
- Okay.
You all right?
Does the car seem a bit more settled?
It's still nervous,
but at least it's predictable.
Yeah.
He doesn't sound
very happy at all, so...
A year ago,
I was fast-tracked into a big team,
but it doesn't mean that I'm here to stay.
You know, as a Red Bull driver,
you're expected to be
getting podiums, getting wins.
It doesn't feel
like he's enjoying driving the car,
the balance that he's got.
Based on the car this weekend?
Yeah, he's not been comfy in it. I...
It's starting to be a bit of a pattern of...
We just need him to get the...
to hit the ground running earlier.
That's all it is.
And then everything
to just be easier for him.
Anyway...
Some of that
will be experience as well.
He's not far
off the podium, though.
Quiet.
Ah, it is, yeah.
Coming back to Spa reminded me
of all the memories from the year before.
The fatal accident
of Antoine Hubert happened
at the famous Eau Rouge corner
just behind us.
at the most dangerous event of the season
in Formula 1 and Formula 2...
Last year, I got moved
from Red Bull to Toro Rosso
and then Anthoine passed away
that same weekend.
It was the hardest moment of my life.
He was such a... a close friend.
Since we were little kids.
We had the same life goal.
He wanted as much as... as I wanted
to be in Formula 1.
Fucking crazy, eh?
After I got moved from Red Bull,
Anthoine sent me a message.
"Prove everybody wrong and...
show them your... your skills and talent."
It is round seven
of this Formula 1 season in 2020.
Hey. How are you?
We nearly got
your fucking number two!
You know he's gonna be the one
on the brink to turn five.
Exactly.
There's only two teams
in the last ten years
that have won World Championships
and that's Red Bull and Mercedes.
And I genuinely think
that we have an outside chance,
but we need both drivers
to maximize the opportunity from the car.
You all right?
If we could put them under pressure,
they would crack.
Just go aggressive.
The pressure is gonna be on Alex
and the best way he can get around that
is to get his first podium.
Here's the starting grid.
Hamilton on pole, Bottas, Verstappen,
Daniel Ricciardo is fourth
ahead of Alex Albon in fifth.
Pierre Gasly starts 12th for AlphaTauri.
He'll have his work cut out
to get anything in this race.
- How much more time?
- Race is two minutes to green.
Okay, Pierre,
you know the target.
And we're racing at Spa.
Ah, fuck's sake!
Lost the rear a bit.
- Come on!
Albon getting squirrelly
coming out of turn one
and that's enabled Ocon
to get ahead of him.
Albon now fighting back
after losing that place at the start.
Let's have another go at him.
Get stuck in.
Go on, Alex!
We can barely catch them with DRS.
Onboard with Pierre Gasly.
You know what our race is.
We go all in.
It's all about maximum attack.
After what happened to Anthoine...
I need to show everybody...
Here they come into the hairpin.
...that I'm performing better.
Be careful there.
You have to be careful.
Pérez is gonna be
under pressure here from Gasly.
What a move that was!
Side by side through Eau Rouge.
That's how we race!
What a job. That's P11.
He's got a great chance.
In fact, he's already passed the Ferrari.
Come on, Pierre.
We are back in business. P10.
Gasly fancies a go, doesn't he?
That's, uh, P9.
Okay, head down, Pierre, head down.
Stroll in front.
Come on, let's get him.
Gasly's now into eighth place.
Alex Albon
not really making much of an impression.
Alex,
it's the last lap now. Stay strong.
Yep, okay.
Uh, gap behind
to Ocon is reducing.
Esteban Ocon,
he's got Alex Albon in his sights.
He's gonna try the move to the outside
and he gets it done.
Oh, for fuck's sake!
Lewis Hamilton, another win.
Mercedes one-two.
It's third place for Max Verstappen,
and Alex Albon just holds onto sixth,
losing out on yet another podium.
Just couldn't make an impact.
Gasly crosses the line
with a fine performance,
gaining four positions to eighth place
and Driver of the Day as well.
I mean,
take a bow, Pierre Gasly.
What a drive, Pierre.
Wow!
Fuck yeah!
Okay, Alex,
hard luck there in the end.
Yep.
It was unreal.
It was a shit race, though.
There's not much more
you could've done.
When things don't go well,
I'm my harshest critic.
You can't... You can't hide it.
It's just really tough.
There's no point
feeling sorry for yourself
and that's all there is to it.
Can we do a little foot tap?
Driver of the Day.
Dude, if it wasn't for social distancing,
I'd give you a hug. What an amazing drive.
You mastered six moves in the end.
Oh yeah?
My favorite one was the one on Pérez.
I was like, "If he keeps going,
we're both in the wall,
and I'm just fucking going for it, so..."
It's such a strange place
for Gasly to be in.
It's just bonkers how well he's done.
He's still got a point to prove
and he still wants that Red Bull seat.
Pierre, what you think
this strong form might potentially mean
for your future career,
from you being dropped by Red Bull?
At the end of the day,
it's... it's not my call.
I've always believed
as long as you put strong performances,
sooner or later, opportunities will come.
It's great to see
our sister team, AlphaTauri, uh,
doing a fantastic job.
Good for Pierre as well.
Uh, he looks very comfortable
in that environment.
He looks... looks, uh, relaxed
and he's driving at the potential
that we knew he had.
Obviously,
Pierre got Driver of the Day today.
Does it put him back in the frame
for a future with Red Bull?
Pierre? Um...
Well, I think he's...
he's, uh, performing well at AlphaTauri,
but I think we're, you know,
we're happy with the way things are.
- Okay.
- Cheers, guys.
See you next week.
Helmut and I looked at,
you know, the information.
Our decisions,
they're not just made on emotion.
They're based on facts.
They're based on a huge amount of data,
a huge amount of analysis.
From a team point of view,
there's been
nobody pushing internally to say,
"We've gotta have Pierre back."
Welcome along
on a Friday afternoon
in this glorious part of Italy.
It's round eight
of the Formula 1 World Championship.
Nowhere excites quite like Monza.
At the Temple of Speed,
a final farewell after 43 years,
it's time to say thank you
at the Williams family's final race.
I told him, now he has to deal
with you at home every day.
Thanks!
I'll be asking you for a job.
Do you need a PA?
Sorry!
Why is it, as soon
as the cameras are on, you mess up?
I just hope we can overtake this time.
- I think it's gonna be hard.
- Yeah.
Ready for a good day.
Remember what I was saying earlier,
if they start hammering you,
don't stand for any bollocks.
We're in control.
You've had your ups and downs,
but Christian and the whole team,
they've been very supportive of you,
publicly at least.
Sometimes, in sport,
you get a result that changes everything.
Is maybe that what you need?
You think you can fight
towards the podium?
It could be that Red Bull
genuinely believe that Alex is the one,
that Alex has the potential
that Pierre didn't.
I don't... Look, I think
Alex is a great racing driver.
I don't think
we've seen the best of him yet.
Uh, we have no interest in... in having
Pierre back, you know, this season.
On the other hand, it could just be that...
they cannot bring themselves to admit
that they made a mistake.
Rumble time.
Welcome to Gas-man's Carpool Karaoke.
So, do you want the news?
"No 2020 Red Bull return for Gasly,"
Horner said.
"Alex is only going to get better."
"He's still pretty young and inexperienced
and we are doing all we can
to support and develop him."
But seriously, it's like...
It's a joke.
How they treat this is a joke.
I have my target.
The fight is on.
And now,
we're gonna score some fucking points.
Sometimes, Formula 1 is not fair.
Unfortunately, that's the way it is.
I feel this is, like, extra small.
No, it's just pumped guns.
But if I get knocked,
I just go back at it even harder.
- Radio check okay?
- Radio is good.
We go to the grid.
Please confirm.
Copy.
When things piss you off,
me, I use this energy
to make me even stronger.
The situation with Alex is very clear.
He knows the pressure that he's under
to deliver a result.
He needs to get a little bit more
of that "fuck you" attitude
that you see the great drivers have.
You know, as a Red Bull driver,
you need to perform
to... to kind of show
the big bosses, really,
that you're there to be in Formula 1.
Alex Albon starts ninth,
desperate to end this run without a podium
for the Red Bull driver.
He's alongside Pierre Gasly
in tenth place.
Ten seconds. Ten seconds.
It's lights out and away we go.
Alex Albon
and Pierre Gasly wheel to wheel.
Oh, contact!
Gasly gets past him.
Can you check my front?
I was sandwiched.
We are checking.
Alex Albon getting it
all wrong at that first chicane
and losing places as a result.
I've got no grip on these hards!
We've got a little bit
of floor damage on the left-hand side.
- So, we're gonna be at the back?
- We are currently P14.
Albon in
serious trouble here. He's dropped to P14.
Okay, Pierre, box, box. Box, box.
Torque one in the pitlane.
Focus on reaction time.
We are good?
We are in a good place.
You're doing a very good job.
Push, push. Push, push.
- Leclerc behind you, one second.
- Copy.
And that is a very big accident.
Leclerc is out?
Confirmed. He went out.
Safety car. Safety car. Safety car!
Okay, Pierre.
They are still clearing the track.
Pit-lane entry is closed at the moment.
I'll keep you posted.
The pit-lane entry
is closed, but Hamilton's coming in.
Who pitted in front of us?
Only Hamilton, but the pit lane
was closed, so he should have a penalty.
Hamilton is under investigation
for pitting when the pit-lane entry
was closed.
And now, the pit-lane entry is open.
There will be some cars
in the pit exit. Everyone is boxing.
Copy.
This is pretty good for us.
So,
this has really changed the order round.
Pierre Gasly pitted way before,
so he's a massive gainer in this.
Okay, Pierre,
we just gained 20 seconds.
- Which position are we now?
- P3.
Now the red flags are out.
We're red-flagging the race.
It's basically a reset.
Incredible scenes at Monza.
Pierre Gasly
is in an unbelievable position right now.
- When you stop, go to P3.
- Copy.
Hamilton is leading,
Stroll is second, Gasly is third.
And we're getting ready
to restart the race on lap 28.
Okay, Pierre,
you know the target now.
Yeah, it's good for us
to just fucking push and see what we get.
In Formula 1,
you never know what can happen.
There is no way
I'm gonna miss this opportunity.
And we're racing again.
Stroll dropping back.
Gasly up to second place.
Okay, push, push. Push, push.
Lewis Hamilton
holds the lead for the time being.
How is the rear slip and braking?
Still all good on data, Pierre.
Still all good on data.
News from race control.
It's a ten-second stop-and-go penalty
for Lewis Hamilton.
And he's coming in.
Hamilton into the pit lane
from the lead of the race
to serve
his ten-second stop-and-go penalty.
Pierre Gasly leads the Italian Grand Prix.
Head down, Pierre, head down.
Keep focusing on the pace.
Copy.
Gasly, Sainz and Stroll,
the one-two-three.
Sainz closing in.
Tell me the gap behind.
Sainz, 2.1 behind
and Stroll is two behind him.
Seven laps to go, seven laps.
How long can Gasly
keep Sainz out of DRS range?
I don't know
if we have more power,
but if we have, let's use it.
This chance might never
come around ever again for both drivers.
You don't know in Formula 1.
You've got to take your opportunities.
Winning a Formula 1 race
was one of my dreams
since I started to watch F1
when I was five years old.
But to win a Formula 1 race,
being in a midfield car,
you've got to risk everything.
Sainz is giving it everything.
Gasly is under so much pressure.
Two more laps. Two more laps.
Okay, push, push. Push, push.
Sainz is charging the battery
to prepare to attack.
We can defend.
Sainz is now within one second.
Last lap. One more lap.
Carlos Sainz is going to get close,
but he's not gonna get close enough.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Pierre Gasly wins the Italian Grand Prix!
Oh my God!
What did we just do?
- What did you do?
- We won the fucking race!
Yes!
Oh my God!
Oh my God, guys. We did it!
Oh my God! Yes!
P1, Pierre, P1!
AlphaTauri, Honda,
all the engineers, all the mechanics,
everybody in Faenza,
thanks to you, we... we did it.
We did it!
Yeah!
You're as good as your last race
in this game,
so perceptions can change
very, very quickly.
Pierre has done an excellent job.
He's driving like he has nothing to lose.
Number one!
Okay, so, finishing order, uh,
was Gasly, Sainz, Stroll.
We were P15.
Okay. Sorry, guys.
Look...
...the situation with Alex is very clear.
That race was a disaster for him,
so we need to see Alex
really grab that seat and make it his own.
The problem is if he doesn't,
then, you know,
we need to look outside and think,
"Okay, if Alex isn't gonna
make that next step,
who do we put alongside Max for 2021?"
Well done to Pierre Gasly!
This is such an amazing moment.
A moment I dreamed about
for so many years.
I just thought,
"Okay, we've done it."
"What more do I need to prove?"
Oh...
I know, in life,
you... you have many obstacles.
After the Red Bull demotion,
I had to face a big challenge.
I had to rebuild myself.
But it's only my third season in F1,
so I'm better than last year.
2021 is gonna be a better Pierre,
and 2022 is gonna be
an even better Pierre.
Ready to give my very best...
...to bring this team
as much success as I can.
Let me get this done,
then you can go.
I need to call my parents as well.
Have you heard them? Fuck,
I cannot imagine how they are right now.
What the fuck?
The target for the season is to survive
as a team.
- It's a very expensive business.
- Couldn't even do one lap!
We need new sponsorship deals.
I'm wheeling and dealing,
Gene, to stay alive.
The German sponsors want German drivers.
I will decide which driver goes this week.
He needs to step it up.
If he doesn't, there are gonna be
some difficult decisions to be made.
It's incredibly hard.
He doesn't want to leave Formula 1.
Stop the car. It's on fire.