- Is Gene here?
- No.
For Americans,
to travel is difficult, you know?
- Lucky for you, isn't it?
- Fucking hell, yeah.
Yeah, I have to speak with him
every fucking day. He doesn't stop.
Hi, Gene.
I said to you, as long as we can afford
what you said to me,
I'm trying to... I'm doing my best
The target for the season
is to survive...
...as a team.
Okay, gonna fix it, you know?
That is what we need to do
every day, Gene.
I'm wheeling and dealing at the moment,
to stay alive.
How do you sum up
your season this year?
It's one short word.
Shit!
What the fuck?
Fucking hell. Who was that?
Grosjean has something of a meltdown.
Jesus Christ.
Brakes gone.
Haas's problems continue.
Oh, Magnussen could be out of the race.
- Sorry, guys.
- Fuck me!
It seems so long ago
that Haas were celebrating.
You know, just week after week
after week of constantly losing
is just not easy to do.
We can't keep running in the back.
I don't want to necessarily win,
but I want to be competitive
once in a while.
Thank you, bye.
Fucking hell.
If I don't do a... a good job,
I should be gone.
If you are not good enough,
you will be, uh, spat out.
Action.
Like a professional.
At least I can do something!
Hello and welcome to Silverstone.
Good day to be back to work, huh?
On the warmest day
in the British summer so far,
we welcome you to the British Grand Prix.
Man, we should be fucking surfing.
Aah.
Keep "aah".
It's a good tone, that is.
Aah.
Sorry.
There's always room for dessert.
I know, but some desserts,
like, let's be honest, ice cream,
you could just keep picking
and eat the whole tub.
- I need a brolly.
- Want this one?
Tim, where's my brolly?
- It's fully the sun now, huh?
- Want an umbrella?
No, fuck off!
That would hurt my ego, you know.
Standing there with an umbrella...
- Wouldn't do much for my ego either.
- Yeah, fucking hell.
"It's a little bit of sun
and I need an umbrella."
Feet, touch the toes,
hold for five seconds,
back up, then carry on for another five.
I think being a small team
has got its advantages and disadvantages.
One of the advantages,
it's more like everybody knows each other.
Like family.
Big stretch
and then back again for five.
But I would say
it's a very dysfunctional family.
- Cheers, guys. Thank you.
- I'm knackered.
Haas has one
of the most stable operations in Formula 1
in terms of staff turnover.
It's like Willy Wonka's chocolate factory.
Nobody ever goes in,
nobody ever comes out.
Romain and Kevin have been with us
for, uh, for a long time now.
Romain was there from day one
and Kevin joined us in our second year
and, uh, especially in Formula 1,
I don't think there's many drivers
which have been so long with a team.
- How's the hand?
- Getting there.
- Is it painful?
- Aches.
I'm Kevin Magnussen
and this is Drive to Survive Season 3.
- Hey, guys.
- Hi, guys, how are you?
Hey, how's it going?
- Well, thanks. How are you?
- Not too bad.
Haas has been my home in Formula 1
for the last four years.
When you spend four years with a team,
you become close with everyone.
Well, we have five fans here.
They have questions for you both.
I feel very happy here,
very comfortable.
I know what the team needs
and what they want from me,
so it... it helps you,
as a driver, perform better
when you have that around you.
What do you listen to
on your headphones before each race?
- Taylor Swift.
- Taylor Swift...
I've heard Romain listen
to Taylor Swift before the race.
I've spent five years
with Haas, wearing the colors.
It's been... it's really good, you know?
Kevin, what do you listen to?
I kind of like to listen to,
like, old Danish rock music.
Not good!
I've put a lot of effort,
a lot of passion and love into the team
uh, since... since day one
and always wanted us
to do better and better.
Where's the driver?
He's on his way.
He's on his last interview.
At the moment,
I'm not happy where we are.
The car last year wasn't good
and this year, we're struggling as well,
so we, uh, need to refresh ourselves
and rethink everything
and see what we do going forward
for the mid-and long-term,
not the short term.
- Hey, Romain. You all right?
- Yeah.
- How was your holiday?
- Yeah, good. Yourself?
After a very strong 2018,
the team started going down,
racing for the last position.
Now, we have absolutely no chance
to be on the podium.
- What about you? Do any drinking?
- Yeah.
Well, I put 2.5 kilos on, so must have!
He should've come out right here
and overtaken Räikkönen,
instead, he came out miles behind.
You learn a lot from tough times,
but you also... you get a stronger bond
in the team between everyone, and...
and that will make us better in...
for the future.
As we've seen
after previous races,
it's very tight
between ourselves and Alfa,
so, obviously, the potential
to get out Q1 is there.
Um, and, obviously that's the main aim
for... for us in this respect.
Our main rivals, they are Alfa Romeo.
I think the rest of the midfield
is... is a touch too far ahead.
Hi, Guenther!
If they're doing better,
I'm not getting upset.
Some you win, some you lose.
But I think they play always fair
and, uh, it's... for sure,
it's not good to... to lose against them.
I need to go to the press pen.
- You have three minutes.
- Got it.
Guenther is a colleague
and I am spending more time, uh,
in my life
with my colleagues than with my wife!
And...
How many assistants
have you got?
I have nobody because I have no money.
You've got three people
running around you.
- Yeah.
- Another one coming. Four now.
We can fight on track,
on drivers,
but at the end,
we are doing the same business
and we can sit down together
and have a coffee.
You're so stupid, Fred!
Fred and myself
are in very similar positions.
We are, I would say,
the only independent teams now.
He's got an owner, I've got an owner,
so we compare the notes.
Haas and Alfa Romeo are incredibly close
competitors in all regards.
Not only do they share
the same engine provider,
but their annual budget
is probably around the same figure.
But Alfa Romeo
have world champion Kimi Räikkönen.
Here's your 2007 world champion,
Kimi Räikkönen.
I'm Kimi Räikkönen
and I drive for Alfa Romeo Racing.
Kimi Räikkönen is
a valuable commodity.
He's got the expertise, the consistency,
a little bit more experience
he can bring to the team.
And he's keeping his seat for 2021.
So, I do the countdown
and then, if you'd like to smile.
Three, two, one.
Thanks a lot.
But he's a funny character
to try and read.
Are you a fan of interviews?
Never been.
Still not so.
In the other seat
is one of Ferrari's junior drivers,
Antonio Giovinazzi.
Hello.
The first Italian driver in Formula 1 for...
a good long time.
Give me your smile in three, two, one.
Perfect.
- Giovinazzi!
- Ciao!
- Hello.
- All good?
Yes.
I can't see you, Giovinazzi.
I'm here. Good evening.
The first thing when my mom saw me,
is always,
"You look so skinny, you need to eat."
What will you eat tonight?
I don't know.
Maybe rice, salmon and avocado.
We were,
you know, a small family
from a town in south of Italy
called Martina Franca.
Are you, uh,
a bit of a hero in Martina Franca?
Yes, yes, yes.
Are you going out on your bike?
Yes. Sometimes I cycle.
The weather is nice over here.
I'm proud
to bring back the Italian flag
in the Formula 1 grid.
Of course, also a little bit of pressure
because I'm the only one.
So, I want to do well for them,
uh, but yeah, just, uh, in the end,
I'm just really proud.
Are you tired?
Uh, I will eat and go to bed.
Perfect.
Okay, take care. Goodbye.
- Good night. Bye.
- Bye. Good night. Bye.
He's... he's wicked quick, Antonio.
But he has some sort
of wild and wacky moments
where he loses control of the car.
And it's a surprise
that they keep him on, really, for 2020.
And finish.
Starting with this one.
For me,
the main thing this season
is that I show to my boss my talent.
It's my dream to score a podium with them.
You know, an Italian driver, in, uh...
with an Italian brand
like Alfa Romeo in a podium,
so this is my dream.
Everybody is supportive behind him
to try to get the best from... from Antonio.
But at the end, you have to perform
and if you don't do it,
you will lose your seat.
That's life.
Hello, everyone.
It's time for the British Grand Prix.
Haas have a lot to prove.
Guenther Steiner
will be feeling the pressure.
A small team like ours
is supported by investors
and in times like this,
they doubt everything.
There's a lot on the table,
but it... it is not anything
that a great race could be changed.
RG hasn't finished
the last five Grand Prix here.
I just fucking want him
to finish the race.
- Radio check, Romain.
- Yeah, radio is very good.
- Radio check, loud and clear.
- Yeah, loud and clear.
Okay, Kevin, have a great race.
Cars being fired up,
anticipation building.
We're racing at Silverstone.
Magnussen has already passed Albon.
Magnussen going
wheel to wheel with Pierre Gasly.
If you back off
in a Formula 1 race,
especially on that first lap,
you'll get overtaken so easily.
Great job.
You can't give away too much.
Whoa, there's a huge crash there.
Ah, fuck.
Oh my goodness me!
He didn't even do one lap!
Is Kevin okay?
Yeah, Kevin's okay.
Poor old Magnussen,
ending up in the gravel trap.
It's not what you want.
Keep pushing
to close the gap to Vettel.
Antonio, we are currently P13.
And behind, we have Grosjean.
This is awesome, dude.
Really good pace here.
Yeah, I'm pushing as hard as I can.
He could drive himself
into contention here.
- Box this lap.
- Copy.
A lot of drivers pitting.
Everybody pouring into the pits.
Apart from Romain Grosjean.
Fucking just pit
when everyone else pits!
Fucking hell!
I'm focusing on time right now.
Get as many positions as I can.
So, crucially,
that's put him into the top five,
but he's going to be really slow
on those old tires.
Okay, boys.
The front left is really struggling.
Fuck's sake!
Sainz is right
on the back of the Haas.
Good job so far.
Keep pushing, Antonio.
We slightly closed the gap
to the guys ahead.
Good performance from Giovinazzi.
He's just gonna keep plugging away.
Here comes Carlos Sainz.
I really don't know what I can do.
And Sainz up into fifth position.
The rear tires,
they're going on me.
Please tell him,
"just stay calm." Calm him down.
Here comes Lando Norris.
The second McLaren is through.
We're gonna get done again in a minute.
Ricciardo's next,
and he's now ahead of Grosjean.
Box, Romain, box.
Grosjean coming for his pit stop.
This stop will be crucial
to keep the Haas team in contention.
Oh my goodness.
It's a slow stop.
There's a gear in there somewhere.
Are you kidding?
What the fuck?
Can't believe what I've just seen!
Fuck!
Why couldn't I engage first?
We will check. We will check.
- We're last now.
- We are fucking last.
Not been a good weekend
for Haas, has it?
Good job, Antonio. We are P14.
The last two corners. Good job.
Well done. Excellent race.
Yeah, thank you very much.
And here's Grosjean,
limping home, plumb last.
Yeah, dude, that's the checker.
I'm sorry, guys.
Sorry.
Normally,
when you drive into the pit,
you go straight to first gear.
He went into neutral.
He fucked it up, you know.
It's his fault, yeah.
Oh well,
I guess we weren't getting points anyway.
No.
Tough times now
for Magnussen and Romain Grosjean.
Fucking hell.
Hi, Gene. Did you watch us?
Oh, yeah.
Uh, front and rear suspension
is for sure broken.
Fucking hell.
And did you see with Romain?
No, no, no, no, no.
He fucked the pit stop up.
Otherwise we would have finished 11th,
Gene, 10th or 11th.
We would have been in front of Vettel.
No. No. No.
I don't want to spend more money
on this team at the moment.
You need to find a sponsor.
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
All right, Gene. No.
I'll speak with you in the week.
Thank you, Gene.
Thank you. Bye-bye. Bye.
I think, for sure, uh,
Gene was not happy with the results.
It's a very expensive business.
Money is, uh, less than it was before.
There is less income.
So, we need to find outside financing
to survive as a team.
The presentation is ready now.
How did you say you were gonna do it?
- I don't have my adapter.
- They must have an adapter there.
I was thinking
we say this is 15 million US dollars.
As long as I have the $15 million,
I'm okay.
On the sponsor side,
there's a negotiation
with a very well-known company
in Germany in the tech business,
and that is the partners you want.
It's very stressful, but I think
Gene trusts me that I can pull it off.
Let's just walk and say hello.
- Hello, Mr. Steiner.
- Afternoon.
We need sponsors
to keep going with the team.
If a partner comes aboard, that would mean
somebody shares the cost of going racing
and we would be more than happy.
The drivers have also sent you
a little greeting
and I got it signed by both Haas drivers.
Personally signed?
Great, thank you.
- A warm welcome here.
- Thank you.
It is important to me
that we are included along the way.
And the question here is,
how can you include us
so we will learn to trust the team?
The sponsorship doesn't come as easy
as saying, "Sponsor me," you know.
For sure there will be mandates to follow.
Maybe
it's not just the sponsor that's new,
but maybe you also have a German driver.
This is enormously important for us.
Sponsors nowadays,
they want to have a little bit
of influence also in the drivers.
So, there is a lot to decide
and to weigh up against each other.
What is the best to do?
And, uh, it needs some thinking
and, uh,
to... to make the right strategic decision.
I don't want to promise
anything I can't do.
I can... I'm not saying it's a yes, but...
I mean, there are possibilities, you know.
- Okay, great.
- Thank you.
Bye. See you next time. Bye. Thank you.
Thank you for your time.
Bye. Thank you.
The easiest would be
to have tons of money,
just keep the same two drivers
and keep on going
and, uh, have no worries,
but there is a... a team
which needs to be kept alive
with the best talent
and the best finances possible.
It's quite a big responsibility.
There is sometimes tough decisions.
Will be very difficult for me to do,
to tell Romain or Kevin it's over.
They will be upset.
They are part of the family.
The big news this weekend
is that Mick Schumacher,
rising star of Formula 2
and son of seven-time world champion
Michael Schumacher,
is here.
Mick Schumacher could be the answer
to most of Guenther Steiner's problems.
Ciao.
Morning. How are you?
But...
Fred Vasseur at Alfa Romeo
is a very shrewd operator.
He also sees the kind of cash cow
that Mick Schumacher could be in his team.
Okay, that's fun.
Mick Schumacher crosses the line
to win for the first time in Formula 2
I'm Mick Schumacher, I'm 21 years old,
and I'm a racing driver.
My dad is Michael Schumacher.
He's seven-time world champion
and he's the greatest.
My dad is my idol, that's for sure.
Obviously, my goal is F1.
There are two teams
which haven't, uh, announced
their driver lineup yet,
which are Alfa Romeo and Haas.
So, yeah, we'll have to see.
I'm here now this weekend with Alfa Romeo,
just to get the insights to feel,
"Okay, how does a racing team
really work on a race weekend?"
I wonder if I printed enough.
Never had this many people.
There's a lot of rumors
surrounding the team.
Um, driver market and...
We're not focusing on any of those.
We're just focusing on doing our job.
Of course I know.
I'm not stupid.
I know that Mick is there
and Mick is doing well in Formula 2.
He is not my main focus now.
My main focus is, uh, is doing well,
and I'm sure if I'm doing well, I will,
uh, I will be still here next year.
I knew that Mick was part
of the Ferrari Driver Academy.
I was already watching him in,
um, in F3,
two years ago or three years ago.
I'm a competitor.
We always want to get more.
If you are happy with what you have,
then you are dead.
Mick is wearing
an Alfa Romeo jacket this weekend,
which doesn't mean
he's next year in Alfa Romeo.
Doesn't mean anything.
Gene, I'm working on the deal
as we said, you need to trust me on that.
Having a German driver
for a German sponsor,
obviously, is crucial.
Mick Schumacher's coming in? No.
Because he's very sellable,
you know, and that's what my point is.
If I've got Schumacher,
I think I can find some more money, Gene.
- It's good to have money.
- Yeah.
So, if... if we get Schumacher,
I think I can... I can find some.
I hope three million.
Between three and five million more.
So, we have got a very good budget,
you know.
Mick, by winning the F2 championship,
for sure, is a hot property.
And with Mick, the other attraction is,
uh, we all know who his father is.
But what can be done? I don't know yet.
But again the pace
of Rafaele Marciello...
These days, for young boys...
...Albert Costa off the race track.
...it is impossible to make it into F1.
You need to think of the future.
Put some money aside
and think about another activity.
I don't know
the talks Mick had with Fred.
I don't know that,
but I just cannot wait around.
Let's do it this week.
I want to use the momentum.
No, we have to do it this week.
I have the offer on the table.
I just have to negotiate the numbers
with him.
I try to do the best
and try to make my point, why...
why he should come to us,
and... and... and work on the deal.
I should get a relatively quick answer.
Hopefully,
he will say this is okay for him.
Okay, let's do that.
A race is starting at two,
then I can't sit here
and be filmed by Netflix, you know.
Then I won't have a job anymore.
The situation is strange
when you have no idea
what's going to happen.
I have a very, very strong feeling
the team is going to change one of us.
I believe the future
is always in your hands.
But, obviously,
I am not the one making the decision.
Radio check, Kevin.
There has been competition from day one
with Kevin.
He's tough on track.
The decision to, you know,
get rid of Kevin or myself...
Put some oil on the fire.
If you want to go fast
at this one, you've got to have balls.
You've got to have balls
and you've got to know the track.
The Haas drivers are racing
to try and stay in Formula 1
at this stage.
They'll be giving it everything.
They certainly will.
Green flag at the back.
Now we wait
for the five red lights to go out.
When they do,
we will be racing at the Nürburgring.
Lights out and away we go
for 60 laps around the Nürburgring,
it's the Eifel Grand Prix.
Magnussen in 14th
has had a rubbish start.
Fuck me!
I'm on fucking ice.
Grosjean's heading backwards.
He's lost four places from the start.
Fuck me. They have no grip.
Here comes Kevin Magnussen
to the inside of Kvyat, for 14th.
And he's done it.
I got hit badly
by some gravel by Kimi
and it's fucking hurting my finger.
Are you okay?
I don't know.
I can't use my left index.
I hope it's not broken.
It will be throbbing.
It will be hurting a lot.
In these cold temperatures,
you'll probably feel it even more.
Antonio Giovinazzi's
made a great start. He's up in 11th place.
Good job, Antonio. Keep pushing.
Obviously heavy traffic.
Impossible to overtake.
Maybe we tell Romain
he's doing the same time
as the guys in front of him
just to keep
his, you know, spirit up, yeah.
Pace is really good.
You're matching Gasly ahead.
Good job, mate. Let's get him.
Räikkönen to the inside of Russell.
Oh, he's got that wrong!
That'll be the end of Russell's afternoon.
Oh my word. What happened there?
Safety car. Safety car.
We've got a virtual safety car deployed
and as a result of that,
this could be pit-stop time.
Box, box.
Copy.
Somehow we need to tell Romain
that if he can do it on a one-stop,
we have points, you know.
How's it going?
I think tires are still okay.
We are thinking
of a variation on Plan B.
Okay,
think and I'll drive fast.
While most of the drivers
are taking advantage of the safety car
to come in for new tires,
Grosjean looks like he's taking a gamble
and staying out.
Okay, dude,
you're gonna be in free air,
so let's push on these tires
and get 'em going.
Okay, Kevin, currently you're P12.
Romain's P10 on his one-stop,
ten seconds up the road.
Giovinazzi ahead is P11.
Antonio Giovinazzi looking
for his second points finish of the year.
We have Grosjean ahead,
nine seconds.
Copy.
Is he pushing flat out, Antonio,
or what is he doing?
He needs to fucking push.
There is Mick Schumacher,
watching on.
He's with the team all weekend.
These laps are good.
You're a second quicker
than Hülkenberg ahead. Let's get him.
Fuck,
that's good times for Romain.
What's happened to Magnussen?
Come on. Come on!
Okay, Kevin, currently P11.
Vettel's behind us.
Mode push. Mode push.
Here comes Vettel,
looking for the inside of Magnussen.
Magnussen tries to cut back.
He's not going to give up that easily.
That's audacious into turn four!
Vettel has the place.
Kevin, push like hell to the end.
- Let's keep going.
- Okay.
Romain, five laps to go,
1.3 back to Gio.
He's got Vettel behind him.
He'll come under pressure soon.
Grosjean ahead. Keep pushing.
It's important to get Grosjean, otherwise
we risk to get out of the points.
Come on!
Three more laps to go, Kevin.
Three laps.
Starting last lap, Romain.
This is brilliant.
Hamilton crosses the line
to take his 91st Formula 1 victory,
and first points of the year
for Romain Grosjean
What a brilliant drive.
That is the checker, mate. P9.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes!
Yes, guys, yes!
Yes!
- Well done, Antonio. P10.
- Thank you.
Checkered flag, Kevin.
Checkered flag. P13.
Sorry it didn't go quite right at the end.
Yeah, good job, guys.
Thank you for the work and, uh,
yeah, you're the boys. You're the boys.
Thanks to everybody.
Great job, Romain.
Thank you, guys.
Thank you for never giving up.
Yeah,
that's not something we do, giving up.
We needed this, huh?
We needed this.
For the whole team,
scoring two points
was a bloody cool moment.
It felt really good, you know. Uh...
For us, P9 is... is the absolute best
on a... on a really good day.
Nice one, good work.
Well done.
We beat everyone that we needed to beat.
- Fucking awesome.
- Where's your broken finger?
- Here, getting better, but...
- Yeah. Is it broken?
No. Hey, hey, hey!
It's not broken, but it's blue.
Let's go. Let's go.
My new job!
- All right, so, forward planning.
- Forward planning.
- What do you know?
- What do I know?
What do you know?
What can you tell me?
Where are the balls in the air?
- Circus.
- Circus, yeah. Clowns.
Circus. Formula 1.
So, anyway,
I will decide which driver goes this week.
You know, it will be quite emotional.
You know, in an ideal world,
my plan would be
that we make that official
the Portugal weekend.
You want my job?
Wouldn't take the pay cut.
Okay. Three, two, uh, one.
Formula 1 arrives in Portimao
for the 2020 Portuguese Grand Prix
and a driver market
has been kicked into overdrive.
Just this morning,
the Haas F1 team announced
that not one...
but both of their drivers
would be leaving the team
at the end of this season.
In a way, exciting as well,
but mostly weird.
Gonna miss the feeling
of Formula 1.
Hello.
Well, news.
Uh, when were you informed,
or was it a decision that was made
between you and the team?
Guenther called me a week ago or so,
um, to tell me that
they were, uh, gonna go for other drivers.
Maybe I'm ignorant,
but I... I felt pretty confident...
...that they'd keep me.
You know, Formula 1 can be a cold place,
uh...
a lot of the time.
Anyhoo...
Yeah, I mean, bottom line is
everyone knows you're gonna
drive the absolute nuts off of this car
until the end of the season.
- You won't take your foot off the gas.
- Absolutely.
But I will always, you know, look back
and... and be disappointed
that I didn't become a world champion.
You know, yes, I'm sad
about not being able to continue,
but I think it's overwhelmingly...
You know, I'm more grateful than sad
about things, you know.
- Thanks, Kevin.
- Thank you.
I'm not really done
with Formula 1,
but maybe Formula 1's done with me.
It's not good for me.
It was, you know,
um, collateral damage, if you want, but,
uh, you know, nothing I can say.
Uh, fair enough. I understand.
Uh, and, uh, we move on.
Uh, to make a decision
to let people go,
it's never a nice thing to do
and, for sure,
somebody's feelings get hurt.
But especially with Romain and Kevin,
they got to be friends.
It is not easy,
but all good things have, uh, an end.
I just have to say hello to him.
- Are you still saying hello to me?
- Huh?
- Still saying hello?
- Yeah.
I know that, yeah.
I'm just joking.
It seems to have been managed
pretty good, you know.
As we said, we are not damaging anybody.
That's the last thing I want to do.
You know that I mean that.
- Because otherwise...
- For sure.
- It's never nice, but hey.
- Yeah.
Life is not ein Wunschkonzert,
as we say in German.
You know? Fucking hell, yeah.
You've got rid
of your sort of two adopted sons.
Uh, so, what's next? Who's coming in?
You're persisting to try to find out
which direction we are going.
Venturing into
a Formula 1 weekend for the first time...
Mick Schumacher.
Next year, we'll have Mick Schumacher
and, uh, Nikita Mazepin as our drivers.
Nikita Mazepin
is one of the talented drivers
in Formula 2 this year
and, uh, his father, he has got
a very successful company as well,
which he may want to promote.
- Hi.
- Hello.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
I was pretty happy
that the rumor mill
was that Mick is going to Alfa
because that distracted
the real negotiations, you know?
It was announced that
Mick Schumacher's gonna be in the car.
Why did you pick Mick?
It's going to be tough for a rookie
next year, isn't it?
I'm sure there will be criticism.
"Two rookies cannot work."
It will be very difficult.
I know the challenge in front of us,
but because nobody has ever done it,
it doesn't mean that it's wrong.
No risk, no fun!
Sainz is going to Ferrari.
- How much are you gonna miss him?
- Uh...
How is this relationship
going to continue?
Okay, Carlos.
No fight with Lando. Let him go.
Fucking hell.
He just turned in on me.
What's he trying to do?
I'm pretty angry.
A very, very nasty crash.
Red flag.
Once you see fire,
that's the worst thing you can have.
You don't think anybody can get out alive
of this one.