I remember as a kid...
I could hear the echo through the city.
It's like this scream.
When they
get into a 200-mile-an-hour car...
...there's an almost
fighter pilot mentality.
Anything can happen.
I always think of my family.
All I do is pray for a safe race.
You need to respect the speed.
But the second a driver has fear,
you need to retire.
Formula One is the ultimate competition.
- Uncontrolled drama.
- Oh, there's a puncture!
- Oh!
Competitiveness,
high stakes, politics...
How can you call that a fair championship?
It is described
as a traveling circus.
We pack it all up,
and 24 hours later,
unpack it in a new part of the world.
We've all got
thousands of employees...
that all share the desire to win.
The drivers
are the best in the world.
We all believe we are the one.
Your teammate
is your worst enemy.
If he beats me every race,
my career's done.
The ultimate goal is to be the best.
If you had Lewis Hamilton's
same car, would you beat him?
Yes.
The highs are very high.
Whoo-hoo!
Thank you, thank you so much.
The lows are very low.
I'm fucking sick of this.
It's about making
the correct choices.
Every day I break out
in a cold sweat, thinking,
"Do I have the skill set to do it?"
The risk of death
will never go away.
Massive accident!
- I'm not worried about dying.
- Whoa.
I'm willing to do anything.
Let's see who's the best.
All right,
am I good to, like, sit?
Yeah.
-  All right. I'm good to go.
-  Okay.
Are you happy with your hair?
I don't know. I haven't seen it.
Prob-- If you've asked me,
then it must look shit.
No, no, no. I'm just...
Am I looking at you
or down the lens?
- At me, sorry.
-  Awesome.
Can I get you to tell me who you are
and what you do for a job?
I'm Daniel Ricciardo
and I'm a car mechanic.
All righty, I got this. I'm gonna nail it.
Three, two, one... I am Daniel Ricciardo.
I was born in Perth, Australia,
and I'm a Formula One driver.
Sounds pretty good when I say that.
I love that feeling of the car
on the edge at such a high speed.
I love the danger.
That adrenaline and that excitement.
More than anything,
I love the feeling of winning.
It's a beautiful thing.
And Ricciardo has got the inside line.
Lewis Hamilton's brave defense
of second place comes to an end.
And down the inside
goes Daniel Ricciardo!
Oh, my God.
That's how it's done, ladies.
Whoo hoo!
And Daniel Ricciardo wins
the Hungarian Grand Prix.
I don't think anyone's smile
could be bigger.
As a kid, I loved motorbikes.
I loved NASCAR.
Oh, shit!
But F1, that was
the fastest circuit cars in the world.
That's really why I got into Formula One.
I wanted to try and see if I could be
the best in the world.
Picturing myself on the top step
of an F1 podium,
I had visualized that feeling as a kid.
To be world champion would mean
the world to me.
Look at this geek here standing beside me.
For my family,
my dream involved sacrifices.
Great start
from Daniel Ricciardo...
My dad was building his own business,
but also taking me karting
on the weekends
and spending the money he'd made
to then put into me.
Don't forget his helmet.
There you go.
I remember as if it was yesterday.
Daniel said to me that he'd wanted
to give it a go in Europe.
Put it on Uncle Daniel.
And a lot of friends said,
"Oh, how could you let him go?"
But he was so determined.
That looks great.
How do you do it?
What am I doing wrong here?
Rip it off, man.
All the struggles,
all the bad days...
leaving home so young.
- Have the rest?
- Yeah.
Winning the world title,
it would make it all worth it.
Baa!
When I got into F1,
everyone knew me as the happy guy
and the nice guy,
but I do have a kind of killer instinct.
I do believe I can be world champion
and for me, it's like,
"Why else would I be doing this?"
And welcome along
for the opening round
of the Formula One World Championship
in 2018.
Welcome to the 23rd
Australian Grand Prix
held here in Albert Park for
the traditional first race of the season.
No Australian has been classified
in the top three of their home race.
Daniel Ricciardo,
ladies and gentlemen.
Is this the year?
First race of the season
is my home one.
Daniel!
I love having a home race.
But it's wild, you know?
Can I get a photo?
There's so much anticipation
being drawn to that first race in March.
Can we get a quick selfie, mate?
-Yeah, of course.
-Cheers, man.
And then, 'cause it's in Australia...
We're all cheering for you.
I'm the only Australian driver.
I get that two-fold.
- Aussie, Aussie, Aussie!
- Oy, oy, oy!
- Let's go, Dan!
- Yay!
How important is this season for you
as being a season in which
you can compete for the championship?
It's super important.
This will see where I am personally,
see where we are competitively...
Everybody recognizes
Daniel Ricciardo
as being one of the biggest talents
in Formula One.
But a lot of people think
it's this year or bust
for him to take his first world title.
I think it's gonna be
a really exciting year
because we've got three teams
that look capable of winning races.
Last season, Lewis Hamilton with Mercedes
and Sebastian Vettel at Ferrari
were the top two.
This season, we're really excited to see
if Daniel Ricciardo with Red Bull
can properly fight with those two drivers.
It's easy to say that a champion
from a previous year is the favorite.
But Red Bull are gonna be
very hard to beat.
- How does it look for you?
- It's looking exciting.
I think it should be close at the top
with Mercedes, uh, Ferrari, Red Bull.
In Formula One,
we've got 10 teams,
and each team is trying to develop
the best car possible.
The more money you spend,
the better your car is likely to be.
But there's a massive difference
in budgets in Formula One.
The smaller teams are quite often
operating on a budget
that's a fraction
of the size of the very biggest teams,
like Ferrari and Mercedes.
So, it's not a level playing field.
Guys, I mean, you know the position
we are in here, you know?
If I understood what Walter
told me last night,
there was one of everything.
I'm Guenther Steiner. I am the team
principal of Haas F1 team.
I love racing, it's my passion.
I started off from the bottom
as a mechanic.
I am doing it a long time,
more than 30 years.
Oh, yeah, and he should be.
Setting up a Formula One team
in the US was my idea,
and I persuaded Gene Haas to do this.
I think at turn one, he had no choice.
He had-- Everybody was going, whatever.
Gene has got
a very successful NASCAR team,
and he knows how racing works.
-Seventy-one.
-Did he hit somebody?
Yeah, Yeah. He, hit...
because he...
There's a lot of money
in Formula One.
Can you compete with the teams
with the big budgets? It's pretty hard.
You know, you're talking
five, six hundred million
to our 140 million.
But, you just gotta keep
trying and trying
and a lot of success in racing
comes down to just being stubborn.
Haas F1 is the first American
Formula One team in more than 30 years
and coming in as a new team in Formula One
is just so difficult.
I'm not convinced, but
I'm cautiously optimistic, as I call it.
In a small team,
we have less parts, less stuff.
We need to do more with less.
And how many people in your team,
all together?
Two hundred twelve.
Mercedes have more people
on holiday at any one time.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
We are the underdogs.
We are new in here.
But, for sure, we're not here just
to make the numbers up.
We are here to compete.
It's the first Friday practice.
Teams have 90 minutes to test their setups
around this three-mile circuit.
One of the most special things
about Formula One
is the way the weekend builds.
Friday is practice.
That's when the teams and drivers get out
on track to try and set their cars up
and make sure
it's performing the best it can.
Saturday, there's qualifying,
to set the order that the cars
will start the race in.
And then on Sunday,
we have the race itself.
Every session is dangerous.
Last season at Melbourne,
during practice, there were three crashes.
You all right?
Are you happy
with the strategy we are taking?
Yeah, fine.
The problem is that at some point,
one's gonna be right,
one's gonna be wrong.
-You never know.
-Yeah, yeah, exactly.
My name's Christian Horner.
I'm the team principal
of Aston Martin Red Bull racing.
So, uh, buck effectively stops with me.
Sebastian Vettel,
you are the world champion!
We're a subsidiary
of an energy drink
that's come along and won four
back-to-back world championships.
But that's in the past.
What do you reckon?
You know, we've spent five seasons now
where we should have been real contenders.
We need to win races this year.
We need to take the challenge
to the big teams.
You all right?
Get out there and enjoy it.
- I will, thank you.
- Yeah?
Let your driving do the talking.
You'll be fine.
Every team has two drivers.
We're fortunate to have Daniel Ricciardo.
He's at the top of his game.
Well, you can see the people who are...
And we've got this exciting,
emerging talent in Max Verstappen.
But you can just feel
that anticipation of,
"Have we designed a good car this year?
Is it gonna be successful?
Is it gonna be reliable?"
Okay, well let's see how we go.
I think it looks okay. I suggest we go
and have little up and down.
Okay.
Let's go, please.
As a racecar driver,
your feeling is so in tune,
that you know, after a few laps,
if the car is fast.
A lot of it, for me,
is confidence within the car
and just having a feeling
under the braking.
'Cause your coming up to a corner,
300 and something kilometers an hour.
Your instinct is like,
"Brake now, brake now, brake now,"
and you've gotta push yourself
to brake later and later
and trust that the car will stop.
He's got confidence in that car.
He is ripping the wheels off that.
Whoo!
What's your headline
for today then?
Red Bull , they could easily
find themselves in the front of the grid.
You're doing a good job.
Thanks, guys.
We had serious pace today.
The car was performing well.
And at the end of the day,
performance is everything.
I wanna win, because it's
what I believe I can do
and I've worked all these years to do it.
So, no one's gonna put more pressure
on me than myself.
So, who can set the fastest lap today
and start tomorrow's race
on pole position?
In qualifying, it's all designed
to set the order
for the start of the race.
Here's the time
that they've all got to beat.
Lewis Hamilton crosses the line.
It's a 1:21.1!
If you start in a good position,
you have a much better chance
of winning the race.
Qualifying is the moment that you see
these cars on the absolute limit.
And the driver pushing it to boundaries
that you don't even know quite
where the edge is.
- My God. That's, uh, Bottas!
- That's Valtteri Bottas!
That's Bottas wrecking his qualifying,
wrecking his car.
It's not gonna polish out, is it?
Guys, I just wanted to speak with you
a few minutes
before we need to go out on the track
and see what we can do. So...
From Gene's and my side, we are confident
that we can do better than last year.
I think on the pit stops, we have got
a few new people and it will be,
I wouldn't say difficult, but we need to
get used to new people in the pit-stops,
so, I think we can do it.
Thank you very much, guys.
How many minutes?
He said it should be really three minutes.
He's warming up the carbon fiber.
My name is Kevin Magnussen.
I am 26 years old
and I drive for Haas F1 team.
Qualifying is really intense.
There is a lot of pressure in Formula One
to deliver results and to perform well.
And that's the hardest thing about it.
We're on-board now
with Kevin Magnussen
underneath the bridge as we go,
and they touch!
And that could have been
very nasty indeed!
I don't have fear when I drive.
I don't ever think about
the consequences of crashing the car.
I'm not worried about dying.
I'll do anything I can
to get the best results possible.
Okay, watch
the traffic light and the white line.
- Did you copy?
- Okay.
To drive a lap fast
is all rhythm and feeling.
You feel just like one with the car,
as if it was your body.
For me it feels like flying.
It's almost like having superpowers.
Here comes Magnussen.
And he's absolutely
nailed sectors one and two.
What's his time going to be?
A 1:23.1,
and that's a sensational lap from Haas.
Well done, son.
He fucking did it. Jesus!
Whoa.
What a performance from Haas.
They'll be fifth and sixth
in tomorrow's race,
the highest they've ever started
in a Grand Prix.
Great job. I'm really proud of you.
Well done, guys.
Fucking hell. Well done.
Well done, man!
Happy.
In the mountains!
Thank you.
Hi, Gene. That wasn't bad, though.
Fuck. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, with the big boys, yeah?
Pretty cool, we start fifth.
Fifth and sixth.
When we started,
everybody told us we will fail.
But Gene supported me all the way
and has put a lot of faith in me
and failing in doing this
is not an option.
We need to succeed.
Twenty drivers, 21 races.
There can only be one world champion.
Welcome along to the Formula One
World Championship.
Dan!
I love race day.
That feeling of having
the fans, you know, right there.
- It's ringing.
- Ah...
Um... Hi, Chris, how're you going?
This is Daniel Ricciardo, Chris.
That's my dad, Dan!
Hometown kid,
so a lot of fans, a lot of support
and let's try and give them
something to cheer about.
-How are you?
-How are you, buddy?
-Good. You just got in? Awesome.
-Good.
-Yeah, thank you.
-Awesome. See you.
Wow. Wow.
I know.
This is how the grid will line up.
The reigning champion,
Lewis Hamilton, on pole.
Kimi Raikkonen in second,
out-qualifying his four-time
world champion teammate, Sebastian Vettel.
Max Verstappen starts fourth,
Kevin Magnussen is fifth,
giving Haas their best ever start.
Daniel Ricciardo is in eighth,
after receiving a penalty in practice.
So, he'll face a huge challenge
to get a podium today.
When the race starts,
it's a great moment.
To be actually in charge
of one of the teams out there,
that is what I dreamt for
when I was a kid.
The atmosphere is tense.
And you can feel
your body is ready to perform.
If someone says
they don't get nervous, they're lying.
The nerves for me is that anticipation
of what we're about to do.
Immediately before a race,
I block out all of the other distractions.
I'm very conscious that,
when I look into the driver’s eyes,
the risk that he's taking on.
You have a car going in excess
of 200 miles an hour,
racing wheel-to-wheel.
These guys have
an almost fighter pilot mentality.
And that's what separates them
from mere mortals.
I remember, when he was little,
going to Melbourne,
we had grandstand tickets
right opposite the pits.
All the drivers are there
and I'm thinking,
"That's somebody's child."
And I was thinking for these poor mothers.
And then I ended up being one of them.
I never, ever, ever thought that
I'd be there one day, watching my son.
Radio, check, check, check,
check, check, check, check, check, check.
Okay, so the latest info...
wind is stronger today.
So, you've got a head-wind into turn one.
Okay.
You've got hundreds of people on the grid.
And then you've got a 30-second warning.
Thirty seconds. Thirty seconds.
And then, all the mechanics go.
The grid is then empty
and it's just you and the other drivers.
Rushing into the first corner,
it's all instinctive.
Great start
from Kevin Magnussen.
He's managed to get past Max Verstappen.
Come on, Max, straighten.
We haven't got time for this.
Daniel Ricciardo down the inside.
He's made up a place.
Emotionally,
we're sort of always up and down.
All I ever do is pray for a safe race.
And then everything else is a bonus.
It's the biggest thing
that we're always worried about.
Number one thing,
don't even like talking about it now.
You know, it makes me nervous.
It's hugely intense.
You're looking an awful lot at numbers,
at split times,
at the sawtooth graphs.
Ricciardo's on a charge,
on the outside of Nico Hulkenberg.
Nice job, mate.
Hulkenberg fights back.
He's got the inside line
but Ricciardo sweeps on by.
It's mentally draining
if you're dealing with two cars,
two different outcomes.
These tires
are getting really hot.
Max, recommend saving your overtake
for the one place you feel
Magnussen is most vulnerable.
And he's gone off!
No! Fuck, no!
Verstappen just spun.
Grosjean goes past,
Ricciardo goes past.
Oh, for fucks sake, man!
All okay, Max?
Yeah.
This is dreamland for Haas.
So, there's
now only Mercedes and Ferraris
in front of the young American Haas team.
This is racing.
It's realizing it's a big opportunity
to ram home what you're doing.
We've got a massive lock up.
That's Magnussen.
Tires are starting to go, guys.
It's starting to understeer
more and more now
Okay. Box, Kevin.
Box, please confirm.
Box, box, box.
In the pit stops,
that is the only time
that you really get
in touch with the team.
You're on your own on the track.
Everything is depending on you.
When you pit, that changes completely.
That's when you realize
how much of a team effort it is.
Kevin Magnussen has pitted.
-I don't think that's tight.
-Which one? Which one?
Left rear. I don't do any other one.
Are you sure it's not tight?
Failure, guys.
And who's that going slowly?
It's Kevin Magnussen!
Kevin Magnussen in the Haas,
he's just come out of the pit lane
and now he's grinding to a halt.
Stop the car. Stop the car.
Stop the car. Stop the car. Stop the car.
Magnussen was on
for a sensational result,
but now he's retiring.
It's heartbreaking.
You don't want it to be true.
And by the looks of things,
one of those wheels
isn't attached properly.
You just cope with it.
They've got two drivers.
You just try to stay as calm
as possible and focus on the race.
Box now, Romain. Box now.
Romain Grosjean has now pitted
and makes his way back onto the circuit.
So Ricciardo now has clear air.
That's good news for the Red Bull team.
As Grosjean--
Is that Grosjean going slowly? It is!
Stop the car. Stop the car.
We have a front left loose.
Romain Grosjean pulling over
in the other Haas.
So both Haases,
as soon as they leave the pit lane,
have ground to a halt.
Unbelievable.
What could have been
one of their best weekends on a race track
has turned into absolute disaster.
When you see it happen on the screen,
you think, "This cannot happen.
This is not real."
We lost it all in two laps.
In Formula One,
the highs are very high,
the lows are very low.
It's easy in my position
to blame somebody,
but then in the end,
the buck stops with me.
You've got a horde of media out here.
Are you happy to speak to people?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
They need to hear. That's fine. Yeah.
It's a sad afternoon.
We've seen all your people.
They're heartbroken,
as well as the drivers.
How is it to be a boss
in a moment like that?
I mean, in the end
as a boss, you need to lead.
I am sure my disappointment
is as big as theirs.
We need first to see what went wrong
before we can fix it.
I just need a bit of a break
Otherwise, you'll say
something afterwards?
- I don't know.
- Okay, thanks.
We were
in fourth and fifth position.
-Just help me with those guys
-Yeah. Yeah.
And that would've been, by far,
the best result for the team
in its history.
I don't know, Gene. I don't have to answer
to that one. We just fucked this one up.
Doesn't make it right.
I know that, you know.
Saying I fucked it up,
it doesn't make it right. It's like...
Same mistake. It's unbelievable.
The two guys putting the wheel on,
they were new.
Fuck! Fourth and fifth, but, Gene,
if we finish fourth and fifth here,
we fucking look like rock stars, huh?
And now we're a fucking bunch of wankers.
Yeah, a bunch of fucking clowns here.
I will do a proper investigation, Gene.
Don't worry, you know that.
I will fix it, trust me.
The wheel just wasn't done enough, huh?
It felt tight, but as it dropped
it visually looked as though
it was loose.
Not done up properly, sir.
You, did you think we train not enough?
Or...
We haven't practiced
this weekend at all. Um...
Tiredness as well...
I don't think that will help.
Just on the back foot this weekend.
But the wheels were
not completely on, you know?
I'm devastated and I am truly sorry, sir.
Raikkonen running
in third position.
Fourth for Daniel Ricciardo.
He's fought his way back
from eighth place.
If he can get on the podium today,
it would mean so, so much
for Daniel Ricciardo.
Hey, that is blistering pace.
I don't wanna let him breathe.
Doing the right thing.
Just keep the pressure on.
Understood.
No Australian has been classified
in the top three of their home race.
He will be doing his damnedest
on this final lap.
You might as well
use the battery.
Understood.
Sebastian Vettel
wins the Grand Prix.
Whoo!
Hamilton second.
Third across the line...
it's just Kimi Raikkonen,
with Daniel Ricciardo in fourth.
Oh!
Half a second, isn't it?
Right on, mate.
Fuck.
That was a very good job today, mate.
You did get the quickest lap of the race.
Yeah, I tried.
We had serious pace today.
We had a real chance at the podium,
and I'd wanted it so bad.
I really believe that I should be
winning more frequently.
I believe I've got the talent
and I put in the work.
So, it's not anger,
but it's frustration that comes through.
And the winner, from Germany,
Sebastian Vettel.
Thanks, Pop.
I'm happy, but I'm pissed.
Probably like you.
Yeah.
Happy, but fuck.
I nearly threw something at the TV.
Yeah. Food delivery.
Anyway, I tried.
Yeah, I know you did.
I know you did.
No, yeah! It was good.
Good result.
You got the crowd excited.
-Yeah, I tried.
-They were cheering you on.
I tried.
I mean, the pace, when you dropped back
and you banked in at 25.
Even I didn't think we were that quick...
It's a long season.
You know,
these cars develop so quickly.
You'll know where you'll be starting,
but you don't know
where you will be finishing.
Things change.
I'd love to be
winning tomorrow, if I could.
That's my ultimate dream.
I'm pretty far from that at the moment.
I know that things like that
don't happen overnight.
I'm in a great team that I can grow
and prepare myself,
and hopefully one day
I can get a chance
to fight for a championship.
We should have done better.
Everybody in Haas wants to do better,
but so does everybody else.
Why you watch Formula One?
You want to see action.
You want to see drama.
You want to see
the underdog making a good result.
A story. Each race should have a story,
and the story should not be
all the time Mercedes or Ferrari wins,
because that story
gets old pretty quickly.
My teammate, Max,
is becoming more of a threat.
He's one of the most exciting talents
in Formula One.
I need to be
the faster driver of the two.
There's no more brutal lesson
than what he's just had.
Fernando Alonso
is my racing hero.
Okay, Carlos. Alonso behind you.
The stakes
have never been higher for McLaren.
I said, "This guy is not beating me.
No fucking way."