[Gasly] Trying to be a good loser.
[panting]
It's all about mental strength.
Pierre... his year got off
to a horrible start.
You could just see this driver
in front of you wilting.
[Gasly grunts]
[Christian Horner] Can't keep making
excuses for him.
It's not good for us as a team.
We're just running one leg in...
If you can't deal with that pressure,
is it time to change?
[Gasly] There is unfinished business
with Red Bull.
[interviewer] I mean,
how do you feel about it?
About the change?
[interviewer] Yeah.
Well, for sure, for me
at the beginning I was surprised
'cause, uh, it's not what they told me.
We're in a unique position in Formula 1
where we have four cockpits.
We've got four cockpits,
we can move the drivers around.
They're all Red Bull drivers.
Toro Rosso drivers are
Red Bull contracted drivers.
[Gasly] The change, the swap,
coming back in Toro Rosso,
I was disappointed, 'cause for me,
I didn't feel like that was really fair.
You are just, like...
You're angry.
[photographer] Action!
[Franz Tost] Was not so confident
with the Red Bull car.
And, uh, that stand to reason
why he struggled.
Then the confidence goes down,
uh, you feel, as a driver, that the team
doesn't believe, anymore, so much in you.
- [in Italian] Good morning.
- Good morning.
[Tost in English] Therefore, it was good
that he came back to us.
Morning!
- Morning.
[Tost] How is everything?
[man] Very well, thank you, yourself?
[photographer] Action.
[Gasly] My goal as a Red Bull driver
will always be
to be in the top team
in that Red Bull car.
You know, you feel the need,
"I need to get there, I need to do it."
Uh, we'll do what it needs
to get back there.
It felt, "Okay, what have we got to lose
by switching these two drivers
to evaluate them to the end of the year?"
[tools drilling]
[David Croft] Here comes Alex Albon now,
round the outside.
[Martin Brundle] That's bold if he's gonna
go past Ricciardo there.
[Croft] What a move!
The rookie, Alex Albon,
passes the McLaren!
[cheering]
[Horner] Alex is exceeding
all our expectations.
You know, we're seeing him
fighting for a podium.
This has been a monumental step for him.
You have to remember, this is
his first year in Formula 1 racing.
[Sofie Albon] You need, like, pajamas.
- [Minki Medina] Yeah.
- [Sofie] You need, like, shampoo.
- I've taken them already.
- And conditioner.
- Bodywash.
- I did. Done that.
Did you get me a shirt?
- [Sofie] Deodorant.
- [Minki] Put some more clothes.
[Alexander Albon] Being an Aston Martin
Red Bull Racing driver,
it's a crazy thing to think about.
Actually, when I think about it now,
it still doesn't feel believable.
Bye.
[Albon] Everything's happening so fast.
I'm, like, not living
with my parents anymore.
Beautiful.
[chuckles] I've got no one to do
my laundry, which I'm very sad about.
Plus, I'm moving to Monaco, so...
I'm going full F1 driver spec,
living the life.
This is my place.
Obviously got an amazing view.
This is where
I'm gonna have my single life.
[Minki] But now, we have to unpack.
It's a big, you know, like a big step,
moving away from home.
[Albon] I realize that I have been
fast-tracked into a big team.
I've done well, but there's
nothing really to say that...
I fully deserve the seat.
You know it could always be
your last opportunity.
This is your chance to show yourself.
They want to see that sign that,
you know, they want you for next year,
and that's what I'm working towards.
I've got to show that I belong here.
[man 1 speaking Portuguese]
Welcome to Brazil.
This is Interlagos.
The circuit is between the lakes.
[man 2 speaking Portuguese]
[reporter 1] Alex,
a very happy week for you
because you have been confirmed
as a Red Bull Racing driver for 2020.
Congratulations.
[Albon] Thank you very much.
So, I've just been announced
that I'm a Red Bull driver for 2020.
Yeah. Very cool.
How do you find out
that you've got the Red Bull seat?
Does it come in an email,
in a phone call?
An email.
- A Post-it Note.
- [laughs]
- On your desk?
- [laughs] Yeah.
I'm... I'm happy. I'm very happy.
[reporter 2] Alex, what did you think
that you did better than Pierre Gasly
to have his seat?
[chuckles] You ask
a very tough question. Um...
Now I've been announced,
it feels really good.
It feels really, really good.
- We are running late.
- [Albon] Why?
- Because you're a chatterbox. That's why.
- [Albon] Let's...
Speaking for England today.
Always, mate, always.
And talking for Thailand.
Hello. Sorry we're late.
- Hi, Alex!
- Hey. How are you?
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
[Gasly] This is so frustrating.
The fact that it's a dream
and the beginning...
And you work so hard every day,
and people helping you,
your family, making big sacrifices
to give you the chance,
one day, maybe, to live your dream.
When you go through these challenges,
you take, like, big hits.
Uh, need to get back up
and just prove my point.
I'm the kind of guy that if I get knocked,
I just go back at it
and try to knock even harder.
[machine whirring]
Everything okay?
All good.
[Tost] Every driver in Formula 1
has something to prove,
especially after the first half
of the season
when he was struggling at Red Bull Racing.
He has to prove that this was a period
where he learned a lot.
Such emotional periods
are so, so important in any kind of sport.
[man 1] Carlos!
[man 2] Carlos! Carlos!
[Zak Brown] This year, Carlos has been
very competitive.
We've all been impressed.
We knew he was very fast,
and I think he's proven that.
[talking indistinctly]
[groans]
[scatting]
I've done a good job
the whole season, really.
I was performing at a high level.
- [Tom Stallard] All right, P5!
- [Sainz] Ay-ay-ay!
Whoo! It's really good.
[Tom Stallard] Flawless.
Great work, Carlos.
[Croft] Carlos Sainz finishes
in fifth place in the McLaren!
[all cheering]
[Croft] And that equals
his best-ever finish...
[man] What's this?
A double shot.
It's probably been
my strongest year in F1.
So it makes me feel proud
and happy about this season.
Morning, Zak.
[Brown] Mornin', how are you?
[Sainz] Good, you?
[Brown] Other than my back's wrenched...
[Sainz] Your back?
Yeah, everyone's been telling me
to work out and lose weight.
I'm working out to lose weight,
I hurt my back.
I'm gonna be as fit as you soon.
- Maybe not.
- Mmm...
[Brown laughs]
This time last year,
we were one of the slowest cars,
and at some events, the slowest car.
This year, it's been
a very successful season,
but still a long way to go
as we look to get back to the front.
[Will Buxton] McLaren,
there's every chance
that if they continue this trend,
they could be competing
with the likes of Red Bull,
possibly Ferrari and Mercedes for podiums.
It's great to see.
They're one of the great teams
of Formula 1 history
with a spring in their step.
[Sainz] For me, I want to prove to McLaren
that they have chosen the right guy.
[commentator 1] Welcome to the penultimate
Grand Prix of 2019. We're in Brazil.
[Horner] To drive for Red Bull,
the expectations on him,
it's high pressure.
[commentator 2]
It's now down to Alex Albon
to deliver week-in, week-out.
[Albon] Being with the top team,
there is that realization
that you are in a winning car.
There's always going to be that sense that
you want to be delivering good results.
The guys have put their faith in me.
Yeah, just get ready.
[Pierre Hamelin] And radio check, Alex.
[Albon] Yep, radio check.
[Mattia Spini] Okay, Pierre,
need to be more strict from the start.
[Gasly] Yeah.
[Croft] Carlos Sainz starts in the back
of the grid after trouble in qualifying.
McLaren's five-year wait for a podium
looks set to continue.
[engines revving]
[Croft] And we're racing in Brazil!
Alex Albon and Pierre Gasly,
wheel-to-wheel!
And Albon gets past him.
[Gasly] Fuckin' hell!
[Hamelin] That was good positioning.
Good job, Alex.
[Croft] Sainz's running last
after the problems in qualifying.
[Sainz] How's my pace?
[Stallard] Pace looks good, Carlos.
[in Spanish] Come on!
Come on!
[Stallard in English] Yes, Carlos.
Great start, mate, great start.
[Hamelin] Doing great, Alex, we are P4.
[Brundle] Alex Albon all over the back
of Sebastian Vettel!
[Hamelin] He's overtaking them.
[Croft] Albon is going right
at Sebastian Vettel!
[Brundle] He's done it!
[all cheering]
[Croft] The youngster
in his rookie season,
never been on the podium before,
finds himself in third place
at the moment!
[Stallard] That's your target, Carlos,
we need to beat him.
[Sainz] Copy.
[Brundle] Carlos Sainz is up to tenth
from the back of the grid.
Really excellent performance.
[Riccardo Musconi]
Let's take care of the car.
Cool the car a bit.
[Croft] There's smoke
coming out of the back
of Valtteri Bottas' Mercedes engine.
[Valtteri Bottas] Lost the power.
[Croft] Valtteri Bottas,
engine overheating.
And it's going to be a terminal problem.
[Sainz] The Haas,
driving super erratically.
[Stallard] Copy.
[Croft] They make contact!
Sainz now up into sixth and on the tail
of Ricciardo for fifth.
Nice move from Pierre Gasly.
[Spini] You're doing a good job, Pierre.
Keep going.
[man speaks indistinctly]
[Croft] Once again, Ferrari on Ferrari,
battling each other!
[Brundle] And Leclerc goes for it,
very late!
Vettel, trying to get back past.
[Leclerc] What the hell?
[Brundle] And this is
totally self-inflicted by Ferrari.
It's both of them! Both cars out!
[Sebastian Vettel in German]
My God, must this happen?
[Vettel in English]
What the hell is he doing?
Try to come in slowly. Slowly.
[Vettel] That's it. I'll drive.
[Brundle] That's definitely not gonna
improve relationships down at Ferrari.
[Mattia Binotto]
Something happening like that,
it's hard for the entire team.
I think we are all very sad
because that's the type of weekend
you would like to forget.
[Croft] The safety car's been deployed
as there's debris on track.
[Hamelin] Both Ferraris are out.
[Albon] Yes.
[Hamelin] Keep going, Alex,
you're doing a great job.
[Croft] It's the two Red Bulls leading,
Max Verstappen, then Alex Albon.
This could be Albon's
first-ever podium finish.
[Hamelin] Keep going, Alex.
Car behind is Gasly.
[Spini] Okay, Pierre, currently P3.
Hamilton behind us.
[Lewis Hamilton] There's a car
ahead of me that's racing.
[Peter Bonnington] That's Gasly.
[Croft] Carlos Sainz is in fifth place,
behind Lewis Hamilton.
- [Hamilton] Safety car in.
- [Bonnington] Okay. Copy this.
[Hamilton] You can't overtake,
so keep it to lane, right?
[Brundle] So, restarts.
Three laps here of absolute pandemonium!
The green flags are there.
It's Verstappen out in front
and pulling away!
[Croft] Hamilton is trying
to get past Gasly!
He's got him!
Albon locks up.
He's the next target for Hamilton!
[Hamelin] Alex, hold Hamilton up.
Keep your position.
[Albon] Fuck!
[all exclaim]
[Croft] Albon's been hit!
The chance of his first podium, gone!
[crew member grunts] Fuck!
[Albon] Oh, no! No! No! No! [groans]
[Hamilton] Hey, guys. Sorry about that.
[Bonnington] Continue. Continue.
[Croft] I reckon the stewards are gonna be
taking a look at that incident.
Hamilton may take a penalty for that.
[Brundle] Max Verstappen comes into the
final corner of the Brazilian Grand Prix.
The checkered flag is out!
[Max Verstappen] Yes! Come on!
[Croft] The Brazilian Grand Prix
goes to Max Verstappen!
[all cheering]
[Croft] Gasly is currently second.
Lewis Hamilton runs third.
[Spini] We have Hamilton behind.
We know the target now.
Keep pushing.
[Hamilton] It's very hard
to keep up with him, man.
[Spini] Keep pushing. Keep pushing.
[Hamilton] Can't close this gap.
[Croft] Gasly comes home
to take second place!
[Gasly] Yeah!
[whooping]
[all cheering]
[Gasly speaking indistinctly]
[Croft] And that is his first podium
in Formula 1.
- [Spini] Unbelievable!
- [Gasly laughs] Incredible!
[Croft] Hamilton comes home third!
Carlos Sainz equals his best performance
in a race by finishing fourth!
- [Stallard] Yes!
- [Sainz exclaims]
[Stallard] Great job, mate! P4.
Who thought it? P4.
[speaking Spanish]
I can't believe it, man! Wow!
[chuckles] Can't believe it, guys.
[Stallard] Unbelievable drive. P20 to P4.
[Sainz] I cannot believe it. What a drive.
Thank you, guys.
Amazing. Amazing.
Yeah! Yeah!
[crowd cheering]
[all yelling indistinctly]
[Gasly] Thank God.
This is the best day of my life.
Guys, thank you!
Thank you so much!
[crew member] Amazing!
[Gasly] You're amazing!
You guys are amazing!
`[cheering intensifies]
It's, uh, the best moment in my life,
'cause it's something you dream
when you're a kid and...
you imagine being in Formula 1,
you imagine being on a Formula...
Like, a podium in Formula 1.
These kind of moments,
that's why you love the sport.
He had a tough start to the season
with Red bull and Toro Rosso.
I think he found himself again
and he was straight away quick.
He was feeling confident to come away
with the second place.
That was, of course, yeah, amazing.
[crowd chanting] Gasly! Gasly!
Gasly! Gasly! Gasly!
[Gasly] Like, just...
so many things happened this year.
It's been, like, such a roller coaster.
[commentator]
Oh, that's a horrible accident!
[Gasly] You know, like, all the stuff
that happened within ten months,
probably one of the saddest moments
in my life, when Anthoine passed away.
First thing... I passed the line
and I thought about Anthoine
because, of course,
you think about these things.
Losing a friend,
that's also what makes you as a...
makes you as a person.
All these experiences
you go through, and...
it is important for me to show
my strength, and mental strength,
that I can go through this
and get the job done.
[all cheering]
[laughs]
[Gasly] I'm super excited about next year.
I want a podium
every weekend, but... [laughs]
[all shout]
[Horner] My mate! Mate, mate, mate!
Don't be too hard on yourself.
[man over speaker]
And the Toro Rosso as well,
to see, you know...
[Croft] We're just hearing that
Lewis Hamilton could be getting a penalty
for his shunt with Alex Albon.
Um, I massively apologize, Albon.
I went for a move, and...
completely my fault.
[Croft] Which means, potentially,
Carlos Sainz could be
promoted into third place.
[Caco] You fought from P20, mate.
- [Sainz] Yeah.
- [Caco] Fucking P20.
- [man] That's enormous.
- [Sainz] I need to know.
I'm, like, in the most awkward moment
of my career.
[man] Of course.
Like, I really, seriously don't have
a clue how to act right now.
Like... just wait.
We're waiting for the final justification
to come out from the FIA,
which will confirm P3.
But we don't know.
[in Spanish] And we are here waiting
to find out if Carlos is getting
his first podium.
[exhales]
- [man in English] I think we should.
- We'll do a team photo, for sure.
- Why?
- We shouldn't go on the podium.
[Caco] Are you telling me
we're not going on the podium?
Why?
Because I just don't want us
to look really desperate.
It's not desperate.
It's a legitimate podium.
First podium of his career
and he's going to look desperate?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Since the day he was born he's been
waiting for this fucking moment.
Are you fucking kidding me, "desperate"?
What the hell? What is wrong with her?
What is wrong with her?
There'll be celebrations
if this happens, won't there?
- Is it confirmed?
- [crew member] Yeah, it's confirmed.
[all cheering]
[Caco] Yes!
[Buxton] Hamilton fighting with Alex Albon
for the podium places,
and ultimately, after the race,
was given a penalty.
So, Carlos Sainz
inherited that third place.
His debut Formula 1 podium.
[all cheering]
After the race, as the lights were going
down and the circuit was being packed up,
he went to the podium.
I think the most unique podium celebration
that anyone's ever had
for their first Formula 1 podium,
because he didn't get to share it
with the two other drivers.
Got to share it with his entire team.
Yeah!
[shouting indistinctly]
They deserve the podium, so...
almost doesn't matter how you get it.
Just the fact that you got
a trophy to bring home
to all the men and women at McLaren
that have been through a lot,
and are working so hard for the team.
It was great to bring home
a trophy for 'em.
Mission accomplished.
- [crew member 1] Three, two, one!
- [crew member 2] Carlos!
[all cheer]
[interviewer] How do you feel
about the season?
Terrible. I wanna quit.
I'm kidding. Please don't play that.
[crowd cheering]
This is Daniel.
It's not. Who would... That's childish.
Are you on Netflix this year?
I don't know. I think they ignored me
for the whole year, so...
- they can fuck off.
- [both laugh]
[Croft] It's the last race of the season
and time for the annual photo call.
[photographer] Okay, guys.
Everybody looking to this camera, please.
Of course I'm kind of sad
to leave the team,
but I'm grateful for the time that we had.
Really enjoyed my ride with them
for the three years we had together.
I'll always look back
and remember those times.
Keep them in good memories.
All right, guys.
I think everybody knows where we are.
We are not where
we wanted to be this year.
I want to take this time
to actually thank you
and tell you, next year will be...
It must be better.
My confidence in the team is still high.
And hopefully just forget about 2019.
It never happened.
[Kevin Magnussen] It's tough to have
a whole year, like, almost written off,
but I think it will...
It'll kind of benefit us in the future,
all the things we've learned this year.
I think we have not to focus
on being the fastest,
but learning as much as possible.
- And then the fast comes on its own.
- [Romain Grosjean] Look at Mercedes.
- What they did was very impressive.
- Yeah.
They were very slow.
Then they got better,
then they got to Melbourne
and they put everything together.
Yeah. Exactly, yeah.
Yeah, but they're five times
world champions. We're not.
- [Romain Grosjean] Six.
- Six, sorry.
[laughs]
[Croft] The magic number is six!
It's Lewis Hamilton!
Champion of the world!
[Bonnington] Get in there, Lewis.
[Hamilton] I can't believe it!
I really can't believe it!
[Bonnington] You did that in style.
[Croft] They are six-time
double world champions.
After taking this photo,
'cause we're on a pretty tight schedule...
When the confetti cannon
goes off, when that photo's done,
we'll then need to leg it back in here.
- 'Cause we're gonna have lunch in here.
- Yeah.
Otherwise, we'll end up mobbed
for half an hour, which, um...
There's a lot of people out there.
There's a lot of people,
so we're last in and we're first out.
We're coming back this way...
for some nosh.
[Hamilton] Should we not
make our way over?
I wanna go and take pictures of everyone.
[man 1] Here we go.
That's the... Yeah.
[woman] Shit!
[man 2] So, no going through the door.
[Hamilton] Damn,
this door is so... [laughs]
[man 1] World champion trapped in door.
[Hamilton] Dangerous doors.
[man 1] Health and Safety executive
would have a field day with that,
wouldn't they?
They'd want to interview you
a hundred times.
Well, I think you got
good insurance, though.
- So I guess I'd just claim.
- [laughing]
[groans] My... My back! My neck!
[man 1] My back! Yeah.
Millions!
Got a new engine stand this year as well.
- Congratulations.
- [Hamilton] Thank you.
- Congratulations. Very well done.
- And to you.
- Thanks a lot.
[Hamilton] No, thank you.
This is so awesome to see all this.
As a kid, I always knew that I'd do
something great, something extraordinary.
But this has been the hardest year.
The team effort is just... it's humongous.
[crowd cheering]
[man 3 over megaphone]
Come on, give him a wave, guys!
[Hamilton] I just feel really grateful
for the opportunity
to be able to work with great people
and win these world titles.
But I look at it and I'm really
just a chink in the chain
of a massive chain
of over a thousand people.
And I'm really kind of
the catalyst at the end.
So, I just feel really grateful
in that respect.
[man 3 speaking indistinctly
over megaphone]
Cheers to the camera!
One, two, three, four, five...
- Six!
- [all cheer]
[crowd applauding]
2020 is set to become one of
the biggest years in Formula 1's history.
Obviously, it's not a very level
playing field at the moment.
The sport has got out of control.
I want to be competitive once in a while.
New set of financial regulations.
So that the big teams
don't have such a big advantage.
Bringing the big spenders
a little bit closer to us.
We need to be ready for that.
[scoffs] Yeah.
They will, I believe,
make a huge difference.
You also have a pretty unique
scenario in 2020.
The majority of the drivers will be
out of contract at the end of the season.
We always wanna be better.
I don't feel too stressed about it.
[groans]
If you ask what it means to win
with Ferrari, I don't know. Because, um...
But I wanna find out.
The political permutations,
the back-door dealings...
You gotta make the most
of your opportunities when you can.
Arm wrestling that goes on
behind the scenes.
The peacock strutting.
It's about, "Push myself against
the best, I wanna be the best."
You're always under pressure.
Diamonds are made under pressure.
I want to be in the fastest car.
Hi!
Make sure that we are that dominant car.
Push Lewis Hamilton all the fucking way.
That's the hardest thing to do.
- It's not going to be easy.
- No.
It's more like a hobby for me.
So, obviously, I don't need
to do it if I don't want.
What are we doing this for?
[laughs]
Next year's gonna be a fun year.
Now we have a new chapter.
We're ready to take it on.