[speaks German]
Good morning.
Oh! My hand! Fuck me.
[country music playing]
Some country. Let's listen to some...
Let's listen to some country music, y'all.
What do you listen to?
- Rock.
- Yeah?
Like?
'70s and '80s. I love the '80s.
But you are more into
your "Señorita" stuff.
[chuckles]
I'm born in '97.
[Marc] When you sign for Ferrari...
it's the pinnacle, you know?
[all cheering]
I'm Sebastian Vettel...
driving for Scuderia Ferrari.
[Mattia] Ferrari's a legendary brand.
Ferrari have always been
part of the motor racing.
[commentator 1] In the field...
Alberto Ascari in a Ferrari...
[clapping]
[Marc] Ferrari is a team who has won
more races and more world championships
than any other team.
Drivers become legends
when they win with Ferrari.
[commentator 2] Michael Schumacher,
the seven-times Formula 1 world champion.
[all cheering]
Michael was my hero in my childhood.
[indistinct chatter]
Michael winning for Ferrari...
[whistling]
[Sebastian] ...being a German driver,
coming to see us as kids
on the go-kart track...
getting to know him.
He was always winning in the red car.
That's what I want to achieve.
That's why I'm here.
[Will] Sebastian won
four world championships with Red Bull.
But Sebastian's move to Ferrari
coincided with the rise of Mercedes.
[Martin] It's high-fives
from Lewis Hamilton,
a five-time champion of the world!
[Will] Sebastian still doesn't have
a world championship with Ferrari.
[Sebastian] Still trying
to get to the top.
That's what drives me.
We're still fighting,
and we're still believing.
[commentator 1] Welcome along
to Austin, Texas,
ahead of the United States Grand Prix.
Around this 3.4-mile circuit...
[indistinct chatter]
[Sebastian] I'm certainly very proud
to be driving the red car,
but so, I think,
is everyone else in the garage.
[indistinct chatter]
The passion that the people have for
the brand is what keeps the myth alive.
[commentator 2] Just three more
races to go,
and the title could be decided
this weekend
if Lewis Hamilton scores
a total of four points
in Sunday's 56-lap race.
[Will] 2019 was the chance
for Sebastian to draw level with Lewis
on five world championships.
It has not quite worked out
as well as he'd hoped.
And it's not just Mercedes
that Sebastian now has to fight with.
[engine revving]
Sebastian now has his work cut out
within his own team.
[in Italian] I woke up
at 5:50 this morning.
- What time did you sleep?
- Ten o'clock.
[commentator 3 in English]
The big news this week,
Charles Leclerc will be joining
Ferrari next season.
The second-youngest Ferrari driver
in history.
[engine revving]
I'm Charles Leclerc, and I'm driving
for Scuderia Ferrari in Formula 1.
[in Italian] Good morning.
I've arrived a bit early.
[in English] Growing up, there was only
one team that was counting for me.
It was Ferrari.
Every time I come to a Grand Prix,
it feels extremely special.
It's all I've dreamt for, really.
- [in French] How are you?
- Good, and you?
- Sleep well?
- Very well.
I woke up very early, but slept well.
Ready for today.
[in English] Ferrari has always
been a legend,
and we need to make sure
that the legend is surviving.
Our intentions as a team
is try to set a winning side.
[Will] It's very unusual for Ferrari
to choose a young driver.
But after a decade
with no championship success,
perhaps trying something a little bit
different is gonna reap its rewards.
[Mattia] I think it's good as a lineup
to have an experienced and a fast rookie.
I think that has been a great benchmark
for Seb as well.
[indistinct chatter]
Here you are.
Sorry.
[soft rock song playing]
[humming and singing along]
What's that? Are you...
What are you singing? You go quite high.
[Charles whistles]
Offspring. This was
when I was your age or younger.
[scats]
Punk rock... no?
[Charles] Uh...
I'm trying to listen, but...
[Sebastian] Certainly,
we are at different stages in our career.
He's very young.
I'm probably not very young,
but also not very old,
but considered older or more experienced.
[Charles] I'm very bad
with the '90s music.
I knew better the '80s earlier
than the '90s now.
[Sebastian] We fight each other very hard
on the track, but off the track,
I think I'd be disappointed
if there would be the wrong sort
of energy going around.
[engine accelerating]
[chuckles]
He loves it. Every morning he's asking,
"Rev it up for me, man! Rev it up."
["Come Out and Play" playing]
- [Charles] Beautiful parking, Seb.
- Yeah, unbelievable.
[indistinct shouting]
[crowd cheering]
The fans of Ferrari are just crazy,
so passionate.
[crowd cheering]
[Charles] It's something
that you don't see anywhere else.
So much passion for one team.
[cheering]
[presenter] And big hand for
Sebastian Vettel and Charles Leclerc!
[cheering]
Charles, you are getting
the biggest following around the world.
There is quite a big difference
from last year to this year on my side,
but that's how it is
when you drive for Ferrari.
We've got the best fans in the world,
and it's great to be driving
for this team. A dream come true.
And we will give our best as we can.
Ladies and gentlemen, Charles Leclerc!
[crowd cheering]
[Will] The Ferrari drivers have been
on something of a journey in 2019.
There has been friction,
there has been difficulty.
[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct shouting]
[Charles] When I signed for Ferrari,
Mattia made it quite clear
that Seb was the number one,
and I was the number two,
and on that I completely understand.
[indistinct chatter]
Despite that,
Charles has been quick from the outset.
[Martin] Dearly beloved,
we are gathered here today
for the Italian Grand Prix
at the Temple of Speed.
Pole sitter, Charles Leclerc.
Hamilton and Bottas
now jockeying for position.
Leclerc goes into the first chicane ahead
by a matter of inches.
[Charles] In Italy,
Monza was absolutely crazy.
The whole country was behind us.
Probably one of the first times
in my career I felt so much pressure,
and I only had one thing in my head,
was to win.
[Martin] We haven't seen a Ferrari victory
in Monza since 2010.
[Mattia] Monza is a very special
Grand Prix in front of our fans.
[all cheering]
So, you've got the pressure
on the shoulders,
and there is only one objective.
[commentator 1] Leclerc and Vettel
are under pressure to pull off
something special
in front of the Ferrari fans.
[engineer] Charles, lap at 24.9.
[Sebastian] Copy that.
[Martin] That's Sebastian Vettel!
And he's spun!
[car screeches]
[Martin] He's coming onto the track
just as Lance Stroll goes past him!
[Lance] He just came back on the circuit
like an idiot.
[Sebastian] I think I have damage.
The front left.
[Martin] And there's anxious faces now.
Sebastian Vettel's Italian Grand Prix
has gone from average to bad, to horrible.
[commentator 2] Sebastian Vettel has
kind of opened the door for Mercedes now
to gang up on Charles Leclerc.
[Martin] He's going
for it again, Lewis Hamilton!
Got a great exit out of the chicane.
Round the curve they go!
Leclerc is on the inside!
Hamilton goes onto the gravel!
And you can hear the cheers from Monza!
[all cheering]
The Ferrari fans loved it!
Mercedes threw everything at him today.
Charles Leclerc has coped brilliantly!
He won in Spa! He wins in Monza!
[Charles shouting] Yes! Yes! Yes!
[all cheering]
[commentator 1] Charles Leclerc is the
winner of the 2019 Italian Grand Prix.
How about that?
[crowd chanting] Ferrari!
Ferrari! Ferrari!
[Martin] No, you are not dreaming.
You've just won the Italian Grand Prix
wearing that infamous red suit.
[Charles] Yes!
[all cheering]
- [engineer 2] P13.
- [Sebastian] Okay, copy.
I took myself out of the race
in the beginning. Sorry for that.
[chanting] Ferrari! Ferrari! Ferrari!
[Charles in Italian] Winning here
is ten times more emotional
than winning anywhere else.
Thanks to all of you.
I don't have the words.
[journalist in English] Sebastian, I guess
it was just one of those days.
Well, not a particularly good one, no.
[crowd cheering]
[announcer] Ladies and gentlemen,
Charles Leclerc!
[Charles] To see so many people
was just absolute madness.
It was probably the best day of my life.
[all cheering]
For Seb, Monza was frustrating,
because when you do a mistake,
and it was his own mistake,
it's always frustrating.
I think certainly there is
a natural rivalry between the teammates.
[Charles] Seb's obviously the first person
you want to beat...
because at the end,
he's the only person on the grid
that has the same car as yourself.
[Will] If Seb thought that
it was going to be
a traditional master
and apprentice narrative,
he's had a bit of a rude awakening.
[indistinct chatter]
Seeing how quickly Leclerc developed
in his debut season with Ferrari...
there is a massive prospect for fireworks.
[Martin] Look at that!
Charles Leclerc flying out in front.
You can't restrain him!
[engineer] Charles, box. Box now.
[commentator] Ferrari have brought
Leclerc to pit,
that could give Vettel the advantage.
That was a quick stop for Leclerc,
but was it quick enough
to get out in front of his teammate?
Vettel's coming down the pit straight.
Vettel's gonna get ahead of Leclerc here,
there he is!
[Charles] What the hell?
[engineer] Charles,
it was the best thing we could do.
[Charles] To be honest with you,
I don't understand at all.
[Martin] Right at the front,
Sebastian Vettel leading for Ferrari.
Sebastian Vettel takes the checkered flag
and wins the Singapore Grand Prix!
[crowd whistling and cheering]
[journalist] Was this scenario
discussed before the race?
Uh, no. No.
[Martin] Leclerc leads, Sebastian Vettel
pulls over to the right hand side
and takes the lead!
[commentator] Leclerc will be
absolutely fuming.
[Charles] Just for me to understand,
the situation was pretty clear, right?
[engineer 1] Yes, Sebastian
will let you by next lap.
[engineer 1] Let Charles by.
Let Charles by.
[Sebastian] Let's break away
for another two laps.
- [Charles] Well?
- [engineer 2] Sebastian, let Charles by.
[Sebastian] You can tell him to close up.
[Charles] You put me behind,
and I respected everything,
but now it's difficult to close the gap,
obviously. We'll speak later.
[Will] Every world champion has
what I term an "inner bastard,"
and it is that ability to make
the tough decision when you have to.
Ayrton Senna once said, "If you no longer
go for a gap that exists,
you're no longer a racing driver."
But for a driver like Sebastian,
that gap doesn't have to be physical.
It's a weakness,
it's a chink in the armor of your rival,
and you take it, no matter what.
I think Charles is developing it.
But he is biding his time
playing the long game.
[Silvia] Hello, everybody.
Now, a couple of things.
Seb versus Charles. There was a big
feature today in La Gazzetta
again saying you are against each other,
but I think they just need
to fill some space.
- [man] Yeah.
- [Silvia] We know you love each other,
so just tell people...
- You can occasionally kiss if you want to.
- No.
[all laughing]
I will not go that far.
- [Sebastian] We'll start by holding hands.
- [Silvia] Okay.
All right.
[Karun] We're gonna see drivers
pushing out there today.
[commentator] Charles Leclerc is a man
who conceivably you think
could be on pole later on today.
[engineer] Try to increase the gap
to Magnussen in front.
And it will be mode push for last corner,
mode push.
Magnussen in front...
[Charles] Something wrong with the engine.
[engineer] Slow button on.
Slow button on.
Stop the car. Stop the car.
[Martin] Leclerc has pulled off
the circuit in the Ferrari.
[engineer] Engine off. Engine off.
- [Charles] I'll get out of the car.
- [engineer] Copy.
[Martin] And that is session over
for Charles Leclerc.
[Martin] It'll be a tough two hours
till qualifying.
[Mattia] You have no time,
really, to analyze.
You just need to react.
We need to make sure
that the car is ready for the quali.
Two hours is very little time
to change a full power unit.
[Karun] There's still smoke coming out
of the airbox.
So much heat!
- [in Italian] You know we lost oil.
- What?
Okay.
Something happened with the engine.
Stay in place.
[commentator 1 in English] Charles
Leclerc's car is ready to go.
They've done a good job here at Ferrari,
getting that new power unit in.
[commentator 2] They've had to use
an older, used engine in the car.
[Mattia] Sorry for Charles' morning.
But try to be sharp.
It will be very tight in the afternoon.
Let's enjoy. Today is the qualifying day.
It would be good to have a good result.
[commentator] It's qualifying,
here in Austin, Texas,
for the 59th World Championship
Grand Prix in the USA.
[all cheering]
It's still the same old story,
who can get the fastest time today?
[Martin] Sebastian Vettel
starts a flying lap.
[engineer 1] Charles three seconds behind,
coming fast.
[engineer 2] Sebastian in front.
Sebastian's in front.
- 3.198. Can you be faster than that?
- [Sebastian] Copy, yeah.
[Martin] Setting the world alight
is Sebastian Vettel
at over 200 miles an hour.
[engineer 2] Let me know
if you can go faster.
Question?
- [Charles] I don't think I can.
- [engineer 2] Copy. Understood.
[commentator] I'll tell you
who's on their back foot.
You've gotta say Charles Leclerc,
just trying to get a handle on this car.
[Martin] Out and across the line
comes Sebastian Vettel,
at 24.6, a personal best.
Where does it put him? Second!
[Sebastian] Okay, guys.
[in Italian] Good work.
Thank you, everyone.
[Martin in English] Charles Leclerc
remains fourth.
[engineer 2] P4, P4.
[Charles] I've lost
so much in the straights.
Anyway, fourth.
[crowd cheering]
[cheering]
[presenter] Please give
a massive welcome to Sebastian Vettel!
[Sebastian] Thank you.
[cheering]
[Sebastian] God damn, I like America.
[crowd laughing and cheering]
In Germany, you know, in Germany...
In Germany, you finish second,
and they're like,
"What's the problem? What's going on?"
I always need to make excuses,
you know? So...
[presenter] Let's go back
a few races to Singapore.
That win made you the third
most winning driver for Scuderia Ferrari.
[Sebastian] Who is ahead? Michael and...
- Michael and Niki. Yeah.
- Niki. So...
[all laughing]
- Not bad names to be...
- No. Not at all. Not at all.
I'm... I don't know, I love the sport,
I love the number sides of it as well.
I'm always thinking that one day
I'll be in my rocking chair,
fat and chubby and old,
and then I can tell my kids, like,
"Look..." You know? "Look at the numbers."
[crowd laughing and clapping]
[Martin] It's the Unites States Grand Prix
at the Circuit of the Americas.
Lewis Hamilton can clinch the championship
for the sixth time
with a good result today.
[indistinct chatter]
What's up, bro? Congrats! You all right?
[Martin] Ferrari are strangely becalm
so far this weekend.
They're not on pole position.
They are on the front row
with Sebastian Vettel.
They're on the second row
with Charles Leclerc.
But we've got an interesting race
ahead of us.
[Mattia] We know
it will be very difficult.
We know our competitors are strong.
They're very strong.
But as Ferrari,
I think that there are no limits.
[commentator] Leclerc has really burst
onto the scene this year
and Vettel maybe has had
his nose put out of joint a bit.
[imperceptible]
- [in French] Good race.
- Thank you.
[Will in English] Ferrari, they are going
through a re-building process.
But when you are fighting
against a team like Mercedes,
can you have a driver war...
that doesn't run the risk of imploding?
[man and women
singing American national anthem]
♪ O'er the land of the free ♪
♪ And the home ♪
♪ Of the brave ♪
[crowd cheering]
[Will] Sebastian Vettel,
he sees his birthright.
He sees his place as the number one.
"And I'll be damned if I'm gonna give
that position up to my rookie teammate...
that a lot of people view
as being Ferrari's future."
[crowd cheering]
[Martin] It's takeoff in Texas.
Decent start from Vettel,
but Verstappen's got a better one.
[commentator 1] Verstappen, he's already
wheel-to-wheel with Sebastian Vettel!
Verstappen has passed him.
Hamilton has passed him
and has made his way up into fourth place.
And you can hear the cheers of the crowd
who rather like that one,
thank you very much.
[Sebastian] I've got some damage.
I don't know where from.
I didn't touch anything,
but I have understeer like crazy.
[Martin] What's happening to Sebastian
Vettel out there? Has he got a problem?
And on the inside, Charles Leclerc
has now got past his teammate as well.
[commentator 1] Sebastian Vettel's
not happy about that.
He's coming back at Leclerc.
But Charles stays ahead,
and he's getting away.
[in Italian] He overtook him.
[commentator 1 in English] It's a lock up!
Vettel is pushing to the absolute limits.
[in Italian] There's a problem, guys.
[Martin] Daniel Ricciardo on the tail
of Sebastian Vettel!
[Sebastian] Something broke.
[Martin] Vettel coming back
at Daniel Ricciardo!
[engine sputtering]
[Martin] What's happened there?
Sebastian Vettel has massive problems!
[Sebastian] I think the suspension
just failed.
Yep, failed. Something broke.
Yeah. I don't know what happened there.
Completely failed.
[engineer] Try to avoid
the curb inside turn eight.
[Charles] Why?
[engineer] Just because Sebastian had
suspension failure there.
We are going plan B, but you need to try
to close the gap to Hamilton in front.
[Charles] Yeah, copy.
[commentator 1] It's up to Charles Leclerc
to bring this home for Ferrari.
[engineer] Okay. Four more laps.
[Charles] Yeah, yeah, yeah. Pushing.
- [engineer] Head down. Try to pass them.
- [Charles] Okay.
[commentator 1] Here comes Lewis Hamilton
adding another championship
to his collection!
He's got six up here in Austin!
It's Lewis Hamilton,
champion of the world!
[commentator 2] Charles Leclerc
across the line. Finishes fourth.
What a result with an old engine.
[engineer] P4.
You have done a good job. Really good job.
[Charles sighs] Thanks, guys.
[Sebastian] He's very fast.
I think he's proven many times.
So he doesn't need to prove that anymore.
As far as we are concerned
working for the team,
I think we are pulling
in the same direction.
I accept the challenge.
[imperceptible]
[Charles] It's been an incredible season.
For me, at the end, it's my first ever
season in Formula 1
fighting for podiums, wins,
pole positions.
The dream is to try and build a long term
relationship with the team.
And, yeah, my future dream
is to be a world champion with them.
[Mattia] I think we're really at the start
of our journey.
In order to win, sometimes,
you need as well to take some risks.
We are all very convinced
on what we want to achieve.
We will not hesitate to be brave
for the future.
[Sebastian] In the end, it's all about...
All about winning.
Competing against the best,
that's one thing.
[indistinct chatter]
Trying to do it with Ferrari
is another one.
[man 1] When are we getting
the Renault team jet?
When you do your first podium.
- [man 2] Ooh.
- [laughs]
- [man 3] What are your best moments?
- [man 4] That's a very short list.
I am very funny, also very good-looking.
Nico Hulkenberg!
- [Claire] Am I still in the lead?
- You are.
Oh! [laughs]
Should Sir Frank Williams'
sack his daughter?
I feel like an idiot.
[man 5] This is where I'm gonna
have my single life.
[man 6] What the hell did you do?
[man 7] This is the best day of my life.