Formula One
has been called the "Piranha Club"
because of the amount
of sniping and biting.
It's much worse than swimming with sharks.
There's
so much money involved in the sport.
It is not just about
what you see at a Grand Prix track.
It's what goes on behind the scenes.
Absolutely cutthroat.
If you want to be strong on the track,
you also need to be strong off track.
Success in racing
comes down to just being stubborn.
A lot of your competitors
will fall apart before you will.
Politics are a big part
of the sport. It can get pretty nasty.
There's a lot of posturing,
positioning, total paranoia.
You always want
to destabilize your competitors.
If you can't take the heat,
stay out of the kitchen.
This is, albeit a short one, the history
of the team, the championship years.
Winning four championships.
Max's first victory.
Daniel's first victory.
What we've actually done in
the last 15 years is pretty significant.
You know, this was our first winner.
This was the first
Driver's Championship car.
It was the first
Constructor's Championship car.
Great job, Sebastian.
Proud of you. Great job.
To take on all the great teams
at that time, you know, really,
the start of a totally dominant period
for Red Bull Racing.
We're an energy drinks manufacturer.
We're the maverick in Formula One.
We've won eight World Championships.
But in the last few years,
we've lagged behind.
We need to challenge the big teams.
Our Achilles' heel has been the engine.
And it is
absolute double disaster for Red Bull.
Both have just plain broken down.
And that's been
immensely frustrating for us.
We have to raise our game.
You know that the good thing
about Renault in Formula One...
I think that, obviously,
the only possibility to live in Paris
and work in Formula One,
which is not that bad.
We are French.
We are passionate.
Renault is a partly state-owned company,
so it really belongs to the French people.
This position in which I am currently,
it's a huge privilege.
Come in. Go on, go on, go on.
Lunch is part of life, so...
It's a very important part of life.
Thank you.
We are a French team.
We have the best table in the paddock.
And it has to be the same at the factory.
Renault is one of the few teams
that make a Formula One engine.
We also happen to supply
those engines to other teams.
Getting a Formula One engine right
is very complicated,
because we are talking
about many components.
Engine technology is very complex.
We also happen
to supply those engines to Red Bull.
It's a customer, but at the same time,
they're our competitors.
We at Red Bull, we don't make road cars.
We're not an engine manufacturer.
We've bought our engines from Renault
for the past twelve seasons.
We pay for the service
that Renault provide...
but we're not consulted on any decisions
that are made regarding the layout,
the cooling, the exhaust,
the integration of the engine
into the chassis.
We have to accept
whatever Renault want to do.
And that is a big, big issue.
Starting to have very strong comments
from Christian regarding performance.
It is very clear
that the relationship with Red Bull
is going to a crunch time.
But the engine is progressing.
It's capable of winning races.
Every single race win that Red Bull had
was with Renault.
We've had a love-hate relationship
with Renault for the last twelve years.
You know, Renault have fallen behind
their rivals in Ferrari and Mercedes,
and, you know, that's caused frustration,
friction in the relationship, tension.
He's clearly someone who wants to control
every single element of this car.
But unfortunately, he has to accept
that there is one element
they're not controlling.
With that engine supply,
we've been paying to fly in first class,
but ended up with an economy ticket.
Bang-for-buck value for money
is crucial to us.
And it's a very, very important year
for the team,
so we need to make a decision.
Daniel, happy birthday.
Yeah, I just got a warm welcome.
I got, um, a birthday...
a birthday massacre.
Aw. Have a great race, okay?
Love you, B.
-Yeah. All right. Gangster.
-Love you.
-I don't even-- It was a very good one.
-That was good, huh? That shit's ad hoc.
I woke up early 'cause it's my birthday.
I was so excited.
I've been with Red Bull since 2008.
Now that contract is coming
to an end this year, and...
when it comes to looking ahead,
you've kind of gotta see who's doing what.
You gotta try and figure out
who's gonna dominate
for the next, you know,
one to three years.
Welcome, Daniel Ricciardo
and Max Verstappen!
A nice birthday present.
Shoe size, 58.
The main thing for me
is to put myself
in the best car with a chance to win
to try and see
if I'm the best in the world
and show what I believe I've got.
Where I am in my career--
I'm 29 now. If I'm ever, ever gonna be
world champion,
making this decision is massive.
One more time,
Daniel Ricciardo and Max Verstappen.
- Anything I need to be aware of?
- Um...
Daniel was positive?
-He said discussions had moved on.
-Yeah.
-The next couple of weeks...
...he would hope to be giving an answer.
-Basically, before the summer break.
-Okay, good. Super.
Yeah.
Let's go here.
You couldn't see any reason why Daniel
wouldn't re-sign with you guys?
That you were confident that he would.
Feeling more confident this week?
We're very happy with Daniel.
We hope that we retain him in the team.
He's in a great car.
He's a championship contender this year.
I can't imagine him anywhere else.
Hello.
Hi, how are you?
We are currently fourth in championship,
and Red Bull are third.
Red Bull is obviously a great brand...
uh, but to drink.
Renault is one
of the largest car makers in the world.
We are here for building
the reputation of our brand.
It's all about playing catch up
against Red Bull.
We have impatient shareholders,
impatient sponsors, impatient drivers.
The Renault team cannot outperform us.
Teammates...
we've been super competitive.
Naturally, with that,
there becomes a competition, a rivalry...
a lot of friction, tension.
My teammate, but also my biggest rival.
I need to be the faster driver of the two.
I hate to lose.
All this contract talk,
it does put more pressure on me.
When it comes to these negotiations,
to strengthen your position,
winning is important.
-Have a good one.
-Thanks.
Get your head down.
Now only moments away
from the start of the Austrian Grand Prix.
- Radio check, please.
- Yep, Rennie, that's good.
- Things should happen today.
Ricciardo needs
his third win of the season here
to stay in contention
for the championship.
Verstappen has started well!
Daniel Ricciardo is trying
to get past Grosjean.
And he's up into fifth!
Renault also battling through the pack.
Carlos Sainz,
oh, bit of a collision there.
Oh, now his teammate Nico Hülkenberg
has a major problem.
Loss of power. I've lost power.
Stop the car, please, Nicky.
You've got fire at the back of the car.
And that's game over.
Appears to be
an engine issue for Renault.
Ricciardo, closing up on Kimi Räikkönen.
Good move, mate. Nice job.
And up into third place now.
Okay, so, Hamilton is only
18 seconds ahead.
Okay.
Into the pit lane,
Lewis Hamilton for Mercedes,
currently in the lead,
but now he's in for his tire change.
Hamilton is in the pit lane.
So, push now. Push on if you can.
Now will Ricciardo
be able to overtake Hamilton
as he comes from the pit lane?
- Gonna be close. Gonna be close.
- Okay.
Hamilton one second behind you.
Red Bull suddenly smell
a victory here today.
Oh!
What was that coming out
of the back of the Red Bull?
Losing gear sync.
Fail. Two fail, Daniel.
We have got an issue.
It's the rear.
It's getting really bad now.
Okay. Fail. Two fail.
We're gonna have to retire, Daniel.
Retire.
Oh, he's got a problem. He's stopping!
Daniel Ricciardo is out of the race.
If you can,
pull over at turn one, please.
Pull over at turn one.
I'll tell you later,
but we've got some issues
at the rear end of the car.
Sorry about that, mate.
Red Bull will not enjoy
the sights of a mechanical problem.
He is out of the Austrian Grand Prix.
Oh, dear. What a shame
for Daniel Ricciardo.
That's blown the candles out
on the birthday cake.
It's been a bad day for Renault.
Their sole remaining car finishes
in twelfth place with no points.
I know what I'm capable of,
but things seem to keep happening
out of my control. It's frustrating.
Do you know what day Max is in this week?
'Cause I wouldn't mind finding
half an hour with him
just in the afternoon.
Cool. All right.
- Okay.
- Okay. Speak to you later.
-Speak to you later.
-Thanks. Bye-bye.
Daniel's contract talks
and discussions have made progress.
The only question that Daniel has,
quite openly is,
is the power unit going
to be able to compete with Mercedes
and Ferrari next year?
That is his only question,
in terms of the team's capabilities.
The only question over our package
for next year is the engine.
I have complete confidence that we can
become the best on the engine side.
Red Bull criticizing its supplier
is absolutely nothing new.
In a few weeks, we will not be
in a position to guarantee supply
to Red Bull anymore.
We need to order parts from the suppliers
to build the engine for next year.
I can't postpone forever--
forever the deadline.
So, if Red Bull Racing wants
to be supplied by Renault,
they need to let us know
as quickly as possible.
What is the best route to competitiveness?
Is it to stay with Renault?
Or is it to move to another manufacturer?
One that would allow us to have
an input into the design of the engine
to create true harmony
between engine and chassis.
It's so crucial
we make the right decision.
At eight a.m. tomorrow morning,
we'll be announcing
we will not be continuing
our relationship with Renault.
We have got a breaking new story...
Christian Horner
is dumping Renault next season.
Renault would stop
supplying Red Bull from 2019...
That's millions of dollars Renault
will no longer be receiving next year.
A blow to the Renault brand, as one less
team has a Renault engine next year.
I'm in a bit of disbelief,
to be honest.
He lost faith.
Yeah...
Who else is in the conference?
- They've got Cyril...
- Great.
-How are you?
-Yeah, could be better.
-Are all your bigwigs here this weekend?
-A few of them, yeah.
I'm sure.
You know, we've decided to take
a different path for next year.
We've been following the progress
of Honda's development very closely.
And the decision we've made
is that Honda is absolutely
the right route for Red Bull.
We're all selfish in this business.
Renault's priorities are--
obviously are their own team.
From 2019, we won't be paying
the amounts we've been paying to Renault.
It's exciting news for us.
2019, we're looking forward to it.
Cyril, can we get Renault's feelings
on the news from this week?
Yeah, well, the implication
of, uh, the termination of the deal
on our budget is really marginal.
Uh... yes, there was a substantial revenue
associated to that supply,
but there were
also substantial costs associated.
And clearly marginal in comparison
to a view of our budget
of our organization, as we speak.
- Thank you, bye-bye.
- That was juicy, wasn't it?
Now, you guys and Red Bull...
shall we say it's not been the happiest
of marriages for the last few years?
Sort of a marriage where you're hanging
around for the sake of the children,
rather than because you're
in love with each other.
The Honda route is the best route forward
for us for the future.
Personally, I'm a bit sad,
because it's been twelve years or so
of my life, dealing with Christian...
No, Renault was very keen
to have us.
They were desperate even till last week.
We feel now that we don't
need Red Bull anymore.
We're still relying on Renault
in our current season.
How can you promise them
that the performance level
will be as high as possible?
And how has this news been received
by Daniel Ricciardo?
I think he sees the logic, the data
that we're looking at.
It's a no-brainer.
So, it boosts your chances
of retaining him.
I would think so, absolutely.
- There you go.
- Thank you very much.
-Thank you.
I think that was all right.
Very entertaining.
I need another excuse for a tattoo,
so I really wanna win a championship soon
so I can get something to represent that.
All this contract talk, it's--
Winning is still the main thing for me.
At least top of my list,
it's be somewhere where I can win.
But I-- Maybe it comes with age,
but it needs to be a happy environment...
to be able to win.
So, um... stay, change,
stick with what we know,
it's all that sort of concoction
of emotions, isn't it?
-It's a big decision.
-Yeah.
I turn thirty next year.
I'm getting old, so...
We're in the privileged position
of having more than one option.
Having interest
from other really good teams.
Yeah, it's just about making
the correct overall choice.
We were both personally surprised
when Max announced that he'd extended.
Their focus looked like Max,
and he should be
the youngest ever world champion.
Those things aren't lost on us.
Welcome to the last Grand Prix
before a three-week summer break.
The drivers and their teams
are getting ready at the Hungaroring.
The relationship
with Cyril's been difficult.
He's an emotional guy.
You never know what you're gonna get.
Comments involving the engine has been
a step too far from Red Bull.
The red line crossed.
We are racing in Budapest.
Verstappen immediately
from seventh up to fifth.
Oh! Ricciardo!
Oh!
Ericsson just careered
into the side of Ricciardo there.
- Daniel...
- I dunno if there's damage.
- Stay out for now. Stay out.
- Okay.
Sergio Perez going past as well.
Fucking Force India passed me.
There's no way he keeps that spot.
Okay, get focused.
Daniel, let's get going.
We are staying out. Stay out. Let's go.
- Understood.
- You know what to do.
Okay.
Daniel Ricciardo, with
a little bit of damage from the start,
now down in sixteenth.
It's very difficult to overtake
on the Hungaroring.
Ricciardo is making a move
and he's got past Perez.
Next up is Vandoorne.
Past Vandoorne.
Ricciardo ducking and weaving.
And he breezes past Fernando Alonso.
Ricciardo really is one of
the best overtakers in the business.
- Next one ahead... Hülkenberg.
- Okay.
Ricciardo now has
two Renaults to overtake.
The first is Nico Hülkenberg.
Oh, and that is spectacular stuff.
Super late on the brakes!
Next one, Carlos Sainz.
And Sainz becomes yet another victim
of Ricciardo in the first corner.
Ricciardo now up to seventh. Phenomenal.
Oh, there's a problem!
- Mate, no power, no power.
- Yep. Mode one.
Max Verstappen
in a nightmare weekend.
Stop the car, please,
on track, Max.
I don't fucking care
if this blows up.
- Okay.
-  Fuck it!
Stop the car, please.
Another power-issue-related
problem for Red Bull.
Piece of shit!
Fuck! What a fucking joke
all the fucking time
with this shit, honestly.
Okay, Daniel, that last lap,
you were the quickest on track.
Yes.
Ricciardo is flying.
All over the back of Kevin Magnussen
in the Haas.
Ricciardo's trying to go
the long way round.
And he's pulled it off!
Another great move!
Here's another place for Ricciardo.
He's fought back from sixteenth
up to fifth, very impressive.
Valtteri Bottas now ahead of him.
Bottas covers the inside.
Ricciardo has to go
the long way around.
Oh! And they touch!
Contact between Bottas and Ricciardo.
Bottas just careered into the side
of the Australian.
There's massive damage
on the side of that Red Bull.
Bottas just locked up
and went into you.
- Yes.
- You are now starting the last lap.
- Okay.
- You can still get him.
Ricciardo goes for it again.
And he overtakes Bottas.
With all that chaos behind,
it's been an easy race for Lewis Hamilton.
A commanding victory
for Hamilton and Mercedes,
winning the Hungarian Grand Prix.
Ricciardo recovers to fourth place.
Well done, Daniel.
Very strong drive.
- Some fantastic passing moves there.
-  Cheers, guys.
It's just a good feeling
when you've done your best,
knowing that I've still got it
and proving it to people.
Renault disappointing
in ninth and twelfth.
And now over a hundred points
behind Red Bull in the championship.
We know
that the second part of the season's
going to be extremely intense...
Very tight against cars around us,
which right now are more competitive
and we need to change
the way that we are doing things
if we want to have any chance
to fight against them.
We had a good meeting last week,
and I'm pleased to announce to you
that we will have an increase
in the financial support
from next year
that we materialize in an extra budget.
We have a strategy.
We have a plan.
We need to see that people respect us.
We are not going to be intimidated,
full stop.
I've been on holiday
for two weeks.
So, I've been training the last few days,
getting back into it.
I just thought about a lot of things
this year and contract talks.
What am I gonna do next?
Red Bull's confident that next year
it's gonna be great.
But Honda, they haven't yet
proven themselves.
I don't know.
It's busy. It's been busy
for several months.
Without Red Bull, Daniel
would not be in the position he is now.
There is a significant
amount of loyalty there.
You have to be respectful of that.
-How's the season?
-Good.
-Yeah?
-Good, yeah.
-Bits we could have been better, but...
-Yeah.
Yeah, we're nine races in.
We've won three of them.
This is the best driver pairing
that we've had in our history.
Daniel's contract's
been talked about since preseason.
And I'm confident that we'll manage
to get things resolved.
I've thoroughly enjoyed watching
his development the last ten years.
He's come through the ranks,
as a member of the junior program.
As soon as he got into
a Red Bull car,
he never stopped overtaking people.
Seven Grand Prix victories
and over twenty podiums,
all achieved in Red Bull racing cars.
Personally, I view him as a good friend.
I'm trying to negotiate terms
with Red Bull.
I feel I've been loyal up until now.
A deal with Red Bull, it's all in front
of me now, like, this is it.
All I've gotta do is sign
the piece of paper.
Okay.
Hmm.
What if I just break free
and-- and make a statement?
Red Bull, I've been there
since I was 18, I think.
Now I have a chance to be an adult
and walk into a team as an adult.
My heart's going.
I've decided to leave Red Bull
and I'll be joining Renault for 2019.
At times, I've found myself frustrated.
I just felt I needed something different.
I like new challenges
and kind of having a fresh start.
Hang on a minute, Daniel
Ricciardo is not re-signing for Red Bull.
He's going to Renault.
Were they expecting it?
No, it definitely caught them out.
Nice morning.
-Maybe we will go the normal way.
-Yeah, do you wanna-- I was gonna say.
You can sneak, but we'll go...
Otherwise you sneak through the paddock--
-Yeah. Nah, I will.
-That's maybe not--
-Let's take it all on the chin.
-Yeah.
All right. Where is the conference?
The top end.
Oh, it's not that crazy.
Cyril.
He needs a driver and an engine.
Yeah.
So have you got money
to spend on your engine,
-now you've spent it all on your driver?
-We've got plenty of money.
It's kind of weird.
Like, super weird.
Yeah.
There's a bit of an-- Is it--
What's the-- Airy?
-Eerie. Eerie.
-Eerie? Eerie atmosphere?
Did something else happen this morning
that I don't know about?
Well...
It's gonna be weird,
but somewhat exciting.
I think it's a good move.
I'm leaving sufficient space for Max.
A question for Christian.
Given the loss of Daniel,
it's obviously very significant.
Is there any added frustration
in losing him to an organization
of which you've been
very publicly critical?
Um...
Of course it was a surprise.
Having had everything in front of him,
that he wanted and had required,
financially, uh, et cetera, et cetera.
Well, I suppose
the whole process with Daniel,
so long as he's comfortable looking
at himself in the mirror
with the choices that he's made,
you have to respect that.
We've had random discussion,
jokes with Daniel since a while.
Uh, it would be hard to put
an exact date on the first joke
about this this type of switch.
Renault can afford pretty much anything.
Renault is the largest car maker
in Formula One, full stop.
He bought into the project
and made his decision.
Thank you.
And the knock-on effects
of Ricciardo moving to Renault
means Carlos Sainz will lose his seat.
Press conference.
We know what they're talking about.
Mmm...
Um... you know what's gonna be
asked, so it's all straightforward.
Is there anything in particular you guys
don't want or want to say?
This year, I wanna do the best on track.
My focus is Spa this weekend.
Next weekend, my focus is Monza.
I want you to cry.
I want you to be really sad.
Kind of just say you're gonna
miss us so much.
Okay, I'll try.
Thank you.
- See you. Bye!
- Bye!
Later.
Now, with Red Bull, it'll be awkward.
I'll expect to be isolated.
People are shocked
in some quarters by the decision.
But I think it comes down
to where you feel wanted.
We had a private meeting
with Renault,
and they walked us through
what was coming.
It really showed you
the might of a manufacturer.
Their ultimate goal, to be
a world-championship-winning team again,
and they have the pedigree for that.
Is he making the right career choice?
In the end, my assumption is
he was running from a fight.
That's the way it feels to me.
Always look ahead.
Focus on going forwards,
not backwards.
Our goal is not just to beat Renault.
Our goal is to try and be world champions.
It's a very dangerous sport,
and it will always be.
Confidence level goes down
when you have a crash like that.
Jules Bianchi has died...
This year, his godson, Charles
Leclerc, made his Formula One debut.
The bigger teams are now
putting their faith in younger drivers.
Wow, look at that.
- LeClerc round the outside!
- Yes!
For Marcus,
it's a little hard to take.
LeClerc is right on his tail now.
I've always dreamed
to be part of Ferrari.
Charles has a mission to do
what Jules should have done.