My objective is that by 2010,
Force India Formula One team
will rightfully occupy
a place on the podium.
I'm Vijay Mallya,
Team Principal
of Sahara Force India Formula One.
I have always been passionate
about cars and racing cars.
So to acquire a Formula One team,
it's like a dream come true.
Nobody ever thought
that there would be
an Indian Formula One team on the grid.
It was just too expensive.
And it seemed more like
a pipe dream than a real dream.
From where we started
to finish fourth, two years running,
there can be no greater satisfaction.
We did it once again, guys!
Once again!
Sergio Perez picks up
a very unlikely podium.
Brilliant, Checo!
Absolutely brilliant.
Now there are constant rumors
about offers to buy the team,
but I've invested blood,
sweat and tears
into Force India.
So I'm fighting every step of the way.
Vijay's always been one of
Formula One's more colorful characters,
known as the king of good times.
But Force India's success has come
from making every penny work for them.
They're one of the most efficient outfits
in the sport.
When you look at Force India
and McLaren over the last few years,
they're completely mirror images
of one another,
because while Force India
has achieved so much with so little,
McLaren,
one of the biggest names in the sport,
seems to be achieving
so little with so much.
Oh, not another problem
for McLaren...
I lost drive...
I need to park up.
- Copy, Stoffel, copy.
- I don't have the same power.
We can't fix it.
Mate, I have no brakes, no tires.
We are out of the points.
I will try to do whatever,
but I don't care too much.
Sounded like a driver who wants
to call it a day, didn't it?
Fernando Alonso becomes
the first retirement of this Grand Prix.
And Zak Brown not happy.
Not where they expected
to be or want to be.
Eric, do you accept any responsibility
for the failings of this car?
And will you resign?
Um, obviously, we are all responsible
for the car performance.
Uh, we are not where we want to be,
we are not happy where we are...
Do you expect still to be
in your job at Silverstone?
Good morning, Fernando. How are you?
Good. Where are you?
So I wanted to let you know,
and we can chat about it further.
Uh, last night
I accepted, uh, Eric's resignation.
Lots of pressure on the team,
as we all know,
and he's been taking the brunt of it.
Obviously it's been a tough
three, four years for him,
and he felt, in order
for us to move forward
with all the pressure,
that it was best he stepped aside.
I think we got great people.
We're gonna recruit some people
and, you know, get the team, uh...
turned around
and make McLaren great again.
I think Fernando's one of the best
drivers in the history of Formula One.
Two-time world champion,
won over thirty races,
recognized by many
to be the best driver in the world.
When you have a driver
of Fernando's caliber,
you wanna keep them
in your racing team.
At the top, there's
one guy responsible now
and you're talking to him.
So the the buck stops with me.
You're absolutely right.
Yeah.
Any time you're responsible
for a large organization,
that comes with a lot of pressure.
So I like that first question 'cause
it'll also suck up about five minutes.
Yeah. That's good.
How's your search
for a technical director going?
Nope. We've already had it.
So, let's get rid of that one.
It's a huge responsibility.
If you can't cope with the pressure,
you can't take the heat,
get out of the kitchen.
Um, he's asked Zak to address
whether it was a voluntary resignation
by mutual agreement.
Yeah. It's inappropriate for me
to get into any details
-of the conversation that Eric and I had.
-Yeah. Those are private matters.
Zak Brown hasn't come from a position
of running a big racing team,
so he's got a huge, huge job on his hands,
especially when you consider
he's got a two-time world champion
in Fernando Alonso,
who demands nothing but the best.
Force India
could never afford an Alonso
or a Lewis Hamilton or a Vettel.
It's not a one man show.
It's a team effort.
And I guess I hired the right guys.
I hired Otmar
as the Chief Operating Officer.
I think he shares
the same passion and ambition.
Drivers, we have Checo Perez.
He's a gutsy driver
and he's got great race craft.
Esteban Ocon,
here's a guy who's young,
he's passionate,
he's hungry, and he's got talent.
Nice job, Esteban. Nice job.
I think he surprised us all
in his first full year in Formula One...
and did himself proud.
Hi, Carlo.
We are here with Roberta.
And she wanted to let you know
that she deserve a lot of present,
a lot of attention.
Oh, thank you, guys!
Yes!
The fact that the team is able
to compete and perform
at such a high level
is absolutely incredible...
especially when you consider
the personal difficulties
that Vijay Mallya's
been going through.
Today, it's the fall from grace
of one of India's most high profile
businessmen, Vijay Mallya.
Prosecution has told the court
that Vijay Mallya avoided attempts
to repay loans to banks,
did not disclose assets,
allegedly diverted loan money
to motor racing.
The allegations are baseless,
unfounded, deliberate.
It doesn't look good
on your Formula One team,
does it, apart from anything else?
Right now, I'm in forced exile.
I am absolutely not guilty
of any one of these preposterous charges.
That is the truth.
It can't be helpful to Force India
to have Vijay facing such difficulties.
And with the banks in India wanting
to get hold of him,
Vijay can't be seen
to be spending loads and loads of money
when other people are chasing him
for loads and loads of money.
There isn't that cash flow
to Force India anymore,
so it's going to be having
some form of impact.
I'm Esteban Ocon, 22 years old,
racing for Force India Formula One team.
Vijay, for sure
it's a tough situation...
for me, for the race team, at the track,
but I can't focus
on all those things.
My job is to stick in the race seat
and put the car as high as I can.
That's the only thing I can do
to help the team at the moment.
Nice view, huh?
From the first race, basically, I'm here,
training hard
and just improving all the aspects.
Mentally, physically...
From my point of view,
here is the best way.
There is nothing except sport here.
No girls, no drinks, no distractions.
Get ready. Go!
The last season,
it's been a very special season for me.
I was very happy with how I progressed,
to be the most successful season
of the team.
And that feeling,
I want to have it more and more.
When I was a kid, it was
a different life then than everyone else.
Tough times. Yeah, for sure.
My parents,
they don't have a lot of of money.
Well, my dad's, yeah, he's a mechanic.
It's really hard to describe the hours
he was doing, when I was going to sleep.
Sometimes he was working all night
and I still saw him in the morning
on the same thing.
My dad always was saying,
"I want a better life for you
than I had for me."
For me, it's everything.
Esteban is my whole life.
I'm still here today for him.
Esteban is my greatest pride.
That's my son.
My dad had his workshop.
I've always been growing,
seeing engines, fuel, rubber, whatever.
I used to be there, you know, playing
with little cars and after that,
you know, I always wanted
to be a racing driver.
Silverstone is a tough track, of course,
because, you know,
it's very quick and very technical.
Okay. I have to close the eyes, though.
I'm a very competitive guy,
you know. I want to be world champion.
I'm not gonna lift the throttle
until I get it.
Stay straight, DRS on,
turn one, flat out.
Turn two, 50 meters.
Down the gears. Low corner.
Have to get on the power.
Bumpy arrival through there.
Brake. Third gear.
Long, long left. Turn seven.
Up on the curb.
Back on the power.
Third, fourth, fifth, sixth, seventh.
On the curb.
Flat out for cross.
All the races give
the same amount of points,
but there are certain races
that you really want to do well.
Silverstone is very special
as a race for everybody.
Formula One is British.
It's a fantastic event, you know.
You have so many fans.
The passion here amongst
the British audience is just exceptional.
Silverstone is an iconic Grand Prix.
It's a great circuit.
It is one of the core Grand Prix
that you wanna have success at.
Silverstone is always one of the races
that we all want to win one day.
A win in Silverstone
makes you feel part of Formula One.
Difficult to explain by words,
but when you are driving
and when you are the paddock...
you know, it's the place to be.
It's the home of Formula One.
It feels special, 'cause it's home
and it's the one race of the year
you can drive from your house to.
I got your note... this afternoon.
I've gotta do the...
FIA and--
You're important,
but you're not morning important.
You're more, like, afternoon important.
Why Eric Boullier was not
the right guy to make McLaren great again?
These look like appointments which
have been made on the instruction of
or with the intention
of pleasing Fernando above anything else.
Is that fair or unfair?
Oh, it's totally inaccurate.
Some things, maybe,
I tried to, you know, give my feedback.
The most important thing is
to improve the car
and to be more competitive
and, you know,
hopefully from this weekend,
we see a step forward.
There is a feeling in the paddock that
Fernando's influence over McLaren
is all-telling and all-important.
You know, people will whisper--
Well, it used to be a whisper.
It's not even a whisper anymore...
that, you know,
it's sort of Team Fernando,
um... that he's making the decisions.
And everyone'll be wondering, what have
you done to your hand? Are you all right?
Yes. Super.
You haven't been punching
the wall again?
- Not yet.
- Thanks, Fernando.
What do you like the most
about the track, which is legendary?
The fast corners.
To drive here in a Formula One car is--
It's experience that... you don't get it
in many other tracks.
Uh, this is very special.
- Thank you. Good luck.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Checo.
Thank you.
What are your thoughts Checo,
on all the shit
that's going on
with McLaren at the moment?
Ooh, difficult, no?
They are putting in all the people
that Fernando likes and that like him.
For me, it can be an option,
that he could become
a sort of owner of the team.
That's what happens
when a driver controls so much.
How do you do? Hi.
- How do you do? Hi.
- Nice to meet you.
I am the subject
of one of the greatest
political witch-hunts in Indian history.
Things are flying at me fast and furious.
And I don't know what
the government is going to do next.
It clearly seems to be getting
more serious behind the scenes.
Vijay's unable to leave the UK
for fear of being arrested,
so the British Grand Prix is the only race
that Vijay can actually physically attend
to watch his own team.
Take care.
But he doesn't want
to give up Force India.
- Hi, Vijay.
- It's his pride and joy.
Question to Vijay.
There has been renewed speculation
about your future ownership
of Force India.
How do you respond to that speculation,
the team is for sale?
In your question you said,
"Renewed speculation," right?
People have been writing
about the ownership of my team
for years now.
I'm sure you will not see anybody
in Force India, indeed myself,
walk around with a "for sale'' sign.
Speculation remains speculation.
It's a Saturday,
and the final practice
before qualifying begins.
Silverstone is a brilliant track
with the fastest, most exhilarating
corners anywhere on the calendar.
Hamilton is pushing hard!
Now, Vettel would love pole position
on British soil.
And here comes Brendon Hartley...
And a big crash there for the Toro Rosso.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Suspension failure.
And we thought we'd have
20 drivers going for pole today,
but we've got 19.
Here is Stoffel Vandoorne.
Is the car okay, Stoffel?
Seriously, the car
is so tricky to drive.
Stoffel Vandoorne
driving very aggressively.
Too much curb, I think, for Vandoorne,
who's damaged his car.
There's a bit of carbon fiber debris now
down at turn six.
Alonso, meanwhile,
is on his first timed lap of the session,
flying through Copse Corner.
Seriously,
we were losing time on the straights.
Okay, Fernando.
Thirteenth for Fernando Alonso.
Vandoorne in 17th place.
Maybe that bit of debris
came off the car
and lost him a lot of performance.
It's been a tough weekend
for him and McLaren.
Now, here comes Esteban Ocon
in the Force India.
Struggling for traction a little bit
coming out of Village,
the tight right-hander,
but looked much neater
through turn four.
Esteban, so you're totally clear ahead.
Yeah. Okay.
He's picked up time, Ocon.
Yes. Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Nice one.
Ocon will start tomorrow's
race in the front half of the grid,
with his teammate, Perez, just behind.
Both McLaren drivers are further back.
-Hi, Vijay.
-How are you?
Very good. Very good. And you?
Good.
You squeezed a lot out of that car
in qualy today.
Little bit makes
massive difference in the end.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome your Force India drivers,
Esteban Ocon and Sergio Perez.
When during the weekend, if ever,
do you think the car's been right?
Um... I-- I feel
like we've always struggled...
going into qualifying.
As soon as the speed kind of scrubs off,
it's like driving on ice.
What's going wrong with McLaren?
There's a lot of politics involved.
There's a lot of money.
It's a lot of decisions that were taken...
that have
become very difficult to reverse.
And I think that's
what McLaren are struggling with.
Who's got a really good question?
- Little kid here.
- Can I have your hat?
You got it.
You know, we're sort of
running out of things to check.
Certainly all the suspension internals
are okay.
All the suspension externals.
There's nothing obvious to find.
Do you think that the ride
was any different in qualifying?
No.
Uh... any thoughts
on the roll stiffness change we made?
- No. No difference.
- Uh, okay.
Three...
Two, one, go!
I think we lost performance, as we know,
in the last couple of races.
Always Formula One car improves
with headwind, but this year's,
it seems that
it is a huge step worse in tailwind.
I know you were testing in Barcelona...
all the ideas, but...
we are in the middle of July,
and we didn't saw any of those.
So... need to speed up.
Enjoy the race tomorrow.
It's coming home!
Welcome along to round ten
of the Formula One World Championship
in front of a record crowd
of 140,000 people.
Every time I see
Sahara Force India Formula One
on the World Championship grid
with Ferrari, with Mercedes,
you know, it's a great sense of pride.
As a kid,
I was watching Formula One on TV,
and I was dreaming, you know,
about being there on the race track.
But now, as a driver, you can't say,
you know, "He's better than me."
You always think you are the best.
I think if you don't start thinking
like that, that's a loss already.
To be fourth
in the championship again,
Toro Rosso, Renault, McLaren,
you gotta beat them. That is the task.
I think this season
really revealed
that maybe we're not as good
as we thought we were.
We should be the best
of the rest right now,
and we're the worst of the rest right now,
which is not good.
Somebody's gotta be accountable.
And right now, it's Zak.
-I'd like to get some points today.
-Fernando's-- Yeah.
-Well, he's got a big chance.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ultimately, we're a Grand Prix
team that's been bred to win races,
so the pressure will be on
for on-track results.
Come on, boys.
When the lights come on,
the adrenaline is pumping...
and the heart certainly misses a beat.
Away we go
at the British Grand Prix!
Whoa!
Contact between Perez and Alonso.
Ooh.
Yeah, I think
we got shoved off at the start.
I think he damaged the front wing.
And Perez is off!
Checo, give us feedback. Give us feedback.
Yeah, someone hit me.
How's the front wing? Did you hit tires?
No, I think it's okay.
Kimi Raikkonen
on the outside, Vettel from Bottas.
They touched!
Hamilton's gone round. He's crashed!
That is massive disappointment
for the British crowd.
What's going through my mind
when I crash?
Avoid. Nothing else.
Choose a direction as quickly as possible
and yeah, try not to hit it.
Fernando Alonso's picked up
a place on Kevin Magnussen.
Great work. Now though, Magnussen
is the car behind you. He could be quick.
Magnussen's coming back at Alonso.
They're going wheel-to-wheel.
What I see from Magnussen,
I never saw in my life.
He pushed me wide at turn seven,
ten, eleven, and turn twelve.
Understood, Fernando. Head down.
It's ridiculous.
Ridiculous!
And someone's had
a big off as well.
Ooh.
-Who's that? Sainz.
-Sainz.
-Sainz!
Sainz and Grosjean.
Gunter must be absolutely ready
to put his fist through the wall.
Now, Esteban Ocon,
Kevin Magnussen right behind him.
Oh, look who's in tenth and in the points,
Fernando Alonso right in there.
We could be in
for a massive 11-lap scrap now.
Oh, Verstappen's off!
We have lost Verstappen,
Grosjean, Sainz, Ericcson,
Leclerc, and Hartley from this race.
Nico Hülkenberg is
about 1.7 seconds clear of Esteban Ocon.
Kevin Magnussen
is ahead of Fernando Alonso.
He's got DRS to attack him with.
Alonso's not giving up.
He's back on the inside of Magnussen.
- Yes!
- Got him.
He's relentless, isn't he?
-He's a monster.
-Yeah.
Alonso, Magnussen, Gasly,
Perez, all in a huge scrap there.
Alonso ahead of Magnussen.
Eighth place at the moment for McLaren.
Well, if you have someone
like Alonso behind you, for sure,
you know he's gonna try hard.
As soon as you do a little mistake,
he will try to get you.
I remember where I come from.
A lot of sacrifices.
So I'm not gonna let anything stop me.
You need to trust your skill,
trust the car and be one.
Ocon crosses the line ahead of Alonso.
Awesome job, guys. Really good.
Really tough race, but good points.
We're really happy.
Great job, mate. Great job.
We could be finished sixth.
We were flying now.
What a shame.
Any time
you haven't maximized the weekend
or you think maybe
you've left something on the table,
that can be frustrating, 'cause points,
especially right now for us,
are very hard to come by.
Eighth is--
is probably not enough
with the performance
we had in the car today.
I would've like to achieved more,
but I think I can say that
about every Grand Prix so far this year.
Fantastic results, you know,
P-7. We are really happy with that.
It was very, very tough race.
Uh... I have to say, you know,
keeping Fernando and Kevin
in the back was not an easy task,
and we're improving,
so that's why I am smiling now.
It is always good to have
a double-points finish,
particularly at home in Silverstone.
I'm extremely proud of my entire team
and all my employees as well.
- How are you, big man?
- I'm good, and you?
Good to see you.
Very well, thank you. Welcome along.
You still gonna be around
by the end of the season?
Why do you ask?
Well, I'm hoping you're not
leaving, that's why.
No, no. Absolutely not.
What you don't want is
for the guys back at the factory
thinking, "Shit, my job's under threat."
If the team's getting sold,
that's not fair on them.
No. I have a famous saying
that I have been saying for decades.
I will believe it when the fat lady sings.
Okay.
Pensions.
We haven't paid 'em in forever.
So if it all gets across...
all the pension stuff will be paid,
so that's all part of the employer stuff.
-You should come up to date.
-It'll get sorted through.
Good. Those are
the only questions they have.
-All the pension stuff will--
-Salaries and pension.
Yeah, yeah.
Is everyone here?
Good morning, everyone,
and, uh, thanks for coming.
As you know,
from what you saw in the press
and in the media that on Friday
there was a case in London.
I cannot answer so many questions.
Please, please.
And our team and company
has been put into administration.
Thank you very much. No further questions.
-Nothing! That's all.
-Force India in administration, sir--
Control of the company sits
with ourselves as administrators
whilst we try and find
a solution that gives you a future
with new owners or new investment.
I am not going to answer any questions.
I've been advised not to.
I know that probably
the most pressing thing
that everyone will be wanting to know is,
are you going to get paid on Wednesday?
And the answer to that is, yes.
When I heard the news that Vijay left,
of course it was difficult, you know,
because I'm--
Vijay, I was very close to him.
Thank you very much.
It's been one of the people
that picked me up in Force India,
basically in the beginning.
-I got myself one in my house.
-Oh, you practice now?
Yeah. Yeah. Yes.
He had always been very nice to me,
and he used to send me a message,
you know, before the race.
"Yeah, Esteban, score points there.
Good luck, and I'm cheering for you."
And I will miss him definitely.
I will miss that passion for the sport,
but I think everyone in F1
wants Force India to keep racing.
The problem is that the last two teams
that this happened, they disappeared.
Force India, that's the big story.
Could the team rise from the ashes
with Lawrence Stroll as the new boss
and his son as their driver?
I'm going into the family business.
Who's going to be out
of a seat for next season? Perez or Ocon?
If you do a strong job on the team,
they can't skip you.
Into the wall goes Esteban Ocon!