All right. I'll call Carlos.
One sec. I'm calling Carlos.
- Hola.
- Hola. Uh, buenas noches.
Who am I speaking with?
Um, you are speaking... You don't know?
Are you joking?
- Who am I talking to? Come on.
- Uh, it's Lando!
Lando!
You and Carlos, as we know,
have struck up a very close bond
with lots of banter
in your relationship as teammates.
We kinda went into the first time meeting
and that was how it all started.
- Been doing well, this cabrón, lately.
- This cabrón! This cabrón!
So we're gonna spend
some more... some more time together.
It's been good for me, um,
obviously, learning from a guy with,
with such experience.
Guacamole.
Guacamoley.
No. "Moley". No.
- Guacamoley.
- No.
You seem to be
the best pairing in the paddock.
Get to the chopper!
I think we have the right balance.
We're sharing good moments together.
Ooh!
How much are you gonna miss him
when he does move to Ferrari next year?
- Uh...
- Hmm...
Big news out of Italy.
In a surprise move,
Carlos Sainz has decided to leave
his Formula 1 family, McLaren,
at the end of the year
to join Ferrari for the 2021 season.
The silly season of driver moves
is happening
in the early part of the season.
Carlos has got to go through
the entire season with his team and Lando
knowing that, at the end of the year,
they're gonna part ways.
It could be very difficult for him.
Shall we go?
Let's go.
Last year, I'm very happy
with my success at McLaren.
- Yes!
- Wow!
- Great job, mate.
- Can't believe it, guys.
It's probably been
my strongest year in F1,
so it makes me feel proud and happy.
That's good.
Mulligan. How bad.
Fore left.
Ah!
Carlos has achieved
so many things in Formula 1.
Especially this last year.
I'm very proud of him.
- Let's go.
- Advantage Jon Rahm.
No, I am Jon Rahm.
Who do you want to be?
Choose.
Today, I am...
Rickie Fowler.
It will be hard
to leave McLaren next year,
but I think being a Ferrari driver
is one of the most special things
in Formula 1.
It's on the checklist
of pretty much every driver.
I've got the opportunity to do it.
This part is very tense.
Come on!
I believe that
Carlos will achieve many great things.
Good shot.
- Did it cross over?
- Yeah.
But Formula 1 is a tough business
and Carlos has seen some tough times.
Nice look at birdie.
Oi! Gentlemen!
Rickie Fowler has just messed up.
He needs to make sure he keeps focused
and he will not have any problem
to find his way to the top.
You should have been Ian Poulter.
Carlos got the opportunity
to go to Ferrari.
But this is a business,
so we'll have to get on with it.
I think,
looking back over the last week,
it's sad to see Carlos going.
But the media, definitely, um,
I think the Seb news was the thing
that took them by surprise.
Mm.
How Seb divorced Ferrari,
that's not very pretty. I think...
Carlos has been doing...
We did agree,
"Let's get a few interviews done."
"We know people are asking about Ferrari,
but let's get interviews out of the way."
So, by the time we get to Austria,
that story's now covered,
we can get back to racing
and he can talk about the rest of the year
with us, which is what he wants.
He's leaving McLaren.
How is this working relationship
even going to continue,
with McLaren knowing
that Sainz is going to Ferrari?
What's going on, dude?
- Hey, Mr. Brown. What's happening?
- How are you?
- Good to see you. Yeah. All good.
- Good.
I, uh, I talked to Carlos earlier.
It's strange also for the team.
We discussed it also with Tom already.
Uh, obviously knowing that he's leaving
at the end of the year,
so at some point the normal rules
of engagement will come into...
into action
with not giving him all the information
anymore etc..
When somebody is leaving
to go and race for a rival,
you don't want them to take
all of the knowledge
that you are going to try and use
to beat that team with in the future.
So, yeah, it's... it's only normal
that a racing driver starts
to get marginalized in his own team
when it's already known
that he's off to a rival.
Austria is a stunning country.
Styria is a wonderful place to be.
And, for the first time,
we have the Styrian Grand Prix.
But, today, it's pouring with rain.
I can't see this drying out
in the near future.
- Everyone good?
- Yeah. You?
Yeah, good.
Do you think that McLaren
will get a podium finish?
I hope so. I hope so.
We're gonna give it a go.
We did it last time.
- If anyone gets it, it might be this guy.
- Lando!
- Hello.
- You're way more excited to see him.
Lando!
Lando came out of the gates,
uh, very strong
and he had an, uh, awesome first race,
and I'm... I'm very proud.
See ya.
He showed a tremendous amount
of speed, a lot of racecraft.
Everything that we said,
"Here's what 2020 needs to look like."
- Hello.
- Tony, show Lando your car!
Nice.
I've had a very good start to 2020,
scoring my first podium in Formula 1
in the first race of the season.
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Yes!
It was a dream start.
Something I never dreamt of,
kind of thing.
I think Lando's success
in the first race
caught everybody by surprise,
especially Carlos.
McLaren's moving
in a new and exciting direction
led by Zak Brown.
I think Lando lies at the heart of it.
Zak loves Lando Norris.
It's almost like
a father-son relationship.
Lando sits at the very center
of everything Zak wants McLaren to be.
It's still incredibly wet out,
but it's now within the bounds
of the drivers to be able to go out.
Lando did a very good first race.
He managed to finish third
and I finished P5.
It actually was very close,
because I was coming from behind
and I had a chance to overtake him
and didn't quite make it stick.
I mean, if I had known it was for
a podium, I think I would have made it.
Myself and Carlos,
we've always had a, a good friendship.
But last year, I was a rookie.
There was a lot of slack.
Whereas this year, I'm pushing him more,
and I guess that's never something
that you wanna see your teammate do.
In 2019,
Lando Norris was in his rookie season.
This year,
Lando's a much more confident racer
than he was.
Green light in two minutes. Two minutes.
My self-confidence as a driver
tells me that I am prepared
to lead this team.
I want to be on top.
They're all trying to get
out there. Vettel is heading the field.
That's one minute now.
Keep me posted on the rain intensity.
Copy, will do.
Green light, and off they go.
Carlos, the radar suggests
this kind of rain for the whole session.
Radar suggests rain should be continuous
and same intensity as this.
Every time it rains
on a Formula 1 track,
you know the whole thing is gonna
go chaotic and it's gonna be a good show.
Oh, and he's spun!
Jesus Christ! Fucking joke, this.
A huge amount of spray
out there. This is really testing.
Whoa!
Fuck.
Carlos is extremely good in the wet.
How smooth he is with the hands,
how he goes on the throttle.
It's unbelievable.
Last lap was P4. Good job, Carlos.
So you'll get three more laps.
Three more laps.
I cannot see a thing.
The Ferrari car's
about a second a lap slower than it was
at this circuit last year.
- Where are we?
- We finished P10.
I tried.
Lando, you're the ninth car
out on track, Carlos in front.
Yeah, I got traffic from Carlos.
Watch for Lando.
What's the rain doing?
The radar suggests
it will get worse through the session.
It's definitely more wet now.
Look how treacherous
the conditions are!
Conditions are getting
pretty bad again.
Yep, okay. Understood.
Be careful.
Oh! Lando Norris
just locking up a bit into turn 1.
Can't see anything.
Not gonna improve.
Okay, Lando.
You qualified in sixth.
- I should've done more.
- Points come tomorrow, mate.
- You've got one lap.
- Let's keep pushing.
Here's Sainz on an impressive lap.
Keep pushing this lap.
Copy.
Sainz next to cross the line. What a lap!
Carlos Sainz will start third on the grid
for McLaren
in a brilliant qualifying performance
from the Spaniard.
Vamos!
You're P3, Carlos. P3.
Bravo, bravo, bravo!
- Vamos! Come on!
- Come on!
One of those laps
that I will remember forever.
It takes big cojones to do a lap like that
in the wet, definitely. Definitely.
Glorious sound
of engines beginning to rev
echoing around the hills here.
The rain has gone away.
It's a glorious day here in Spielberg.
- Hi. How are you?
- Hello.
I'm good. And you okay?
You're in charge today.
So, go get 'em!
Lewis Hamilton,
the first man
to take at least one pole
in 14 consecutive seasons.
He starts on pole position,
and alongside him, Max Verstappen,
who's on the front row, second on
the grid, for the third consecutive race.
Behind these two, on row two,
Carlos Sainz of McLaren,
third on the grid for the second...
It'll be close.
Renault, McLaren, Racing Point,
fighting for positions.
We look forward to this one.
They spur each other on,
don't they? Fighting it out.
They do.
Carlos, more experienced than Lando.
When it comes down to it,
they're very serious individuals,
and they both want to beat each other
so badly.
You can see the desire to beat each other
has gone up some.
So it's a very, very healthy, uh, rivalry.
But you never wanna favor drivers.
On track, the frustrations
are going to be more pronounced
when the fight between them
is as close as it is.
Will Carlos still be the top dog
at McLaren, as he was in 2019?
- Okay, Carlos, radio check.
- Yeah, radio's good.
It's all got quite serious this year.
I think it's game on.
Good start, Carlos. P3.
High-speed section was good.
I'm happy
where I am at the moment.
Copy.
The two Ferraris,
Sebastian Vettel
and Charles Leclerc, make contact!
I got pushed aside.
What the hell?
Box, box.
Sebastian Vettel,
first retirement of the race.
Caution, debris.
Be careful.
Copy.
We can go racing again.
Let's get back to the battle out in front.
Carlos Sainz in third place.
Next car behind is Lando.
Gap to Lando, 2.5.
Carlos, if he gets to one second,
we're gonna consider team orders.
Look, the two McLarens
are gonna have a little tussle as well.
Lando, keep close on Carlos.
Gap to Carlos, 1.3.
Lando, I need you to get closer.
Gap to Carlos, one second.
- Can I push? We should go racing.
- Carlos, we have to let him go.
Lando, he'll get out of your way.
He just turned in on me.
What's he trying to do?
Lando, just be mindful.
Just be mindful.
Okay, Carlos, no fight with Lando.
Team decision.
Fucking hell.
Anytime that we need
to let the other driver through,
it's only because we think
that's the faster car.
Appreciate it, guys.
Instead of it being me
having to let him go
and sacrifice my race in some ways,
uh, it's been the opposite way around,
and I've been the one
in the, the prime position.
We're on the final lap.
There goes Lando Norris,
round the outside.
Norris could take this.
Norris is past the Racing Point!
Come on!
Oh, it's a tight finish!
It's a photo finish!
P5.
Whoa!
What a race. What a race!
Lando Norris, what a grandstand finish.
Yes, Lando! Yes!
Yeah, boys!
That is racing, mate.
That is racing. Well done.
What must Carlos Sainz be thinking?
He had to give up his position
to Lando Norris.
Ferrari are lagging, to say the least.
He's obviously gonna move to the Scuderia.
Can't back out now, can you?
The team let Lando overtake me. So, uh,
I am pretty angry right now.
I don't really show
a lot of anger and rage,
mainly because
I'm not that kind of character.
At some point, I always end up,
I don't know, throwing a glove
or just a small gesture.
If I do some kind of that,
it shows that I'm really, really angry.
I just, I'm just taking it inside.
- Where am I sitting? There?
- Oh! Damn!
- Just dried his seat for him.
- He's contaminated it.
He's actually just injured me, mate.
Uh, yeah?
Let me see. Can I take care of it?
- Shut up.
- Can I massage it?
Just get to Ferrari already, mate.
In some ways, it's already kinda started,
the little bit of a tail-off,
um, with him obviously going
to Ferrari next year.
Carlos, one. Lando, zero.
Thing is I'm gonna do something to him,
and he's gonna get real...
- I never get angry with you.
- Yeah, you do.
- No, I'm not...
- You do.
There's never hard feelings.
Last year, Carlos and Lando
had this... had this real bromance,
and that's very rare in Formula 1.
This year is very different.
Have you guys missed each other?
- Not at all?
- No.
Yeah, the gloves are off
between those two.
It's the Hungarian Grand Prix.
And it's lights out, and away we go.
Sainz has pitted.
It's an awful stop.
What is going on? He's lost so much time.
- Oh my God.
- Sainz finishes ninth.
That's the checkered flag.
Not quite the race we wanted.
Verstappen gets away well.
Sainz is making a move on Norris.
A lot of vibration on the car.
I don't know why.
Carlos Sainz, and he's got tire problems.
Whoa, puncture. Puncture.
Sainz's tire's gone.
- Fuck!
- We'll have to box.
Fuck.
Norris is fifth.
- Good race.
- Well done.
What a grandstand finish.
Unbelievable.
I'm starting to get frustrated
because nothing seems to go right
for me at the moment.
Carlos Sainz,
heading out onto the grid.
There's some smoke
coming out of the car.
Yeah. Box, box. Something broke.
Something big.
Carlos, that's, uh, dead.
You can get out.
When you have
that sort of failure,
where you're not even able to compete
or to start a race, um...
It's lights out,
and away we go.
They weren't held for long.
Hamilton, away well.
...it's the biggest disappointment.
- Lando Norris in 11th.
- I feel very down at the moment.
This, the scrap
for the final points place.
And upset.
I've lost 30 or more points this year.
At the press conference,
they always ask...
They always ask me what car I drive.
They say, "Pagani? Porsche? Ferrari?"
"McLaren?"
"McLaren." And I say, "Golf!"
Every professional athlete needs
their own time.
My family has always been next to me.
It's where I feel the most comfortable.
Come on.
Let's get going quick no?
- Come on.
- It's windy, isn't it?
He doesn't want
to spend much time stretching.
When he's here,
in a way, he's recharging batteries.
You ready?
The life
of the Formula 1 driver is not easy.
Motorsport is like that.
Motorsport is up and down.
And to have somebody you know
you can trust is, uh, super crucial.
Okay.
Terrible!
When things go wrong,
you need to be honest with yourself.
Learn from the bad things,
and if you need to cry, you cry,
but learn, make the mistakes,
trust in your talent, trust in your ideas,
trust the way you want to do things.
You suddenly start to think
in a different way on a few things,
and then you are changing your approach.
You change as a person, you know,
and then, suddenly,
you make a step in your career.
You must try to analyze,
and then turn the page, fully committed,
fully concentrated in the next race.
I think it's the right approach.
Good morning, everybody.
It's the Italian Grand Prix,
and here we are at Monza.
This is the temple of speed,
and the home of Ferrari.
Speeds today
in excess of 215 miles an hour.
The streets, usually adorned
with thousands
of Ferrari's passionate fans,
or Tifosi,
as they're affectionately called.
This year, mostly watching
from the safety of their own homes.
You can see how passionate they are.
There's a hotel close to the track
a lot of drivers stay at.
You can see, there was evidence
of a lot of them standing there
trying to get a glimpse of their heroes.
Hey, guys.
Grazie.
See you there.
Ooh, Tifosi!
Wave at them.
Ferrari is known
for having that extra pressure.
It's nearly like a religion here in Italy.
We're gonna have a lot of time
and a lot of opportunities.
Thank you so much.
Tifosi, the media, everyone
is expecting Ferrari to be winning.
If they're not winning, there's pressure.
- Buongiorno.
- Ciao.
Go ahead.
I think that adds
a bit more pressure to the drivers.
Ferrari! Ferrari! Ferrari!
In Monza,
I think,
if you have any affiliation with Ferrari,
whether you're a current driver
or going to be there,
there's probably, uh,
an increased intensity to it.
- Carlos!
- Hi.
Carlos probably feels
a little bit of the pressure.
He's soon gonna be a Ferrari driver,
so that puts a big spotlight on you.
But, uh, for sure,
Lando's performance this year,
and, uh, Carlos's bad luck along the way,
won't be, uh, putting him
in the happiest of moods at all times.
- Macchiato. There's the tea.
- Thank you very much. Thank you.
So, compared to Lando,
this was his fastest through turn one,
compared to our fastest from turn one.
You can see he's challenging the fronts
just as much in this phase.
But his style is that he won't extend
holding the brake here.
Because he always just programs himself to
come off the brakes the same each corner.
It's just the subtle difference
in that he's got the tow here.
You've not quite got it.
We're not asking you
to adopt Lando's approach to the braking.
- It's how we optimize your approach.
- Yeah.
I think any time things don't go your way
for a driver, you get disappointed.
It's a... It's a very emotional,
passionate, uh, sport.
There's times
the drivers make some mistakes.
My father taught me
to be hard-working,
to have the right attitude.
Without hard work, dedication,
it's pretty much impossible
to get to where you want.
Carlos desperately needs
a good race.
He knows the Tifosi will welcome him
with open arms
if he can have a great race in Italy.
Every time you arrive to a track,
you know you are gonna be
part of their family next year.
That feeling is difficult to explain.
And it's part of why I'm so excited
about going to Ferrari.
All 20 drivers on the grid
have a similar level of talent that I do.
So there's only two things then that
you can control, which is your fitness,
but also be as mentally well-prepared
and self-confident as you can.
- You were fastest last lap.
- Copy.
Carlos Sainz is steaming along.
How quickly can he get through the pack?
Carlos Sainz is looking
to make up a place around the outside.
Come on!
Nice job.
These key overtakes
could be critical for the podium,
or even the win.
Carlos, you can be patient with Räikkönen.
You can be patient.
Carlos Sainz
is going for it with Kimi Räikkönen,
who gives him enough space,
and Sainz moves up into second place!
This is a very strong position for McLaren
as it stands at the moment.
Sebastian Vettel down in 17th,
and under pressure from George Russell.
The Ferraris
are going a little bit backwards now.
And Sebastian Vettel goes
straight through the polystyrene blocks.
Brake line exploded.
Oh dear, oh dear.
Just going from bad to worse.
What a dismal season
poor old Seb is having.
That's Charles Leclerc!
And that is a very big accident.
My goodness, Ferrari. What is going on?
What a horrible, horrible
Italian Grand Prix for the Scuderia.
How tight
is that Ferrari contract?
Looking like a brilliant
afternoon if you're a McLaren fan.
Carlos, this is good. Pace is good.
Guys, we could get both cars on
the podium, so let's get working together.
Carlos Sainz departs the McLaren team
to go and join Ferrari.
How he would love to go to the Scuderia
as a race winner.
He has a lot of pace.
The gap is 4.3.
This is still on. This is still on.
Okay, okay, okay.
Carlos Sainz is now charging him down.
We need to be patient. Come on.
They will get there.
Carlos Sainz,
he's got his dad's winning mentality.
You can do this, mate.
Keep your head cool.
I want this win, Tom.
He's fucking fast. Come on.
Five laps to go. Five laps.
Gap, 2.8.
Gap every lap.
Copy, 1.7.
Woo!
Sainz is tantalizingly close now.
Come on!
Three laps to go, Carlos.
Maximum focus now.
- No mistakes.
- Copy.
- C'mon!
- Go on!
Come on!
It is last lap shenanigans here at Monza.
- Come on!
- Go on, lad!
We've got DRS
onboard the McLaren. It'll be very close.
Jesus Christ! Come on!
It's going all the way down to the wire.
And look at that!
Sliding through the Ascari chicane.
It's like watching his father
doing rallying,
but we're watching Carlos Sainz
in Formula 1.
He's given it absolutely everything.
Carlos Sainz comes home
for second place,
and what a great fight he gave.
P2, buddy.
Great work, mate. Great work.
I am a big fan of your work.
Oh!
Thank you, guys.
We tried our best, I think.
Thank you. Amazing weekend.
I'm actually very, very happy, and...
Um, yeah, particularly proud
of what I have achieved.
I think there is a part of Carlos
that probably
would love to stay at McLaren.
In second place, Carlos Sainz!
Ferrari, last year,
they were still podium contenders.
Now, you would say,
in some of the races, they've been
seventh-best team.
And you would say
it's one of the worst decisions
you could possibly make.
He probably is regretting it.
Um, even if he says he's not,
he probably is.
Already starting to feel
what it's gonna be like next year,
and that is a feeling that no one's
gonna be able to take away from me.
Going to Ferrari, it's something that...
It's impossible to regret.
How much are you gonna miss him
when he moves to Ferrari next year?
Say it. Yes, you're gonna miss me.
Say it now.
- You can't force me to say it.
- Yeah. Say it.
When I'm passing him on the racetrack,
I can wave at him.
Can't find a team.
- Everyone is booked?
- Yeah.
Big weekend
for many drivers who come into this race
uncertain of their futures.
They say sportsmen die twice.
Once when you lose your career...
- Will you be here next year?
- Don't know.
It's bad luck.
...and once at the actual end.
There's a big incident. Red flag.
- Who is it?
- Has he got out?
A very, very nasty crash.