I think, realistically, for 2019 and 2020,
I'd be surprised if Mercedes' dominance
didn't continue.
Those are the guys
who are always at the top.
[Claire Williams] It's very difficult
for teams that don't have the budget
the bigger teams do.
How can a team like ours
really necessarily compete?
[Christian Horner] Mercedes are
our biggest competitor.
They're the team
that are doing the winning at the moment,
so they're the team that we want to beat.
Formula 1 racing
is very much like war planning.
We set our targets,
develop the power unit,
and then deploy it on the field.
We are confident
about what we are able to achieve,
but we must not let one bit of complacency
creep in.
I need many fellow warriors on my journey.
We win and we lose together.
Just take it one by one.
Let's crush them.
My name is Toto Wolff
and I am the team principal
of the Mercedes Petronas
Formula 1 team.
I was an entrepreneur my whole life.
- Hi, mate.
- I'm having these guys all over me
- like you guys.
- [Daniel Ricciardo laughs]
[Toto Wolff] In business,
you can always find excuses.
You can twist the story in your favor.
- [Ricciardo] See you.
- See you.
But in motor racing,
the absolute truth of the stopwatch
will tell you whether you've done
a good enough job or not.
I like the honesty about it.
[beeps]
[engineer 1] Can you make it
back to the pits?
[Wolff] Back in the day, this was a team
that was not winning races.
[bleep]
[engineer 2] Out of the race.
Stop. Stop. Stop.
In the summer of 2012,
Niki Lauda was asked to join the board
and to help steer the team
into a more successful trajectory.
At the same time, Daimler approached me,
whether I was interested
in leading the team.
And this was an offer
that I couldn't turn down.
Niki was one of the greatest
racing drivers that have existed.
He has become a world champion
and then almost died
in a race car accident.
Half his body burned.
Overcoming his own pain, coming back,
winning a world championship
made him very strong.
[Niki Lauda] Winning is one thing,
but out of losing, I always learned more.
Because you don't waste time
blaming somebody else.
Analyze yourself,
change yourself to be successful.
[William Buxton] Niki Lauda's role in the
success of Mercedes cannot be overstated
because Niki had the ability
to make things happen.
Even though he'd stopped racing,
he was such a racer.
Niki was a key element
in convincing me to join the team.
If it wasn't for Niki
picking up the phone and calling him...
Lewis, I don't think,
would ever have considered moving.
That's Niki. That's his power.
[reporter] We are here
for the 2012 Japanese Grand Prix.
All the talk in the paddock right now
revolves around Lewis Hamilton
and his move to Mercedes.
In 2013, the tide changed
and we started to become more competitive.
We were a regular challenger
for race wins and podiums.
[crowd cheering]
Just wanna say a big thank you
to my fans.
Hey!
- You happy, right?
- Absolutely.
Having had success, been a world champion,
he understands what it's like
to have the pressure in that car.
He is one of the power units
behind the team's success.
[commentator] That's five world
championships in a row for Mercedes.
An amazing achievement.
[Wolff] Over the years that Niki
and I have been in teams together,
what started as a joint journey
among colleagues
has developed into a friendship.
[anchor 1] The world of sport
is mourning the death of Niki Lauda.
[anchor 2] The three-time champion leaves
a legacy in his sport like no other.
[anchor 3] Niki will forever be
in our hearts and enshrined in history.
[host] Good morning, Toto.
Good morning.
As you can imagine, this is, uh,
very difficult.
Um, very difficult for the team,
for all of us.
[indistinct chatter]
Uh, I keep looking at the pictures...
and, um...
find myself with tears in the eyes
every half an hour...
because he's not there anymore.
That is somebody that is so dearly missed
in this team,
and dearly missed in Formula 1.
I feel that we have lost what was
the heart and soul of Formula 1.
[Hamilton] I miss having
conversations with him.
I got to visit Niki.
We spoke a lot. We were sending videos
to each other when he was in hospital.
I was just trying to send him
positive messages,
just to keep his spirits up.
He would send me back messages
on his high and his low days.
[Hamilton] We're gonna
lose this race, Bono.
I can't keep the car behind.
He was with us in spirit, still is.
[commentator] Hamilton wins
the Monaco Grand Prix.
[Wolff] Lewis, that was a victory worth
Niki. Unbelievable job, congratulations.
[Hamilton] That was definitely for Niki.
I really was fighting
with the spirit of Niki.
Niki's been such an influential person
in our team,
helping us get to where we are, so...
I know he'll be, uh, looking down
and I know he'll take his hat off today.
So, I was just trying to stay focused
and trying to make him proud.
And, uh, we're gonna try to continue that
through the year.
[crowd cheering]
Niki's loss will have hurt Mercedes.
And with this kind of a gut punch, yeah,
the question will be asked
of how much it will affect the team
this season.
[crowd cheering]
[indistinct chatter]
[Wolff] Because it's
the German Grand Prix,
we wanna do particularly well here
because of our home crowd.
- [announcer talking indistinctly]
- [crowd cheering]
[announcer speaks German]
- [camera shutter clicks]
- [indistinct conversation]
Oh, yeah.
I'm the one-eyed
amongst the blind here, no?
[Guenther Steiner] You're the most
important one, though, so...
you can be late.
[chuckles]
So arrogant.
Be a bit more intelligent today
than normal.
- What?
- Be more intelligent today.
I'm always intelligent.
You don't get the humor.
[in German] You can speak German.
I know that you're married
to an English woman,
but you can speak German to me.
[Wolff] But you have less oxygen
up in the mountains.
[Steiner] Yes, but then, when we come
down, we are the best runners.
[host in English] Welcome to the
Friday press conference
ahead of the 2019 German Grand Prix.
[camera shutters clicking]
[in German] How do you put this on?
You're really stupid
if you can't manage to do that.
You've been here a thousand times.
[in English] Even the guy from
the mountains knows how to put it on.
The only one not is Toto,
so that proves a point.
[journalist] Toto, if I could start
with you, please.
You're celebrating 125 years
in motorsport.
What would it mean to win this race,
given that you also have
the title sponsorship?
We're having a dedicated livery,
we're wearing
a different team kit tomorrow
and lots of activities are on the track.
But on the other side,
it's 25 points that are as many points
as on any other given circuit
and we just need to add
another good race performance
in order to make a step
towards a championship.
- [Wolff] You okay?
- [engineer] Yeah, you?
You never know what's around the corner,
but at the moment,
everything seems all right.
That'll do for now.
That'll do for the next 20 minutes.
[Wolff] Yeah.
[Horner] We won the championship
four years in a row.
2010 to end of 2013.
Then Mercedes have won it
every single year since then.
They're rivals.
They're the team that we want to beat.
[tools whirring and drilling]
[Wolff] For me,
there is 1,600 superstars in Mercedes.
But the strengths of the team,
it's every single individual.
I cannot drive the car.
I am not able to design
an aerodynamic surface.
But I try to understand everything
around the guy who can.
And I try to provide a framework
for these individuals
to perform at their best.
[technician] What was your other question?
The other question
was in terms of the upgrade package.
[Hamilton] Even though
we're relatively fast,
the front end is really, really weak...
[Wolff] I think the best Formula 1 drivers
have some common traits.
Talent, nurture...
and adversity...
and overcoming the adversity,
and this is the single most important
ingredient I have seen.
[Hamilton] I remember how hard
my parents worked.
They sacrificed everything they have,
so when I get in the car, I...
I don't want to squander
what they worked for.
Right, any questions?
Drivers okay?
All right, thanks, everyone.
[Wolff] We have the challenge
of managing two drivers within the team.
Lewis is the best racing driver
of his generation
with five world championship titles.
Valtteri is
an extremely talented, uh, racing driver.
He's performing on a very high level.
[Valtteri Bottas] To be in the same team
with Lewis,
to be honest,
sometimes it's a pain in the ass,
because he's pretty quick. [chuckles]
You know, he's tough to beat.
It was a very conscious decision
to take Valtteri on board.
[Bottas] There was many
difficult things to accept
in terms of in which kind of role
I had to be in the team,
in more like a supportive role.
But it's difficult.
The only thing I want to do as a driver
is win the race.
When Lewis beats me...
it's like turning a knife in me.
People can think whatever they want.
I'm here to win.
[engines revving]
[commentator] Mercedes celebrating
125 years in motorsport.
The team decided to go back to 1954,
their first-ever Formula 1 Grand Prix
and deck the team out in '50s gear.
It looks brilliant.
[Wolff] It's a long history
and a long tradition,
so we are getting dressed up.
We are not celebrating a lot normally.
It's the first time that I can remember
that we are making such an effort
for one single event
in terms of the extra activities.
[in German] I get scared
when I see you. [laughs]
[Wolff] I'm a Mafia boss.
[speaks German and chuckles]
[in German] We are dressed up today
in 1950s outfits,
a tribute to 125 years of motorsport
and we're walking around like a carnival.
[presenter] There are lots
of Lewis fans here, of course.
He doesn't feel well.
Can you enlighten us?
Is it dehydration, or what is it?
Yeah, he's really not feeling well.
There is a virus
making the rounds in the paddock,
which he has caught.
[in English] It's not like man flu,
it's real.
I said to him
that if he doesn't feel well,
he can easily skip the briefings
and go in the motorhome.
[Hamilton] Burning up.
Shit, it's too hot in here.
As a racing driver, you can't ever be ill
on the race weekend,
you always have to arrive 100%.
But I had a fever of 40 degrees.
I was just feeling weak. I was...
Massive sweats.
I was barely sleeping.
[Buxton] Qualifying sets the grid
for Sunday,
so any driver being ill
is an issue for a team,
but especially
when it's your lead driver
and the guy gunning
for a world championship.
Obviously, they've got Valtteri
and the reserve driver, Esteban Ocon,
but going into your 200th Grand Prix,
your 125th anniversary,
you want your lead driver there,
fighting fit and leading your charge.
[Bono] Lewis, how you getting on?
Relatively speaking.
[Hamilton] Yeah, it's...
[Hamilton breathing heavily]
Qualifying's a fast-paced
hundred-meter sprint.
High-intensity, high focused,
highly charged.
It's all about being calm, composed
and centered,
but I'm getting in the car,
body's feeling sore,
my heart is racing.
[Hamilton] Just give me normal gloves.
They won't fit on.
[Wolff] Lewis, hi, this is Toto.
I've opened the channel. Tell me.
[Hamilton] It's just a long run.
Don't... don't feel great.
But, uh...
I'm okay to drive.
Good to go.
[Bono] Okay, good man.
[commentator] Lewis Hamilton, he must be
looking over his shoulder a little bit.
The young guns,
Max Verstappen, Charles Leclerc,
are really getting their act together.
So far, he's had an answer to everything.
[engine revving]
[commentator 1] Verstappen
across the line.
He's quickest at the moment.
But Charles Leclerc
is going quicker than Verstappen
by 3.5 tenths of a second.
[Bono] Lewis, you're all clear behind.
[commentator] Lewis Hamilton
begins his first lap.
[commentator 2] That's a horrible first
sector for Lewis Hamilton.
He took a lot of curb
on the way into turn one
and I think that threw him slightly wide.
[Hamilton] I got traffic on my lap.
[Bono] Copy.
[commentator 1] Lewis Hamilton,
13th fastest.
And that is not gonna be good enough.
He's going to have to go
way faster than that.
[Hamilton] How far was I off there?
[Bono] I'd say, in terms of sectors,
to Leclerc, it's 4.5, sector one,
6.5, sector two, and 4.5, sector three.
[Hamilton] It's difficult to put
into terms just how hard it is.
You're chasing milliseconds.
But as a kid, I always knew that
if I just work harder than everyone else,
I should be able
to achieve something extraordinary.
And that's how I've been wired.
[Hamilton] I'll see how much
I can catch up.
[commentator 2]
Hamilton's going faster now.
[Hamilton] Am I in trouble?
[Bono] Negative.
Currently P3, six tenths to Leclerc, P1.
Okay, Lewis, you're good to go.
[commentator 1] Max Verstappen
is the challenger to the Mercedes.
[Bono] Lewis, keep the pace up.
[commentator 2] Hamilton very quick,
fastest of the weekend so far.
[commentator 1] And Lewis Hamilton
is on provisional pole.
So, here come the challengers.
Valtteri Bottas first.
Crosses the line. Can't beat his teammate.
Hamilton,
will he be beaten by Max Verstappen?
No!
[Bono] Get in there, Lewis.
That's the one, mate.
[commentator 2] Hamilton was half a second
faster than Bottas.
Max Verstappen splitting the two Mercedes.
Lewis, this is Toto.
You never stop to amaze us.
Congratulations.
[Hamilton] Thank you, Toto.
Good job, guys.
I don't know how we did that one,
but grateful for all the hard work.
[commentator 1] In their 200th Formula 1
Grand Prix start,
Mercedes will be starting
on pole position.
[presenter] Congratulations
to the top three qualifiers
for the 2019 German Grand Prix.
Starting in third place
will be Valtteri Bottas,
in second, Max Verstappen,
and taking the 87th pole of his career
and his fourth of 2019,
our pole-sitter, Lewis Hamilton.
[journalist] Question for Max.
So, Max, you're starting second tomorrow
and do you think, tomorrow,
you can have...
[Hamilton] Each year, it's a new challenge
from different people.
[Max Verstappen] Yeah, I believe
that normally, in the race,
we are always
a little bit more competitive.
Of course,
I'm starting on different tires...
[Hamilton] All these drivers
are incredibly talented.
It's small percentages between us all.
[Verstappen] Yeah, we're working hard
on it, and I'm pretty pleased about today.
[Hamilton] It's easier to chase
than it is to lead.
All I can do is just put all my energy
into that car.
- [camera shutter clicks]
- [indistinct chatter in German]
[Wolff] Formula 1 is a hostile environment
that will judge you every single day
and that gives it
a huge intensity and pressure.
And on the free evenings,
you want to leave the hostilities
of the paddock behind.
Most of the evenings,
it was Niki and myself.
We would always travel together.
I lost a friend when he died.
Niki was particular, you know,
when you get in the car.
I guess we are the same.
All that needs to be
in the central position.
Twenty-two degrees.
All these little things in the middle,
then Niki was happy.
Being able to have a dinner together,
which we had every single day
on the racetrack,
is a safe environment that I miss.
I think about our friendship
every single day.
I miss having an ally,
having a sparring partner, a spokesperson
in the paddock.
Since Niki's not around anymore,
it feels different.
I miss him so much.
[Ted Kravitz] Yes! Wet race!
I've been waiting all year for this.
This is fantastic.
[crowd cheering]
They always say rain is the big equalizer
in Formula 1,
because your equipment
doesn't matter so much anymore.
It's all down to feel.
And where you can find the grip
around the track.
[Wolff] When the weather changes,
it is what makes motor racing excited
because it gives it a certain sense
of vulnerability.
It's not always the quickest car
and quickest driver wins the race.
[tools drilling]
[Horner] A bit of patience
in this weather.
[Verstappen] Yeah, and...
good communication.
[Horner] Absolutely.
Just keep us informed.
- You see more than we do on the pit wall.
- [Verstappen] Yeah.
- [Horner] Dutch weather!
[Horner] I have a feeling that if we
can put a bit of pressure on Mercedes,
I think that they could be exposed.
That makes the dynamic,
you know, quite interesting.
[Horner] I hope that we get
an exciting race.
I'd love to see Verstappen and Hamilton
have a good fight.
- Good race.
- That's a good one, yeah.
[Wolff] This is a sport
that is so intense.
It is about delivering 21 times
every single year
against the best competitors.
We are only as good as our last race.
[Hamilton] The biggest challenge
for a racing driver
is punching out results
weekend after weekend.
Not making mistakes.
[Bono] Lewis, in terms of the radar,
we think it's gonna be more of the same.
So, light rain
for the next 30 to 60 minutes.
My approach is always one race at a time
because you don't know what's ahead,
so you just focus on what's
in front of you in the present.
[engineer] One minute.
Fifteen seconds.
[engines revving]
[commentator 1] Hamilton gets away
pretty well, but Verstappen is struggling.
[tires screeching]
[Hamilton] It's still slippery
as hell, man.
[commentator 1] Oh, there's a spin.
It's Sergio Perez.
[Sergio Perez] Sorry, guys.
[commentator 1] Huge amount of spray.
This is really testing.
[Bono] Lewis, Valtteri is the car behind
and a gap to Verstappen.
[commentator 2] Verstappen
in his pursuit now of Bottas.
[indistinct commotion]
[engineer] Just be patient, Max.
[Bono] Lewis, let us know
if you think it's ready for dry tires.
[Hamilton] Because you're doing
200 miles an hour,
it's really hard to see
if the track is dry or wet.
I'm okay for now.
These tires are knackered, though.
You go to turn six, it's raining heavily,
you go to turn two, it's dry.
[Bono] And we have rain in the pit lane.
[commentator 2] Oh! That is Carlos Sainz.
It's still raining.
[commentator 1]
Here's Verstappen losing it.
[Verstappen] Fuck's sake!
[commentator 1]
Oh! And Leclerc's gone off!
[Charles Leclerc] Fuck!
[commentator 2] Hamilton is the
race leader, cruising out in front.
[Bono] Looks good now.
Valtteri six seconds behind,
Verstappen 7.2.
[Hamilton] Box, I lost the frickin' wing.
[Bono] Yeah, coming in.
[Hamilton] How bad is the damage
to the car?
[Bono] Uh, we need to have a look.
Lewis coming in. He needs a front wing.
[man 1] No, it's Lewis here.
Drive through.
Seventy-six.
[Hamilton] You need to hurry up. I'm here.
[man 1] Don't put these tires on, guy.
Front wing off, please.
[man 2] Seventy-six.
[man 3] Set 16 for Lewis, set 16.
- [man 1] Lift it up.
- [man 2] Wing change.
[Hamilton] Come on, let's go.
Average pit-stop length in Formula 1
is about two seconds.
[Hamilton] Time to get out.
[man 1 talks indistinctly]
So, a minute is a year
in Formula 1 terms.
[commentator 1] Finally, he pulls away
after a minute spent in the pit lane.
[Hamilton] Then I got back going
and your confidence
really takes a beating.
And then it's really hard
to build it back up.
[commentator 2] There is the Renault
of Nico Hulkenberg.
This is one of the craziest races.
[commentator 1] Max Verstappen
has retaken the lead.
[commentator 2] Stroll's second,
Kvyat's third.
[Hamilton] What position
have I dropped back to?
[Bono] Unfortunately, Lewis,
you dropped back to position 12.
[commentator 2] Hamilton got some
catching to do.
[commentator 1] Game on
in the last 16 laps.
I don't think
I've ever been a great loser.
Or great in defeat.
It's just in my DNA.
[commentator 2] Hamilton pushing hard.
[Bono] You were purple sector
three last lap.
Okay, so push, push.
[tires screeching]
[commentator 2] Oh! He just keeps it out
of the wall there, Hamilton!
If a team make a mistake,
it is kind of out of your hands,
but if you've practiced and practiced
and you've put so much focus and effort in
and then you drop the ball...
[commentator 1] A rare error.
...oh, it's really hard to deal with.
[Hamilton] Retire the car.
[Bono] Negative, Lewis, negative.
There's always opportunities.
[Wolff] We must never give up,
even if the situation looks desperate,
because even if
it's just about collecting a single point,
that can make a difference
to a championship.
[Bono] So, Lewis is out of the points.
We're fighting for P2. Come on.
[Buxton] All of the team's hopes
now sit with Valtteri
to bring home the result they want
on their 200th Grand Prix.
In that moment,
you know you have a great chance.
[Bono] Come on, Valtteri.
It's critical to get through.
It always makes you push even harder.
You know you have a great opportunity
to get some big points.
[crashes]
[commentator 2] And that's Bottas!
Bottas has put it in the wall!
[in German] Fuck! How is this possible?
[Bono in English] Everything okay,
Valtteri?
[Bottas] Yeah, I'm all good.
I'm sorry, guys.
In turn one, there was this one dry line.
I must have gone in
just a tiny bit too quickly.
Obviously,
we are speaking about millimeters.
I just drifted onto the damp part
on the outside.
Immediately, I knew...
there wouldn't be really a way
to catch it.
I knew that was it.
I wasted one of the big opportunities
for the title.
There's so many team members
that are giving their absolute everything
and with one single mistake of one driver,
you can lose it all.
[Bono] Valtteri's just gone off
at turn one.
[Hamilton] How's it gone this bad?
[commentator 2] It has not gone well
for the Mercedes team today.
We lost the race
because we weren't good enough.
Our racing wasn't good enough.
[commentator 2] And it's fireworks
and flames for Max Verstappen,
the winner of the German Grand Prix.
[Horner] Well done, guys.
Fucking mega!
[all cheering]
That was terrible today.
[man] It was more than terrible.
[Wolff] Catastrophic.
What did you say?
I couldn't hear you.
A tough day at the office?
No, it was a total crap, fucking shit,
awful day at the office.
Not a tough day at the office.
When you screw up,
you want to identify the person.
It's how the human mind works.
But we have a no-blame culture.
We blame the problem
rather than the person,
which is easier said than done.
- [journalist] That was not easy, right?
- No.
[journalist] What went wrong?
[Wolff] It all went wrong.
[host] Okay.
Who would like to take the first question?
Toto, just how embarrassing
is this for you?
Home race for the team,
having Netflix here,
you know, you've got the outfits...
Everything was poised for the celebration,
but you've ended up with a car in 11th
and a car in the kitty litter.
Can't be too good.
[Wolff] You want to have a headline
for The Sun from me?
I'm not gonna give you a headline.
[journalist] I'll do that, don't worry.
Yeah, I know.
Um, it was a terrible day for us.
Should I actually respond to you
when you give me such an answer?
[journalist] Why not?
Um...
Lewis put the car in the wall
and then we made the wrong call
with the tires.
The tires were not ready.
But, uh, yeah, I wouldn't want to pin it
to one bad decision or one incident.
There was a multitude of things
that went wrong.
[Hamilton] I'm really sorry.
[Wolff] No, when we make mistakes,
we all make them together.
[Hamilton] I'm so fucking sorry, man.
Just rolled out that fucking corner.
Fuck.
I think coming in around the bollard
was the right reaction.
You would have lost tons of time
into the lap with a half-broken wing.
We would have made a better tire decision,
that's for sure,
but the reset reaction is coming in.
You just lost your front wing.
I wouldn't beat myself up on that one.
Yeah.
Fuck.
I'm still just baffled...
with how it went from
bad to worse today. And, um...
Yeah.
All I can say is,
just on my behalf, sorry...
for not, uh, pulling through.
[Lauda] Everybody makes mistakes.
Vital mistakes.
For me, this was not a problem.
[Wolff] We need to remember
that Niki would say
that as a team,
you will always have setbacks.
There's not one single team out there
that wins every race.
But the most difficult races,
the most painful events,
are the ones where you learn the most.
At the end, we will learn from it.
We will recover and come out stronger.
[Geri] Who's your favorite driver?
Whoever's winning for us.
Just make sure the car looks like that
at the end of the session, yeah?
Everybody's expecting
to see the Red Bull cars
near the front of the field.
[Pierre Gasly] No!
He needed to come in
and change his underwear, I would think.
We're gonna remove that subject
and put you in place.
- Can you win this weekend?
- Yeah!
You can occasionally kiss if you want.
[Wolff] Everybody expects us to win.
But we need to fight to stay on top.