We're not doing any
exercises that you don't know. All right?
That's important.
So, we get
the central nervous system firing
in sort of a race intensity.
It's really high intensity.
And then the lateral band walk,
we'll do that twice through.
And then we'll go get in the sauna
and shower.
No cameras in this room, though.
You don't want to see
what happens in there.
Let's go!
I think motorsport has been
in my blood since I was a kid.
Power. Up. Power.
I was actually two years old
when I was given my first go-kart.
Power, power, power, power!
Run! Run! Come on. Push, push, push.
My name is Carlos Sainz,
I drive for Renault Sport Formula One.
Faster feet. Come on.
Faster, faster, faster...
Born in Madrid, Spain.
Smash it against the wall.
Come on.
When I was nine years old,
I remember seeing Fernando Alonso
winning the World Championship.
In 2005, I meet Fernando Alonso
in the Spanish Grand Prix.
I remember going back home
and saying to my dad,
"I want to be like Fernando Alonso.
I want to be a Formula One driver."
I hope one day I can add my name
to the list of Spanish drivers
that have won a Formula One race.
Fernando, who will win in
the championship between you and Carlos?
I think, uh, this is difficult to predict,
but, you know,
it depends of our teams a little bit.
But, um, if I have to bet my money,
I will put on McLaren and myself.
What's happening to Carlos Sainz
in his battle with Fernando Alonso?
Sainz has taken
the long way around, onto the gravel.
That's never gonna win out
that particular Spanish duel.
Fernando Alonso is on his way home now!
Fifth place in this race
and what a performance that is!
I think it was definitely a good race,
and we should be proud of that,
but yeah,
I think there is a lot more to come.
Carlos Sainz now
puts Fernando Alonso under pressure...
Is he gonna try and launch one?
He is, down the inside!
Alonso saw him coming.
And there's Carlos Sainz.
But Fernando Alonso got the inside line
and just cuts him off.
Fernando Alonso is my racing hero,
but I really wanna beat him,
because I've been losing against him.
I really want payback.
My view of McLaren
has always been
that they are the best racing team
in the world.
When I got the call to work here,
it was extremely, uh, special.
My name is Zak Brown.
I'm executive director
of McLaren Technology Group.
I've been in motor racing my entire life.
I'm now 46 years old.
We have a lot to offer at McLaren.
We've been absolutely dominant
over the years.
And McLaren
have already broken
just about every record in the book.
To show up every day
and look down the boulevard,
and have the first thing you see
is Niki Lauda's car.
And Ayrton Senna's car.
Ayrton Senna crosses the line.
He is world champion.
We've got thousands of employees
running around here
that all share
the same passion and desire to win.
We've got a massive fan base,
but it's been pretty hard to cheer for us
'cause we've not been anywhere near
racing at the front.
You know, it's been
a difficult five-year run.
-Yeah, take that. Okay.
-Get rid of this...
'cause you're kind of shifting.
This is all drivers.
I felt I could contribute
to making a difference.
We do everything in dollars.
If you're happy for me to flip them
all to dollars...
-put that down on the last page.
-Flip 'em. Flip 'em all to dollars.
-Okay.
-Otherwise it starts becoming a bit...
And so, I wanted
to get into an environment
that I had some work to do,
as opposed to maybe joining
a team that's on the top,
and you've got kind of only one way to go.
Winter testing is
the first opportunity that we get
to see the new cars for this year
out on track.
It's really a first opportunity
for the teams to put their cars
through their paces,
to see if they're as good
as they hope they're gonna be,
if they're as fast as they hope
they're gonna be,
and crucially, if they are reliable.
The stakes have really never been higher
for McLaren.
They are trying to rebuild themselves into
a competitive championship-winning team.
After so many years of disappointment,
if they don't get it right this year,
they're gonna lose their driver.
I think Fernando is
one of the best drivers
in the history of Formula One.
I don't think there is a team
that wouldn't love to have Fernando
in their racing car.
So, to have him stay with us, I think,
is a big vote of confidence
of how he feels we will race this year.
My name is Fernando Alonso.
I am two times world champion
and I race for McLaren.
I have a lot of power on the things
that I may say,
so I feel that responsibility,
that leadership, and I try to guide
the team in the best way possible.
I feel confident this year.
We wanna come out pretty strong
and demonstrate
that we're gonna be back
to our winning ways.
Radio check.
Okay, Fernando.
Yeah, that sounded clear for me.
Winter testing is always a moment
of the year where we are all optimistic.
We have a lot of trust
and faith on the car.
We try to stretch the car, you know,
to the maximum.
Okay, nice work, Fernando.
I need multi-function C2,
position four, please.
Yes, okay.
When I joined the team, we were
fighting for the world championship
and that was a different role
than what we have now,
which is trying to fight back and bring
the team back to the top positions.
Okay, Fernando,
this pace is really good.
Copy.
- Alonso.
-  It is Alonso!
Alonso's had a crash. Well, he's gone off.
A wheel has come off his car.
It's rare
this happens in testing.
It's better that it happens now than
it happens once you get to the first race.
But it's... shall we say,
it's a worrying thing to happen?
Fernando's not gonna be happy.
In Formula One, it's not easy
to hide anything in winter testing.
If we assume that it's like this
for the rest of the day...
Then we go to another plan.
So many people
and so many cameras.
There are a lot of eyes on everyone.
Yeah.
We need to have this?
At this crucial moment?
I don't want to...
Go and handle it. Go.
We are ready for a cracking
2018 Azerbaijan Grand Prix.
The paddock is really
starting to come to life.
I'm excited. Excited to be back here.
Obviously, I'd love to win.
It should be a fun race.
The race that could just
conjure up anything in the next 51 laps.
And you can feel it,
the pressure in the air.
Make sure to be
very clear in your analysis of the tires.
But it's better to have--
Even if one is the best,
it's better to have two optimized
than one that is...
-One and a half?
-Yeah. Not-- Not half for a grand prix.
The electronics...
2018 has to be
a season where Renault
shows that we are progressing...
and for our ambition to be fighting at
the top in a few years' time is credible.
My name is Cyril Abiteboul.
I am Managing Director
of Renault Sport Formula One.
But what's fantastic
is our line-up of drivers.
Carlos and Nico
is one of the strongest in the grid.
-You won't make it...
-No, there was no turning back.
The midfield is extremely tight.
McLaren, right now, uh...
they are our most direct competitor.
If we have the ability to beat them,
it will say a lot about
the progression of Renault.
We need to deliver
what people are expecting from us.
If I don't deliver... I'm fired.
There's always gonna be people
making mistakes in Baku.
For me, it's one of the most
challenging tracks
in Formula One at the moment.
And just a reminder about
the tailwinds in three, four, 15 and 16.
If you stay out of trouble,
you could actually think about
a top five finish.
Radio check.
Yeah, Fernando,
loud and clear for me.
It is the fastest street circuit
in the world and you know
always that gives a lot of adrenaline
for the spectators.
And for drivers as well.
So the cars begin
the formation lap in Baku,
one more chance to warm their tires
and warm their brakes...
It's a very particular track,
because you've got the first sector
that is dominated
by ninety-degree corners.
If you talk to the drivers,
they'll tell you that it's like driving
very, very fast in a cage.
Then you've got sector two,
which is very twisty in the old town.
So, that's very different.
Sector three is pretty much
one corner and a straight.
Okay, Fernando, five seconds to go.
It's a dash down to turn one then,
who's gonna come out on top?
So far, all getting away cleanly.
And there's damage!
Wow, it's full of debris.
There's contact
down into turn two!
Fernando Alonso and Sirotkin
going wheel to wheel.
Oh, no!
There's contact for Fernando Alonso.
Puncture switch.
And Ocon in a collision.
Ocon is out of the race!
Unbelievable.
You take care in corner one, corner two,
and they crash into you.
Fucking stupid!
It's a black flag situation.
What this guy's been doing?
Destroy the complete race.
We had two punctures
and the car was nearly undriveable.
Okay, I need to box.
It was not fair to have that damaged car
on lap one
and not having the possibility
to fight back.
You know, that anger to go back
to the pit lane and change those tires--
You know, the desire of "keep racing".
It was not the moment to retire that car.
I think most drivers
would have parked the car
and wouldn't have even thought
about continuing in the race.
Okay, Fernando, the race isn't over
for us. The race isn't over.
Okay, Carlos, how is the balance?
Yeah, all good.
Here goes Carlos Sainz.
He's up in sixth place.
Tries to go around the outside.
Nothing doing.
At that point in the race,
I really started attacking
and really pushing flat out.
Carlos Sainz. He's on Verstappen's tail.
Brilliant racing from all three drivers.
My name is Carlos Onoro,
I'm Carlos Sainz's manager and his cousin.
I mean, for me,
it's heart attack after heart attack.
Qualifying until the end of the race,
it's like a roller-coaster.
Carlos Sainz looking very racy...
And it means a lot
to be racing against Red Bull
and to be pressuring them.
In a race like Baku where you see
that he's fighting for fourth,
for fifth position, which is not normal,
it's always exciting.
Verstappen might go
down the inside. And he does so!
A podium is always something
that you are aiming for.
The difficulty is that there
are three top teams,
two cars each.
That's already sixth position.
That leaves little room for us,
but who knows?
Maybe there will be
that opportunity for us,
and we need to be sure to seize
that opportunity if it's given.
Sainz swoops
round the outside of Verstappen.
Nice move there
from the driver in the Renault.
Tires are super soft.
I'm starting to degrade a bit
at the rear tires.
I'm going to start losing time
with the Red Bulls.
Okay, so, box this lap.
Box this lap.
Coming.
Carlos Sainz into the pits, then.
He's had to let the Red Bulls go.
The Red Bulls had pulled away.
They were ten, fifteen seconds ahead of me
and they were both fighting each other.
Ricciardo desperate
to get past Max Verstappen.
But Verstappen aggressively defending
against his teammate.
-  Yellow flags turn one. Take care.
- Yellow turn one.
- Debris at turn one.
- Double yellow at turn one.
Both Red Bulls off at turn one.
That's 25, 30 points
we just fucked away there.
When you are driving for one
of the teams in the midfield,
I'm not gonna say I would celebrate
the top team's crashing into each other,
but if Carlos goes up two places
because the drivers decide to collide,
it's good for him,
and he gained two places for free.
Safety car. Safety car.
Safety car in this lap.
Okay, which position am I?
You're currently P-7.
Okay.
Now we've got--
I don't know how many laps to go,
but not many until the end,
so... new tires.
We need to overtake Grosjean.
Right, onboard then with Grosjean.
He's weaving around, trying to get
temperature into the tires...
And he's gone and crashed!
Oh! Ooh. There you go.
Okay, Grosjean crashed.
Nice one. P-6.
Safety car...
I'm fucking speechless.
I cannot fucking believe it.
That's how quick things can change
in Formula One.
Ouch.
Back with Fernando Alonso.
Fernando, you're doing
an amazing job. This pace is really good.
Okay.
Okay, guys,
how many laps to the end are we now?
Seven laps remaining now.
You're gaining four-tenths per lap
to the cars ahead.
- Keep focus.
-  Copy.
There's a puncture
for Valtteri Bottas!
It's a flat!
He ran across some debris.
Oh!
Ah, tire failure!
At that point, I remember thinking
about giving it a shot
at that podium place.
Let's go, Carlos.
Let's go, let's go.
We have two laps remaining now.
Copy.
Sainz has pulled out
from behind the slipstream.
Nice move, there.
And he's now up into fifth place.
Nice job, Carlos. We need
to focus on the last lap. The last lap.
Copy.
Hamilton takes the checkered flag
and Carlos Sainz comes home
to finish in fifth.
That means Fernando Alonso finishes
as the second Spaniard in this race.
- Nice job, mate. P-5, well done.
- Good job, guys.
Following his earlier incident,
it's amazing Alonso finished at all.
Only a driver of his caliber
could've gotten that car to the end.
Well, you feel proud of your team,
of your, um, abilities also,
driving that car,
of your commitment.
You ended up with a P-7 and you feel,
very, very proud of that drive.
It was, by far, the best race
of the season for me, personally.
Despite the start, we will fight
until the checkered flag.
-You did great. Podium next.
-Yeah.
Finishing fifth
was the best team result
since we returned to Formula One.
But we are still behind McLaren
in terms of the championship.
-Well done, mate. Nice drive.
-Thank you.
It was one of those weekends
that you go back home really happy
because you've contributed
to a very big team result.
Yeah, really good.
The Red Bulls were all over the place.
Thank you.
You guys must have been enjoying it
from the outside.
Yeah, we did. Yeah, yeah.
LeClerc got
a very good slipstream from me.
But then I got him back easily.
I said, "This guy is not beating me.
No fucking way."
I went-- I went bananas to him like...
Azerbaijan Automobile
Federation. Well done, gentlemen.
No, no, no. Come on!
No, no.
Every time I'm in Spain,
I try to organize a dinner at home.
How badly they’re playing!
You get
to disconnect a bit from the races
and you really get to have fun.
That's a foul!
Don't let him go. Of course.
I love it.
Carlos, he's
my younger cousin, so we are very close.
We've been very close
since he was born, basically.
- Hey! Fuck off, man!
- I can't believe it.
No shit. What a shitty pass, Marcelo.
His father is my uncle.
Even if you haven't heard
about Carlos Sainz, the motorsport legend,
when you meet him,
you can tell he's a powerful guy.
- Damn it! Come on man!
- Come on please!
Look! Cheat, cheat! Damn!
And obviously,
if you know something about sports,
Carlos's father is an icon of motor sport.
For Carlos Junior, growing up with his dad
has had positives and negatives.
You've got free advice from a legend.
At the same time,
I think it was a little bit tough
because everywhere
that Carlos went racing,
he was, like, pointed out that,
"Look, that's the son of Carlos Sainz.
I wanna beat that guy."
That kind of jealousy,
he has had to prove a lot of people wrong.
If I could be invisible,
I would love to be invisible.
- How's it going?
- Good.
This is his life, his sport, his time.
I have been enough time in the camera,
so I'm quite happy to leave him alone.
Obviously, I know that my dad
is a very famous name.
I'm incredibly proud to be his son,
but me, personally,
I want to create my own name,
my own career in Formula One.
Carlos is still growing,
he's still maturing, somehow,
and I remember
how I was with 22, 23.
He's quite smart... sometimes.
Ollie!
Aw! Look at this!
This is not a dog.
This is... a piece of shit!
Carlos!
Everyone, the F1 world champion.
Give a big hand to Fernando Alonso!
Fernando Alonso!
Hi, everyone. Well, the truth is…
It is emotional
racing in Spain for me.
You know, it is once a year
that you have the home Grand Prix.
Please do not push.
For safety reasons,
please do not push, por favor.
You know, the amount of work
you put off track to make people happy,
to sign as many autographs as possible,
to take time for the kids,
to take pictures,
to give presents, you know,
whatever you can do to make people happy,
you try to do it that weekend.
Fernando!
They want us to do a lap in these ones,
but we cannot fit in the seats. Too small.
Yeah, it is a bit.
I've not been go-karting in fucking years.
- Yeah?
- I'm too old.
Still fun. Still good fun.
Yeah, I haven't done it for so long.
Karting has been, for me,
probably the best part
of my racing career.
I've been in go-karts
for more than 15 years
and probably the best memories
are coming from that part of my life.
Yeah. None?
To hold on, it's hard. So hard.
You ahve to go little by little.
We can't overtake?
You can't, no.
It's just an exhibition today.
But you overtake.
Today is just an exhibition.
Today we came here
to see you taking it easy.
When you start racing
and you jump in a go-kart
for the first time...
um, there is some kind of, uh, freedom.
As a kid, you normally follow your parents
and your friends
and your teacher at the school.
Everything is always
behind, uh, some rules.
The first time you are behind the wheel,
you are yourself and you are alone
on the race track.
That feeling, I think, together
with the speed and with the adrenaline,
is something
that is difficult not to fall in love.
My dad comes nearly to every race,
maybe 16, 17 races a year out of 21.
My sisters and my mom told me
that he gets a bit too nervous
if he doesn't come
to a Grand Prix weekend.
Come on!
I reckon Grosjean's not coming
around turn one.
What do you reckon?
- He might make one, but two...
- Okay, yeah.
In the midfield,
all Spanish eyes
will be looking
at  Fernando Alonso in the McLaren
and Carlos Sainz in the Renault.
Alonso's in eighth, just one place
ahead of his fellow Spaniard.
Just do what we agreed.
I am a competitive guy.
I always visualize winning.
That guy who was your hero,
your killer instinct immediately comes in
and you suddenly take it
as one rival more that you want to beat.
When you are on the grid,
you go into that zone,
into that moment of,
"this is just a car and yourself."
Compete, race, win.
You just need to deliver.
- And radio check, Carlos.
- Yeah, all good.
There is
only one guy who's allowed
to talk to the driver
when he's out there on track.
It's a race engineer,
and for Carlos, it's Karel.
Okay, Carlos. Good luck, mate.
Last car approaching the grid.
And it's a good start
for Carlos Sainz.
Let's go.
Can he keep
ahead of Alonso into turn one?
Oh, he just manages it.
But he's out wide and in the gravel.
That's Alonso's chance
to go out round the outside,
he's in trouble too.
And off is Grosjean!
Massive accident.
That looks like Romain Grosjean
very much out of this race.
Oh, and there's a Renault
involved as well.
Is that Carlos Sainz? I think it is.
-Is that Carlos?
-Shit!
No, that looks like
Nico Hülkenberg.
Hülkenberg is out of this race.
That's Hülkenberg!
It was Grosjean.
Exactly why I said at the beginning,
I said he's not coming around turn one.
We can get racing once again.
Sainz is up in eighth place.
And Sainz is pressuring
Magnussen for seventh.
Tries to go around the outside
at turn three.
Not gonna get through there.
Down into eleventh.
And here's Alonso in eleventh. He's now
trying to attack Ocon in the same way
and he is going to go around the outside.
He's still got it, hasn't he?
What a move!
Okay, Carlos, so box this lap.
Coming in, Carlos, pit lane.
So you will be close
to Ericsson on pit exit.
Okay.
Alonso's caught Hartley
on the straight. And he's got him.
Sainz is going for it here
with Marcus Ericsson.
Trying to go around the outside.
Ericsson just leans on him.
Oh, they're gonna touch,
aren't they?
That is some great
side-by-side action.
Unbelievably close.
He has to look after his tires.
Our race isn't with Ericsson, mate.
Sainz is desperate
to overtake Ericsson.
But Ericsson is long overdue a pit stop.
Don't forget, these tires need to last
Sainz until the end of the Grand Prix.
Why I cannot pass?
He's too fast on the straight.
Keep him calm. Keep him calm.
He doesn't need to pass.
And it's the cars behind
he needs to worry about.
Does he know that's
LeClerc and Alonso behind him?
Okay, Carlos,
behind you have LeClerc and Alonso.
Let's stay calm.
We need to focus on tires.
Copy.
In the race, you go into
that more aggressive mode.
You know that you are
in your home Grand Prix
and you know that you need to make moves
to try and gain positions,
to try and put on a good show.
His race is with LeClerc
and Alonso behind, not Ericsson.
That's what I just told him.
Well, tell him again,
and tell him to drop back
and stop fucking racing him. Please.
If you won't tell him, I will tell him.
He's going to wear his fronts out,
and we're gonna lose this race.
Look after the tires
and bring it home, please.
Marcus Ericsson is finally
off to the pits,
unleashing Sainz into seventh place.
But just behind is Charles LeClerc,
who's getting passed by Fernando Alonso.
Alonso in eighth now.
Next car behind you now
is Alonso.
Six laps to go.
We just had quite a pressure drop
through turn three.
When you say "drop,"
you mean a little tiny, wincey one
or something to be scared of?
Quite scared, yeah.
We were down to around two bar.
Okay.
Oh, the engine, engine.
- It's fuel pressure.
- I had a fuel drop-out.
Turn the engine up, please, Karel.
Scenario one, scenario one.
Sainz has engine trouble.
He'll be down on power
for these final few laps.
Broken?
I cannot believe it,
we were so close to the end.
Carlos Sainz has Fernando Alonso
breathing down his neck.
Right, what can we do
through three?
We can go a little bit easier
through three
- so we don't get those drop-outs?
-  I'll suggest that.
It will help,
but it probably won't stop it.
Okay, Carlos, we need to take it easy
through turn three.
How easy? Like, how much?
We need a big lift-off.
Like that is good.
Like that is very good.
Okay, keep doing that, please.
Alonso is eight seconds behind,
eight seconds behind.
So, I really needed to slow down,
but at the same time,
I had Fernando pushing behind me.
Okay, Fernando,
Sainz is slowing.
Now I want 100% focus on Sainz.
Okay.
He said, "Engine, engine."
He has to take the third turn very slowly.
You'll see how Fernando
pushes now.
Fernando Alonso has just put in
his fastest lap of the race.
Okay, Carlos, five laps to go.
I asked to my engineer
to keep telling me
the lap times of Fernando.
Okay, two laps to go,
and a five-second gap to Alonso behind.
Fernando, last lap
you were two seconds quicker than Sainz.
- One lap left, right?
- One lap.
Alonso
is continuing to gain on Sainz.
This is the last lap.
We didn't know
if we were gonna make it.
There it is, come on.
And there's Carlos Sainz!
And the Renault does it!
Finishing seventh in front
of McLaren's Fernando Alonso.
What a relief.
Look where Fernando had him already.
Up to his neck.
Nice job, mate, P-7, P-7.
Well done.
Good job, Carlos. We beat McLaren.
Ah, when he opened the radio and went,
"Engine, engine, engine,"
-it's like, "No fucking way."
-I know.
Great to get ahead of Alonso at the start.
And McLaren. We've overtook them
in the championship.
We had some high hopes.
I think we are the underdogs now.
It's not a place McLaren is used to being.
So, we dropped one point behind Renault.
It's a very decent finish for us.
I think we have a team that is definitely,
finally starting to believe.
Fernando was, you know,
the first world champion
in Formula One for Spain.
Carlos has a great respect for him.
You know, he's competing with his hero.
Good job, guys. Good job.
Fernando is the best driver
in motor sport at the moment.
So, I know I'm fighting against the best,
even if it's for P-7.
Obviously, Fernando and Carlos
are a different generation.
Carlos knows he's the next Spanish driver
in Formula One,
but he wants to do things his own way.
It's incredible, no? How life is?
You know, when I met him when I was ten,
who would've told me that,
14 years later,
I would've ended up
battling against the best.
- Okay, cheers, guys.
- Cheers!
This year, I have to look
for another contract.
Daniel is very much at a crossroads.
What if I just break free?
Max is their chosen star.
The better I do,
the better offers I get.
Until I lift that trophy,
I won't be satisfied.
This is my time.
It's my fucking time.
What has happened
to Daniel Ricciardo?
I'm losing power...