Formula One is a very
dangerous sport, and it will always be.
Incredibly,
both drivers were okay.
Safety is always
on the agenda in Formula One.
A lot of work has been done
behind the scenes.
But you see a lot of accidents now
where you don't necessarily expect drivers
to walk away.
Prior to twenty years ago,
they wouldn't necessarily have done so.
Everyone breathed a sigh of relief
when the Scot got out
relatively unscathed.
Amazingly, no one is seriously injured.
I'm okay, but, yeah, it was,
it was quite-- quite a big one.
Ayrton Senna was widely regarded
as one of, if not the greatest
racing driver that ever lived.
And when he was killed,
we hoped it would be the last fatality
we ever saw in Formula One.
But in 2014, we lost Jules Bianchi.
Formula One driver,
Jules Bianchi, has died.
He left such a mark in the sport
and will be remembered forever.
He was very close to Ferrari.
Maybe he should drive
for Ferrari one day...
This year,
his godson, Charles Leclerc,
made his Formula One debut.
What Charles is doing
is a continuation of Jules' legacy.
Charles has a mission...
a mission to do
what Jules should have done.
My name is Beat Zehnder.
I'm the team manager
of Alfa Romeo Sauber F1 team.
We are based in Switzerland.
We're very punctual, very precise.
We're very honest, sometimes too honest.
Pretty sure if we would be
a little more dishonest,
probably we could have more success.
We are talent spotters.
Very successful drivers
started with Sauber.
Michael Schumacher.
Sebastian Vettel.
Then we had Kimi Räikkönen.
He's won the championship with Ferrari.
In total we've got something, like,
12 World Championship titles
from a driver which came from Sauber.
But last year we finished bottom
in the Constructors' Championship.
Over the last year,
we have improved a lot.
The difference is the involvement of Fred,
who restructured the company.
Fred is the boss.
He looks a bit grumpy from time to time,
but he's a very funny guy.
I am Frederic Vasseur.
I am the CEO and Team Principal of Sauber.
Two years ago, Sauber was in big trouble.
We have a fantastic wind tunnel,
which we didn't use
for two consecutive years
because we didn't even have
the money to pay the power.
And now we're back to good times again.
I think the last
six or eight months, we are improving.
But the next races
will be very important for Sauber.
And then we will see what are
the driver option for '19.
This year,
we've got two great drivers.
I think the potential was there,
but it was just, uh... unfortunate.
Marcus is five years
in Formula One.
He's a very hard worker
and he has improved a lot.
But yeah, our race pace
was quite strong, actually.
Charles, very young, very motivated.
One of the biggest talents
I've ever worked with.
He's 20 years old.
Probably one of the best newcomers
in the last two decades.
At the moment,
Charles is achieving better results.
Of course, for Marcus,
it's a little hard to take.
I drove there in 2010.
You drove there?
You were probably
in go-karts or something.
A kid.
What were you, ten years old?
No, I was twelve.
My name is Charles Leclerc
and I'm driving
for Alfa Romeo Sauber F1 team.
I'm driving in Formula One
for the first time this year.
I am from Monaco.
I remember watching the Grand Prix
at four years old
in my best friend's apartment,
in the exit of the first corner.
And, yeah, I was always searching
for the Ferrari cars, to be honest.
It's-- It's a childhood dream.
I've always dreamed
to be a part of Ferrari.
I mean,
Ferrari is such a big thing.
You can't imagine to be one
of the two drivers that is in this team.
It's a team that is so mythical.
This will be the target next year.
Whether I will achieve it or not,
I don't know.
I always think the thing
that I just need to do
the best job possible in the car
and then the rest will come.
Kimi Räikkönen!
Kimi! Kimi!
Kimi Räikkönen's had a glittering
and glorious career here at Ferrari.
But, of course, he's no longer
the spring chicken he once was.
Kimi, coming to you.
When will we know more about your future?
It's not up to me. Uh... that's about it.
Not my decision in the end so...
For a long time,
people have expected Kimi to move on.
If Kimi is on his way out...
that frees up one of
the most coveted seats in Formula One.
Can Charles Leclerc be a Ferrari driver
after just one year in Formula One?
Um... it's not normally
a decision Ferrari makes,
to go for youth,
and so it's pretty unlikely.
I think we've had
an incredible first part of the season.
Leclerc is driving
a brilliant race
with so little experience in Formula One.
The thing that's been really impressive
about Charles Leclerc
is that he went into a car
that wasn't all that competitive
at the start of the year.
And he's been getting
the best out of it so regularly.
Yes, yes, yes!
Great race, Charles.
P-6 at the end. Fantastic drive. Good job.
Charles Leclerc around
the outside! Wow, look at that!
And he's still so young.
Ah, fuck!
Sorry. Sorry for the bad word.
One moment stands out for me,
which was in Formula Two
when he got to Baku,
and he'd lost his father earlier
in the week.
And we're talking literally
48 hours later, he was in the car.
He then went out, fell to last place,
fought his way through, and won the race.
This was a kid who'd just lost his father.
And he was a kid at the time.
He's a teenager.
To have that kind of mental strength,
I'd never seen anything like it.
Welcome to Round 13
of the Formula One world championship.
It is the Belgian Grand Prix.
Radio check.
Radio check, Charles.
Copy. Loud and clear.
And it's locking up and a crash!
And Fernando Alonso goes over the top
there of Charles Leclerc's Sauber!
Whoa. An aerial accident there!
And Charles Leclerc makes his way
back to the pit.
He was an innocent bystander in that.
Leclerc, very well protected
from what could've been
a very nasty incident.
Formula One is a very
dangerous sport, and it will always be.
Crashes happen,
and they will always happen.
Glad it's nice weather.
It wouldn't have been the same otherwise.
In Spa,
it was quite impressive
from the outside, from the images.
But inside the car,
it wasn't that big of a shock.
I just don't think about it
once I'm in the car.
Everything that is danger I forget it.
A bit more difficult to put
than a Formula One suit.
At least we are warm.
The situation I was in,
in the last three years
with the loss of my father
and my godfather, Jules,
it was very difficult to take,
and I think it has made me
a lot stronger as a person.
I remember Jules
coming to my first international race.
He gave me a lot of advice
through the years.
I've had some very good times with him.
He had proved himself,
and I think it was just a matter of time
of him being in Ferrari.
I can remember at the moment
of the crash of Jules.
And I could see in my father's eyes
that there was something wrong.
Towards the end of the race,
the conditions were very wet.
Lap 42, Sutil lost control on turn seven.
A recovery vehicle was dispatched.
Bianchi lost control of his car
and hit the back of the tractor.
I went to see
Jules at the hospital.
And saw how serious it was.
At that moment, we all had
the hope to see him back at one point,
but unfortunately,
this moment didn't happen.
When Jules and my father passed away,
there's not one race going by
without me thinking of them.
They made me the guy that I am now
and also the driver that I am now.
Jules deserves that Ferrari seat.
So that's why
I really want to achieve that.
To just thank him for everything
he has done for me.
- Where is it?
- The car is in the truck.
- Really?
- Yes.
Nice. Really cool.
I'm Pierre Gasly.
I'm 22 years old from France.
I'm driving for Toro Rosso Honda.
It's my first full season in Formula One.
A number of the bigger teams are now
putting their faith in younger drivers.
I think the example of Max Verstappen
has really convinced teams
that drivers are good enough
at a much younger age
than perhaps in the past.
Pierre Gasly is Red Bull's choice
of driver to replace Daniel Ricciardo.
He's been so impressive
for Toro Rosso this year.
Pierre Gasly doing
a sensational job for Toro Rosso.
His first full season with the team.
Gasly going past Leclerc.
Okay, Pierre. P-6.
Whoo hoo!
Yes! Yes!
Bahrain stands as, I think, one of
the biggest shocks of the season.
P-4. P-4. Fantastic.
This is amazing.
Unbelievable! Unbelievable.
Stand up
and applaud the Frenchman!
Pierre, you'll be promoted
to Red Bull next year.
Can you believe the progress
and how quick it's been for you?
Yeah. I'm just super excited about it.
It's a massive step.
There's a sort of moment
you get only once in your life,
and, um, it was
really, really something crazy.
I'm extremely happy for Pierre.
And I think he deserves a Red Bull seat.
And this is very good to see that
the big teams trust the young drivers.
I know Pierre since such a long time.
We started our karting careers together.
We go in holidays together, and I think
he's probably one of the only drivers
that I can call a good friend
out of racing,
which is very rare in this sport.
Our first race with Charles
was probably 2005,
when we were really small, sort of
eight, nine years old, racing together.
And I remember,
like, we got on really well straight away.
In my opinion, you can have
good friends in Formula One.
You just need to know how to separate
what happens on track and off track.
It's something we dreamed about,
and finally ten, twelve years later,
everything is happening and we are there.
Highest level in motorsport
in Formula One.
My name is Marcus Ericsson,
and I'm a driver
of Alfa Romeo Sauber F1 team.
I'm from Sweden.
I've just turned 28.
I see myself in my prime of my career,
to be honest.
But I don't have a contract
for next year yet.
It's no secret I want
to stay in Sauber.
I think that's been part of that team
for a long time now,
and we've made
some great progress this year.
It feels like I'm continuing
to prove myself, what I can do.
Super performance
by Marcus Ericsson.
Here we go.
Ericsson against Hartley, up the inside...
And Ericsson is back in the points.
Top ten Marcus Ericsson.
Good session for him.
Whoo hoo.
P-9. Well bloody well done.
Thanks.
And I can't wait to get in the car again
and have a strong weekend.
Welcome along then
on a Friday afternoon
in this glorious part of Italy.
We have arrived in Monza.
We have come for the Italian Grand Prix.
It is the temple of speed.
It is time for second practice.
A lot of drivers
have sorted out their future.
I don't think Marcus Ericsson
is one of them at the moment.
Okay, Marcus,
we should have the green light
in five seconds.
And green light, green light.
Straight out.
Okay, Marcus. Radio check.
Yeah. Right here.
Okay.
Okay, that's plus seven all around.
You have nobody behind at the moment.
Go for it.
- Oh. Something's off.
- Ooh. That's a big crash.
And that's the Sauber
of Marcus Ericcson.
That's massive.
You okay?
If you see a car
spinning and turning like he did...
and him travelling at 340 kph...
the first thought you have
is obviously the safety of the driver.
Marcus Ericsson's Sauber
lying by the side of the track.
You okay?
No idea what happened.
- Okay. Are you okay?
-  Yeah, I am okay.
Marcus is okay.
He went to the medical center.
For sure he was, first, a bit
disappointed and also bit shocked.
The accident was
a technical problem on the car.
He was a victim,
nothing he could do to avoid the crash.
In the end of the day,
you know, it was incredible
to be able to walk away
from an accident like that.
Ten, fifteen years ago
a similar incident could have been fatal.
Monza,
I was feeling confident going there.
I was feeling confident in the car,
and then I had that massive crash.
It's obviously quite a scary thing
to have, you know?
It came out of nowhere,
doing 200 miles an hour.
And I was a passenger.
It happened so fast.
But whilst the crash was happening,
the time went a bit slower.
I remember just thinking,
"What's going on?"
I was so confused why I was flying
around in the air...
My confidence level and everything goes
down when you have a crash like that.
And you have to sort of
start building yourself up again.
Going to Singapore now and...
Okay. Again.
On top. There. That's all.
Singapore is, in my opinion,
the toughest race of the year.
It's key for my future in Formula One.
Significant changes are afoot
at Ferrari for next season.
After five years, in his second stint
with Ferrari, Kimi Räikkönen is leaving.
Räikkönen will stay
in Formula One though... but with Sauber.
Well, Kimi,
if we could start with you, please.
You say it wasn't your decision
to leave Ferrari,
but it was your decision
to go back to Sauber.
So just talk us through
why you're doing that.
Why not?
Because I want to go.
And you're still passionate
about racing? The fire is still--
No, I-- I'm not, actually, you know?
I'm just by pure, uh... head games
for you guys out there, yeah.
Well, Kimi, thanks for the insight.
-Let's move on.
-No worries.
When we had the chance
to get Kimi onboard,
we did everything to make it happen.
Kimi Räikkönen coming next year,
probably another driver,
which is gonna give Kimi
a really hard time.
Any news on who that might be?
For sure, we have to sit down next week,
-and we'll take a decision quite soon.
-Yeah.
But, uh... for sure,
it's important, the lineup.
So, strategy at Singapore
um, is dominated by two things,
safety cars and track position.
We haven't made
a decision of the second seat.
It is important for the team
to make sure that we have the best driver
alongside Kimi.
When he comes to this side
of the driver lineup,
there is always one party
who is not happy with the decision.
Fred deals with such situations
in the best possible way.
Kimi going to Sauber, it's big, big news.
Didn't really see that coming.
It means that, you know,
it's one seat less in Sauber, so...
I know there's a lot of drivers
that want that final seat,
including myself.
So in Singapore,
I need to deliver for sure.
It's my last chance to do it.
We have the best view in Singapore.
Yeah.
You can see about 70 percent
of the track.
I don't know Singapore at all.
It will be my first time here...
and my first night race in Formula One.
It's a very important weekend.
So, I can't wait to discover the track.
So, Singapore
is gonna be a first for me.
Only driven this track in the simulator
and on my Playstation, so...
So... the target is that next year,
I'm the one in the middle.
I'll be good.
I'm not gonna take the Red Bull yet.
No, actually, I'm gonna take it.
Fuck it. I always take it.
Looks like a really exciting,
challenging track.
Very technical, so exactly
the sort of track I like.
Wow. That was a nice one.
Everyone's talking about 2019,
but I still have races
to go with Toro Rosso,
and really want to make
the best out of them.
The 15th round of the 2018
Formula One World Championship.
Arguably the most spectacular,
it's the Singapore Grand Prix.
This spectacular city is taken over by
a 3.14 mile circuit on the city streets.
There are 23 corners
to make up a lap,
more than any other race
on the current calendar.
One thousand seven hundred and seventy-one
light projectors
make sure the drivers
can see where they're going at night.
It's a very special event.
Singapore, because of being
at the equator,
is very hot. It's very humid.
The humidity is 85 plus percent.
So it's very demanding
for the whole team.
For the pit stop crew,
they're wearing their race suit.
And, obviously,
especially for the drivers.
It's physically
the hardest they'll push all year.
So when they're training
at the start of the season to be fit,
the race they're thinking of
that they have to hit the level
is the Singapore Grand Prix.
If we were to work out
the difference of balance
in the short run...
It's really hot in the cockpit,
up to sixty degrees in the race.
One of the longest races of the season
as well, two hours.
Let's go for bath.
During the weekend, we have
this ice bath, as well, after each session.
It might look a bit silly, you know,
on camera, but....
I just know it's good for my body
It's so cold in the thing.
Just like Sweden,
winter ice bath.
Jumping in the frozen lake.
And when I go up from the bath,
make sure the cameras are focusing
on the right, uh, areas, yeah?
I'll keep it here.
The weapon
is not very big at the moment.
The race is going to be
tough on everyone.
Everyone will overheat, cars and bodies.
I think I started the weekend
two kilos heavier than I am now already.
So, I will lose quite a bit again
for the race.
Find the limit, stay at the limit,
you can do it.
I think
before you jump in the car,
there's a lot of things
spinning around in your head.
Charles Leclerc will need to show
that he's worthy of a Ferrari seat.
Charles has added pressure
in that sense.
You want to perform. You want
to do well for yourself, for your team.
Marcus needs to make sure he's scoring
points and finishing in the top ten
if he wants to be
in Formula One next year.
Singapore is a race that could make
or break Marcus' Formula One career.
There's all these emotions,
and then you sort of jump in the car
and all that sort of just goes away.
Then you just go into your bubble
and you just focus on the job.
And they all thread their way
through the first three corners.
Esteban Ocon going into the wall!
That's what teammates are about.
We have
another first lap accident.
Wheel to wheel, Sebastian Vettel
ahead of Max Verstappen.
Yeah, I got overtaken.
Yeah, Gasly ahead.
Good job, Pierre. Good job.
Keep going.
Behind you, there is Leclerc and Ericsson.
Okay, Marcus,
you're doing good. Keep pushing.
Push more if you can,
put some pressure on Gasly ahead.
Great battle here.
Charles Leclerc, trying to get past
the Toro Rosso of Pierre Gasly.
We are really good friends,
but, of course,
you race each single guy
on track the same way.
We've raced since we were kids
in mini karts against each other.
Gasly ahead
seems to struggle with the tires.
We had some exciting
and tight battles.
- Struggling so much, guys.
- Push, Pierre. Push.
Ooh. Big lock-up
for Pierre Gasly there.
And that's gonna cost him a little bit.
Charles Leclerc is right on his tail now.
Of course, when I finish
in front of him, I'm happy,
like he is
when he's finishing in front of me.
Charles Leclerc
almost shoving him around the corners
as they go over the Anderson Bridge.
Leclerc does the old switch-a-roo.
The rivalry's there.
We both wanna be the best.
Come on!
Winning races,
fighting for the championship.
Come on!
That puts Charles Leclerc
ahead of Pierre Gasly.
Well done, Charles, good job.
Tires are completely gone.
Box, box, Pierre.
The race is super, super tough.
Pure pain, you know,
you're dehydrated, getting headaches,
you're really, really tired,
you're struggling with concentration.
Feels like an eternity.
You're a bit like in a tunnel.
It's extremely intense.
Okay, Marcus, you're doing well.
We are P-8 at the moment.
Keep pushing.
Marcus Ericsson still is
the only driver out there
who hasn't pitted.
Ericsson must have all the grip
of an eel swimming in olive oil.
And Sainz gets past Ericsson.
My tires are gone.
Box, box, box.
Okay, Marcus,
the situation, you are P-11.
Ahead of you is Hülkenberg.
Hülkenberg is now ten seconds ahead.
Sixteen laps to go. Go for it.
Go, Marcus!
That's eight seconds
to Hülkenberg, eight seconds.
Okay, Marcus, Hülkenberg
is now seven seconds ahead.
Push.
You are a second a lap quicker
than Hülkenberg.
You can do it.
Copy.
Hülkenberg is now six second ahead.
-We're on him.
-Ah, we catch him.
There.
Okay, Hülkenberg, five seconds ahead.
Copy. Push.
Seven laps to go. Push, push, push.
Five laps to go.
Four laps to go.
Three laps to go.
Two laps to go. Keep pushing.
Last lap, last lap.
Maximum attack now.
Lewis Hamilton,
wins the Singapore Grand Prix!
Okay, Marcus, that's it.
P-11.
- Yeah, thank you.
-  Thank you, buddy.
Ericsson once again finishes
just outside the points.
Okay, Charles, that's it.
P-9 at the end.
Excellent race again.
Ah.
Thank you. Very good race.
Okay, Pierre. P-13, P-13
Yeah, yeah.
You've got so much adrenaline
and concentration when you drive.
And suddenly, your body
feels completely different.
You really feel exhausted
at that time.
I think that was the toughest
eleventh place of my career.
You work so hard for two hours
to not get rewarded with points
when you're so close.
It was very hard to accept.
Marcus?
Hey?
How do you feel?
-Pretty good.
-Yeah?
-It's a pity, huh?
-Yeah. It was close.
It was close.
So close. So far away.
I do deserve a sandwich, though.
And maybe a drink later,
but don't tell anyone.
The big news this week,
where have you been if you've missed it,
Charles Leclerc
will be joining Ferrari next season.
So, yeah, I cannot believe it.
It's incredible.
Selfie, selfie.
Ferrari driver. Ferrari driver.
Oh. I was really believing it.
-I know.
-All right.
Congratulations. Well done, mate.
Thank you. Hello. Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Charles Leclerc will be
the second youngest Ferrari driver
in history.
Yeah, it feels incredible.
They just told me that
we have chosen you as the race driver
for Scuderia Ferrari next year.
And I was just,
"Are you joking or..."
And he was like,
"No, no. Of course, not.
We have chosen you."
And it just felt unbelievable.
-Hey, man, congrats.
-Thank you, man.
Jules probably deserved this place
more than I do,
and I'm extremely happy to be the one.
And I'll try to honor him
the way he deserves,
and bring him the success
he deserves to have.
Are you okay, Nico?
Get me out. There's fire.
-  Yeah.
- There's fire.