Every single one of us at Renault,
our focus is on the stability of the team.
Pure focus on this season's performance.
Oh, what's happened
to the Renault here of Daniel Ricciardo?
Is he stuck in third gear?
What a mess.
Daniel Ricciardo, out of the race.
Shit.
We need to be in a position to fight
for podiums and then fight for wins
and then fight for championships.
But Daniel has put a stop to all of that.
The big news of the week
is that Daniel Ricciardo
is on his way to McLaren.
What do you make of that?
I've done my best in not being hurt,
in not making it personal,
Daniel leaving me.
- Hey, dude.
- Hey.
Ricciardo's on a monster salary,
so from Renault's point of view,
they're sort of thinking,
"Come on, we've given you
everything you've asked for and more,
and you've not actually given us a chance
to prove we're on a better trajectory
than McLaren."
What's been,
I guess, hurting the most,
is the fact
that it's not the long-term project
that I thought we had signed up for.
Why McLaren, do you think?
Ask him.
Ask him. Ask him.
- All right, let's go.
- Let's do it.
- Are we taking the buggy?
- Yeah.
Oh, happy days.
This is a setup, by the way.
- Yeah.
- This is rad.
Yeah.
We can just train here.
This is a good little deck.
I'll get you to do a bit
of original Bagger boxing warm-up, mate.
Why does your hair always look so good?
- Do you dye it?
- Just don't wash it.
It looks darker.
No shit, actually.
I'm not just saying that.
You look good when you do it too.
- Yeah?
- Mm.
All right, let's do it.
Three, two, one, go.
Obviously, yeah,
it was my decision to leave Renault.
But, uh,
yeah,
there was a few sleepless nights, I think,
trying to figure out what was best.
I feel you can be honest with yourself
when you're on your own.
I'll get a chance to,
like, reflect on last year.
The goals when I joined Renault was,
by year two,
the podium was really
what we believed we could be at.
But...
...it can't get worse than last year.
Here comes
Daniel Ricciardo in the Renault!
Okay, let's give a big round of applause
to Daniel, please. Thank you.
Ricciardo was promised
a team that could
take the fight to the big teams,
and when he joined it, it was actually
a team that went backwards.
Oh, a big plume of smoke
from Daniel Ricciardo!
Oh dear!
Even from that point,
I was asking questions, like,
"Can I win with all cars finishing?"
Uh...
It still hurts to say this.
Like, the reality is no.
Everything just cut out.
That looks like a massive engine problem.
Deep down,
I knew that I had to go.
So I chose to leave.
Daniel Ricciardo leaves Renault.
They've lost
their star driver effectively.
Last year, there was always
conversations going on with McLaren.
I think they made the biggest step
out of any team in 2019.
Lando Norris, round the outside!
The Renault looks slower
than a slow thing down the straights.
And I did
take my age into account. I'm 31.
So I can't afford
to chance any more seasons.
- How are you, dude?
- All good.
And I just felt McLaren was in
a better place than... than Renault was,
and that was really what...
what drove me to that decision.
Hello.
Welcome along
ladies and gentlemen to round two.
Hello.
We're still in Austria,
still at the Red Bull Ring,
but this is the first ever
Styrian Grand Prix.
Okay, you've got five minutes
until the next thing.
- Okay.
- Which will be in your driver room.
Hello.
Oh. Can I come here or not?
Of course.
- Hey. How are ya?
- Hello.
Or whatever it is. We could do that.
- You're okay? All good?
- Good, mate. Yeah.
- Feels good to be back into it.
- Yeah.
It doesn't feel
like it's been that long actually.
No. It's amazing
how quickly it all comes back, huh?
So tell me, is, uh,
is Cyril talking to you yet?
Yeah. Yeah.
That'd be about right.
Oh well.
It's probably
a bit like being dumped by a girlfriend,
but she hasn't moved out of the house yet.
- All right. I'll go see my guys.
- All right.
All right, boys. Have fun!
It must be
an odd dynamic for Cyril.
Hello.
Knowing
for the entirety of the season
that he's going
to their biggest competitor.
I'll give you some knuckles.
Can you go away?
Without the microphone.
It is tough.
You naturally shut down
to that individual, because,
you know, they've... they've left you.
Cyril, no doubt,
took that very personally.
With the breakup,
uh, there was a period of time
where we've not spoken.
Don't forget your mask.
I am emotional. I am Latin.
I am a bit Mediterranean and French.
So I am emotional.
I'm not going to change what I am.
Frankly, I think he's making a mistake.
Oh, actually, I'll take a water.
The drivers
with the biggest results, biggest success
have also been the ones
that have been able to take their time
and to bring stability in their own life,
in their own career.
But right now I have to accept
that our priority
is to believe in the dynamic with Daniel.
We need to focus on the season
that we need to do together.
Hey.
All right.
Oh well.
Itchy.
Five days since we last
put the cars on this circuit, we go again.
Here comes Daniel Ricciardo.
With Daniel leaving,
deciding to do something different,
it's a very difficult situation.
But on the top of that,
there is one more layer of complexity
to deal with right now.
There goes Lance Stroll
in the Racing Point
with an awful lot of pace.
It's only the second race of the season,
but we've got our first controversy,
and it's one that's been brewing
ever since Racing Point unveiled a car
that the paddock quickly nicknamed
the "Pink Mercedes,"
because the other teams
think it's so similar-looking
to last year's
all-conquering Mercedes Formula 1 car.
Racing Point insist
they've done absolutely nothing wrong,
the car is completely legal
and within the regulations.
But this sleeping giant, which now has
big funding from Lawrence Stroll,
I think has got a lot of teams scared.
Here goes Sergio Perez.
He's absolutely flying.
You love racing, it obviously
doesn't get any better than Formula 1.
This year, we're already witnessing
the team, with the right resources,
getting an opportunity
to show what they can do.
Watch out for Perez and Stroll.
Racing Point certainly have pace.
We have bigger aspirations
than that.
And that's winning.
He's going well.
This season,
it seems like we've got a good chance
of being better than McLaren,
than Renault.
We'll have a very good chance
at, uh, finishing either at the top
of the midfield or a little bit higher.
Racing Point,
I want to understand,
um,
what happened there, frankly.
We have a car that is very much
uh, like the Mercedes car of last year,
painted in pink, obviously.
That's hurting,
because I don't understand.
We've made such big steps
from where we were last year.
It's hard to believe.
And I have, uh,
you know, a great car under me.
So I'm really just riding a good wave.
And, uh, there will always be
controversy in this sport.
There's no peace in Formula 1.
No team should enhance
the competitiveness of another team,
other than as per the regulation.
We'll talk after the race.
- Yes.
- Good.
A number of teams want to
understand exactly what's behind the car.
I think it's the tip of the iceberg,
that, uh, it needs to be looked at
much more closely.
It can give you
a good leapfrog up the order,
and that situation can't occur.
Obviously,
we've been quite vocal this year
that, um, you know,
we don't think what they've done
with their race car this year,
uh, is right.
Yeah, I heard what Zak said.
Quite frankly, I don't think
he's ever engineered a car in his life.
I don't think he's ever drawn a part
in his life.
So for him to say that,
that doesn't hold any water with me.
It's approaching 2 p.m.
About 15 minutes to go till lights out.
The cars are leaving the garage.
You can hear the rev...
Here today, for sure,
there's probably people,
you know, in Renault
who maybe think where you're at,
and kind of where your head is
and where your commitment is,
but my hunger for beating every driver
on the grid is still the same.
Five zero.
Ooh!
The man is light.
I'm not just driving
for a paycheck, put it that way.
100% athlete.
From my side, I...
I 100% want to try and...
get it through to Cyril
that, you know, look, um,
"McLaren is 2021."
"I'm not thinking about that now."
"I still really, really, really want to do
what I can with you guys."
It's immensely difficult,
but it's really important
to leave the emotion on one side.
With Daniel and myself,
I don't want
to build bridges artificially.
Right now, our focus, our single focus,
needs to be on beating Racing Point.
We have 20 drivers taking part here.
This is gonna be a helter-skelter...
Cyril and I still have
a whole season in front of us
to get that podium.
So let's focus on
kicking some arse.
71 great laps, I'm sure, to come.
It's the first ever Styrian Grand Prix,
and it's lights out and away we go!
Here comes Sergio Perez.
Is he gonna launch one
right around the outside?
He is. Outrageous pace from Sergio Perez.
Perez, up to fifth now.
Lance Stroll is also going to be
having a go at Ricciardo before too long.
Stroll, 0.6 behind.
Okay. Understood.
Stroll, 0.4 behind you.
Stroll, 0.3 behind.
Final lap. Lance Stroll
goes down the inside of Daniel Ricciardo!
Ooh! He barges his way through!
That was a clumsy move there.
Let's go! Big points in the bag.
Nice one, guys.
I saw him
at the apex at the last moment.
If I turned in, we'd crash.
Pretty shit day.
Shit. Shit!
I hate those fucking pink cars.
We'll talk
about how Renault got on today.
We're gonna talk first about Racing Point.
Lance, talk us through your race.
Yeah, some,
uh, great points for the team.
Um, there was a lot...
All I thought about
after the race was the battle with Stroll.
A bit of a controversial one.
Stroll went off the track
and Daniel had to take avoiding action,
if Daniel hadn't got out,
he would've been pushed off
and contact would have been made.
I was obviously upset with him.
But I also felt like
the Racing Point is so fast
they're gonna be a threat,
I think, at every circuit we go to.
Oh, fucking hell.
I was, I dunno, four tenths up
when I came into the pits or something.
- Yeah.
- But, still, the pace. I was...
struggling to hold on
to the Racing Points.
- Which is what we discussed this morning.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Well...
- Fuck!
A number of teams
in the paddock
have got an issue
with that Racing Point car.
But all it takes is one team to protest,
and the first one that did
was Cyril and Renault.
We have decided to protest
against Racing Point.
We believe that this car is not legal,
doesn't comply with the regulations,
and, as such, should be sanctioned.
Renault have gone after
a part of the car
that you cannot see with the naked eye.
They're focused
on Racing Point's brake ducts.
Last year,
to help us with brake duct design,
we purchased some information
from Mercedes.
Information on listed parts is not allowed
to be passed from team to team,
which means you have to design
and develop 'em yourself.
The brake ducts were
a non-listed part last year
and are a listed part this year.
I don't think the FIA can point to a rule
that we contravened.
Everything we did was legal,
and for anybody to suggest otherwise,
um,
is incorrect.
Today,
I have the hearing for Racing Point,
set up by the FIA with the stewards
that will be judging the case.
My responsibility is to...
to make sure that I look after Renault.
We are not fighting
on a level playing field.
Marilyn, how are you?
I'm very well, thank you.
I want to understand
what Formula 1 stands for today,
and what will it stand for tomorrow?
That's what's at stake.
Not started yet. No.
It's very much the governing bodies
that are leading the show.
The FIA needs to set the tone
of what we will be up and doing.
"Please wait.
The meeting host will let you in soon."
It's not like the race start.
It doesn't start on time.
So, Racing Point.
Racing Point's arguments
are bullshit.
Those parts are what make
the difference in performance.
It's the parts
that increase the performance
and everyone looks after themselves.
That's fundamentally what makes Formula 1.
It's not very cool, all this.
Mm.
It's not the essence of F1. It's not.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, for sure.
Today, we've gotta deal
with the Renault protest, the verdict.
However, we're good at overcoming
those types of regulations
and extracting the most performance
out of a car.
- I'm gonna go call Lawrence.
- Yeah, okay.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
Lawrence Stroll is someone
who doesn't do things half-heartedly.
And he provided the very good people
at Racing Point with more resource.
I mean, the whole Racing Point saga,
it's just a little bit of, uh, comedy.
We have the hearing
for the protest.
What if it's illegal?
Then what's the next step?
I guess, if it's illegal,
it should be, uh, disqualified from all
the races that we've protested so far.
Yeah, that's good.
For me, it's very difficult,
'cause, you know,
it's all about the politics outside
and the talks and who decides what,
and, you know, it goes out of your control
and that's as simple as that.
- Will they have to change the part?
- They would have to.
- Go. I'll see you guys later.
- Strategy meeting.
- Is it now?
- Uh...
There's always two sides
to a protest in Formula 1.
But Renault feel that what Racing Point
have done this year crosses the line.
So today's judgment,
today's ruling from the FIA,
has massive ramifications
for the future of the sport.
It's been a long time coming,
but we're expecting the results
of the FIA protest any minute now.
As we know, Renault are...
Okay, we win, but not completely.
- Oh.
- Protest is upheld.
A 200,000 euro fine for each car
and a 7.5 points deduction for each car.
- 7.5 points. From what?
- 7.5 points?
Yeah.
15 points for the constructors.
Out of how many scored?
Forty-two.
And do they make tea all weekend
for all the teams
or is there any kind of forced labor?
Can I drive Otmar's car?
I think he's got a fantastic collection.
If I can drive his collection of cars,
I'm fine.
No, that's... that's a fucking...
that's fucking bullshit.
Let's be factual.
This decision, frankly, it's unfair.
What we've done
is completely legal,
and our competitors are kicking themselves
for not having thought of doing the same.
Racing Point have been fined
for their use of these brake ducts,
but they're allowed to keep using them.
Renault are not happy,
and they're not the only ones.
McLaren and Williams have joined
the appeal, and, crucially, Ferrari.
Is the penalty the right one?
Just a starting point.
I think, you know,
everyone's got to kind of work together
when we see something in the sport
that we think is outside the rules.
I think this is the, uh, start
of this situation, not the end.
Right.
I know that Racing Point
didn't do anything wrong.
Some people felt under pressure
with their performances
and started on that mission,
trying to find reasons
why their performances were not
at the level they should have been.
We just acknowledged that
they did a good job, and others didn't.
Racing Point. Well, Otmar, fined,
points deducted, 400,000 euros.
Does it feel
like a real knockdown right now for you?
Well, it's not ideal.
It's a shame that the protest was upheld,
but we did absolutely nothing wrong.
Otmar, 24 hours to appeal. Will you do it?
We read the sporting regulations.
There is nothing specific in there
that says we couldn't do what we did.
But the car is legal.
The brake ducts
are compliant with the regulations
and we can continue to run 'em
for the rest of the year.
Um, so are you gonna appeal?
You have 24 hours.
24 hours.
They're saying that you've got
no intentional wrongdoing, is the gist?
Yeah, I think
there's no wrongdoing whatsoever.
It's just the rules were ambiguous,
and still are today.
The verdict itself is flawed.
We invited the FIA into the factory.
We showed 'em all of our designs,
and they were completely fine with that.
So the verdict today was, um...
uh, illogical to me.
We didn't... We didn't contravene one rule.
That's ridiculous.
Yeah, the fine's a joke, isn't it,
to someone like their team owner.
There he is.
♪ Down at the bottom of the ocean ♪
♪ Down at the bottom of the sea ♪
♪ I will stay down, down ♪
♪ Gone, long gone ♪
Okay,
whenever you're ready to roll.
- In your own time
- Baby, go.
Good morning.
I do not often speak publicly.
However, I'm extremely angry
at any suggestion that we have cheated.
This team, under various names, has
competed in Formula 1 for over 30 years.
Between 2016 and '18,
this was the fourth-best team on the grid.
We've always been a constructor,
and will continue to be so in the future.
Beyond the clear fact that Racing Point
complied with the technical regulations,
I am appalled by the way
Renault, McLaren, Ferrari and Williams
have taken this opportunity to appeal,
and, in doing so, attempted
to distract from our performances.
These accusations
are completely unacceptable and not true.
They are dragging our name
through the mud,
and I will not stand by, nor accept this.
In closing,
we did absolutely nothing wrong.
We stayed within the rules.
And we will demonstrate and prove that
through the appeal process.
Thank you for your time.
- Good?
- Good.
- Very good.
- Nailed it?
Nailed it. Well done.
This whole
"Pink Mercedes" thing is nonsense.
Our competitors, I think
they have to look at their own competence.
They have their own factories.
They have their own guys.
They simply didn't do a good enough job.
Okay, now let's race
and let's fix this problem.
Uh, mate,
he wants us to be ready.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
The Racing Point protest,
at the end of the day,
I see them as a competitor right now,
and if they're faster,
we've gotta find a way to do better.
We're 40 minutes away
from the start of the British Grand Prix.
Glorious sounds
of engines beginning to rev...
It's up to us now to demonstrate
what we have to achieve as a team.
And what you want is to win.
And we want to beat them.
- That front wing looks like ours, Cyril.
- Yeah.
We took some pictures.
Fuck!
One minute.
Engines start, and drop the car down.
As of today,
a very basic goal I have for myself
is to leave this track with no regrets.
No hesitations. Just conviction.
Decisiveness.
I want to beat that team.
You have to do it. It's just...
You have to do it.
Great start for Daniel Ricciardo!
Okay, Lance,
Ricciardo close behind.
Okay. Copy.
Okay, Daniel, just keep pushing.
Yep. Understood.
Here comes Daniel Ricciardo
round the outside of Lance Stroll.
Come on, DR!
He's done it. Gets the move done.
Frickin'!
He's pulling away from me..
- Allez!
- Yeah!
Shit. What happened?
Okay, Esteban.
It's Stroll in front of you.
Vettel behind you.
Copy, yeah.
Here comes Sebastian Vettel!
Locks up, can't get past Ocon.
All of us at Renault, we have a vision
for where we want to take the team.
With Daniel leaving,
Esteban is absolutely crucial.
Ocon to the inside
of Lance Stroll into the left-hander.
Wheel to wheel,
Stroll's trying to hang on,
and he manages it.
Ah, c'mon!
Here comes Ocon again!
This time, to the outside.
Stroll squeezes him.
And he still keeps hold of ninth place.
Push all you've got.
I am pushing.
This is gonna be tough.
Ooh, there's a lock-up as well.
So is the pressure intensifying, I wonder,
as Esteban Ocon is now
only half a second behind Lance Stroll?
C'mon!
Two drivers, really going for it.
And Esteban Ocon is past the Racing Point!
C'mon!
Yes!
Having stared at the back
of that Racing Point all race long,
Esteban's got past
and up into eighth place.
Now we've got a race.
So Hamilton leads from Valtteri Bottas.
Then, in third, comes Max Verstappen.
Behind them though, they're still
squabbling away for position.
Okay, Daniel,
so currently, you're P7.
Same pace as Norris and Sainz ahead.
Understood.
Ricciardo is putting
Lando Norris under pressure.
Ah, brilliant stuff there.
He moves up into sixth place.
Go on!
Come on, DR! Boom!
It's game on now, isn't it?
Okay, nice job.
Sainz in front of you, next one.
Okay.
One thing I must say is that,
watching Daniel,
right now, it's something that's making me
feel the frustration and disappointment.
Not just for what we have achieved
so far together,
but also for what he would achieve
after... after that.
But he decided to make the decision
when he decided to make it,
with just one year together,
in such a short region of time.
You're doing a good job.
Two tenths quicker than Sainz ahead.
Okay, yep. Understood.
Here come the Mercedes,
stretching their advantage out front.
Oh, and what's happened? Bottas.
There's a puff of smoke there.
We'll try and figure out what's happened.
So Bottas has
a front-left puncture.
Understood.
Now, Bottas pits.
Sainz and Ricciardo
go through ahead of Bottas
Okay. Currently, you're P5.
Seeing a few punctures.
How are the tires?
They're okay.
I can hold this for now.
Carlos is struggling
with vibration,
so let's keep the pressure up on him.
Let's go.
Ooh, Sainz has gone wide.
The same thing's happened to the McLaren.
The tires are failing at Silverstone.
Come on, Daniel!
And Ricciardo's
got through, up to fourth position.
Yeah! Go on!
Nice job, mate.
Let's bring it home now.
Daniel Ricciardo is
on his way
to take fourth position in this race.
What a performance that is.
Woo-hoo!
Fuck.
Nice. Nice. Nice.
He gave everything.
Great race, Daniel.
Got a bit exciting at the end.
Super race. Thanks a lot.
And Esteban Ocon crosses
the line to finish sixth.
Great drive, Esteban.
Awesome. Good points.
Super team result. Super.
The last three laps,
just mayhem, mate.
Mate, good race. P4, boy.
- Yeah.
- You and Esteban were doing well.
You have the perfect lineup
to be ready
for that kind of opportunity, right?
Exactly.
I mean, when the car is reliable...
I have to admit that,
with Daniel, I want to move on,
so that we are extremely focused,
150% focused,
on what's going to be
a super-intense season together.
Everyone wants
to talk to you. Everyone.
Maybe another lap or two,
we could be on the podium,
but, uh, we have next week,
another chance.
We all want
to see Daniel on the podium with Renault
as quickly as possible.
Right now, we have a job to do together.
To finish fourth,
it's really cool, so very happy.
Um, yeah,
just feels quite rewarding, this one.
- So close!
- So close.
- That's good.
- Thank you for that. Thank you.
- No worries.
And thank you
for a couple of very nice maneuvers.
It was nice.
It was fun, huh? It was a fun race.
- Crazy.
- Thanks for that. Cheers.
Here, today,
after what we have achieved together,
maybe all of us are a bit closer.
I am in the process
of rebuilding my relationship with him.
Even though I have...
I have full confidence
that he will regret his decision.
Sitting here today, I don't know if
it's the best call I've ever made or not.
I've obviously, in a way,
taken a bit of a punt.
It could swing either way.
I'll need a whiskey.
Pierre Gasly,
what an incredible run of form.
Now we're gonna score some fucking points.
Alex has to prove
he's worthy of that seat.
Albon and Gasly, wheel to wheel.
The fight is on.
Last year, Carlos and Lando
had a great relationship.
This year, is very different.
Carlos, one. Lando, zero.
How do you sum up
our season this year?
It's one short word.
Shit.