[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.76,0:00:03.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《哥谭》前情提要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Previously on Gotham...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.31,0:00:04.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生  你认识他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The Doc, you know 'em?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.38,0:00:05.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, I know The Doc.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.69,0:00:08.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时我们会寻找我们并不想找到的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sometimes we search for things we don't wish to find.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.88,0:00:10.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我享受做哥谭女王\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I enjoy being the queen of Gotham.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.31,0:00:11.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴我们达成了共识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Glad we understand each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.67,0:00:14.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还有其他办法可以伤害你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There are other ways for me to hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.38,0:00:15.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么在让你不安  吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Something's eating at you, Jim,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.78,0:00:16.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不把这事说出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And you're not gonna feel clean
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.87,0:00:18.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会一直不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}until you get it off your chest.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.61,0:00:20.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这下妥了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's done now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.91,0:00:22.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在索菲娅·法尔科内家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm at Sofia Falcone's.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.39,0:00:24.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚射杀了猪头人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I just shot and killed the Pyg.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.12,0:00:25.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来阿卡姆对你很不错嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I see Arkham's treating you well.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.91,0:00:27.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见了  奥斯瓦尔德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Good-bye, Oswald.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.82,0:00:28.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我终日被人囚禁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I am held captive,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.91,0:00:30.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才智被困于牢笼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}all my brilliance locked away.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.27,0:00:31.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're still there.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.54,0:00:33.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要帮我想办法逃出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And you're gonna help me find a way out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.27,0:00:33.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I need a name.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.00,0:00:34.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾薇·佩珀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ivy Pepper.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.82,0:00:35.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识艾薇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know Ivy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.68,0:00:38.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  戈登  她变样了  变了很多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, Gordon, she's changed. Like, a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.41,0:00:40.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉萨路水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Called Lazarus Water.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.07,0:00:41.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算拿它做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What are you going to do with it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.60,0:00:43.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要制造奇迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm going to make miracles happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.65,0:00:45.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稍微收敛一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Reel it in a little?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.86,0:00:47.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是要我打给你的监护人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Or should I call your keeper?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.32,0:00:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打给阿尔弗雷德  他不会接的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Call Alfred. He won't answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.78,0:00:50.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-为什么  -因为我把他解雇了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Why? - 'Cause I fired him.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.78,0:01:48.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一个在这儿上班的人呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where is the other guy who works here?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.29,0:01:49.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说哈维吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You mean Harvey?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.53,0:01:52.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他请病假了  要给他留言吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's out sick. You want to leave a message?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.46,0:01:59.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.74,0:02:03.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  需要我和他说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right. What should I say?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.95,0:02:04.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都不用说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.14,0:02:07.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你们所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because all of you,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.15,0:02:11.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的血肉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}with your blood and your flesh
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.30,0:02:13.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及你们将成为的东西...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and what you will become...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.23,0:02:17.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就是我的留言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}...you are the message.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.11,0:02:39.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个好人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He was a good man.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.72,0:02:42.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然马里奥不在了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It doesn't matter that Mario is gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.22,0:02:43.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你永远是我嫂子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You'll always be my sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.45,0:02:46.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于法尔科内  家庭至上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}For Falcones, it's all about family.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.24,0:02:48.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I appreciate that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.68,0:02:51.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妯娌之间说真话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, sister to sister,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.19,0:02:54.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是为了看照片而来的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}we're not really here to look at photographs.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.41,0:02:58.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整个哥谭只剩一个区域\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's only one neighborhood in Gotham
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.96,0:03:00.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有臣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that hasn't bent the knee.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.81,0:03:03.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈何岛从不屈从于外界的老大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The Narrows has never submitted to an outside boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.21,0:03:05.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是哥谭以前从没被我这样的人统治过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's never been someone like me ruling Gotham.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.62,0:03:07.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.18,0:03:09.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.33,0:03:10.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收税\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A tax.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.06,0:03:13.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈何岛全部收入的30%\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}30% on all income coming from the Narrows,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.33,0:03:14.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,合法收入和非法收入\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}legal and illegal.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.07,0:03:17.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里的家庭都只能勉强糊口度日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Every family there lives hand to mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.97,0:03:19.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会挨饿的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They'll starve.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.43,0:03:21.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都需要做出牺牲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We all have to make sacrifices.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.27,0:03:24.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天之内给我答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll need an answer by the end of the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.35,0:03:32.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要我俯首称臣  为保和平  我愿意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want me to kiss the ring, I'll do it to keep the peace,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.06,0:03:34.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你这个要求是不可能的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but what you're asking for is impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.04,0:03:37.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会想出办法的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You'll find a way.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.37,0:03:40.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是说家庭至上吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thought it was all about family.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.14,0:03:44.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没说是快乐的家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Never said it was a happy family.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.65,0:03:54.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.43,0:04:10.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你来见我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you for meeting me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.01,0:04:18.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母的基金会今晚要举办年度晚宴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My parents' foundation is having their annual dinner tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.40,0:04:19.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想我们可以一起去  -我怎么觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- I thought we'd go. -Somehow, I don't think
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.95,0:04:21.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你大老远地约我过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you called me all the way down here
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.18,0:04:23.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是来谈慈善晚会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to talk about a fundraiser, did you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.51,0:04:26.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布鲁斯  你到底\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Bruce, what exactly
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.65,0:04:29.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要我做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is it that you want from me?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.30,0:04:36.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Help.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.84,0:04:39.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我理清前路  我一个人不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Figuring this out. I can't do it alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.87,0:04:40.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.66,0:04:44.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔弗雷德  我需要你帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Alfred, I need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.88,0:04:50.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.74,0:04:55.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.24,0:04:57.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能就这么大摇大摆地出现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Listen, you can't just waltz back in here
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.62,0:05:00.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫我去给你洗衣服  泡茶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and expect me to go and clean your smalls and cook your tea,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.29,0:05:01.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不想想你都做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}after what you've done.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.09,0:05:02.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔弗雷德  我并不是要那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Alfred, I'm not asking for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.38,0:05:03.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我变了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.24,0:05:04.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你变了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, you have, have you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.24,0:05:06.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光说你变了是一回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}See, it's one thing saying that you've changed
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.46,0:05:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真正改变是另一回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and another actually changing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.98,0:05:10.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  让我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, show me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.30,0:05:14.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看到你怎么变了  我再考虑一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Show me how you've changed, I might reconsider.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.42,0:05:18.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么给你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Show you how?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.63,0:05:27.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就得你自己想去了  是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's for you to figure out, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.27,0:05:36.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是作为朋友请求你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm asking as a friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.20,0:05:38.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I am not your friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.67,0:05:41.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾是你的管家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I was your butler.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.75,0:05:44.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你解雇了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And you fired me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.07,0:05:51.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,茶钱他来付  小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He'll pay for the tea, miss.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.51,0:06:05.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望小莱能和索菲娅谈出个好结果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sure hope Lee is gonna figure something out with Sofia.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.40,0:06:07.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟她是你的今生挚爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Lee being the love of your life and all.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.66,0:06:08.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.73,0:06:12.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那些神经病药并不会把我变没的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, those cuckoo pills aren't gonna make me go away.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.67,0:06:15.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但至少能阻止你再跑出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, they have stopped you from getting out
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.82,0:06:18.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试图杀小莱  所以我能接受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and trying to kill Lee again, so works for me!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.37,0:06:21.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有邮件来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Mail arrived.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.69,0:06:23.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾德·尼格玛收
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.57,0:06:26.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁寄来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, who's it from?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.73,0:06:28.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥斯瓦尔德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oswald.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.44,0:06:31.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我想道歉"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"I want to apologize."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.85,0:06:33.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我们能再做朋友吗"  什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Can we be friends again?" What?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.79,0:06:35.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他胡扯什么  我绝不会原谅他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What is he-- I'm never gonna forgive him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.76,0:06:37.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这封信写得不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, I think it's a nice letter.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.68,0:06:39.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.20,0:06:40.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, Ed.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.66,0:06:42.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西有两只眼睛  却看不见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What has two eyes but can't see?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.64,0:06:44.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西有两...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What has two...?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.77,0:06:57.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  这可是新花样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Good Lord. This is new.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.30,0:06:59.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更凶悍了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}More aggressive.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.62,0:07:02.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,植物直接破肉而出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Plants are literally bursting through their flesh.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.49,0:07:06.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.67,0:07:08.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻离开那东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get away from that now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.57,0:07:09.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.05,0:07:12.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些尸体里长出了同样的花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Same flower growing out of these bodies.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.40,0:07:14.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个武器吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's a weapon?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.51,0:07:16.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戈登\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Gordon.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.43,0:07:18.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这肯定是艾薇用拉萨路水干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This must be what Ivy did with the Lazarus Water.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.52,0:07:20.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用它增强了毒植物的能力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Used it to increase the potency of a toxic plant.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.89,0:07:23.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-种子让它能空气传播...  -布洛克在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- The seeds made it airborne... - Where's Bullock?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.02,0:07:23.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.54,0:07:24.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在这里工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He works here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.04,0:07:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈维杀了艾薇的父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Harvey killed Ivy's father.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.97,0:07:34.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.02,0:07:38.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Too late.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.44,0:07:39.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, we're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.97,0:07:45.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的  吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Damn it, Jim!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.82,0:07:47.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉姆  搞什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Jim, what the hell?!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.45,0:07:49.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们得赔我的门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, someone's paying for that door!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.34,0:07:50.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾薇·佩珀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ivy Pepper.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.24,0:07:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁  -马里奥·佩珀的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Who? - Mario Pepper's kid--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.84,0:07:54.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在研究一种生物科技\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}she's been working on some biotech.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.04,0:07:56.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她袭击了你的酒吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She attacked your bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.15,0:07:58.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当惨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.87,0:08:00.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酒保唐尼怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Donnie, the bartender?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.92,0:08:02.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.37,0:08:04.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.93,0:08:08.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你才是目标\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look, I got to think that you were the target.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.60,0:08:10.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉姆  我射杀艾薇·佩珀的爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Jim, I only shot Ivy Pepper's dad
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.78,0:08:13.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了救你个蠢货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}because I was saving your stupid hide!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.23,0:08:14.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不能怪我  -伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- You can't put this on me! - Guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.70,0:08:16.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没有怪你  -伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- I'm not putting it on you! - Guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.09,0:08:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了大众的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In the interest of public safety,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.41,0:08:19.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们决定公开录像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}we have decided to share the footage,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.52,0:08:21.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即将播出的视频\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}so in a moment, the video we are about to show you
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.84,0:08:24.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们今早收到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is from a tape received this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.62,0:08:28.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再次提醒  内容会令人不适\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And again, let me warn you, it is very disturbing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.31,0:08:31.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,植物爱我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Plants love us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.38,0:08:35.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们给我们食物  庇护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They give us food, shelter,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.76,0:08:37.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有我们呼吸的空气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}the very air we breathe.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.07,0:08:40.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我们是怎么回报的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And what do we do in return?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.09,0:08:42.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀死它们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Kill them.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.17,0:08:45.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那就是我们的天性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because that's our nature.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.51,0:08:49.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们制造痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We cause pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.09,0:08:54.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识的所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Everyone I've known
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.44,0:08:57.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都只会伤害我  背叛我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}has only hurt or betrayed me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.23,0:09:01.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我内心一直知道我该怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe I've always known in my heart what I needed to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.03,0:09:04.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在我终于有这个能力了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I finally have the power to do so.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.61,0:09:09.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把你们的城市还给植物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm giving your city back to the plants,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.92,0:09:11.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那些伤害过我人的开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}starting with the people who hurt me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.25,0:09:14.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你也有份\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So if that's you...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.28,0:09:17.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你大限已至\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}your time is coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.91,0:09:21.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来我们知道她的打算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Guess we know what she's up to.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.37,0:09:22.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.37,0:09:24.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要杀死哥谭的所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She's gonna kill everyone in Gotham.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.91,0:09:26.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Starting with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.51,0:09:33.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,初步报告显示多家新闻机构\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Preliminary reports indicate that simular tapes
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.55,0:09:36.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都收到了类似录像带...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}have been delivered to multiple news organizations...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.42,0:09:40.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  那是什么东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait a minute. What's that there?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.31,0:09:42.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨莉餐馆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Sully's Eatery."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.08,0:09:45.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在艾夫斯广场  这房子肯定就在街角对面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's in Ives Square. House must be right across.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.41,0:09:47.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该去警局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You should go to the precinct.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.30,0:09:49.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会像懦夫一样躲起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, I'm not hiding like some freaking coward.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.67,0:09:52.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗  她为了找我而害死了四个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right? Four people are dead because she wanted me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.23,0:09:54.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那我们就一起解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay. Then we'll work on it together.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.85,0:09:55.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以戴上警徽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You can wear the badge.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.77,0:09:59.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞清楚  吉姆  我不会也永远不会为你工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get this straight, Jim! I ain't working for you now or ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.43,0:10:01.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在奈何岛的线人比你们任何人都多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I got more contacts in the Narrows than any of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.42,0:10:04.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要一个人找到她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm gonna find her, alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.15,0:10:10.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我先找到我的裤子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Once I find my pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.87,0:10:17.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这说不通啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Doesn't make any sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.46,0:10:20.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里没有钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's no money here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.86,0:10:22.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是为了权力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, so it's about power.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.25,0:10:25.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过愿俯首称臣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I offered to bend the knee.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.41,0:10:31.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要的是她知道我给不了的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She's asking for something she knew I couldn't give.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.61,0:10:33.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She wants...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.53,0:10:37.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想惩罚我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She wants to punish me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.70,0:10:38.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}For what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.35,0:10:42.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  但你无法对抗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know, but you can't fight an enemy
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.00,0:10:44.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不了解她动机的敌人  小莱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}whose motivations you don't understand, Lee.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.37,0:10:54.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们...是哥谭最棒的探子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You... are the greatest spies in all of Gotham.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.38,0:10:57.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们到处都有耳目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You have eyes and ears everywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.60,0:11:03.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈何岛的存亡就靠你们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The survival of the Narrows depends upon you!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.06,0:11:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁能查出索菲娅·法尔科内\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Whoever learns why Sofia Falcone
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.98,0:11:10.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么想击垮小莱·汤普金斯将会得到...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}wants to destroy Lee Thompkins will receive...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.00,0:11:13.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全套的百科全书\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}a complete set of encyclopedias.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.16,0:11:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有T的那辑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Minus the "T."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.31,0:11:20.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再加20块\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Plus 20 bucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.21,0:11:21.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yes! ‭
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.25,0:11:23.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Go get 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.04,0:11:37.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没有虚张声势\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She wasn't bluffing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.63,0:11:38.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么多植物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}With this many plants,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.50,0:11:40.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她能杀死成千上百个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}she could kill hundreds, if not thousands, of people.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.89,0:11:44.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去别的房间看看能不能查出她去哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Search the other room for any signs of where she's heading.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.91,0:11:56.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备怎么处置她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What are you gonna do to her?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.21,0:11:59.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.71,0:12:00.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.85,0:12:03.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚看到新闻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I just saw the news.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.62,0:12:05.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她今天又杀了四个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She killed four more people today.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.03,0:12:07.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你早就知道她躲在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You knew where she was staying.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.28,0:12:08.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你早点告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you had told me,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.96,0:12:10.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们可以救下那些人  -或者不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- we could've saved lives. - Or not.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.58,0:12:12.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你甚至没法阻止她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, you couldn't even stop her
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.86,0:12:14.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,催眠你手下的警察\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}from hypnotizing your own cops.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.18,0:12:17.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你来干什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So why'd you come here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.95,0:12:21.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟她讲讲道理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To try to reason with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.55,0:12:23.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到她说了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Have you heard a word she said?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.03,0:12:23.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个狂徒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She's a fanatic.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.64,0:12:25.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She's my friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.88,0:12:27.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还指望我做什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, what do you expect me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.93,0:12:30.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她再跟你联系的话  通知我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She contacts you again, call me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.96,0:12:33.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会想办法找到她  低调缉拿她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll try and find her and bring her in quietly.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.73,0:12:35.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除此之外  别去阻拦她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Otherwise, stay out of her way.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.49,0:12:39.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Harvey?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.81,0:12:42.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有线索了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I got a lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.18,0:12:43.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.15,0:12:49.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敲打了几个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I knocked some heads,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.37,0:12:51.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打听到一个性感红头发女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}heard a hot redhead was poking around
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.13,0:12:52.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在隔壁那家廉价酒吧找人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in that dive bar next door.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.92,0:12:55.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是在奈何岛雇廉价打手的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That is the place in the Narrows for low-end muscle,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.10,0:12:57.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我想她要是有什么大计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}so I figured if she was planning something big,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.25,0:12:59.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她去酒吧或许是为了招人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}she might've gone there to recruit.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.29,0:13:00.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里是后门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's the back entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.60,0:13:02.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的线人说就是在那里...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's where my contact said that...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.18,0:13:07.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  戈登警探\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello, Detective Gordon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.56,0:13:09.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}On the ground, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.09,0:13:10.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈维  上报\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Harvey, call it in.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.92,0:13:13.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很美  你不觉得吗  吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She's beautiful, don't you think, Jim?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.77,0:13:17.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下武器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Drop your weapon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.54,0:13:25.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的情况不太好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You don't look good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.52,0:13:28.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用药过量了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Think you might be exceeding your recommended dosage.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.01,0:13:30.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you experiencing...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.83,0:13:33.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"四肢颤抖"  是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"trembling extremities"? Check.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.42,0:13:36.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"认知功能障碍"  绝对有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Cognitive impairment"? Definite check.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.73,0:13:39.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  老实说  你怎么可能知道呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Though, to be fair, how would you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.80,0:13:40.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.12,0:13:42.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想吃多少药随你的便  爱德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Take all the pills you want, Ed.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.46,0:13:43.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只会越来越强大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm only getting stronger.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.80,0:13:45.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快  我就会挣脱出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Soon, I'm gonna be out,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.71,0:13:47.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时  好戏就开场了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and the fun begins!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.97,0:13:48.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.88,0:13:51.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会让你得逞  因为我知道你要干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I won't let you, 'cause I know what you'll do.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.10,0:13:52.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说杀掉小莱吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, you mean kill Lee?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.43,0:13:55.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我大概会这么做吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, I guess I will do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.58,0:13:56.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你阻止不了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And you can't stop me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.89,0:13:58.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以做一些事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There are things that I can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.64,0:13:59.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Like what?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.76,0:14:01.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得面对现实  兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You need to face it, pal.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.01,0:14:03.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只有自杀才能摆脱得了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The only way you'll get rid of me is to kill yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.32,0:14:09.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你真是比我聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I guess you are smarter than me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.61,0:14:12.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会真想...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You wouldn't actually...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.18,0:14:13.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.56,0:14:17.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.40,0:14:21.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说放下枪  吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I said drop the gun, Jim.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.88,0:14:31.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你相信命运吗  戈登警探\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Do you believe in fate, Detective Gordon?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.03,0:14:34.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天我去找那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I went out today to test my plants
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.40,0:14:36.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打死我父亲的人试我的植物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}on the man who shot my father.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.40,0:14:38.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他不在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He wasn't there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.86,0:14:40.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人失望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was disappointing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.30,0:14:44.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他找到了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then, he found me,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.37,0:14:49.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我意识到我可以让他把他的搭档也引过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I realized I could make him deliver his partner as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.39,0:14:52.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fate.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.17,0:14:53.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别屈服  哈维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stay strong, Harvey.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.31,0:14:54.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在控制你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She's controlling you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.46,0:14:55.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还挺喜欢这样的  吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I kind of like it, Jim.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.55,0:14:57.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜蜜的俘虏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sweet surrender.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.63,0:15:01.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要帮助  艾薇  让我去找塞琳娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You need help, Ivy. Let me find Selina.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.74,0:15:02.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她想帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She wants to help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.59,0:15:03.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Quiet.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.97,0:15:05.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.49,0:15:08.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚还有大事  要杀很多人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Big plans tonight. Lots of people to kill.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.52,0:15:10.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布洛克警探\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Detective Bullock?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.51,0:15:11.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事  小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ma'am?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.33,0:15:12.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了你的搭档之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}After you kill your partner,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.50,0:15:15.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定要一枪打爆自己的脑袋  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}be sure to shoot yourself in the head, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.40,0:15:16.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Copy that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.41,0:15:27.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哈维  -别妄想靠耍嘴皮来脱身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Harvey... ‭- Don't even try and talk your way out of this!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.04,0:15:27.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I wouldn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.32,0:15:30.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有个小问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But quick question.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.45,0:15:34.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾薇的头发是赤褐色还是猩红色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is Ivy's hair more auburn or scarlet?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.57,0:15:38.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  这问题问得好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I, um... That's a good que...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.71,0:15:46.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我不会做好准备吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Think I didn't come prepared?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.64,0:15:50.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总是低估我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You always underestimate me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.36,0:15:54.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是我冲你开枪的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's not why I'm shooting you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.61,0:15:57.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们该  说明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I just think we should, uh... clear the air.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.11,0:16:01.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说什么  我洗耳恭听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What do you want to talk about? I'm all ears.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.94,0:16:05.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如  你偷了我的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How you stole my job, for starters!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.60,0:16:08.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那工作真的属于你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Was it really your job, though?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.07,0:16:12.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之所以能得到  是因为一名警监死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, you only got it 'cause one captain died,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.06,0:16:14.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-另一名疯了  -才不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- and the other one went nuts. - Like hell!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.86,0:16:15.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了我该做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I paid my dues!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.68,0:16:17.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那份工作是我应得的  被你夺走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I earned that job, and you took it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.83,0:16:20.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是指你打伤了佩特尔警官那次吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You mean like the time you gut-shot Officer Patel?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.81,0:16:24.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是个  失误\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That was... A mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.69,0:16:26.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别看低了自己嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, give yourself some credit.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.38,0:16:29.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是从房间另一头击中了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did shoot her from across the room.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.45,0:16:32.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你之后却无法面对她  记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Although you couldn't face her later, remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.78,0:16:35.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你第二天没有勇气去见她  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You didn't have the courage to meet her the next day, did you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.22,0:16:38.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个懦夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You coward.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.13,0:16:39.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Screw you!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.70,0:17:03.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没开门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're not open.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.72,0:17:05.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想见你  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- I wanted to see you. - Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.02,0:17:07.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们上次碰面时你还不够混吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because you weren't big enough of an ass the last time I saw you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.28,0:17:10.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-塞琳娜  -我没工夫跟你纠缠  布鲁斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Selina... - I don't have time for this, Bruce.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.64,0:17:12.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了一些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Something happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.51,0:17:14.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要找个人谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I need to talk to someone.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.33,0:17:15.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那去找阿尔弗雷德啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, then go find Alfred.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.37,0:17:21.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You did.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.97,0:17:23.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他不想搭理你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And he wanted nothing to do with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.58,0:17:26.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔弗雷德真明智\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Smart guy, Alfred.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.00,0:17:30.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能至少听我说完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Will you at least hear me out?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.19,0:17:32.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  布鲁斯  因为艾薇在到处杀人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, Bruce, because Ivy's out there killing people,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.48,0:17:34.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得找到她  阻止她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I need to find her and stop her.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.07,0:17:36.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以不管你现在有什么心事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So whatever problem you have going on right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.80,0:17:38.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得自己想明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you need to figure it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.45,0:17:40.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟阿尔弗雷德道歉去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, say sorry to Alfred.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.58,0:17:44.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不管发生了什么  肯定是你的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}'Cause I'm sure whatever happened was your fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.58,0:17:53.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据我的探子说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}According to my spies,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.12,0:17:58.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,索菲娅和吉姆有过一段恋情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sofia and Jim were carrying on an affair,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.96,0:18:01.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但被吉姆结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}till Jim ended it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.12,0:18:03.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以严格说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, technically,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.12,0:18:05.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的前男友睡了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}your ex has been sleeping with
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.36,0:18:06.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你死去丈夫的黑帮妹妹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}your dead husband's mafiosa sister...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.77,0:18:08.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  爱德  我懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, Ed, I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.35,0:18:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果索菲娅睡了哥谭市警局的警监\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If Sofia was sleeping with the captain of the GCPD,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.00,0:18:15.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那肯定是为了权力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}it was a power play.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.83,0:18:16.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果没成功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And it failed.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.22,0:18:19.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是她的下一招\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm her next step.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.74,0:18:23.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不我干脆满足她的愿望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why don't I just give her what she wants:
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.44,0:18:26.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,控制吉姆·戈登的筹码\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}power over Jim Gordon.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.98,0:18:29.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真愿那么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You would do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.15,0:18:32.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是想报复吉姆  虽然他是活该\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not trying to get back at Jim, though he deserves it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.65,0:18:34.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的工作是确保\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My job is to make sure
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.84,0:18:36.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奈何岛人民的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that the people of the Narrows are safe,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.68,0:18:39.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会尽一切所能确保这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I will do everything in my power to ensure that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.10,0:18:45.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.05,0:18:47.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小莱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Lee...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.37,0:18:49.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.73,0:18:54.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.21,0:18:59.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have to leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.29,0:19:13.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哈维  哈维  醒醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Harvey. Harvey, come on. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.72,0:19:15.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  -我在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Okay. - Where am I?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.01,0:19:18.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被催眠了  我需要你集中精神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You were hypnotized. I need you to focus.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.57,0:19:21.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾薇向你透露她下一步的目标了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did Ivy give you any clue about who she's targeting next?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.39,0:19:22.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信我被她控制了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can't believe I let her get to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.88,0:19:24.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想帮忙吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, you want to help?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.03,0:19:26.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这么帮  她说什么了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here's how. Did she say anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.85,0:19:29.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Something about, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.02,0:19:31.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"他们靠杀害植物中饱私囊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"They get rich by murdering plants"?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.04,0:19:34.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么她要针对一群有钱人咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So she's targeting a group of rich people?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.37,0:19:36.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在她家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}At her place,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.19,0:19:39.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她试了一些高档衣服和鞋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}she was trying on fancy clothes, fancy shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.02,0:19:40.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,派对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A party?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.07,0:19:42.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说她还有大事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She said she had big plans,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.32,0:19:43.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不能迟到  -走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- couldn't be late. - Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.90,0:19:46.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-对  很上档次的场合  -不  拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Yeah, black tie. Fancy-schmancy. - No, no, no. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.73,0:19:49.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流浪汉慈善晚会什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, like a charity for hobos or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.29,0:19:51.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚是韦恩基金会的年度晚宴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wayne Foundation's annual dinner is tonight,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.91,0:19:53.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哥谭广场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}over at Gotham Square.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.29,0:19:54.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  叫突击队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right. Get the Strike Force.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.80,0:19:57.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全套防弹衣  防毒面具  非致命子弹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I want full body armor, gas masks, nonlethal rounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.65,0:20:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对付植物吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}T-To fight plants?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.00,0:20:02.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我被艾薇控制时  她还催眠了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When Ivy got me, she was hypnotizing
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.13,0:20:03.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一堆廉价打手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}a bunch of low-end muscle.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.72,0:20:04.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.43,0:20:10.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的很需要你帮忙  哈维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Could really use you there, Harv.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.96,0:20:13.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉姆  她控制了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Jim, she got in my head.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.32,0:20:16.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在真的不能信任自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I really, I just don't trust myself right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.78,0:20:18.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你在这里帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right. You can help out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.74,0:20:19.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Man the phones.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.85,0:20:25.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, Jim.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.59,0:20:30.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把这一切怪在你身上太久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I spent too long putting this all on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.02,0:20:33.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之间的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What happened between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.92,0:20:38.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  我只能怪自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fact is, I only got myself to blame.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.93,0:20:43.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会打来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll call.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.56,0:20:54.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托马斯和玛莎·韦恩基金会
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.66,0:21:08.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  女士们先生们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And now, ladies and gentlemen,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.54,0:21:14.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有请主持人  布鲁斯·韦恩上台\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}please welcome to the stage our host, Bruce Wayne.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.83,0:21:22.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,韦恩基金会
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.17,0:21:27.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Good evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.58,0:21:31.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎参加第三届\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Welcome to the third annual dinner
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.37,0:21:34.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,托马斯和玛莎·韦恩基金会年度晚宴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}for the Thomas and Martha Wayne Foundation.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.06,0:21:38.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年  我们将四百万美元的善款...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This year, we disbursed $4 million in...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.66,0:21:51.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们将四百万美元的善款...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Uh, we-we disbursed $4 million, and, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.43,0:22:09.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母一生都在帮助他人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My parents spent their lives helping people.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.21,0:22:13.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是那么为他们骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I was so proud of them,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.32,0:22:15.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一直希望他们为我骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I always wanted them to be proud of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.29,0:22:23.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我眼看着他们被杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And then I saw them get murdered.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.68,0:22:29.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能挺过来  是因为我身边一个人帮我撑了下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I survived because someone in my life kept me going.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.86,0:22:32.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's been everything to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.77,0:22:35.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,导师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A teacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.88,0:22:37.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保护者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A protector.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.36,0:22:42.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就像我的父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's been a father to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.45,0:22:50.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望  他能明白这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I hope... I hope he can see that.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.69,0:22:55.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再给我一次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And give me another chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.96,0:23:00.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.43,0:23:13.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.51,0:23:16.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这番话很让我感动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That meant a great deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.75,0:23:20.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不能帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I can't help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.14,0:23:25.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你接受真实的自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not until you accept who you really are.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.71,0:23:30.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我真实的模样  我见到了我内心的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know who I am. I've seen what's inside me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.11,0:23:32.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黑暗和愤怒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Darkness and anger.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.78,0:23:34.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那之下呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But what's beneath that?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.33,0:23:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一颗痛苦的心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's a heart that feels pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.55,0:23:41.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的心  它让你想帮助其他人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Your heart, it's what makes you want to help other people.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.44,0:23:43.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的心是你的力量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Your heart is your strength.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.20,0:23:48.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拒绝了黑暗  就是否认了这力量\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Deny the darkness and you deny that.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.44,0:23:52.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但接受它  是你必须自己做到的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But accepting that is something that you must do on your own.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.21,0:23:53.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Do you understand me?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.80,0:23:59.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不该向你求助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I was stupid for reaching out.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.93,0:24:07.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好一番讲话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That was quite a speech.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.00,0:24:08.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello, all.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.23,0:24:12.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是艾薇·佩珀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm Ivy Pepper.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.77,0:24:15.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, no. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.16,0:24:17.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stay seated.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.20,0:24:35.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Can I just say...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.14,0:24:37.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}this is crazy!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.12,0:24:42.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, this whole thing was your idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.21,0:24:45.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你才是聪明的那个  你不总这么说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And you're the smart one, as you always tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.94,0:24:47.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真逗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, very funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.65,0:24:49.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, fine!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.75,0:24:52.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fine! You win!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.14,0:24:53.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.83,0:24:55.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You win.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.71,0:24:59.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打败了我  你就想听到这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You beat me. Is that what you want to hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.26,0:25:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That is very nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.03,0:25:04.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是得这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I still have to do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.37,0:25:06.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.77,0:25:08.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait. Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.59,0:25:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What if there's a way
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.79,0:25:11.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以不让任何人受伤呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to do this where nobody gets hurt?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.90,0:25:14.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't believe you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.06,0:25:16.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打算就这么自杀  都不听我说说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So you're just gonna kill yourself without hearing me out?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.74,0:25:20.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我的  爱德  有个办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm telling you, Ed, there is a way
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.41,0:25:23.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以挽救小莱  而不用你自杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to save Lee without killing yourself!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.27,0:25:26.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者说杀死我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Or killing us.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.81,0:25:32.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm listening.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.87,0:25:39.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些猩红的花多美啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Aren't these crimson flowers lovely?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.56,0:25:47.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个帅哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're a handsome man.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.33,0:25:50.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你想从生活中得到更多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But you want more from life.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.85,0:25:52.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉得到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can feel it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.03,0:26:03.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,布鲁斯  艾薇·佩珀在里面吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Bruce! Is Ivy Pepper in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.42,0:26:06.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾薇  没有吧  我没见到她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ivy? No. I mean, I didn't see her.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.50,0:26:09.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你快走  我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get out of here. Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.91,0:26:13.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攻破门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Breach that door!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.81,0:26:25.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.26,0:26:28.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要把这个房间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}are going to turn this room
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.96,0:26:33.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变成世界上最美的花园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}into the most gorgeous garden the world has ever seen.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.58,0:26:36.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们只需要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All you have to do...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.21,0:26:39.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深呼吸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is take a deep... breath.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.44,0:26:45.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有志愿者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A volunteer.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.46,0:26:51.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哥谭市警局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}GCPD! GCPD!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.12,0:26:54.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把枪放地上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Drop your guns on the ground now!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.88,0:26:58.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Kill everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.67,0:27:12.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你负责这里  我去追艾薇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You got this. I'm going after Ivy.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.07,0:27:51.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带你走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm getting you out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.17,0:27:51.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Come on, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.77,0:27:52.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Listen, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.89,0:27:55.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们需要你的帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}People need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.43,0:27:58.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is who you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.51,0:28:18.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守住门  我去找他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Watch the doors. I'm gonna go look for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.33,0:28:21.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪了  小子  你怎么逃也逃不掉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where'd you go, punk? You can run, but you can't hide.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.24,0:28:35.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-放下枪  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Drop it! - ‭No!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.33,0:29:42.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听到新闻了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You hear the news?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.36,0:29:47.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯子艾薇·佩珀袭击了韦恩基金会晚宴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Crazy Ivy Pepper attacks the Wayne Foundation dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.34,0:29:50.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll be honest,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.10,0:29:52.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚的事并不完全如我所愿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}the evening didn't turn out quite the way I'd hoped.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.82,0:29:56.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说你没能杀掉那里的每一个人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You mean you didn't get to kill everyone in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.07,0:29:58.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Something like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.86,0:29:59.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你逃掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You got out.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.64,0:30:01.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回来了这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Made it back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.84,0:30:07.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一向擅长生存\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You always were the survivor.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.42,0:30:11.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你教我的  塞琳娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, you taught me that, Selina.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.05,0:30:15.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,袋子里是什么  艾薇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's in the bag, Ivy?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.89,0:30:25.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我从韦恩集团偷来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's the last of the Lazarus Water
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.50,0:30:27.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后的拉萨路水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I stole from Wayne Enterprises.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.48,0:30:29.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好拿去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So you can go
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.57,0:30:32.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,培养更多植物  来杀更多人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and make more plants to kill people?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.22,0:30:38.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别想了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, that ain't gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.01,0:30:43.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要阻止我吗  塞琳娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you gonna stop me, Selina?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.59,0:30:49.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要让我回忆起过去的日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You gonna remind me of the old days,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.26,0:30:51.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我不是这样的人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}tell me I'm not this person?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.83,0:30:54.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们现在没什么可说的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, I think we're past words now.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.85,0:31:06.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塞琳娜·凯尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, Selina Kyle
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.22,0:31:09.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是个英雄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}turns out to be the hero.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.81,0:31:16.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是英雄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm no hero.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.57,0:31:25.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只需要轻轻一刮  塞琳娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}One scratch is all it takes, Selina.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.76,0:31:28.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这次没有解药了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And there's no antidote this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.57,0:31:32.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死翘翘的塞琳娜再也别想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And there's no more jumping across rooftops
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.03,0:31:34.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,飞檐走壁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}for little dead Selina.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.67,0:31:36.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会记住的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll keep that in mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.95,0:31:43.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得跟我打  塞琳娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're gonna have to fight me, Selina.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.11,0:31:46.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别想永远逃避\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You can't run forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.02,0:31:50.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想逃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I wasn't running.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.54,0:31:53.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是想拿到这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I was getting this.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.31,0:31:58.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你打算用来培养植物的东西吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is what you're gonna use to make all your little plants?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.44,0:32:02.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我最好是别把它掉地上咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So I guess it's safe to say that I shouldn't drop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.61,0:32:03.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手  塞琳娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stop, Selina.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.06,0:32:06.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以让你走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I will let you leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.60,0:32:07.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let me?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.72,0:32:12.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不打算把我变成个什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're not gonna turn me into some
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.06,0:32:15.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天竺葵之类的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}geranium type thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.67,0:32:18.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太好心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's so generous.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.45,0:32:21.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.72,0:32:27.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能跟他们站在一边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How can you side with them?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.23,0:32:31.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些伤害我们的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All the people who hurt us.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.75,0:32:36.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他们是无辜的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You think they're innocent.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.29,0:32:39.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都有罪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They're guilty.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.14,0:32:43.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个城市里的每一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Every person in this city.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.52,0:32:46.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都在吐出毒素\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They spew out poison.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.98,0:32:50.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么会没被那窒息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How are you not choking on it?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.47,0:32:55.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一让我窒息的  艾薇  就是你的疯狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The only thing that I'm choking on, Ivy, is your insanity.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.97,0:33:07.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该那么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You shouldn't have done that.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.25,0:33:10.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你要死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now you're gonna die.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.57,0:33:11.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾薇  看下面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ivy, look down.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.12,0:33:22.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.28,0:33:23.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.31,0:33:26.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那现在怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, what happens now?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.09,0:33:29.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们互相残杀吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We kill each other?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.15,0:33:30.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可以这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's an option.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.31,0:33:33.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一向觉得自己比我强\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You always did think you were better than me.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.50,0:33:35.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是的  我本是你的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's not true. I was your friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.28,0:33:37.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们曾是朋友  艾薇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We were friends, Ivy.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.44,0:33:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己也这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You said so yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.07,0:33:43.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是很久以前了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That was a long time ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.03,0:33:46.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在是另一个人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm a different person now.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.15,0:33:52.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我想要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This isn't what I want.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.84,0:34:12.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再别碍我的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't get in my way again.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.59,0:34:31.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手举起来  带武器了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Lift your hands up. Got any weapons?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.63,0:34:35.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差点以为这不会是一场愉快的谈话了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'd almost think this wasn't going to be a friendly conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.37,0:34:37.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是谨慎而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just being careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.60,0:34:38.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们没问题  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- They're clean. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.56,0:34:40.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明智\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Smart lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.09,0:34:45.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你想要奈何岛一切收入的30%\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So you said you wanted 30% of everything in the Narrows.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.94,0:34:47.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What if I told you
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.66,0:34:49.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有更好的东西可以给你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I had something more valuable to offer?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.77,0:34:52.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Such as?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.32,0:34:54.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吉姆·戈登\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Jim Gordon.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.59,0:35:00.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道别人不知道的他犯下的罪行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know crimes he's committed no one else does.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.50,0:35:02.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可以让你得以控制他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It would give you control over him.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.45,0:35:06.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这肯定比这里的三成收入更有价值\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Surely that's worth more than 30% of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.05,0:35:08.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己就有吉姆·戈登的黑料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have my own dirt on Jim Gordon.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.18,0:35:09.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不能用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But you can't use it.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.77,0:35:13.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则  你也不会坐在这里威胁我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Otherwise, you wouldn't be sitting there threatening me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.92,0:35:15.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Would you?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.51,0:35:19.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,索菲娅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sofia,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.31,0:35:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受我的交易吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}take my deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.00,0:35:31.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有更好的办法能让戈登顺从我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have a better way to bring Gordon around.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.17,0:35:35.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.19,0:35:39.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撑住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stay with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.11,0:35:40.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撑住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stay with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.11,0:35:45.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你别想活着出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're never gonna get out of here alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.87,0:35:48.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的人会杀了你的  -你的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- My people are gonna kill you! - Your people?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.57,0:35:50.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为这些枪是谁藏的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who do you think planted these guns?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.42,0:35:52.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You can come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.66,0:35:59.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊  医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How you doing, Doc?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.26,0:36:03.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要让桑普森掌管奈何岛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm having Sampson run the Narrows.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.50,0:36:06.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该趁有机会时杀了我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, you should've killed me when you had the chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.55,0:36:07.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Mm, the fact that you didn't
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.24,0:36:09.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让我知道了我需要的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}told me everything I needed to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.80,0:36:12.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.22,0:36:17.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于我们是家人  我就只废你一只手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Since we're family, I'm only going to do one hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.13,0:36:34.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她丢到街上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Throw her on the streets.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.62,0:36:38.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让奈何岛看到他们女王的惨相\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let the Narrows see their queen.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.64,0:36:53.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现场情况依然混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The scene here remains largely out of control
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.02,0:36:55.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但艾薇·佩帕依然在逃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but Ivy Pepper remains at large.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.30,0:36:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调查人员仍在场内...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now, inside, we have a team of investigators...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.50,0:37:08.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.82,0:37:11.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.08,0:37:14.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.12,0:37:26.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.88,0:37:29.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  打扰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sir? Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.99,0:37:31.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是亲属吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you family?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.02,0:37:34.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是警察\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm a cop.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.51,0:37:38.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不肯说是谁干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She wouldn't tell us who do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.11,0:37:46.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用她说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She didn't have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.20,0:37:58.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿卡姆可不常有自愿入院的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Arkham doesn't get many volunteers.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.58,0:38:01.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我是谁吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You do know who I am, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.61,0:38:04.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,精神病罪犯足以概括了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Criminally-insane pretty much covers it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.94,0:38:06.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看好条款\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Read...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.38,0:38:07.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就签字吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and sign.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.17,0:38:09.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll be back.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.18,0:38:18.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真讨厌被你说对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hate that you were right about this,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.58,0:38:21.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这能保证她的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but it'll keep her safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.40,0:38:22.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, Ed?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.87,0:38:24.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西有两只眼睛  却看不见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What has two eyes but can't see?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.47,0:38:25.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, this again.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.13,0:38:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两根针\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Two needles.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.51,0:38:30.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半个"密西西比"  谁在乎呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Half of "Mississippi." Who cares?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.63,0:38:34.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该在乎  爱德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You should, Ed.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.39,0:38:42.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道你会来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I knew you'd come!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.16,0:38:47.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道你会看懂我的信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I knew you'd understand my letter!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.02,0:38:48.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道我会...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How did you know I'd be...?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.98,0:38:50.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.49,0:38:52.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是在跟你说话  爱德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not talking to you, Ed.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.95,0:38:55.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在跟他说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm talking to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.05,0:39:00.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他读到我的信了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He read my letter!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.59,0:39:05.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,读一下每句话的第一个词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Read the first word of each sentence.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.16,0:39:12.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"请把爱德带来阿卡姆  我才能释放你"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Please bring Ed to Arkham so I can set you free."
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.71,0:39:14.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西有两只眼睛  却看不见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What has two eyes but can't see
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.53,0:39:16.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他面前发生的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}what's happening in front of him?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.12,0:39:17.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德·尼格玛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ed Nygma!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.47,0:39:21.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我来是为了救小莱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No. I came here to save Lee.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.07,0:39:22.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他读了我的信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He read my letter!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.99,0:39:24.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.55,0:39:25.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're wrong!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.29,0:39:27.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是爱德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I am Ed!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.85,0:39:29.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德华·尼格玛  仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Edward Nygma! That is it!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.95,0:39:32.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小莱相信我  她看得到真正的我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Lee believes in me. She sees me for who I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.47,0:39:35.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我看到了他  爱德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I see him, Ed!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.33,0:39:36.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.74,0:39:41.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小莱·汤普金斯或许让爱德变强大了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Lee Thompkins may have made Ed strong,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.30,0:39:44.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我看得到另一个你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but I see the other you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.36,0:39:50.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个我不敢说他名字的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The one whose name I wouldn't speak.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.04,0:39:53.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但因为他赢得了这个资格\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But because he has earned it,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.17,0:39:57.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也因为我需要他  我要说出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and because I need him, I'm saying it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.79,0:39:59.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  求你  不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, please! Please don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.68,0:40:02.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我需要你  -不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- I need you... - Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.25,0:40:05.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谜语人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Riddler.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.38,0:40:29.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们开工吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Shall we get to work?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.18,0:40:42.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.57,0:40:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么从屋顶下来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}how'd you make it off the roof, then?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.17,0:40:48.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旁边大楼的消防梯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A fire escape on the next building.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.14,0:40:51.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要逃离戈登\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why'd you run from Gordon?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.76,0:40:54.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你大可告诉他那是你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, you could've told him it was you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.17,0:40:58.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.99,0:41:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是  不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I just... couldn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.02,0:41:10.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要帮助他人  阿尔弗雷德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm going to help people, Alfred.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.30,0:41:14.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我要为此接受自己的全部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And if that means accepting every part of myself,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.14,0:41:16.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不论好坏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}good and bad,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.32,0:41:19.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}then I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.94,0:41:25.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.82,0:41:28.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母会希望如此的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's what my parents would have wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.39,0:41:31.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你父母会非常为你骄傲的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Your parents would be very proud of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.86,0:41:37.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为你骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm proud of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.98,0:41:44.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔弗雷德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Alfred?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.71,0:41:49.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你需要车回哥谭  我可以送你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you need a ride back to Gotham, I can drive you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.88,0:41:52.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪都不去  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, I'm not going anywhere, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.89,0:41:55.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm home.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.40,0:42:13.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Congratulations.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.00,0:42:16.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说你挽救了大局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I heard you saved the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.34,0:42:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Good job.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.37,0:42:21.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能做警监\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's a reason you're captain,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.66,0:42:25.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我只是个给酒鬼倒酒的50岁窝囊废是有原因的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I'm a 50-year-old screw-up pouring shots for barflies.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.79,0:42:30.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确有原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's a reason, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.36,0:42:31.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不是你想的那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's not what you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:34.67,0:42:36.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞砸了  哈维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I screwed up, Harv.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.57,0:42:38.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞砸得很严重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I screwed up bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:39.70,0:42:41.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你帮忙才能拨乱反正\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I'm gonna need your help to make it right.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:43.88,0:42:45.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是索菲娅雇了猪头人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sofia hired the Pyg.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.51,0:42:48.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I knew.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:50.94,0:42:52.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明明知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I knew,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.00,0:42:55.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是掩盖了真相\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I covered it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.44,0:43:08.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我要扳倒她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And now I'm gonna take her down.

