I can't believe Metro News 1 is just
forwarding you all this fan mail now.
- I know. I quit, like, four months ago.
- Wow, you had more fans than I thought.
And only about 60% of them
are prison inmates.
What are these guys thinking?
I am way past my dating prisoners phase.
It's like, hello,
I'm not 19 anymore, you know?
Lottery girl's on.
I just feel sorry for these women.
This is where broadcast careers go to die.
Check it out. I make it fun.
I invented a little game.
Tonight's lotto numbers are...
...nineteen...
Age you moved to New York
after a photographer "discovered" you
at a food court
and said he'd get you in Vogue magazine.
Fifty-three...
Number of semi-nude pictures
he took of you
before you realized he had no connection
to Vogue magazine.
- Twenty-two...
- Age you claim you are.
- Thirty-one...
- Age you actually are.
Forty-five.
Number of minutes it would
take me to get you into a cab,
- out of your dress, and into my Jacuzzi.
- And the super big ball is...
What happens after
we get out of the Jacuzzi.
What up?
Kids, by the winter of 2009,
Robin had been unemployed for months.
But there was a glimmer of hope.
- Hey!
- Hey, how'd the audition go?
Well, I went in there feeling really good.
I heard it was just me
up against two other girls.
Listening.
- Hi.
Robin Scherbatsky.
And you are?
You've obviously
never spent any time in Denver.
Rochelle Harper, News Center 12.
We were only the number one station
in the Rockies for five straight years.
I was an anchor here in town
at Metro News 1.
Ooh, an anchor.
You must have a killer signoff phrase.
- I'm sorry?
- You gotta have a killer signoff phrase.
Like Walter Cronkite.
"And that's the way it is. "
So what's yours?
Well, I would just always end
with a simple
"From all of us here at Metro News 1,
have a good evening. "
Mine is "From all of us here
at Barney's apartment, get out. "
You didn't let those reporter bitches
psych you out, did you?
And the President's economic team is
hoping to have a proposal before Congress
by the end of the month.
From all of us here at News 10,
have a good evening.
So, good night, New York.
And may the road ahead
be lit with dreams and tomorrows.
Which are lit with dreams, also.
Wow. That's terrible. And bad, also.
I wasn't done.
Stand tall, New York.
Trustworthy. Recycling.
Wear a condom.
Wear a condom?
I'm not gonna be
the new Channel 10 anchor, am I?
This just in. No.
Maybe the problem is your resumé.
See how mine is lean and mean?
Yours is too cluttered.
Like everything on your resumé
is so relevant.
"Program Director,
88.1 Wesleyan University Radio?"
- Oh, God.
- Dr. X? You're still bragging about Dr. X?
- Who was Dr. X?
- Nobody knows.
- He was this genius mystery DJ.
- It was Ted.
- His identity remains a secret to this day.
But this phantom of the airwaves
changed the very face of college radio.
- It was Ted.
- And your show sucked.
Dr. X here, shooting truth bullets
at you from an undisclosed location.
Because if they knew where I was,
they'd shut me down.
You're on the third floor of the Student
Center next to the game room, you tool.
I've been getting a lot of letters
about my segment
on how racist the school's meal plan is.
How are you getting letters
if no one knows where you are, douche?
That's why I'm organizing a happening
outside the dining hall,
Monday at midnight.
It's high time
the food service puppet masters
took ignorance and injustice off the menu.
Hey, Ted,
we need a fourth for foosball.
What are you doing in here, anyway?
Dude, get out of here!
I'll be there in a second.
So, remember, dining hall,
Monday, midnight.
Another Dr. X happening.
I'll be there,
because X marks the spot-ot-ot-ot.
If you think people liked your show,
they did not-ot-ot-ot.
This is weird. Look what got mixed in
- with your fan mail.
- What?
It's from the U.S. Department
of Immigration.
It's postmarked two months ago.
- Oh, boy.
- What is it?
It's about my work visa.
Unless I can find a job
in the next seven days,
they're gonna send me back to Canada.
I can't believe
you might be kicked out of the country.
I know. My whole life is here.
No. We won't let this happen.
I mean, one of us will help you find a job.
Yeah, I bet I can get you
something at my school.
No, guys. It doesn't work that way.
Robin only gets her work visa
if she gets a job in her field.
I mean, you know what? I guess you
could stay if you married a U.S. citizen.
Yeah, that could work.
No, no. They could never process that and
make it official in time. That won't work.
I'm screwed. I've been sending out
my reel for three months, and nothing.
Well, maybe there's something in your reel
that people aren't responding to.
Let's take a look at it, right?
That's a good question, Norm.
Okay, the first thing is from when I was
a cub reporter for Channel 22 in Red Deer.
In Alberta. In Canada.
Ooh.
- Canada.
- Right.
Well, the snow's coming down pretty hard,
but these intrepid fishermen are
still happy to be out competing,
in Lake Athabasca's Bass
Fishing Jamboree, an August 1st tradition.
Back to you, Norm.
What? That was my first job.
It shows where I came from.
Unless a bear attacks you
in the next three seconds
and you snap its neck with your legs,
that has no business being on your reel.
No, no, I get it, I get it.
Where you're from
is part of who you're selling.
For instance,
under Special Skills on my resumé,
I mention that back in Minnesota,
I was the 1995 Nicollet County
Slam Dunk Champion.
You put dunk champion on your resumé?
Yeah, why wouldn't you?
A lot of companies have basketball teams.
It's good for them to know
that Vanilla Thunder
can still take the rock to the hole.
- They called you Vanilla Thunder?
- Yeah, Vanilla Thunder.
The Ghost in the Post.
The Human Turnstile.
I didn't play that much D.
- You can't still dunk.
- Of course I can.
- Well, I mean, I could, until recently.
- Until the injury.
- It's called iliopsoas tendonitis.
- Yikes. That sounds bad.
It's more commonly known
as dancer's hip.
Dr. Goodman...
Oh, come on! lliopsoas tendonitis.
That's what it's called.
That's all it's called.
Iliopsoas tendonitis.
It's a basketball injury.
You know, it's no big whoop.
Dancer's hip, Marshall has
something called dancer's hip.
Okay, no, no, okay.
They only call it that, look, because
it's very common with ballet dancers.
So, tell me, do any of the other little girls
in your class have dancer's hip?
Yeah, sure.
- I have more of a technical question.
- Yes?
Is it easier to dance
when you don't have external genitalia?
Good, don't build to that,
just go right for it.
Guys, come on.
Marshall didn't get this injury from dancing.
Thank you, Lily.
Clearly, the stirrups were set a little
too wide during his last trip to the gyno.
Guys, guys, I hate to cut you off
before Marshall bursts into tears,
but, Robin, check this out. What you need
is an awesome video resumé.
Like mine. I present
barneysvideoresume. com.
Oh! Hello.
Barney Stinson,
you've achieved great success in business,
athletics and personal relationships and
have been an inspiration to many people.
Is that you? Are you interviewing yourself?
How can it be me? That guy's British.
What would you recommend
to your numerous admirers
who want to reach their highest potential?
And a wee bit Scottish.
The first thing you need to know about
success is that it doesn't just come to you.
Most people associate success with money
and power, but really, it's a state of mind.
You had to be on a motorcycle to say that?
And when it comes to success,
the only limit is that there are no limits.
Hey, I didn't know you knew how to
stand near a horse, that's impressive.
Barney, I don't get it. You don't do
a damn thing in any of these clips.
Exactly. Because that's who
Corporate America wants,
people who seem like bold risk takers,
but never actually do anything.
Actually doing things gets you fired.
In fact, I'm writing a book
on this very phenomenon.
Really, you're writing a book?
No, that would be doing...
Are you even listening?
All my life, I have dared
to go past what is possible.
To the impossible?
Actually, past that,
to the place where the possible
and the impossible meet to become
the possimpible.
The possimpible? Really?
Inventing your own word
shows creativity and vision.
Visativity.
If I can leave you with one thought,
it's this,
nothing and everything is possimpible.
Barney Stinson, Barney Stinson
That guy's awesome
Is that you again?
Are you singing a song about yourself?
Absolutely not. That would be lame.
Stinson, Barney Stinson
singing this song
That would be really lame
One of the many admirers
who think that guy's awesome
Perfect and available
Awesome, awesome, awesome
awesome, awesome, awesome
Awesome! Awesome!
Awesome, awesome, awesome
awesome, awesome, awesome
Awesome!
That baby got me 11 job offers.
- No. No way.
- Yeah.
- Barney, that was ridiculous and insane.
- Insane-ulous.
- Make me one.
- What?
- Yes, now you're talking.
I'm about to be deported. I'll try anything.
Okay, we better get started.
There's a lot to shoot,
and I don't think I can use any
of the footage I already have of you.
What footage do you already have of me?
Let's just get started.
Sweetie, are you still upset
about the dancer's hip jokes?
No.
We were just kidding.
We all know it's a basketball injury.
Yeah, no, totally.
- Lily, I have something I need to tell you.
- What is it?
I dance more than you know.
- What?
- I dance, more than you know.
I don't know how to respond to that.
So, Robin, what does
being a reporter mean to you?
- Well, ever since I was a little kid...
- Cut!
Robin, you're getting bogged down
in specifics.
I need you to just say vague,
confident-sounding buzzwords,
like synergy and dynamism.
You can make up a word, like linkativity.
How will sounding like an idiot
get me hired anywhere?
Okay, fine. Don't do it.
Anyway, I'm sure there are plenty of
exciting stories to cover back in Canada.
I just read that the mayor of Winnipeg's
nephew went ice fishing
and caught himself a 16-pound walleye.
"Reporting live from the worst place
in the world, I'm Robin Scherbatsky. "
Okay, fine. Roll camera.
- Connectitude.
- Love it.
- Transformatation.
- Earn it!
Linkativity!
Yeah, linkativity's mine.
So, how much dancing
are we talking about?
I don't... I guess I'd say medium.
Why are you dancing so much,
and why don't I know about it?
It's something I do when I'm alone.
You know, like if something good happens,
I get excited and I need to move,
and I just...
I don't know. I don't want to
even talk about this anymore.
So that's how you injured your hip?
Hey, did you hear? They're giving us
a half day today. We can leave at 2:00.
Great! Thanks, Herm.
Barney, these costumes are ridiculous.
Plus, the Amazon warrior princess armor
gave me a rash.
Cards on the table, you weren't
the first lady to wear that in here.
But it conveyed power. And so will this.
What I need you to do now
is break these 15 bricks
with your forehead.
What? But you didn't do a damn thing
in your video.
You just stood near a horse
and sat on a motorcycle.
That's because I'm a man.
You're a woman.
The assumption
is that you can't do anything.
- But you have to prove society wrong.
- I can't break 15 bricks with my forehead.
Robin, it's not 1950 anymore. Yes, you can.
- I'm out of here.
- What? Why?
None of this is going to help me get a job.
I'm about to get kicked out of the country.
I know what I have to do.
Is this where the lottery girl auditions are?
Yeah, right here.
So, kids, your Aunt Robin
had reached her low point.
She was auditioning to be the lottery girl.
- And tonight's lotto numbers are...
- Hold it.
Say the line before you press the button.
- It builds the suspense.
Okay.
And tonight's lotto numbers are...
- Seventeen...
- Stop her.
- Hold it.
- Why did she say it like that?
It's like she's not even happy
about the 17 coming up.
- She seems mean.
- Yeah, she seems super-mean.
Can you take another run at 17 for us?
Seventeen.
Okay, I don't even understand
what she's doing.
- Let me try something.
- All right.
Try being a little more wry.
Wry? About the number 17?
- Wry, with a little bit of a...
- Twinkle.
...twinkle.
Seventeen.
That was great!
Hey, Marsh, I got you a light beer.
I know how you dancers
are always counting calories.
It's not funny, all right?
The doctor says if it gets any worse,
I might need surgery.
Vaginal rejuvenation surgery?
You know who didn't do a lot
of operating on vaginas in college?
- Who?
- Dr. X.
- He did just fine!
- You know what?
Both of you geniuses need to take
that weak-ass crap off your resumés.
I mean, you are not Dr. X anymore,
and you cannot dunk anymore.
Let it go.
So Marshall and I
are the only people at this table
with weak-ass crap on their resumés?
What are you implying?
Oh. Oh, wow. I don't know!
Does the date July 4th, 1995
mean anything to you?
You son of a bitch.
Time! And the new champion, with
29 hot dogs, Lily "The Belly" Aldrin!
How is that relevant
to teaching kindergarten?
It teaches kids that
I can eat a lot of hot dogs very quickly.
- Yeah, but you can't do it anymore!
- You can't dunk anymore, lady-hips!
- How dare you! These hips can...
- Guys, guys!
I didn't even get the lotto girl gig.
I have to move back to Canada.
I can't believe this.
I remember the night
before I moved down here.
They threw a going-away party for me.
They gave me a camera so I could
take pictures and send them home.
And everyone was so sure
I was gonna be such a big success.
I'm really gonna miss you guys.
- What happened?
- Robin has to move back to Canada.
Oh, my God. How awful.
I mean, for one thing,
it's gonna be a really long commute.
What do you mean?
I finished your video resumé on my own,
messenger-ed it
to every station in the city.
A guy from Channel 8 called. He loved you.
- He wanted you to come in and audition.
- Oh, my God!
I told him no.
Robin Scherbatsky doesn't audition.
- He gives you the job or nothing.
- So I got the job?
No. He cursed me out and hung up.
But then Channel 12 called.
They also loved you.
They offered you a job
hosting their new morning talk show.
Barney, that's amazing!
- I told them to shove it.
- Dude!
Which only made them want you more.
So, they jacked up their offer by 10%.
Congratulations, Miss Scherbatsky.
It looks like you're gonna have to stay.
- You're not about to dance, are you?
- No, I'm good. I'll do it later.
Oh, my God. How did you pull this off?
- I am the master of the possimpible.
- You really are. Thank you.
So,
thanks to your Uncle Barney,
we got to keep your Aunt Robin.
There's so much stuff in my life
No room for me to grow
And the rest of us decided
it was time to let some things go.
Well, except for Lily.
- And time!
- What's the count?
Thirty-three!
Under the waterfall
It's cool and cold and clear
Why is no one coming to my happenings?