1
00:00:02,207 --> 00:00:05,074
天呐 你知道到时候派对上有香槟对吧
Oh, my god! You know that there is gonna be champagne at this party, right?

2
00:00:05,076 --> 00:00:06,943
知道 知道
I know, I know.

3
00:00:06,945 --> 00:00:08,444
但等我们到了那儿啊
But we're gonna get there and it's gonna be

4
00:00:08,446 --> 00:00:10,713
那可是人人都在夸你的新书呢
everyone congratulating you on your book,

5
00:00:10,715 --> 00:00:12,782
大伙说啊 这本书可算是开天眼了
saying, "This is a revelation!

6
00:00:12,784 --> 00:00:14,951
你一定可以在咱们的见证下终结贫困的
You're gonna end poverty in our time.

7
00:00:14,953 --> 00:00:17,620
这可是本前无古人 后无来者 不分类型 史上最强的神书啊
This is the greatest book anyone's ever written in any genre."

8
00:00:17,622 --> 00:00:19,255
只有你会这么说 亲爱的
You're the only one that says that, sweetie.

9
00:00:19,257 --> 00:00:20,323
呃 这是事实啊
Well, it's true.

10
00:00:20,325 --> 00:00:23,660
在你被一大波粉丝们淹没之前
So before I lose you to your adoring public,

11
00:00:23,662 --> 00:00:25,662
我想花点时间 就咱俩
I just want to take a moment, you and I,

12
00:00:25,664 --> 00:00:29,032
庆祝一下这最美好的一年
To celebrate the best year of our lives.

13
00:00:29,900 --> 00:00:31,267
新年快乐
Happy new year.

14
00:00:31,269 --> 00:00:32,568
新年快乐
Happy new year.

15
00:00:37,475 --> 00:00:40,109
今晚咱嗨到底
We go big tonight!

16
00:00:40,111 --> 00:00:41,611
别激动啊大兄弟
Easy there, buddy.

17
00:00:41,613 --> 00:00:43,446
我们都已经老了 别忘了
We're old people, remember?

18
00:00:43,448 --> 00:00:45,315
我们连中发都已经好久没玩了
We haven't even gone medium sized in forever.

19
00:00:45,317 --> 00:00:48,918
穿着这裙子把你拖回家 我可吃不消
And I cannot carry you home in this dress.

20
00:00:48,920 --> 00:00:50,019
亲爱的 放轻松
Sweetie, relax.

21
00:00:50,021 --> 00:00:51,254
我有数
I got this.

22
00:00:51,256 --> 00:00:52,588
信你才怪
Yeah, right.

23
00:00:52,590 --> 00:00:54,824
接下来会怎样我一清二楚
I can see your whole future.

24
00:00:54,826 --> 00:00:57,660
明天你一定宿醉到头疼死
You are gonna be so hungover tomorrow.

25
00:00:57,662 --> 00:00:59,095
-我一定没事的  -嗯
-I'm gonna be fine. -Hmm.

26
00:00:59,097 --> 00:01:01,431
我可是发过誓的 别忘了
I made a vow, remember?

27
00:01:01,433 --> 00:01:02,298
孩子们
Kids...

28
00:01:02,300 --> 00:01:03,466
关于这个誓背后的故事
The story behind that vow

29
00:01:03,468 --> 00:01:06,202
发生在巴尼和罗宾婚礼那天早上
took place the morning of Barney and Robin's wedding.

30
00:01:06,204 --> 00:01:09,172
你瞧 在前一天晚上喝大发之后
You see, after drinking way too much the night before,

31
00:01:09,174 --> 00:01:11,174
你们巴尼叔叔的回忆里
This is all your uncle Barney remembers

32
00:01:11,176 --> 00:01:13,343
他婚礼那天的前两个小时是这样的
from the first two hours of his wedding day.

33
00:01:19,983 --> 00:01:21,384
就是这样
And that's it.

34
00:01:21,386 --> 00:01:22,518
而我们其余四个的
Now here's how the rest of us

35
00:01:22,520 --> 00:01:24,020
记忆里是这样的
remember those two hours.

36
00:01:25,457 --> 00:01:26,389
找到他了
Found him.

37
00:01:28,392 --> 00:01:30,960
你知道吗 这其实比我预期的要好多了
You know, he looks better than I thought he would.

38
00:01:30,962 --> 00:01:34,530
太阳公公晒屁股啦
Rise and shine.

39
00:01:34,532 --> 00:01:36,432
抬起腿来 咱来一发
Up and at 'em, let's do this.

40
00:01:37,334 --> 00:01:38,868
煤气泄漏了
There's a gas leak!

41
00:01:39,837 --> 00:01:41,204
宾馆着火了
The building's on fire!

42
00:01:42,940 --> 00:01:44,073
你的鞋和皮带不搭
Your shoes don't match your belt!

43
00:01:54,185 --> 00:01:55,451
大事不妙
Uh-oh.

44
00:01:55,395 --> 00:01:58,451
{\a10}{\fs18}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H000000&}{\bord1}周日\N早上8点\N　\N

45
00:01:56,885 --> 00:01:58,451
{\a10}{\fs18}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H000000&}{\bord1}婚礼前10小时

46
00:02:00,520 --> 00:02:02,520
{\a1}{\fs17}　　　　 老爸\N　　　  　　 老妈\N　　 　　 浪漫史\N{\fs16}{\bord1}{\3c&H00DCE1&}　　  　　　　第九季  第十八集\N
{\fnDaxlinePro-Regular}{\fs19}{\b0}{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\3c&H2F2F2F&}{\4c&H000000&}{\a1}　　　　　S09E18 Rally

47
00:02:02,630 --> 00:02:06,130
{\fs16}{\bord1}翻译: @毒舌的吊儿郎当 @仑仔鱼虾一整晚\N{\bord1}{\3c&H00DCE1&}@Mr_Gao703 @云湾森川如风 @CIA_Kevin

48
00:02:06,131 --> 00:02:09,231
{\fs17}{\3c&H00DCE1&}{\bord1}统筹+校对+后期+时间轴+压制\N{\3c&H007EFF&}大洋彼岸牵肠挂肚肉鸭鸭 十四时外辗转难眠小花花

49
00:02:09,415 --> 00:02:11,815
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献

50
00:02:11,936 --> 00:02:14,303
好吧 目测我的未婚夫尿裤子了
Okay, I think my fiance peed himself a little.

51
00:02:14,806 --> 00:02:17,140
噢 到明天我就能说
Oh, tomorrow I'm gonna be able to say

52
00:02:17,142 --> 00:02:19,476
我老公尿裤子了
My husband peed himself a little.

53
00:02:19,478 --> 00:02:20,944
别担心
Don't worry.

54
00:02:20,946 --> 00:02:22,112
是我不小心把冰茶溅上去了
I accidentally spilled some iced tea on him.

55
00:02:22,114 --> 00:02:23,346
哦 那就好
Oh, thank god.

56
00:02:23,348 --> 00:02:25,682
其实我并没有把冰茶溅上去
I didn't really spill some iced tea on him.

57
00:02:25,684 --> 00:02:27,283
天呐 这可不妙
Oh, god, this is bad.

58
00:02:27,285 --> 00:02:29,019
再过两个小时就要在灯塔那里
We're doing family wedding pictures

59
00:02:29,021 --> 00:02:31,154
拍结婚全家福了
at the lighthouse in two hours.

60
00:02:31,156 --> 00:02:32,889
这全都是我爸买的单
My father is paying for the whole thing.

61
00:02:32,891 --> 00:02:34,391
巴尼要是不出现 他非杀了他不可
He's gonna kill barney if he doesn't show up.

62
00:02:34,393 --> 00:02:36,059
好啦 你爸确实强悍了点
Come on, your dad's tough.

63
00:02:36,061 --> 00:02:38,328
但一次小小的宿醉他总不会不理解吧
But won't he understand a good old fashioned hangover?

64
00:02:38,330 --> 00:02:40,563
我爸的血腥玛丽配方可是
My father's recipe for a Bloody Mary

65
00:02:40,565 --> 00:02:43,166
把番茄汁换成狼血
trades out tomato juice for wolf's blood.

66
00:02:43,168 --> 00:02:44,501
真剽悍
Ooh. Ooh.

67
00:02:44,503 --> 00:02:45,735
血腥玛丽
Bloody Mary?

68
00:02:45,737 --> 00:02:48,571
听起来倒更像是血腥恐惧
Sounds more like a Bloody Scary.

69
00:02:49,373 --> 00:02:50,507
我再说一遍
I'm gonna say it again.

70
00:02:50,509 --> 00:02:51,875
-哦 等一下  -血腥玛丽 听起来倒更像...
-Uh, hold on. -Bloody mary? Sounds more...

71
00:02:51,877 --> 00:02:53,076
你们忘了
You guys are forgetting

72
00:02:53,078 --> 00:02:55,712
巴尼•斯丁森有个超能力
Barney Stinson has a super power.

73
00:02:56,881 --> 00:02:58,715
他从来拍不出难看的照片
He can't take a bad photo.

74
00:03:00,084 --> 00:03:01,851
扶好 好嘞
Okay, here.

75
00:03:01,853 --> 00:03:03,219
瞧好了
Watch.

76
00:03:07,058 --> 00:03:08,191
伙计们 巴尼可能真的挂了
Guys, Barney may be dead.

77
00:03:08,193 --> 00:03:09,359
行了
That's it!

78
00:03:09,361 --> 00:03:11,528
我跟你们说 我们都真心太老了
You know what? We are all now seriously too old

79
00:03:11,530 --> 00:03:12,996
这种傻事咱做不起
To keep doing this to ourselves!

80
00:03:12,998 --> 00:03:14,497
我在此发誓
I vow here and now

81
00:03:14,499 --> 00:03:18,101
从今以后绝对不会再喝成这个样子
That I shall never again get that drunk in my life!

82
00:03:18,103 --> 00:03:20,670
没错 他后来没守住誓约
Yeah, he'd wind up breaking that vow.

83
00:03:20,672 --> 00:03:22,906
而且只要我毛发依然旺盛
And I will not break that vow

84
00:03:22,908 --> 00:03:25,275
就绝对不会破这个誓
As sure as I will always have a full head of hair!

85
00:03:25,277 --> 00:03:27,877
{\a6}2020年

86
00:03:25,277 --> 00:03:27,877
今天的另一场竞选
In other elections today,

87
00:03:27,879 --> 00:03:30,013
是角逐纽约州最高法官席位
in the race for New York State Supreme Court,

88
00:03:30,015 --> 00:03:31,281
布莱德•莫里斯法官
Judge Brad Morris...

89
00:03:31,283 --> 00:03:33,349
天呐 瞧瞧这身肉
Mmm, just look at him.

90
00:03:33,351 --> 00:03:35,018
我真想摸个遍
I would love to rub that down.

91
00:03:35,020 --> 00:03:36,086
失态了
sorry.

92
00:03:36,088 --> 00:03:40,223
其支持率正以可观的优势领先马修•艾瑞克森法官
Has increased his sizable lead ver judge Marshall Eriksen.

93
00:03:40,225 --> 00:03:42,225
这本该是个庆功会的
It was supposed to be a victory party.

94
00:03:42,227 --> 00:03:44,227
亲爱的 你已经很出色了
You ran a great campaign, baby.

95
00:03:44,229 --> 00:03:47,330
是啊 但是这是我这辈子神经最紧张的三周了
Yeah, but it was the most stressful three weeks of my life!

96
00:03:49,700 --> 00:03:51,601
{\a6}四小时后

97
00:03:49,700 --> 00:03:51,601
从其它地区的结果看 出现了一次惊天逆转
And in other results, a surprise comeback.

98
00:03:51,603 --> 00:03:54,804
我们现在宣布纽约州立最高法院竞选的获胜者是
We are now ready to call the new york state supreme court race

99
00:03:54,806 --> 00:03:56,706
是法官马修•艾瑞克森
for judge Marshall Eriksen.

100
00:03:58,376 --> 00:04:00,310
几分钟后 我们将会对法官艾瑞克森
We'll go to judge Eriksen for a live statement

101
00:04:00,312 --> 00:04:02,078
进行现场采访
in just a few minutes.

102
00:04:02,080 --> 00:04:04,047
跟大软糖法官再说一遍
Come again for judge fudge?

103
00:04:05,249 --> 00:04:06,382
作为你们的下一任专员...
As your next commissioner...

104
00:04:06,384 --> 00:04:08,551
州立最高法院法官
State supreme court judge.

105
00:04:08,553 --> 00:04:10,086
...在高谭市...
...of gotham city...

106
00:04:08,553 --> 00:04:15,492
{\a6}这段马修喝醉了 把自己当成蝙蝠侠里的人物

107
00:04:10,088 --> 00:04:12,288
纽约州
the state of new york.

108
00:04:12,290 --> 00:04:15,492
...我起誓会让蝙蝠侠更加努力工作
...I vow to make batman work harder.

109
00:04:15,494 --> 00:04:16,793
我说啊
I say

110
00:04:16,795 --> 00:04:19,662
不管多大事都来找蝙蝠侠吧
shine that bat-signal even for small stuff.

111
00:04:19,664 --> 00:04:22,132
比如 嗯 铲雪啊
like, uh, shoveling snow.

112
00:04:22,134 --> 00:04:26,236
或者比如 嗯 警马在公园里拉屎了之类的
or, like, uh, if a police horse dumps out in the park.

113
00:04:26,238 --> 00:04:28,638
好了 就说到这 谢谢  
Okay, well, that will be all at this time, thank you.

114
00:04:28,640 --> 00:04:30,306
-就说到这  -好了
-That's all. -Okay.

115
00:04:30,308 --> 00:04:31,341
晚安
Mmm, good night.

116
00:04:31,343 --> 00:04:33,009
再也不这样了
Never again!

117
00:04:33,011 --> 00:04:34,611
我发誓
I vow it!

118
00:04:34,613 --> 00:04:36,246
我现在更担心的是几个小时之后
I am more worried about the vows I have to take

119
00:04:36,248 --> 00:04:38,815
我要和这一滩货宣誓了
with this useless pile of garbage a few hours from now.

120
00:04:38,817 --> 00:04:40,083
我们该怎么办啊
What do we do?

121
00:04:40,085 --> 00:04:41,284
你们说这有多讽刺
You guys see the irony here.

122
00:04:41,286 --> 00:04:42,452
唯一一个可能让
The only person who could possibly get

123
00:04:42,454 --> 00:04:44,020
巴尼醒过来的人
Barney back on his feet

124
00:04:44,022 --> 00:04:45,155
就是巴尼自己
is barney.

125
00:04:45,157 --> 00:04:46,089
是这样的 这些年来
See, over the years,

126
00:04:46,091 --> 00:04:47,323
我们都喝过一样东西
We'd all come to experience

127
00:04:47,325 --> 00:04:49,192
巴尼称之为...
something barney called...

128
00:04:49,194 --> 00:04:51,995
斯丁森宿醉灵
Stinson's hangover fixer elixir!

129
00:04:51,997 --> 00:04:53,096
风靡全国
The most effective

130
00:04:53,098 --> 00:04:54,264
有史以来超级无敌有效的
post-bender, head's-too-tender ender

131
00:04:54,266 --> 00:04:55,265
解酒神器
from here to denver.

132
00:04:55,267 --> 00:04:56,466
这里面有什么
What's in it?

133
00:04:56,468 --> 00:04:57,967
-问得好  -啊 我收回
-Glad you asked. -Ah, I take it back.

134
00:04:57,969 --> 00:04:59,969
-哥伦比亚大学 1941年...  -我收回还不行吗
-Columbia university, 1941... -I take it back, I take it back.

135
00:04:59,971 --> 00:05:01,838
富兰克林•德拉诺•罗斯福总统
president Franklin Delano Roosevelt,

136
00:05:01,840 --> 00:05:02,841
众所周知他是一个世界闻名的
whom we all know is most famous 

137
00:05:02,841 --> 00:05:04,441
超级酒鬼
for being a world-class drunk,

138
00:05:04,443 --> 00:05:06,976
签署了一项顶级机密的科学项目
Commissioned a top-secret scientific project--

139
00:05:06,978 --> 00:05:09,779
研制出能够治疗常见宿醉的灵药
develop an elixir to cure the common hangover.

140
00:05:09,781 --> 00:05:12,115
那么醉醺醺的老富兰克林选择了哪位杰出的科学家
And what brilliant scientific mind did boozy old fdr pick

141
00:05:12,117 --> 00:05:14,951
-来完成这项历史性的人物呢  -听着
-to head up this historic task? -Look.

142
00:05:14,953 --> 00:05:16,953
我头痛得要命 我们来速战速决吧
My head really hurts. Let's just speed this along.

143
00:05:16,955 --> 00:05:18,054
很明显你致敬了
You're clearly ripping off

144
00:05:18,056 --> 00:05:19,956
曼哈顿计划的故事
the story of the manhattan project,

145
00:05:18,056 --> 00:05:19,956
{\a6}曼哈顿计划是为制造原子弹的计划 由罗斯福总统签署

146
00:05:19,958 --> 00:05:22,292
计划负责人是罗伯特•奥本海默博士
which was run by Dr. Robert oppenheimer.

147
00:05:22,294 --> 00:05:25,962
所以我猜那个人应该是你的某个远亲...
So I'm gonna guess it was your distant relative...

148
00:05:27,331 --> 00:05:29,499
...巴奈特•斯丁森海默吧
...Barnert Stinsonheimer?

149
00:05:29,501 --> 00:05:32,669
看来某人的历史学得不错哈
Somebody's read their history books.

150
00:05:32,671 --> 00:05:34,704
传说中的曼哈顿计划
The too many manhattans project

151
00:05:34,706 --> 00:05:37,173
起初遇到了不少麻烦
hit a few snags at first.

152
00:05:37,175 --> 00:05:38,374
第一批药剂爆炸了
The first batch exploded.

153
00:05:38,376 --> 00:05:40,310
听起来像这样的
Which sounded kind of like this.

154
00:05:40,312 --> 00:05:41,978
-嘭  -哦
-Boom! -Oh!

155
00:05:41,980 --> 00:05:43,079
你这个贱人
You suck.

156
00:05:43,081 --> 00:05:44,314
让人家说完啦
Just let me finish.

157
00:05:44,316 --> 00:05:46,349
但是第二批药剂
But the second batch...

158
00:05:46,351 --> 00:05:48,218
很可惜 也爆炸了
sadly also exploded.

159
00:05:48,220 --> 00:05:49,319
-嘭  -哦
-Boom! -Oh!

160
00:05:49,321 --> 00:05:51,187
你怎么还在这儿啊
Why are you here right now?

161
00:05:51,189 --> 00:05:52,522
你到底想不想听这个故事啊
Do you want to hear the story or not?

162
00:05:52,524 --> 00:05:53,990
当然不想 快走
Absolutely not. Please leave.

163
00:05:53,992 --> 00:05:55,158
在一些尝试和挫折之后
After some trial and error,

164
00:05:55,160 --> 00:05:57,560
斯丁森海默博士终于找到了
Dr. Stinsonheimer finally found

165
00:05:57,562 --> 00:05:59,429
那个神奇的配方
the magic formula.

166
00:06:02,099 --> 00:06:03,266
等一下
Hang on.

167
00:06:03,268 --> 00:06:04,500
洋葱圈
Funyuns?

168
00:06:04,502 --> 00:06:05,902
堂多姆苏打水
Tantrum soda?

169
00:06:05,904 --> 00:06:06,769
是啊
Sure.

170
00:06:06,771 --> 00:06:08,104
在1941年吗
In 1941?

171
00:06:08,106 --> 00:06:09,339
是啊
Sure.

172
00:06:09,341 --> 00:06:10,373
他们从那以后就没做过新的堂多姆了
They haven't made new tantrum since then.

173
00:06:10,375 --> 00:06:11,441
那玩意命挺长的
That stuff lasts a while.

174
00:06:11,443 --> 00:06:14,711
最后是这样的 灵药实在是太成功了
Anyway, the elixir was such a success.

175
00:06:14,713 --> 00:06:17,213
他因此获得了兄贝尔奖
He was awarded the bro-bel prize.

176
00:06:17,215 --> 00:06:19,215
真实的故事
True story.

177
00:06:19,217 --> 00:06:20,350
嘭
Boom!

178
00:06:20,352 --> 00:06:21,584
又怎么啦
Wh-wh-why?

179
00:06:21,586 --> 00:06:23,052
这次我是逗你玩的
That time I was just messing with you.

180
00:06:23,054 --> 00:06:24,654
快把那个什么破饮料给我
Just give me the stupid drink.

181
00:06:27,225 --> 00:06:30,293
然后最疯狂的事情发生了
And the craziest part was...

182
00:06:33,597 --> 00:06:36,232
我还真觉得好一些了
I-I feel better.

183
00:06:36,234 --> 00:06:38,268
这些年来 我们每个人都发现了
Over the years, each of us would discover

184
00:06:38,270 --> 00:06:40,069
巴尼的灵药的确很管用
that Barney's elixir actually worked.

185
00:06:40,071 --> 00:06:41,738
简直是好多了
Like, way better.

186
00:06:41,740 --> 00:06:42,905
这里面有什么 再说一遍
What's in this thing again?

187
00:06:42,907 --> 00:06:44,607
这是斯丁森家族的秘密
Stinson family secret.

188
00:06:44,609 --> 00:06:46,809
哦 拜托 你在故事里都说了大部分原料了
Oh, come on, you told me most of the ingredients in your story.

189
00:06:46,811 --> 00:06:48,411
就告诉我秘密的那个吧
Just tell me the secret one.

190
00:06:48,413 --> 00:06:50,046
哈 我永远都不会告诉你的
Ha! I'll never tell you.

191
00:06:50,048 --> 00:06:52,282
我要它陪我进坟墓
I'll take it with me to my grave.

192
00:06:52,284 --> 00:06:53,316
去你的 巴尼
Damn it, barney!

193
00:06:53,318 --> 00:06:54,784
你为什么总是这么自私呢
Why are you always so selfish?!

194
00:06:54,786 --> 00:06:56,319
我们想过要帮你的
We are trying to help you!

195
00:06:56,321 --> 00:06:57,387
好了 我们得想办法在婚礼合照之前
Okay, we somehow have to get the leaky barf bag

196
00:06:57,389 --> 00:07:00,089
让这个尿裤子的酒鬼重新站起来
back on his feet before the wedding pictures.

197
00:07:00,091 --> 00:07:02,459
好吧 我们知道巴尼想让我们怎么做
Well, we know what barney would want us to do.

198
00:07:02,461 --> 00:07:03,459
老巴去度假

199
00:07:04,628 --> 00:07:05,628
说茄子
Say cheese.

200
00:07:05,630 --> 00:07:07,263
茄子
Cheese!

201
00:07:07,265 --> 00:07:08,231
不要
No!

202
00:07:08,233 --> 00:07:10,233
我们不用老巴去度假这招
We are not doing weekend at barney's!

203
00:07:10,235 --> 00:07:11,301
但是那是我们的梦想
But that's the dream!

204
00:07:11,303 --> 00:07:13,336
我简直不相信我说了这句话
I can't believe I just said that.

205
00:07:13,338 --> 00:07:14,337
总得有人出个靠谱的主意啊
Someone suggest something useful!

206
00:07:14,339 --> 00:07:15,838
好了 我们这么做
Okay, here's the plan.

207
00:07:15,840 --> 00:07:17,507
马修 你和泰德去找齐
Marshall, you and ted go gather

208
00:07:17,509 --> 00:07:19,075
我们已经知道的原料
the ingredients we do know.

209
00:07:19,077 --> 00:07:19,809
罗宾
Robin,

210
00:07:19,811 --> 00:07:21,411
你把巴尼喊醒一段时间
You wake up barney long enough

211
00:07:21,413 --> 00:07:23,279
问出来那个秘密原料是什么
to find out the secret ingredient.

212
00:07:23,281 --> 00:07:27,183
我呢 冲到楼下spa区去做我约在8:15的手足护理
And I'll race down to the spa to keep my 8:15 mani and pedi.

213
00:07:27,185 --> 00:07:28,284
好了 行动吧
Okay, let's do this!

214
00:07:28,286 --> 00:07:29,285
贱人
Bitch?

215
00:07:29,287 --> 00:07:31,587
你敢走出那扇门 我就让扎布卡做我的伴娘
Walk out that door and I tag in Zabka as my maid of honor.

216
00:07:31,589 --> 00:07:34,324
好吧 我们从简单的做起
Okay, let's start simple.

217
00:07:34,326 --> 00:07:35,491
给他清新的海洋空气
Fresh ocean air.

218
00:07:35,493 --> 00:07:36,526
来吧 宝贝
Come on, baby.

219
00:07:36,528 --> 00:07:38,161
来吧 亲爱的
Come on, honey.

220
00:07:38,163 --> 00:07:39,562
来吧 亲爱的 对了 宝贝
Come on, love, yeah. Baby, baby.

221
00:07:41,832 --> 00:07:43,466
我去按电梯
I'll get the elevator.

222
00:07:43,468 --> 00:07:45,501
哦 我去弄些水
Oh, I should get some water.

223
00:07:53,080 --> 00:07:55,081
好了 那...
Okay, so...

224
00:07:55,083 --> 00:07:57,083
一不小心把他扔下楼梯
Accidentally throwing barney down the stairs

225
00:07:57,085 --> 00:07:59,285
都没把他弄醒
Did not wake him up.

226
00:07:59,287 --> 00:08:01,554
头在楼梯上一路撞下去
Nor did banging his head on each step

227
00:08:01,556 --> 00:08:03,089
我们再把他一路连拉带拽弄上来都没弄醒他
As we dragged him back up here.

228
00:08:03,091 --> 00:08:05,658
那么 我们如何把他弄醒
So, how do we wake him up long enough

229
00:08:05,660 --> 00:08:07,460
然后抓紧问他秘密配料是啥
To tell us the final ingredient?

230
00:08:07,462 --> 00:08:09,062
当我和我的妹妹
You know, when my sister and I

231
00:08:09,064 --> 00:08:10,930
起床困难的时候
Had trouble getting up for school,

232
00:08:10,932 --> 00:08:12,966
我爸爸倒是有些挺有爱的把戏
My dad a few cute little tricks.

233
00:08:18,907 --> 00:08:19,939
我真的会剪的
I'll do it!

234
00:08:19,941 --> 00:08:22,075
我发誓我绝对会剪的
I swear to god I'll do it!

235
00:08:22,077 --> 00:08:24,143
你爸爸以前真的这样对你的
Your dad used to do this to you?

236
00:08:24,145 --> 00:08:25,912
那次是用斧头砍卷心菜娃娃
Well, it was with a cabbage patch doll and an ax.

237
00:08:25,914 --> 00:08:26,980
不过道理是一样的 相信我
But same idea. Trust me.

238
00:08:26,982 --> 00:08:29,282
之后我上幼儿园就再也没迟到过了
I was never late for kindergarten again.

239
00:08:29,284 --> 00:08:31,818
啥 不要吧
What? Come on.

240
00:08:35,824 --> 00:08:37,023
我跟着马修发誓
I second marshall's vow.

241
00:08:37,025 --> 00:08:40,259
我永远永远也不会喝的这么醉
I will never, ever get that drunk again.

242
00:08:40,261 --> 00:08:42,161
嗯 她喝醉了
Yeah. She would.

243
00:08:42,163 --> 00:08:44,163
{\a6}卫斯理安大学
2030年

244
00:08:42,163 --> 00:08:45,498
我的宝贝儿子上大学啦
My baby boy's in college.

245
00:08:45,500 --> 00:08:46,866
你的内衣带够了吗
Did you pack enough undies?

246
00:08:46,868 --> 00:08:48,001
是的 妈妈
Yes, mom.

247
00:08:48,003 --> 00:08:50,503
你爸爸在这个神圣的走廊上
Your father did a lot of puking

248
00:08:50,505 --> 00:08:52,605
吐过很多词
In these hallowed halls.

249
00:08:52,607 --> 00:08:54,807
在我们研究醉酒学的时候
From-from binge studying.

250
00:08:54,809 --> 00:08:56,509
可算圆回来了
Saved it.

251
00:08:56,511 --> 00:08:57,610
这倒提醒我了 先生
That reminds me, mister.

252
00:08:57,612 --> 00:08:59,178
不到年龄别喝酒
No underage drinking.

253
00:08:59,180 --> 00:09:01,147
泡酒吧喝酒
No good comes from hanging out

254
00:09:01,149 --> 00:09:02,982
一点好处都没有
in bars and getting drunk.

255
00:09:02,984 --> 00:09:05,818
但你们从20多岁开始的故事都是在酒吧
But every story from your 20s starts in a bar.

256
00:09:05,820 --> 00:09:07,120
听妈妈的话
Listen to your mother.

257
00:09:07,122 --> 00:09:09,522
你不在家里我们可怎么办啊
Oh, what are we gonna do without you in the house?

258
00:09:10,825 --> 00:09:12,959
我们终于把他撵出去了 干了
We got him out of the house! Drink up!

259
00:09:17,399 --> 00:09:19,932
哦
Oh...

260
00:09:22,036 --> 00:09:25,071
-你个老混蛋  -你个老混蛋的小混蛋
-You son of a bitch! -You son of a me!

261
00:09:25,073 --> 00:09:27,407
好了 大部分的配料都在单子上了
All right, we got most of the ingredients on our list.

262
00:09:27,409 --> 00:09:29,409
姜 香蕉 炸洋葱圈
Ginger, bananas, funyuns.

263
00:09:29,411 --> 00:09:31,411
没想到那个小卖部还卖堂多姆
I cannot believe that minimart sold tantrum.

264
00:09:31,413 --> 00:09:33,046
都已经停产好几年了
It's been discontinued for years.

265
00:09:33,048 --> 00:09:34,080
呃 嘿
Uh, hey.

266
00:09:34,082 --> 00:09:36,516
你把那个瓶子扔给我吧
Will you, uh, toss me that bottle?

267
00:09:36,518 --> 00:09:38,017
嗯 好的 我们好久没这么玩了
Oh. Yeah, we haven't done this forever.

268
00:09:39,754 --> 00:09:40,753
哥们
Dude!

269
00:09:40,755 --> 00:09:41,754
你已经成年了
You're a grown man.

270
00:09:41,756 --> 00:09:43,089
{\a6}堂多姆的真正意思是发小孩脾气

271
00:09:41,756 --> 00:09:43,089
怎么还乱甩堂多姆呢
Why you throwing a tantrum?

272
00:09:43,091 --> 00:09:44,157
好梗
Nice!

273
00:09:44,159 --> 00:09:45,258
太赞了
So awesome!

274
00:09:45,260 --> 00:09:46,325
太赞了
So awesome!

275
00:09:46,327 --> 00:09:47,360
好了 单子上就只有
Okay, there's only

276
00:09:47,362 --> 00:09:49,195
这一样东西没有了
One more item on the list and...

277
00:09:49,197 --> 00:09:51,230
很奇怪的东西
It's an odd one.

278
00:09:51,232 --> 00:09:53,166
-荤油  -荤油
-Grease? -Grease.

279
00:09:53,168 --> 00:09:55,768
在远汉普顿旅馆 我们做菜不用荤油
At the farhampton inn, we don't cook with grease.

280
00:09:55,770 --> 00:09:57,770
我们的菜都是有机的
Our menu is organic.

281
00:09:57,772 --> 00:09:59,572
从地里到桌上 现种现吃
Farm to table, locally grown.

282
00:09:59,574 --> 00:10:01,874
没有"荤油"
No "Grease."

283
00:10:01,876 --> 00:10:02,875
先生
Sir,

284
00:10:02,877 --> 00:10:04,544
我大明尼苏达
I am from minnesota,

285
00:10:04,546 --> 00:10:06,412
顿顿都有大荤油
Where every meal is cooked with grease.

286
00:10:06,414 --> 00:10:09,182
我爸爸称赞这种食品
And my father dubbed that food the tastiest eats

287
00:10:09,184 --> 00:10:12,018
是世间最美味的
In the whole gosh darn world, so...

288
00:10:12,020 --> 00:10:13,186
那么令尊身体可好
And how is your father's health?

289
00:10:15,923 --> 00:10:17,256
重点是真的很好吃好吗
Point is, it tastes really good.

290
00:10:17,258 --> 00:10:18,591
还有
Also, uh,

291
00:10:18,593 --> 00:10:20,526
我们还要帮一个朋友醒酒
We need it to help a friend recover from a hangover.

292
00:10:20,528 --> 00:10:22,361
等会
Wait a second.

293
00:10:22,363 --> 00:10:24,197
这里有培根
There's bacon right here.

294
00:10:24,199 --> 00:10:25,298
只要有培根
And where there's bacon,

295
00:10:25,300 --> 00:10:26,566
就肯定有培根油
There's bacon grease.

296
00:10:26,568 --> 00:10:28,101
我们都扔掉了
Which we throw out.

297
00:10:28,103 --> 00:10:30,203
再说我们今天也不会再做培根了
And we aren't making any more bacon today.

298
00:10:30,205 --> 00:10:33,039
除非早饭结束前有人在十分钟之内
Not unless it all somehow gets eaten in the ten minutes

299
00:10:33,041 --> 00:10:35,141
把这些全吃了
Before breakfast is over.

300
00:10:36,610 --> 00:10:38,111
不要 不要
No, no, no!

301
00:10:38,113 --> 00:10:39,378
泰德 别那么看我
Ted, do not give me that look!

302
00:10:39,380 --> 00:10:40,613
堆成山的食物
A mountain of food.

303
00:10:40,615 --> 00:10:41,948
还有倒计时 来吧
A ticking clock? Come on!

304
00:10:41,950 --> 00:10:43,216
你就是为这个而生的
You live for this stuff!

305
00:10:43,218 --> 00:10:45,118
不 我又不是野生动物
No, I'm not a wild animal.

306
00:10:45,120 --> 00:10:47,420
我是哥伦比亚毕业的律师
I'm a columbia-educated lawyer,

307
00:10:47,422 --> 00:10:50,490
在35岁之前就当上了法官
Poised to become a judge before age 35.

308
00:10:50,492 --> 00:10:51,891
这倒提醒我了 你被哥伦比亚大学录取的时候
And remind me, how did you celebrate

309
00:10:51,893 --> 00:10:53,426
是怎么庆祝的来着
Getting accepted into columbia?

310
00:10:53,428 --> 00:10:56,229
12分钟内猛灌八磅软糖
You eat one eight-pound block of fudge

311
00:10:56,231 --> 00:10:58,297
在我幼小的心灵上留下了不可磨灭的伤痕
In 12 minutes and you're marked for life.

312
00:10:58,299 --> 00:11:00,299
你才没有伤痕呢
You're not marked for life...

313
00:11:00,301 --> 00:11:01,300
大软糖
Big fudge.

314
00:11:01,302 --> 00:11:02,635
我洗手不干了 好吧
I'm out, okay?

315
00:11:02,637 --> 00:11:03,736
你把培根吃了
You eat the bacon.

316
00:11:03,738 --> 00:11:05,238
你知道我不行
You know I can't.

317
00:11:05,240 --> 00:11:06,405
-我过敏  -泰德
-I'm allergic. -Ted.

318
00:11:06,407 --> 00:11:08,141
这几年我都想告诉你
I've been trying to tell you this for years.

319
00:11:08,143 --> 00:11:09,842
你对培根过敏是假的
Your bacon allergy is a lie

320
00:11:09,844 --> 00:11:12,078
你妈妈骗你的 这样你小时候的饮食才健康
Your mother made up so you'd eat healthy as a kid.

321
00:11:12,080 --> 00:11:14,313
不 我是对很多东西都过敏
No, I'm just allergic to a lot of stuff.

322
00:11:14,315 --> 00:11:15,781
培根 甜甜圈
Bacon, doughnuts,

323
00:11:15,783 --> 00:11:18,151
万圣节糖果
Halloween candy.

324
00:11:18,153 --> 00:11:20,286
不说谢谢
Not saying thank you.

325
00:11:20,288 --> 00:11:21,854
哦 我了个擦
Oh, my god!

326
00:11:21,856 --> 00:11:23,089
那老东西骗我
That bitch lied to me!

327
00:11:23,857 --> 00:11:26,092
好吧 我吃
Okay, I'll-I'll do it.

328
00:11:26,094 --> 00:11:28,494
不过 我都不确定我喜不喜欢培根
But I... Look, I don't, I don't even know if I'll like bacon.

329
00:11:35,636 --> 00:11:37,503
怎么样
What do you think?

330
00:11:39,641 --> 00:11:42,108
我看见上帝的真容了
I have seen the face of god.

331
00:11:44,178 --> 00:11:47,747
好了 只有一个方法没试过了
Okay, there is one thing we haven't tried yet.

332
00:11:47,749 --> 00:11:49,682
咱们百合吧
Making out with each other.

333
00:11:49,684 --> 00:11:51,417
你真觉得这样能弄醒他
You really think that will wake him up?

334
00:11:51,419 --> 00:11:52,685
弄醒谁
Wake up who now?

335
00:11:55,991 --> 00:11:57,991
瞧瞧这滩湿热翔
Look at this soggy bag of snot.

336
00:11:57,993 --> 00:11:59,993
够了 我也跟着马修发誓
That's it, I am joining marshall's vow.

337
00:11:59,995 --> 00:12:03,096
我永远永远也不会喝这么醉了
I am never, ever getting that drunk again.

338
00:12:03,098 --> 00:12:05,899
孩子们 你们懂的
Kids, you see where this is going.

339
00:12:05,936 --> 00:12:07,604
{\a6}布宜诺斯艾利斯 阿根廷
2016年

340
00:12:08,936 --> 00:12:11,204
昨晚那是真的吗
Did last night really happen?

341
00:12:11,206 --> 00:12:13,506
我觉得是
I think so.

342
00:12:13,508 --> 00:12:15,441
咱说好了
Look, let's just agree.

343
00:12:15,443 --> 00:12:17,844
今天一天谁都别说话
Absolute silence for the rest of the day.

344
00:12:21,049 --> 00:12:22,916
又来了
Every time.

345
00:12:22,918 --> 00:12:23,883
你要我去抱她吗
You want me to get her?

346
00:12:23,885 --> 00:12:26,119
不了 我来吧
No, I got her.

347
00:12:28,890 --> 00:12:31,357
好宝贝 不哭啊 乖
Yeah, I know, I know.

348
00:12:36,130 --> 00:12:37,964
嘿 巴尼
Hey, barney?

349
00:12:37,966 --> 00:12:38,731
怎么了
Yeah?

350
00:12:38,733 --> 00:12:40,433
这孩子是谁的啊
Whose baby is this?

351
00:12:40,466 --> 00:12:43,731
你们在这干吗

352
00:12:43,766 --> 00:12:45,731
你们房间在厅对面

353
00:12:48,966 --> 00:12:50,031
傻逼美国酒鬼

354
00:12:47,041 --> 00:12:48,175
呃 真对不起
Uh, pardon.

355
00:12:52,113 --> 00:12:53,913
妈你怎么能这样对我呢
How could you, mom?!

356
00:12:53,915 --> 00:12:55,081
你拥有通往天堂的地图
You had the map to heaven

357
00:12:55,083 --> 00:12:57,450
却从没给我指过路
and you never showed me the way.

358
00:12:57,452 --> 00:12:59,385
愿你在没有培根的地狱里腐烂
May you rot in the bacon-less hell

359
00:12:59,387 --> 00:13:01,988
就像我之前的人生一样
that I've lived in my entire life.

360
00:13:01,990 --> 00:13:04,223
是啊 这些培根 脆香美味刚刚好啊
Yeah, they-they, uh, crisp it up real nice here.

361
00:13:04,225 --> 00:13:05,325
-是不是  -那当然了
-Don't they? -Mm-hmm.

362
00:13:05,327 --> 00:13:06,326
那是用什么熏的 苹果木吗
What is that-- applewood smoked?

363
00:13:06,328 --> 00:13:07,427
我跟你说啊 泰德
You know what, ted,

364
00:13:07,429 --> 00:13:08,928
这培根你可是吃了不少了
You've been going at it real hard.

365
00:13:08,930 --> 00:13:10,296
要不你休息一下吧
Why don't you take a breather?

366
00:13:10,298 --> 00:13:11,798
我开车 咱俩回家
And I'll drive us home.

367
00:13:14,601 --> 00:13:16,169
恭喜你们
Well, congratulations.

368
00:13:16,171 --> 00:13:17,937
这是你们要的荤油
Here's your grease.

369
00:13:17,939 --> 00:13:19,072
不许碰
No!

370
00:13:19,074 --> 00:13:21,074
你回来再把我手指头咬掉了
I don't want to lose a finger.

371
00:13:21,076 --> 00:13:22,008
-给  -谢了
-Here. -Thanks.

372
00:13:22,010 --> 00:13:23,009
好了 泰德 咱走吧
All right, ted, let's go.

373
00:13:23,011 --> 00:13:24,043
不 不走
No, no!

374
00:13:25,312 --> 00:13:27,413
我终于找到了我的另一半了 马修
I finally found the one, marshall.

375
00:13:27,415 --> 00:13:30,083
她的名字叫培根
Her name is bacon.

376
00:13:30,085 --> 00:13:32,986
跟你说 我妈做的生菜番茄三明治里要是加上这个就完美了
You know, this would go great on one of my mom's LT sandwiches.

377
00:13:30,085 --> 00:13:32,986
{\a6}BLT sandwich 培根生菜番茄三明治

378
00:13:32,988 --> 00:13:34,520
哥们儿 你可得悠着点啊
Buddy, you got to take it easy.

379
00:13:34,522 --> 00:13:35,755
就不
Never!

380
00:13:35,757 --> 00:13:38,124
我今儿要把我这辈子没吃的培根都补回来
I got a lifetime without bacon to make up for.

381
00:13:38,126 --> 00:13:39,826
我就一直吃一直吃
I will keep eating and eating

382
00:13:39,828 --> 00:13:41,361
一直吃到...我的天 救救我
and eating... Oh, god, help me.

383
00:13:41,363 --> 00:13:42,528
我不行了
I'm going down.

384
00:13:42,530 --> 00:13:44,330
这是我这辈子第一次
And that's the first

385
00:13:44,332 --> 00:13:47,033
也是唯一一次吃培根
and last time I ever ate bacon.

386
00:13:47,035 --> 00:13:48,701
他就是不醒
He's not waking up!

387
00:13:48,703 --> 00:13:49,702
我黔驴技穷了
I'm out of ideas!

388
00:13:49,704 --> 00:13:51,637
咱俩可什么方法都试过了啊
We've tried everything!

389
00:13:51,639 --> 00:13:52,939
还有一种没试过
Not everything.

390
00:13:53,874 --> 00:13:55,441
莉莉•艾尔德林
Lily Aldrin?

391
00:13:55,443 --> 00:13:56,876
我们百合吧
Let's make out.

392
00:13:58,313 --> 00:13:59,812
你确定吗
Are you sure?!

393
00:13:59,814 --> 00:14:01,214
当然 宝贝 我确定
Yeah, baby, I'm sure.

394
00:14:01,216 --> 00:14:03,016
那么...
Um...

395
00:14:03,018 --> 00:14:05,018
好吧 不过 你看啊 我是说
Okay, well, you know what? I mean...

396
00:14:05,020 --> 00:14:07,387
这可能根本就行不通呢
It probably won't even work.

397
00:14:07,389 --> 00:14:09,155
而且这样做也好傻嘛
And it was stupid.

398
00:14:09,157 --> 00:14:10,390
我也好傻嘛
I'm stupid.

399
00:14:11,993 --> 00:14:13,559
你真美
You're beautiful.

400
00:14:19,401 --> 00:14:21,534
继续 别停 继续 别停 继续 别停 继续 别停
More, more, more, more, more, more, more, more.

401
00:14:21,536 --> 00:14:22,535
天哪 他醒了
Whoa, he's awake!

402
00:14:22,537 --> 00:14:24,003
你们怎么做到的
How'd you do it?!

403
00:14:24,005 --> 00:14:25,038
没干什么特别的事儿啊
Nothing special.

404
00:14:25,040 --> 00:14:26,039
给他喝水啦 有点耐心啦
Hydration, patience.

405
00:14:26,041 --> 00:14:27,173
快问 不然他又躺下了
Quick, before he passes out again.

406
00:14:27,175 --> 00:14:28,474
巴尼
Barney!

407
00:14:28,476 --> 00:14:30,376
斯丁森宿醉灵的最后一个
What's the secret ingredient

408
00:14:30,378 --> 00:14:33,046
神秘配方到底是什么
in Stinson's hangover fixer elixir?

409
00:14:33,048 --> 00:14:34,547
挺住 清醒点
Come on, stay with us.

410
00:14:34,549 --> 00:14:36,983
神秘配方
The secret ingredient

411
00:14:36,985 --> 00:14:38,251
是...
is...

412
00:14:38,253 --> 00:14:39,819
什么也不是
Nothing.

413
00:14:39,821 --> 00:14:40,653
你说什么
Huh?

414
00:14:40,655 --> 00:14:43,022
我吃太多培根了
I ate too much bacon.

415
00:14:43,024 --> 00:14:45,258
斯丁森宿醉灵
Stinson's hangover fixer elixir

416
00:14:45,260 --> 00:14:48,494
是我骗你们的
is a lie.

417
00:14:48,496 --> 00:14:51,064
这就是秘方
That's the secret.

418
00:14:51,066 --> 00:14:53,066
你...
You...

419
00:14:53,068 --> 00:14:55,301
我觉得我也得躺一会儿了
You know, I could use a little lie-down myself.

420
00:14:56,709 --> 00:15:00,877
这么说 根本就没有什么斯丁森宿醉灵吗
So, Stinson's hangover fixer elixir is a lie?

421
00:15:00,879 --> 00:15:02,910
你干嘛要这么骗我们啊
Why would you lie about that?

422
00:15:02,911 --> 00:15:03,913
就为了拿我们找乐吗
just tomess with us?

423
00:15:03,914 --> 00:15:06,214
就跟每个高中都有一个学生
Like that one jerk in every high school

424
00:15:06,216 --> 00:15:07,616
用假蘑菇骗人
who brings in fake mushrooms

425
00:15:07,618 --> 00:15:08,717
就为了看谁会傻到
just to see who's gullible enough

426
00:15:08,719 --> 00:15:09,918
真的认为蘑菇会走路么
to think they're tripping?

427
00:15:09,920 --> 00:15:11,753
你大爷的 奥利•冈德森
Damn you, Ollie Gunderson.

428
00:15:11,755 --> 00:15:14,489
我就觉得那些蘑菇跟丰年虾的味儿差不多
I knew those shrooms tasted like sea-monkeys.

429
00:15:11,755 --> 00:15:14,489
{\a6}sea-monkeys 一种虾 可用作鱼饲料 国内多称作"丰年虾"

430
00:15:14,491 --> 00:15:16,091
你怎么知道丰年虾是什么味儿的啊
How do you know what sea-monkeys taste like?

431
00:15:16,093 --> 00:15:17,826
我的哥哥们...
My older brothers are not...

432
00:15:17,828 --> 00:15:19,895
也不是什么好人
the best people.

433
00:15:19,897 --> 00:15:20,829
你干嘛要骗我们呢
Why did you lie?

434
00:15:20,831 --> 00:15:22,831
我...
I...

435
00:15:22,833 --> 00:15:26,168
爱你们啊
Love you guys.

436
00:15:27,170 --> 00:15:29,638
他爱我们吗
He loves us?

437
00:15:29,640 --> 00:15:31,139
咱再给他从楼梯上扔下去一次吧
Let's throw him down the stairs again.

438
00:15:31,141 --> 00:15:32,274
-好啊  -好啊
-Yeah! -Yeah!

439
00:15:32,276 --> 00:15:33,408
等会儿等会儿等会儿 你们仔细想想
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! Think about it.

440
00:15:33,410 --> 00:15:34,643
巴尼第一次给咱们
The first time Barney

441
00:15:34,645 --> 00:15:35,644
喝那个东西的时候
gave us that drink,

442
00:15:35,646 --> 00:15:36,678
咱们的宿醉都发生在
those hangovers all happened

443
00:15:36,680 --> 00:15:38,814
人生中最灰暗的时刻
at the worst possible moments.

444
00:15:38,815 --> 00:15:40,949
{\a6}六年前

445
00:15:38,816 --> 00:15:40,949
记得吗 马修在他律师资格考试期间的第二天
Remember? Marshall thought he botched day two

446
00:15:40,951 --> 00:15:43,752
{\a6}全美各州律师资格考试 为期最少两天 一些州为期三天

447
00:15:40,951 --> 00:15:43,752
他压力太大了 然后喝了个烂醉
of the bar exam, so he freaked out that night and got wasted?

448
00:15:43,754 --> 00:15:45,787
现在我连最后一天的考试都赶不上了
Now I'm gonna miss the last day of the bar?

449
00:15:45,789 --> 00:15:47,189
我这辈子都当不成法官了
I'll never be a lawyer!

450
00:15:47,191 --> 00:15:49,758
我应该回去当个组织结构管理者的
I should just go back to being a manager at structure.

451
00:15:49,760 --> 00:15:51,660
知道那个全场背心九折优惠吗
That ten percent off all vests sale?

452
00:15:51,662 --> 00:15:52,828
那是我的点子
That was my idea!

453
00:15:52,830 --> 00:15:54,129
其实就是把所有卖不出去的衬衣的
As was cutting the arms off

454
00:15:54,131 --> 00:15:55,463
袖子剪了 当背心卖出去
all the shirts that weren't selling.

455
00:15:55,465 --> 00:15:56,998
我就应该干那个
That's where I belong.

456
00:15:57,000 --> 00:15:59,100
不是的 马修
No, marshall.

457
00:15:59,102 --> 00:16:00,836
你会成为一名律师的
You're gonna be a lawyer.

458
00:15:59,102 --> 00:16:00,836
{\a6}一年半前

459
00:16:00,838 --> 00:16:02,304
不 我做不到的
No, I can't do it.

460
00:16:02,306 --> 00:16:04,940
你能做到的 你第一天重回直播间的时候
Yes, you can. Your first day back live on the air

461
00:16:04,942 --> 00:16:07,343
那场面 一定是 传...等一下...
is gonna be legend-- wait for it--

462
00:16:07,345 --> 00:16:08,377
{\a6}两年前

463
00:16:07,345 --> 00:16:08,377
奇
Dary!

464
00:16:08,379 --> 00:16:10,179
今天你们幼儿园组织的
Your kindergarten field trip

465
00:16:10,181 --> 00:16:12,147
"手提钻与汽笛博物馆"之旅
to the Jackhammer and Siren Museum today...

466
00:16:13,150 --> 00:16:15,317
一定会是传奇
...Is gonna be legendary.

467
00:16:15,419 --> 00:16:16,718
{\a6}四年半前

468
00:16:15,419 --> 00:16:16,718
不 才不会呢
No, it's not.

469
00:16:16,720 --> 00:16:18,754
再也没有传奇了
Nothing's ever gonna be legendary again.

470
00:16:18,756 --> 00:16:21,156
我永远走不出这个阴影的
I-I'm never gonna recover from this.

471
00:16:21,158 --> 00:16:22,458
不就是喝醉了嘛 泰德
It's just a hangover, ted.

472
00:16:22,460 --> 00:16:23,725
不是那个
Not that!

473
00:16:23,727 --> 00:16:26,328
我刚被人甩在圣坛上了啊 巴尼
I got left at the altar, barney.

474
00:16:26,330 --> 00:16:29,998
我现在是一个被人甩在圣坛上的人了
I'm now a guy who got left at the altar.

475
00:16:30,000 --> 00:16:32,434
再没有好转的可能了
There's no coming back from that.

476
00:16:32,436 --> 00:16:34,503
喝了这个
Drink this.

477
00:16:34,505 --> 00:16:36,572
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.

478
00:16:37,841 --> 00:16:40,609
巴尼胡编了所谓的斯丁森宿醉灵
Barney made up the stinson's hangover fixer elixir

479
00:16:40,611 --> 00:16:43,011
却让我们都相信了 我们可以挺过来
So we would all believe that we could rally.

480
00:16:43,013 --> 00:16:46,281
虽然是假的 但它起到了效果
I mean, even though it's fake, it-it worked.

481
00:16:46,283 --> 00:16:47,616
就好像丹波的神奇羽毛
Like-like dumbo's feather.

482
00:16:46,283 --> 00:16:47,616
{\a6}{\fs16}迪士尼动画«小飞象»中 一只鸟给了丹波一根神奇羽毛 让丹波以为自己可以飞翔了

483
00:16:47,618 --> 00:16:49,651
丹哥的神奇羽毛
Dum-bro's feather.

484
00:16:49,653 --> 00:16:50,686
心灵安慰剂
A placebo.

485
00:16:50,688 --> 00:16:52,454
兄灵安慰剂
Place-bro.

486
00:16:52,456 --> 00:16:53,489
小糖丸
A sugar pill.

487
00:16:56,494 --> 00:16:58,494
他用胡扯让我们复原
He lied so we'd be okay.

488
00:16:59,997 --> 00:17:02,498
巴尼真的好爱我们
Barney does love us.

489
00:17:02,500 --> 00:17:05,601
真希望我们能用他帮我们的办法 帮到他
I wish we could help him out the way he helped us.

490
00:17:05,603 --> 00:17:07,703
但是不到二十分钟就要开始拍婚礼照片了啊
But the wedding photos are in 20 minutes.

491
00:17:07,705 --> 00:17:09,605
我爸肯定要气炸了
my dad's gonna be so pissed.

492
00:17:09,607 --> 00:17:11,006
没错
Yup.

493
00:17:11,008 --> 00:17:13,075
巴尼现在死人一只
Barney's a dead man.

494
00:17:16,108 --> 00:17:17,675
老巴去度假

495
00:17:26,122 --> 00:17:27,356
巴尼
Barney?

496
00:17:27,358 --> 00:17:28,557
你是有点...
You were always a bit...

497
00:17:28,559 --> 00:17:31,193
话痨 还是 金发话痨
Chatty and blond

498
00:17:31,195 --> 00:17:32,794
对我来说 跟娘们一样
For my taste. Like a woman.

499
00:17:32,796 --> 00:17:35,531
但是这新一面的你
But this new side of you--

500
00:17:35,533 --> 00:17:36,632
安静
Quiet,

501
00:17:36,634 --> 00:17:38,133
稳重
Steady?

502
00:17:38,135 --> 00:17:40,168
我很喜欢
I like it!

503
00:17:40,170 --> 00:17:43,405
儿子 今天你赢得了我的尊重
You've earned my respect today, son.

504
00:17:43,407 --> 00:17:44,640
我要和你击出最高荣誉的掌
I request the highest of fives.

505
00:17:44,642 --> 00:17:46,074
-哦 天啊  -淡定
-Oh, no. -Stay cool.

506
00:17:46,076 --> 00:17:49,378
我来解决
I got this.

507
00:17:54,918 --> 00:17:56,518
我真不敢相信
I don't believe this.

508
00:17:56,520 --> 00:17:58,220
你们用了老巴去度假这一招
You did weekend at barney's.

509
00:17:58,222 --> 00:17:59,488
而且竟然奏效了
And it worked.

510
00:17:59,490 --> 00:18:02,691
天啊 今天最好也不过如此了
God, today's gonna be all downhill from here.

511
00:18:02,693 --> 00:18:04,226
哇 这话说的新娘真爱听
That's what the bride wants to hear.

512
00:18:04,228 --> 00:18:05,594
不 我不是那个意思
No, that's not what I meant.

513
00:18:05,596 --> 00:18:07,396
我是说老巴去度假
I just mean weekend at barney's

514
00:18:07,398 --> 00:18:10,032
绝对比我们的婚礼精彩一千倍
Is a thousand times more amazing than our wedding could ever be.

515
00:18:10,034 --> 00:18:12,834
我去弄点咖啡喝 我可等不及看照片了
I'm gonna get some more coffee. I can't wait to see the photos!

516
00:18:15,672 --> 00:18:17,406
嗯 他信了
Well, he bought it.

517
00:18:17,408 --> 00:18:18,507
我们也是善意的谎言啊
We lied out of love.

518
00:18:18,509 --> 00:18:19,908
看看他有多开心啊
Look how happy he is.

519
00:18:19,910 --> 00:18:21,577
他完全不知道我们取消了
I mean, he has no idea we had to cancel

520
00:18:21,579 --> 00:18:23,278
婚礼拍照 然后我爸暴怒
The wedding photos and my dad was so angry,

521
00:18:23,280 --> 00:18:25,714
冲进我们的屋子对他的裆部一顿暴踢这回事了
He came up to our room and kicked barney in the crotch.

522
00:18:25,716 --> 00:18:28,550
这其中最好的一点就是 你爸爸完全不知道
And the best part is your dad has no idea.

523
00:18:28,552 --> 00:18:30,519
他依然爱我
He still loves me.

524
00:18:30,521 --> 00:18:33,522
另外 有人和我一样蛋蛋很疼吗
Hey, do anyone else's balls hurt?

525
00:18:33,524 --> 00:18:34,723
嗯 这样
And, look,

526
00:18:34,725 --> 00:18:35,924
还是有些好事情发生的
Some good came out of all this.

527
00:18:35,926 --> 00:18:37,526
看你醉成那样 我们都发誓了
Seeing you like that, we all vowed

528
00:18:37,528 --> 00:18:39,561
永远都不会喝得那么醉了
Never to get that drunk again.

529
00:18:39,563 --> 00:18:41,029
嗯 其实我没有
Well, actually I didn't.

530
00:18:41,031 --> 00:18:42,297
但是我现在发誓
But I will now.

531
00:18:42,299 --> 00:18:43,532
再也不喝这么醉了
Never again.

532
00:18:43,534 --> 00:18:45,267
-再也不喝这么醉了  -再也不喝这么醉了
-Never again. -Never again.

533
00:18:45,269 --> 00:18:46,802
孩子们 不管我们有多努力
Kids, no matter how hard we try,

534
00:18:46,804 --> 00:18:49,538
即使在我们最佳状态的时候也会把持不住自己
Even the best of us go a little too wild sometimes.

535
00:18:49,540 --> 00:18:52,474
{\a6}2022年元旦

536
00:18:49,540 --> 00:18:52,474
但是在那些时光里 我们真正需要的
And in those moments, we all need

537
00:18:52,476 --> 00:18:54,610
就是爱我们的人帮我们一把 让我们继续前进
Someone who loves us to help us rally.

538
00:18:58,815 --> 00:19:00,816
-新年快乐  -好的
-Happy new year. Okay.

539
00:19:00,818 --> 00:19:02,384
刚才那声音实在是太大了
That was, that was way too loud.

540
00:19:02,386 --> 00:19:04,486
你简直就是在对我吼叫
You're practically screaming.

541
00:19:04,488 --> 00:19:09,157
你现在需要斯丁森宿醉灵
What you need is stinson's hangover fixer elixir.

542
00:19:09,159 --> 00:19:11,159
尽管意味着撒一两个小谎
Even if that means lying once in a while.

543
00:19:11,161 --> 00:19:12,161
真管用吗
Does it work?

544
00:19:12,163 --> 00:19:13,395
绝对管用
Totally works.

545
00:19:17,167 --> 00:19:18,834
正常反应 慢慢喝
It's normal, it's totally normal.

546
00:19:22,739 --> 00:19:24,506
我好爱你
I love you so much.

547
00:19:24,508 --> 00:19:25,474
我也爱你
I love you, too.

548
00:19:25,476 --> 00:19:27,609
快 快
Whoop, whoop.

549
00:19:27,611 --> 00:19:28,977
最好快点喝
Better drink it fast.

550
00:19:28,979 --> 00:19:29,645
妈咪
Mommy!

551
00:19:29,647 --> 00:19:30,979
嘿 看看谁来啦
Hey, look who it is!

552
00:19:30,981 --> 00:19:32,414
抱住她
Get her!

553
00:19:37,989 --> 00:19:39,223
我真不敢相信我们今天接吻了
I can't believe we kissed today.

554
00:19:39,225 --> 00:19:41,325
奇怪吧
Weird.

555
00:19:41,327 --> 00:19:42,893
我倒挺替
I-I feel kind of bad

556
00:19:42,895 --> 00:19:45,596
马修和泰德感到遗憾的 他们都没看到
That, um, ted and marshall missed it.

557
00:19:45,598 --> 00:19:47,731
嘿 我们应该在他们面前
Hey, we should kiss one more time

558
00:19:47,733 --> 00:19:51,268
再亲一次 就那样 让他们吓尿...
In front of them just to, like, blow their minds.

559
00:19:51,270 --> 00:19:52,836
是吧
Right?

560
00:19:52,838 --> 00:19:54,104
不 我看还是算了吧
Nah, I don't think so.

561
00:19:54,106 --> 00:19:55,839
就是 对
Exactly, totally.

562
00:19:55,841 --> 00:19:59,276
哈哈 那两位 你们也看不到我们俩接吻
Ha-ha, guys, you don't get to see this kiss either.

563
00:19:59,278 --> 00:20:00,878
所以我们去哪
So, where should we go?

564
00:20:00,880 --> 00:20:02,713
衣柜 阁楼
Closet, patio?

565
00:20:02,715 --> 00:20:04,081
哦 我记得桑拿还开着
Ooh, I think the sauna's open.

566
00:20:04,083 --> 00:20:05,449
嗯 我...其实...
Well, I... Actually...

567
00:20:05,451 --> 00:20:09,053
实话说 对我来说 感觉怪怪的
To be honest, it-it felt kind of weird to me.

568
00:20:09,055 --> 00:20:10,254
一次就够了
Once was enough.

569
00:20:10,256 --> 00:20:11,455
就是
Totally.

570
00:20:11,457 --> 00:20:12,590
我们可以亲
We could kiss.

571
00:20:12,592 --> 00:20:13,624
也可以不亲
We could not kiss.

572
00:20:13,626 --> 00:20:15,025
但我们可以亲
We could kiss.

573
00:20:15,027 --> 00:20:16,026
对我来说没什么
Doesn't matter to me.

574
00:20:16,028 --> 00:20:17,027
这想法可真傻
It's stupid.

575
00:20:17,029 --> 00:20:18,929
我真傻
I'm stupid.

576
00:20:21,867 --> 00:20:24,134
太傻了
So stupid.

577
00:20:24,367 --> 00:20:31,367
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看

578
00:20:31,369 --> 00:20:53,367
欢迎关注百度老爸老妈浪漫史贴吧
字幕组新浪微博及人人网公共主页@HIMYM字幕组

