Some kids dream of
being astronauts.
playing baseball.
When I was a kid,
I had only one dream.
To build a skyscraper.
That's stupid.
There were some
obstacles along the way.
But eventually my
dream came true.
I became an architect.
Morning, everyone!
So, I had an idea
for the atrium.
Ready?
Columns.
That's stupid.
Sync by vNaru
I... I can't believe you
knocked over my model.
Well, it's just...
it's not exactly new, is it-- columns?
I mean, what's your next
groundbreaking idea-- ceilings?
Floors?
Windows?
I know what you're thinking:
Who's this jerk?
Well, this jerk was
Hammond Druthers,
a legend in the
architecture community.
Very big in the '80s.
He was also far and away
the worst boss I ever had.
Then I designed the Spokane
National Bank Building.
And suddenly... I was his boss.
- And he didn't like it.
- Stairs?
And to be honest,
I wasn't sure I liked it either.
See, before,
when I was just another employee,
I was happy, carefree.
The guy who hung out in the break
room making fun of the boss.
Did you see what he
was wearing today?
It was like his pants were
being held up by his nipples.
Yeah, and that shirt with the flowers,
I get hay fever just looking at it.
But suddenly I was
a different guy.
Hey, guys.
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Um... nice shirt.
Thanks.
The hours were insane.
I was always working even
when I wasn't at work.
Oh, Robin...
I just had a great idea.
Oh, do whatever you want to
me just don't wake me up.
Before, I used to be this guy.
Dude, of course you should take the
day off for the Foo Fighters concert.
Just say you're sick.
But now...
I was this guy.
Sick, huh?
Unbutton your shirt.
Hmm... "Foo Fighters."
Get back to work.
But still,
the worst part was Druthers.
- Well, I was thinking...
- Ceilings? Oops.
Said that already. Then again,
you seem to like rehashing old ideas.
I'm kidding, of course.
Another hole in one, boss.
Oh, wow,
he must be really good-looking.
Why would you say that?
Well, 'cause only good-looking people
can get away with saying things like that.
I have found that to be true.
It's a blessing
and a curse really.
Ted, you can't let him
treat you like that.
Yeah, you gotta ask yourself,
who's the boss?
- Tony.
- Angela. - Mona.
Mona?
Watch it more closely.
Rock your world.
So, what are you gonna do?
Well... it's awkward, I mean,
the guy used to be my boss.
So, I went to talk to
the managing partner.
Fire him.
Well, sir, I was thinking he could
just be put on a different project.
Fire him!
He's an arrogant,
washed-up, pain in the ass.
In fact,
fire everyone on that project.
Druthers, Mosby,
the whole lot of them.
Mosby, sir? I, I... I hear
Mosby's doing some great work.
Fine, Mosby can stay.
But tell him he's on thin ice.
Come here.
I like you, Crosby.
You mind if I charge my phone?
Knock yourself out.
Well, Ted, if you do fire Druthers,
the key is timing.
Remember when I had to
fire my makeup artist?
Vicki, um...
I'm so sorry about this,
but there's been some
budget cuts and, um,
we have to let you go.
I mean, after tonight.
I still need my makeup
for the broadcast.
So...
Our thoughts and prayers go out
to the families of the victims.
You know what? I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna fire
Druthers tomorrow.
- Oh, my God!
- What?
- Do you know about this?
- No.
What is that?
Only the greatest thing ever.
Wait, wait, wait--
that's not enough buildup.
If they were to cure
cancer tomorrow,
this would still be the greatest
thing to happen all week.
Okay. Now you're ready
for naked Marshall.
Oh, my God.
This is awesome times awesome.
It's awesome squared.
I know, right?
Behind the piano this whole time.
Wait. If Marshall went to
all this trouble to hide it,
he clearly doesn't
want us to find it.
Oh, come on, Robin.
No, I'm saying that he must be
really embarrassed by this.
We are gonna have so much fun.
I know!
We're gonna have so much fun!
Oh, sorry I'm late;
lunch ran a little long.
You wanted to see me, Mosby?
Uh, yeah, like four hours ago.
Well, excuse me,
for spending the last four hours
drawing designs
for your building.
This is a cocktail napkin.
Covered in profanity.
Look, Hammond, um,
there's no easy way
to say this, so...
why don't we just, um,
step into your office.
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
- # Happy birthday to you #
- Oh, you had me. You so had me.
♪ Happy birthday, dear Hammond ♪
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
So, you didn't fire him?
I can't fire a guy on his birthday.
Everyone would hate me.
Besides, they put a party hat on me.
My authority was compromised.
Oh, hey, Marshall. Have a seat.
I know how much
you love stools.
Thanks. Yeah,
stools are better for your posture.
And, uh... I... got you a rose.
Thank you. That's so sweet.
You guys are being... so sweet.
Hey, guys. Guess what I got.
A new dart.
Oh, wow, a new dart.
Hey, that new dart is great.
I did not know you were such
a fan of new dart, Barney.
Oh, yes, Robin,
I just love new dart.
Nude art.
- Nude art.
Okay, all right, so what,
you guys found the painting, huh?
I knew this day would come.
How did you know that?
Because I didn't
hide it very well.
So the story on the painting is that,
back in college,
Lily wanted to do a nude
study for her art class.
Marshall wasn't
so into the idea.
Well, I just...
don't think that some dude
should drop trou just
to pose for you.
It's for class, and it's just that
weird kid Hunter from my freshman hall.
The frisbee dude
with the soul patch?
He's like the hottest
guy in school!
No, he's actually
a little husky...
Oh, he's just huggable!
And complicated...
and a little bit of a jerk.
Just enough so you think
maybe you can change him.
Okay, just forget it.
Call me old-fashioned,
I just think that I'm the only
guy you should see naked.
Well, then you'll
have to do it.
Are you kidding me?
What if somebody sees it?
We're not in high
school anymore.
People don't make fun of you
for posing nude for a painting.
We're adults now.
We totally saw your butt.
This painting has caused
too much grief already.
I'm destroying it right now.
Oh, no,
what's the matter, Marshall?
Where is it?
I'll tell you where it is if
you'll answer these riddles three.
You hung it up in the bar,
didn't you?
Yo, why you gotta
ruin my riddles?
Field trip!
Oh, no. Someone put your
painting up behind the bar.
Classic!
What a memorable prank.
Hey, Marshall.
What'll you have?
What'll I have?
Um, I don't know, maybe a beer
and that nude painting of
me hanging behind the bar!
Ooh, I'm sorry,
that painting's property of the bar.
I know that Barney gave
you that painting.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Whatever he's paying you,
I'll pay you double.
I doubt it.
Whatever he's paying you,
I'll give you that plus ten bucks.
I doubt it.
All right, you know what, Carl, you
just lost yourself a regular customer.
I doubt it.
This painting is the worst thing
that's ever happened to me.
Okay, where should we put it up next?
In his law school?
Ooh on the side of a bus.
Oh, oh!
How much do billboards cost?
Easy, Scherbatsky. Finesse.
I've got a five-year
rollout plan.
I'll have you know that painting's
got commitments all over the city.
Then, after New York...
One of my worst
fears has come true--
I just saw Marshall
grabbing himself naked.
Well, I gotta go.
Believe it or not,
I have to go back to the office.
Oh, I'll go out with you.
Bye, guys.
You know, I wish everyone didn't
have to make fun of that painting.
Eh, we're not making fun of the painting,
we're just making fun of Marshall.
The painting's
actually really great.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
Well, thank you.
You know, seeing it again
makes me miss painting nudes.
What?
Paint me.
Who's that?
Who's out there?
Hammond, is that you?
Mosby?
Druthers and I were
alone in the office.
If I was gonna fire him,
this would be the best
chance I'd ever have.
Uh, look, just a second, Ted.
Uh, no, I,
I really need to talk to you.
Look, there's no
easy way to say...
What, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
I'm standing here
wearing pants.
Are you sleeping here?
What's going on?
Okay, fine, yes.
Not that it's any
of your business
but my wife had a little
spat a few weeks ago,
and I've been sleeping
here until she cools off.
Okay, well, uh, you're right--
that is none of my business.
Uh, look,
there's no easy way to say this-- I...
Who am I kidding?
She's never gonna take me back.
It's okay.
What did you want to say to me?
Happy birthday, buddy.
So, you've been
living at the office?
Yes.
I'm an architect
without a home.
You see the tragic
irony in that?
- Yeah, I do.
- 'Cause I design homes.
- I see it.
- But I don't have a home.
Not lost on me at all.
But I don't understand--
why don't you just go to a hotel?
You could be sleeping on
a mattress instead of...
what appears to be torn-up
drawings of my building.
Why would I go to a hotel,
when any second,
she's going to call and
tell me to come home.
She's a very special lady, Ted.
She's quite... mannish.
She gives me what I need.
Do you understand that?
Uh, no, I don't.
If you were lost
in the wilderness,
she can provide for me.
Well, that's the dream.
I'm glad you came
here tonight, Ted.
Me too, Hammond.
- Call me Ham.
- No, thanks.
- Hammy D?
- No, I think just Hammond.
So, I'm guessing
you didn't fire him.
I was this close.
Meanwhile, Lily had
been up all night
in the grips of a dilemma.
- Oh honey, you're awake?
- I'm awake.
- Is everything okay?
- Yeah.
I've kind of been
wrestling with something.
What if I told you I had a
way to pay for our honeymoon?
Baby, our honeymoon's
already paid for.
We're going to Howe Caverns.
Well yeah, but-- but what if we didn't
want to spend our honeymoon in a cave?
It's not just a cave,
it's a whole labyrinth of caves.
It's an underground adventure.
There's a cave that's so dark that
you don't even know you're in there.
I mean, we're going to experience
a whole new kind of dark.
Well, what if I found a way
to make a little extra money
so that we spend our
honeymoon not in Howe Caverns,
but in Scotland?
- Loch Ness?
- Yeah.
And you know, Edinburgh and
the Highlands and Glasgow...
Loch Ness. Nessy.
Baby, I would love to search for the
enchanted creature of the Emerald Loch,
but... we can't afford that.
Maybe we can.
Paint me.
Okay, I don't get this.
You've been making fun of
that painting all this time
and now you want
me to paint you?
We knew we could torture
Marshall because he has shame.
I do not.
In my body,
where the shame gland should be,
there's a second awesome gland.
True story.
Yeah, that's not the gland
I'm worried about painting.
Yeah.
A nude Barney is a challenge.
But I think you're talented
enough to immortalize this.
Now is the time-- I'm 31.
I'm at the peak of
my physical beauty.
If I were a woman,
I'd have passed it long, long ago.
Long ago.
Forget it.
I promised Marshall he was the
only guy I would ever see naked.
I'll give you $5,000.
We're going to Loch Ness!
Yeah!
That cabby would not shut up.
Yeah, we should
call him a gabby.
I think it, you say it.
Hey, uh... thanks for putting
me up last night, buddy.
Give 'em hell.
Morning, team.
So, I have given
it some thought,
and I say we revisit columns.
Oh, God, not this again.
Ted, a man in a toga just arrived
and delivered a parchment.
Let me read it:
Oh! It's from ancient Greece.
They want their basic
architectural elements back.
- Geez.
- What?
You didn't hear me?
Toga, parchment...
Can I see you for one second?
Ooh, I'm in trouble now.
What are you doing?
I thought we were friends.
You slept on my couch,
you ate my cereal.
I tossed you more toilet paper.
We are friends.
But that doesn't magically
make your bad ideas good.
What? I don't believe this!
You're, you're,
you're wearing my clothes!
And my
girlfriend's... sneakers--
man, you have
weirdly small feet.
Ted, I hope that you're not going
to let our professional woes
interfere with our friendship,
because I really kind
of need you right now.
Okay, let's get this over with.
Hey, hey!
I don't want you phoning this in.
This painting could, someday,
become a serious work of art.
I mean, you have been
blessed with an amazing gift.
Thank you.
I meant me.
Now, I like how you captured
Marshall's essence.
Goofy and unburdened, with wit.
But me,
I want something more regal.
Something my progeny
could look at and say,
"There's stands
Barnabus Stinson."
He was wise...
and strong.
I don't think your
sword will fit.
I get that a lot.
And so, as Lily began painting,
Marshall thought
about the $5,000
and what his fiancée
was doing to earn it.
This isn't right.
This isn't right at all.
Finally, he could
take it no more.
Hold still.
- Hold still!
- Paint faster!
Okay, I guess it's time.
Drop your shorts.
Yeah.
Wait, wait!
That wasn't enough buildup.
I need...
In a world without justice,
one man--
- Oh, just drop them!
- All right.
- No! No, this is not right!
- We had a deal!
Well, I'm going back on the deal.
Barney, get out!
- You...!
- It's over!
Lily, I can't let you
go through with this!
I found a castle we can stay in,
but it's an extra two grand.
It's just not right!
It's beautiful and
they say it's haunted.
I can't let the woman I love
compromise her values for money!
I totally think we can get
some more money out of him.
I'm never letting my
fiancée, ever...!
Oh, you're still here?
Before you say anything,
I'll give you an
extra five grand.
We accept.
You people are so
easy to control.
Dance for me, puppets, dance.
And that's how Uncle Barney paid
for Lily and Marshall's honeymoon.
Come on, Ted, listen,
why don't we get back
and finish drawing the
plans for a building
which, in my opinion,
is never going to get built,
so you and I can get out of here
and grab a couple of beers.
No.
Look, Hammond,
there's no easy way to say this but...
Looking for Hammond Druthers.
Oh, that's me.
I'm Hammond Druthers.
These are divorce papers.
You've been served.
Oh, God.
She's really going
through with this.
So that's it. It's over.
There is no easy way
to say this, but...
She's giving me the
remains of Wolfie?
My dog is dead?
Oh, my God.
I can't believe this.
She always played
too rough with him.
Believe me,
there is no easy way to say this--
- # Happy birthday to you... #
- You've got to be kidding me!
Guys, you have no idea how much
this means to me right now.
Wait, his birthday
was yesterday!
Yeah, but a bunch of us were up
at the conference in Montreal,
- so we thought...
- No! No birthday! No!
I got something to say
and I'm gonna get it out.
Hammond, listen to me.
I am sorry that your dog died,
and that your wife is
divorcing you and that...
your life is falling apart and that
these guys missed your birthday.
And there is no
easy way to say...
What are you doing?
What's going on?
Oh, God...
Oh, come on, you're not going
to pull that, are you?
Oh! Look, yeah, right.
Now we're falling onto the ground.
Well, nice try, but guess what?
You're fired!
You're fired--
you get it? You hear me?
You're gone! You're fired!
In my defense,
I think we all suspected Hammond
might have been faking.
On the plus side, the EMTs seem to
think he's going to be just fine
and, as you saw, they did admit that
I did not cause the heart attack,
even if they said it
a bit begrudgingly.
And there it was, rock bottom:
They all hated me.
But just when all seemed lost,
I had the greatest idea
of my entire career.
Margarita Fridays--
great idea, boss.
Okay, it's done.
I'm gonna step out,
so you can admire it.
Thank you very much, Lily.
Marshall, do you
have the money?
- Yeah.
- Let's get out of here!
A smooth area?!
You gave me the Ken doll?!
She left out Little Barney.
Barnacle Junior.
My Barnana is...
Barnito Supreme.