Every architect can point to that
one design that changed their career.
For me,it was around the
time of my 31st birthday.
It wasn't a museum or a
concert hall or a skyscraper.
It was something else.
We're opening a restaurant called Rib
Town,and we want it to be shaped...
Like a cowboy hat.
Look,I need the work.
I don't have any other options.
Well,there's always that teaching job.
Yeah,I didn't work this hard toe stuck
in some crappy,dead-end teaching job.
No offense,Lily.
I got peed on three times
today. No arguments here.
I just gotta nail this hat building
so,I'll see you all in three days.
For the next three days,I worked
harder than I'd ever worked in my life.
And I got... nowhere.
Hey,Ted,whatcha doing?
Designing a building shaped like a hat.
- Now a good time to chat?
- No.
So,what do you think of Robin?
Barney,I really need
to get to work,so...
Great.Say you and I went suit-shopping,
and you happened upon a beautiful
suit,a beautiful Canadian suit.
Double-breasted.
You try it on,but it's not
exactly the right fit for you.
So,you put it back. Then I try it on.
I don't really want to take the
same suit that you had your eye on,
but at the same time,I
really like that suit.
Buy the suit,Barney. You
clearly care about it.
Tell the suit how you feel.
Okay.
But Ted,remember that that
was your answer because...
The suit is Robin. I know!
Right?
- I'm with you,buddy.
- You are now.
Because I explained it to you.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:咔肉肉
How I Met Your
Mother Season04 Episode24
Come on,dude,you've been at this
for three days without a break.
Now,it's your birthday.
Come up to the roof
and have a beer with me.
No can do. Presentation is tomorrow.
Hat buildings don't design themselves.
It's a rib joint for fat tourists.
Just make sure the doors are wide
and the chairs are reinforced.
Now,birthday beer on the roof. Let's go!
Why do you want me to
come up to the roof so bad?
What,are you throwing
me a surprise party?
What? Ted,we threw you a
surprise party last year.
Okay,you don't get two
surpse parties in a row.
I mean,the fact that anyone showed up at
the first one was surprise enough,right?
Two surprise parties in a row!
That is rich! That is rich!
Classic! He still won't come up.
Come on. What the crap?
I knew having a second
surprise party was a bad idea.
Yes,Robin,I know.
This party is... it's a
disaster. It was my idea.
I take responsibility.
And there's really only
one thing to do about it.
- Oh,Marshall,no.
- Lily,I have to do this!
No point in putting it off any longer.
I should explain.
You see,a few years earlier...
No,uh-uh,forget it. This
is so not pimped out.
If anything,this is pimped in.
You know who knows how
to live? Those people.
Ah,the rooftop patio one
building over from ours.
Across a chasm of just six or seven
feet awaited a landscaped paradise.
And best of all...
That looks to be one hot tub.
Great. How do we get over there?
What are we gonna do? Jump?
I can jump that far.
Marshall,lately it takes you
two tries to get off the sofa.
You can't jump that far.
- Really?
- Really.
Watch me.
But he didn't jump.
******
This actually is kind of nice.
Right? Right?
Okay...
And in the years that
followed,he kept almost jumping.
Okay... Okay!
But each time,without fail...
Okay. Here we go.
He didn't jump.
But don't worry.
'Cause if I can make this jump
tonight,it's totally gonna save the party.
Honey,please get down from there.
Lily,when Evel Knievel sat astride his star-spangled
rocket on the rim of Snake River Canyon,
do you think his wife
said,Honey,get down from there?
For the last time,I
am not Linda Knievel!
I will never be Linda Knievel!
You don't need to remind me.
Marshall,please don't do this.
Lily,but I gotta do this.
- You can't do this.
- Why?
You want a reason? I'll give
you a reason. I'm pregnant.
Oh,my God!
Oh,my God,really?
Lily,I mean,I noticed that you
gained some weight lately...
I was lying,you jerk!
Oh,go ahead and jump. I hope you die!
That's all the permission I need.
Listen,Robin...
- There's something I have to tell you.
- But wait.
Before you do,I have to
tell you something first.
What is it?
I think I'm in love with you.
It's Ted. Everybody shh!
Hey,Ted,what's up?
It's here,Lily.
It's looking at me.
What is?
The goat.
Now,I've told you some of
the story of the goat already.
How Aunt Lily invited a local farmer to come
talk to her class,and how he brought a goat,
and how he told the whole class what he
was gonna do to the goat later that day.
And how Aunt Lily,in a fit of mercy,bought the
goat off the guy in order to commute its sentence.
Lily,something amazing has happened.
I was talking to Robin,I was
all set to tell her how I feel,
but before I could,you'll
nev believe what she said.
I think I'm in love with you.
What did you say?
What do you think I said? What would
anyone say to something like that?
Yeah... Robin,listen.
You're great. I mean,you're really
awesome,but I mean,we're friends.
It's probably a bad idea.
I-I guess you're right.
Uh,have a good party.
You too,kiddo.
What?
It's like,as soon as she
said that,no more feelings.
I'm not in love with her anymore.
So,you've been in love with
this girl for the past year,
and the second she reciprocates those
feelings,just like that,you're over her.
How great is that?
No! No! This is a washcloth. Not food.
What the...
Okay... this is it.
Here we... Go!
This is it.
Tracey,Tracey,tell Lily
what you just told me.
Um,that I just moved to New York?
No,no,but tell her how you got here.
I just got off the bus from Iowa.
Just got off the bus from Iowa!
How lucky is it that an aspiring dancer
just off the bus from Iowa runs
into the producer of the Rockettes?
I feel like I'm in one of
those classic show biz stories.
Oh,honey,you are. You really are.
Hey,Tracey,why don't you make me one of those
rum and beers that your dad loves so much?
Sure thing!
- Damn it.
- What?
Everybody always says,Don't tell Lily.
Lily can't keep a secret.
And,usually,they're right.
But this time,I kept the secret.
And then you come along with this crap and
you force me to pull an old classic Lily
and spill the beans!
What beans? There's beans?
There's beans.
The suit is Robin.
I know! Right?
I'm with you,buddy.
You are now.
Because I explained it to you.
There you go.
Oh,crap.
He said that? Oh,my God!
What a tremendous
ground-breaking surprise!
- How long have you known?
- Eight months.
And you've kept it a secret
since then? Good for you.
Yeah. Good for you,Lily.
I mean,what a bombshell.
Who saw that coming?
- How long have you known?
- Seven months,29 days.
God,what am I going to do?
I don't know. What are you going to do?
I'm going to marry Barney
in a big church wedding.
And we're going to move to some sleepy New
Hampshire town and open a bed-and-breakfast.
- Aww,really?
- No!
It's Barney. I mean...
it's Barney. But it's Barney.
I got to tell him no.
Oh,man,you're going to break his...
Whatever it is that pumps that
black sludge through his veins.
Crap. You're right.
The first time Barney expresses
feelings for a girl and she rejects him?
And not just any girl. I mean...
It will destroy him.
Okay,well,first of all...
Second of all,there is a maneuver you can
try. It's high-risk,but it's also high-reward.
For lack of a better
term,I'm going to call it...
The Mosby.
- The Mosby?
- No,she couldn't Mosby him.
She could Mosby the crap out of him.
What's the Mosby?
Robin,you remember your
first date with Ted?
You wanted to hop on the
T-train and take a ride downtown.
I was ready to jump that turnstile.
What changed all that?
- I think I'in love with you.
- What?
The Mosby!
That is genius. And,um... excuse me.
I mean,you're very pretty,but you're
freakishly tall,and you don't believe in ghosts.
So,when she said she thinks she's in
love with me,she meant the opposite.
Exactly. And look how well it
worked. You're back to normal.
Yes. Yes,I am.
And it is great. It's awesome.
- So,Robin's not in love with me.
- Nope.
Why not?
Mr. Goat?
Okay. That's it.
Stupid goat.
I do not understand your
fascination with this washcloth.
I guess at's what happen when
you have a brain thsize of a...
No,no,no!
Okay,okay,okay...
Hey,Marshall,can you just go get Ted?
Lily,I was just about to jump.
Didn't you hear me saying
"Okay" over and over again?
Oh,I'm sorry. Go ahead and jump.
No,it's fine. Sorry,everybody.
Lily won't let me jump.
Yeah.
Thank God.
Hospital!
So,what happened exactly?
What happened is you let a freaking
wild animal into our apartment.
I was savaged.
That is the sweetest,cutest
little goat in the whole world.
Sweetest,cutest little
goat in the whole world?
I was prettyleep-deprived
at this point,
so this probably isn't how it really
happened,but here's how I remember it.
So,you're the guy who tried
to make it with a goat?
Hey,if anything,that goat
tried to make it with me.
- Can I go,please?
- Sure,you can go.
But remember,buddy,"baa" means "baa."
Great. Great. Now I'm going
to be late for my presentation.
Thanks a lot,Mr. Goat.
Mr. Goat? Ted,that goat's
a girl. Her name's Missy.
You got beat up by a girl.
- So. You're in love with me.
- What?
Oh,yeah. Very much.
Okay,you can knock it off. Lily told me.
Damn it. Lily!
I can't believe you would do that.
It's just... Like,I care
about you,Barney. And...
This kind of stuff,the emotional stuff?
It's not your thing. I thought
I'd save you the trouble.
Well,maybe I don't want
to be saved the trouble.
Maybe I want the trouble.
I haven't wanted the
trouble in a long time.
But with you,the trouble
doesn't seem so. troubling.
I don't know. I thought...
I guess I thought you felt the se way.
Maybe I do. I don't know.
I'm not exactly the biggest
confronter of feelings.
I mean,clearly,there's
something between us.
Maybe my head was saying,"Nip it in the bud"
because my heart was saying something else.
Look... I have feelings for you,Barney.
Maybe I even love you.
- This is going pretty fast,don't you think?
- What?
We have a really good friendship going.
Why screw up a good thing?
- Friends?
- Friends.
Oh,my God. You just did it
again. You just Mosby'd me.
- I did not.
- You did. You little minx.
Okay,you're right. I did just Mosby you.
Why are you so afraid
of giving this a chance?
Because I am scared
of how much I like you.
Whoa,this is a bad idea.
You're right. This is a mistake.
- Yes. No.
- I love you.
- Let's be friends.
- Okay,friends,then.
- I love you.
- Let's get married.
- No,you're smothering me.
- Okay,forget it.
You know what? We can
sort this out later.
- Yeah,that sounds good.
- That sounds good.
It had been a long and
crazy night,but that morning,
against all odds,I made
it to my presentation.
Here you have it,gentlemen. Rib Town.
Right? Right?
Yeah.
Ted,listen. You're great,and
you've done a real...
special job here,and you're going to make
some other restaurant very happy someday,
but,uh,we have,uh,decided to go...
- another direction here.
- What?
Feast your eyes on...
- Rib Town!
Sven.
I'll tell you one thing.
I'm never eating ribs again.
Yeah,right.
I am never... eating ribs... again!
In front of Ted!
This is a disaster.
How am I going to come back from this?
Okay,I'm just going to ask this.
Do you really want to
come back from this?
What's that supposed to mean?
Architecture is killing you,Ted,and
it's killing us to watch it killing you.
You're like that goat
with the washcloth.
You want it so bad,and every time the world tries
to take it away from you,you keep grabbing it.
But you know what? It's just a
washcloth. Why do you even want it?
Because I... I have to
be an architect. That's...
that's the plan.
Screw the plan. I planned
on being a famous artist.
Marshall planned on being
an environmental lawyer.
Robin planned on being a TV reporter.
I am a TV reporter. I'm on
every morning at 4:00 a.m.
Is that still on? Oh,good for you.
Somebody watch it,please.
Barney planned on being a violinist.
- Lily.
- Don't tell me things.
Look,you can't design
your life like a building.
It doesn't work that way.
You just have to live
it,and it will design itself.
So,what,I should just do nothing?
No. Listen to what the world is
telling you to do and take the leap.
You're right. You're absolutely right.
I love you,Lily.
Oh,no. Metaphorical
leap. Metaphorical leap!
- This is not cool.
- Don't do it.
No!
- I did it!
- Baby,you did it.
- I can do anything!
- Yes,you can.
I'm getting a motorcycle!
- You absolutely are not!
- Okay,sorry. Guys,me on over.
That was the year I
got left at the altar.
It was the year I got knocked
out by a crazy bartender.
The year I got fired.
The year I got beat up by a goat.
A girl goat,at that.
And damn it if it wasn't
the best year of my life.
Because,if any one of those
things hadn't happened,
I never would have ended up in a which
turned out to be the best job I ever had.
But more importantly,I
wouldn't have met your mother,
because,as you know...she
was in that class.
But of course,that story
is only just beginning.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents