[cicadas chirping]
[dog barking]
[child, speaking Arabic] Mother?
Mother?
I had a nightmare.
I saw them shoot him, in the dream.
[woman speaks Arabic]
[sighs]
Mama, why did he die?
Because that is what's written
in God's book -
Say, "Nothing shall befall us,
except what God has ordained."
Did God not love him?
God loved him so much...
He took him sooner than we wanted.
Does God love me that much?
Yes...
but God has a different plan for you.
[child] How will I know?
[distant explosion]
[mother] He will reveal it to you
when you're ready.
[distant explosion]
[sniffling]
Mamma.
[explosion close by]
[gunfire]
[woman, in English] US foreign policy
has come under criticism once again
with the resurgence of ISIL in Syria.
Since allied forces left the region
in 2019,
several cities have fallen
to the caliphate in swift succession
in its expansion south.
The city of Damascus has been under siege
for months now,
worsening the refugee crisis.
It seems nothing but an act of God
can stop the ancient city
from falling to the caliphate.
[man yelling in Arabic]
Today, God gives us Damascus!
[radio chatter in Arabic]
[crowd clamoring]
DAMASCUS, SYRIA
DAY 85 OF REBEL SIEGE
Help us!
We're trapped!
Please let us out!
We'll die here!
Help us!
Let us out!
[distant gunfire]
[man, in Arabic]
Jibril? When did you escape?
Samer?
They said you joined the rebels.
Your family was worried about you.
Where's your family?
[distant gunfire]
[men speaking Arabic]
[man] Listen to me!
Listen to me, my brothers and sisters.
They pretend to preach God's word,
and all they do is twist its meaning.
It is written in The Book.
"They shall be held up to shame
in this world...
they have incurred God's
most inexorable wrath...
a shameful defeat awaits them!"
A defeat awaits you!
[in Farsi] May the Devil swallow you up!
I've looked the Devil in the eye.
He cannot swallow me.
[in Arabic] It is written -
Say, "Nothing shall befall us,
except what God has ordained."
[men shout out]
[man] It is forbidden
to misquote the scriptures!
[preacher] Look at you.
You've suffered more than anyone
on this earth.
You're surrounded by enemies
who want to eradicate you.
[crowd clamoring]
[man] Load the artillery! Quickly!
The sandstorm's upon us!
Believe me when I say God
will defeat your enemies!
Because God wants you to live.
Mark my words!
On this day, mark my words!
God's hand will turn them away!
Salvation is at hand!
[rocket flying overhead]
Everybody, get inside!
[screaming and yelling]
Salvation is at hand!
There is nothing to be afraid of!
Heed my words!
This is their last gasp...
...their dying breath.
[Samer] Jibril... [yelling]
[preacher] Mark my words...
the scale has tipped!
History has ended!
[continues preaching in Arabic]
[crowd yelling and screaming]
[newsreader] It lasted a record 43 days,
a sandstorm of biblical proportions,
covering the city of Damascus
in a blanket of dust.
The devastation is still untold.
Roads and motorways have been
rendered inoperable,
the city's international airport
closed for weeks,
virtually stranding the city,
causing hundreds of businesses
to shut down.
- [crowd yelling]
- But despite the catastrophe,
there were celebrations
across Damascus today,
as ISIS militia finally withdrew troops
from their long-held position
outside the ancient city,
after the month-long sandstorm
literally buried their ground forces,
cutting off the chain of supply.
The White House announced today
the end of ISIS as a threat
in the Middle East.
This was ISIL's last stronghold in Syria
after the resurgence of 2019,
and this finally spells their end.
So, yes, we're very grateful
for the weather.
[Keneally] The president said he was
hopeful this development would open up...
All right, you can sit up
- and get dressed now, Ms. Geller.
- [sighs]
Has the doctor gone over everything
with you?
Uh, yes.
You'll probably feel funny
for the first few days...
I know. This isn't my first time.
[man on TV] we are... this is one
of the many...
...southern California,
it's barely recognizable...
- [sighs]
- [phone alert]
[sobbing]
[sighs]
- [Ms. Geller] You're a philosophy major.
- [man] Yes, ma'am.
[Ms. Geller] So, why do you wanna work
for the CIA?
I think it's one of the most
important jobs a person can have.
Keeping our country safe.
Upholding its values.
What's a misconception
that some people may have about you?
That I'm judgmental.
- So, you're not?
- Not really.
I accept
all different kinds of people.
Would you accept a criminal?
If he'd served his time
and was remorseful.
- Would you trust him?
- No.
Not with... everything.
What wouldn't you trust him with?
My family.
- A secret.
- [beep]
[Ms. Geller] The truth?
Would you trust him
to tell you the truth?
Well, the truth has
many different versions.
So it's hard to say.
The truth has many different versions?
The truth is pretty gray.
I'm gonna stop the interview there.
I know I shouldn't be telling you this,
but I won't be recommending you.
Uh, why not?
The CIA is like a holy order.
It's a doctrine that you live by.
People's lives depend on the decisions
that we make,
the actions that we take.
When you're in the trenches,
you need to know who your enemies are.
The truth may look gray,
but I assure you it is not.
I'm sorry.
[bleep]
[crowd chanting in Arabic]
[sighs]
[chanting in Arabic] Messiah! Messiah!
[chanting continues]
[increases volume]
Messiah! Messiah! Messiah!
[bleep]
[chanting continues]
[pauses video]
[all yelling] Messiah! Messiah!
[chanting] Messiah! Messiah!
[chanting continues] Messiah! Messiah!
[Jibril] Imam?
Where do you lead us, Imam?
To our destiny.
Messiah! Messiah! Messiah!
[horns blaring]
[chanting fades]
[distant siren wailing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[sighs]
[phone alert]
[phone alerts]
[sighs]
- [phone chimes]
- [sighs]
Dad, what part of "I'm working"
don't you understand?
Well, I was just wondering
how it went today at the clinic.
[sighs] Fine. Just... just like last time.
- What are you doing working?
- Please, Dad.
No, you need your rest.
You're not taking this seriously.
Of course I'm taking it seriously.
[phone alert]
- I gotta go.
- All right.
Get some sleep.
Good night.
I love you.
- [bleep]
- [sighs]
What do you got?
Rumor is he's from Egypt.
I listened to those other files.
I'm hearing, uh, some other accent.
Iranian, maybe,
which likely means he's Shi'ite.
He just led 2,000 Syrian Palestinians
into the desert.
What's a Shi'ite doing
leading a bunch of Sunnis?
Yeah, feels like trouble.
I'll put him on our watch list
and get eyes on him in the morning.
- Thanks, Q.
- Okay.
[chiming]
[sighs]
[men shouting]
[in Arabic] "If you look for truth,
you may find comfort.
If you look for comfort,
you will never find truth."
[man] Why do you quote an infidel?
Who are you to judge who's an infidel?
- People are hungry, Imam.
- Don't interrupt, boy.
Why do you call me Imam?
Because you are great.
No greater than you.
"There is no deity but God."
But you turned away evil
as you said you would.
He turned away evil.
But He works through you.
"Did He create you in jest?
Without purpose?"
You expect a shoemaker's son
to know the scriptures?
Do you serve God?
Yes.
Then He works through you.
He works through everyone.
You mean He works through all
who righteously follow Islam.
Don't tell me what I mean.
Why are there no women here?
[laughter]
[cleric] Surely you're not serious.
[laughs]
[clattering]
Go find a woman...
and give her your seat.
This man is the Devil.
He has led us into the desert
with no food.
And to leave me now is to perish.
I'm here to tell you to throw away
your assumptions about God.
Stop clinging to what you think you know.
In this hour,
mankind is a rudderless boat.
Cling to me.
[sighs]
[distant siren wailing]
[coughs]
- [waiter] Hey, we're closing in 20.
- Already?
It's three a.m.
I'm sorry.
Am I stopping you from getting home?
It's my job. Gotta be here anyway.
[he sighs]
The Clash of Civilizations.
Samuel P. Huntington.
How you finding it?
Dry.
Poli sci?
- Yeah.
- Senior year?
Uh-huh.
When's your paper due?
Tomorrow.
The only thing you have to remember
is that he was right.
Huntington predicted that the primary axis
of world conflict after the Cold War
would be along cultural
and religious lines.
It's exactly what's happening
in world politics today,
so just... center your paper
around that argument.
- Uh... You teach?
- No.
Just a nerd.
[chuckles]
My boss calls you Ms. Night Owl.
I have a nickname?
I think he likes you.
I'm Eva.
Keon.
Nice to meet you, Keon.
Wait, so, what do you do...
if you don't teach?
I work in international relations.
That's what my uncle used to say.
He worked for the CIA.
- You a field agent?
- I never said I worked for the CIA.
He died.
My uncle. In Turkey.
- [sighs]
- Last year.
That bombing.
Terrible.
I'm sorry to hear that.
He was doing what... what he loved.
[cicadas chirping]
[praying in Arabic]
[Samer, in Arabic] What is he doing?
Hm?
[Jibril] Talking with God.
He looks crazy.
He stood for 30 days
on the Gate of St. Thomas
and preached without food or water,
during a sandstorm,
while we hid in a building,
fearing for our lives.
[scoffs]
You don't believe
he really did that, do you?
He is Isa returned.
al-Masih.
[al-Masih] Jibril!
Sit down with me.
Do you know there is a star
for every soul?
Do you believe me?
Yes.
Imam... is my mother in a good place?
She's where God wants her.
She is with Him?
Do you think...
He would forsake a soul as good as hers?
I miss her.
I want to see her.
It's good you're thinking about
the next life.
Why have you come now?
It's pointless to question these things.
I'm here...
in this moment because
I have always been here in this moment...
and so have you.
You have light in you, Jibril...
but God is going to ask some hard things
of you.
I am ready.
Pack up the camp. We're moving.
[crowd chanting in Arabic] Messiah!
"Masih" in Arabic means "Messiah."
[chanting] Messiah! Messiah!
So, this is a cult?
Possibly. ISIL use this type
of apocalyptic propaganda all the time,
and to good effect.
This guy's just taken it
to the next level.
So, he's some rival faction? Al-Qaeda?
- We don't know who he's associated with.
- What do we know about him?
That's the concerning thing.
He's come out of nowhere and he's leading
desperate people into the desert.
To what end?
Well, if it's a cult,
he could be leading them to their death.
Or he could be creating an army.
An army of sick and starving refugees?
He's creating a cause, in the hope
that other people will join him.
- That's a lot of speculation, Eva.
- It's my job to speculate, ma'am.
He has over 2,000 followers.
What if he turns out
to be another al-Baghdadi?
I'd like to keep an eye on him.
Minimal resources.
Thank you, ma'am.
[whirring]
What do you have over Syria?
[crowd approaching]
We'll lose range in about four minutes.
What are we looking for, exactly?
Can you zoom in on that?
Closer?
There we are.
They're nowhere near Damascus.
[Eva] Where are we?
[technician] There's Damascus.
- And that's...
- Israel.
He's led us to our deaths.
He's led us into battle!
[cheering]
[ululating]
Collect all the weapons.
[Eva] Get me Director Bailey.
We need to get a message
to that security post in Israel.
Imam, what do you want us to do?
Dig a hole and bury them.
Then how do we fight?
[pop music playing]
[man singing in Hebrew]
[woman] Shit.
[man, in Hebrew] What?
We've got a crazy fucker.
[man sighs]
Hello there, crazy fucker.
[in English] Oh, shit.
Oh, shit, shit, shit, shit.
[woman mutters in Hebrew]
Fuck.
[man, in Hebrew] Patrol house 283ip.
Repeat, 283ip.
Request immediate reinforcement.
[radio chatter in Hebrew]
[both speaking Hebrew]
- [woman] Shit!
- [man] No!
- [yells in Hebrew]
- [radio chatter]
- No, no, no!
- [both speaking Hebrew]
[screaming]
[in Arabic] Be strong.
God is with you.
[in Hebrew] Hands up!
Hands away from your clothes!
[female soldier] Get down!
- [on radio] Hold fire!
- Where the hell is reinforcement?
[in Hebrew] These people need food.
Lebanon is that way.
Lay down on the ground. I said lay down!
[male soldier] Hands up!
Stand down.
Arrest him.
[woman, in English] A dramatic arrest
took place at the Israeli border...
[Arabic]
The occupying forces have refused...
the Palestinian refugees
entry back into their homeland,
led by a man they call al-Masih.
- [English]...crowd was fired at...
- ...man from Lebanon...
- ...Israelis to the Syrian border...
- ...so far refused the refugees passage,
- criticised by Muslims worldwide...
- ...a caravan of asylum seekers...
[in English] As displaced Palestinians,
they claim they are entitled passage
into the West Bank as rightful citizens.
Okay, we'll go again.
And someone fix my hair.
I look like Phil Spector.
[helicopter engine]
[man grunting]
[phone ringing]
[sighs]
[ringing continues]
Shit.
[door opens]
[sighs]
- [woman, in Hebrew] What are you doing?
- What's it look like?
You can't just let yourself in.
I pay for this place.
There's my princess.
Daddy!
Let me look at you!
I'm all sweaty.
Ah!
You're supposed to call
and let me know you're coming.
They're the rules.
[in English] Fuck the rules.
[in English] Great way to talk
around your daughter.
Oh, like she never heard that from you?
- Where are you going?
- I need to take a shower.
[in Hebrew] This isn't a hotel.
Do you ever clean up?
[in English]
Did you just come here to judge me?
When are you going
to move your shit out?
...arrested this morning,
when attempting to cross the border.
- He is being held in...
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- [phone rings]
- I came to see Eli.
[in Hebrew] Oh, so you bothered this week?
[in Hebrew] Have you got a job yet?
[in English] My job is to look after
our daughter. You should try it sometime.
Go get your coat, princess.
Hello.
Yeah? It's my day off.
When?
Okay.
[in English] Are you going
to break her heart again?
REFUGEE LEADER ARRESTED
We'll eventually pull something on him,
but it's gonna take time and resources.
The fastest way to get to know him
is to meet him.
He's not our detainee,
so, for the moment, he's not our concern.
Israel's handling it.
[Eva] I wouldn't
underestimate this guy, sir.
This wasn't just aimed at Israel.
He knows that
America has to defend Israel's position,
and as long as those starving people
sit at their border,
the more indefensible
that position becomes.
We'll get dragged
into something we don't want.
Why don't you let the politicians
worry about that?
That wasn't very politic.
But it's the truth.
My God, you're like your father.
[horns blaring]
[clanking]
[door slams]
[water dripping]
[in English] This is my day off.
I don't want you to waste my time,
so it would be best
if you just answer my questions.
Why are you here?
[in English] To see the Holy Land.
Welcome to the Holy Land.
- So, I'm free to leave?
- I ask the questions here.
Who are you?
[in Hebrew] The Word.
[Aviram, in Hebrew] The Word?
[in English] Do you even know
what that means?
- [in English] Yes.
- Yes?
So, you are "the word"?
Okay, Mr. The Word,
I don't care if you sit here and rot,
I just don't want you
to waste my fucking time.
So, where did you learn all your Hebrew?
Here.
So, you're from here?
Originally.
From where? Ramat Gan? Jerusalem? Where?
- Why, you assume I'm Palestinian?
- Oh, you're not?
- So, you're Jewish?
- Originally.
Originally.
And now, you're what?
I'm with God.
God.
I don't see him.
You will.
Will I?
Why don't you take God
and stick him up your fucking ass?
What were you doing in Syria?
Delivering a message.
- A message from who?
- My father.
And who is your father?
[in Hebrew] That will be revealed in time.
Why not save me the fucking suspense
and just admit it now?
[in English] Because, Aviram,
it's not time.
Who told you my name?
[in Hebrew] No one needed
to tell me your name.
You are in my father's book.
Don't fuck with me.
[in English] Your anger is misplaced.
You don't want to know
about my anger.
[in Hebrew]
You hold onto hatred like it's a prize,
when it's the weight around your neck.
[in English] You want to hurt me...
like they hurt you.
You talk a lot of shit.
You hurt a lot of people.
It's part of my job, yes.
You enjoy it.
I take pride in my work.
Except for that boy.
What boy?
The boy, in Megiddo.
Is that when you stopped believing?
I ask the questions here.
[in Hebrew]
He is waiting for you, Aviram...
whenever you are ready.
[chair scraping]
[door opens]
[door closes]
DELETE FILE
Hey!
[in Hebrew] Put him in the hole.
- [pool balls click]
- [sighs]
[in English] You look like shit.
[in Hebrew] Have you seen Omer?
[in Hebrew] Why would I do that?
Because he's your brother.
He did something stupid,
I'm not going to take pity on him.
[sighs] I love your compassion.
The country's crumbling
and he decides to rob a fucking store.
He deserves what he gets.
[in English] What's up?
[in Hebrew] You're angrier than usual.
[speaks Hebrew]
You...
You've never mentioned Megiddo
to anyone?
Why would I do that?
Why are you even talking about it?
Nothing.
[whirring]
[bleep]
0% MATCH
[speaking Hebrew]
- Hey, thief. Give it back.
- [mutters]
Goodnight.
[alarm chirps]
[grunts]
[gasping]
[Aviram, in English] You know how many
times I've sat opposite that hood?
[in English] 227.
And every time, it was me.
We could go on doing this forever,
you know?
It's up to you.
This is no solution.
Who are you?
The better question is...
who are you,
Aviram Dahan?
I'm the one asking the questions.
Are you?
[grunts]
[shudders]