I saw him first on TV,
the Temple Mount thing.
That's the first I heard of him.
It's a chance. [laughs]
A chance to believe.
I just... want to be here, uh...
with him, I...
I don't even have to see him.
I haven't seen... al-Masih yet, but...
when I do, I'll know.
Because I've seen God's eyes.
And I'll know
if he's who they say he is...
the moment I look into them.
[phone chiming]
[loud ticking]
[sighs]
Oh, shit.
[children playing outside]
[lock clicking]
Sorry.
[Miriam] I'll go... I'll go... I'll get...
I'll get it!
[man] I'll do this side, you do there...
Under the wipers.
Hey. Make sure you get all the cars.
[host] Reverend, tell us, why do you think
God chose your church to be saved?
[Felix] I think that's a question
you might want to put to God,
- but what I can say is...
- [phone alert]
...it's an incredibly humbling feeling,
and it's incredibly humbling to see
so many people turn up to our town
to support us.
[host] Some are here for support,
but others have come
looking for something, too.
What do you think they're looking for?
[Felix] An answer.
[rings]
[host] To what?
[Felix] Their prayers.
- [man shouting]
- [reverse indicator bleeping]
[man] Yeah, that line there.
Don't worry about it!
...here in Dilley, Texas, the aftermath...
[man on loudspeaker] Down below.
Make way for FEMA medical...
[man] Come on. Hold on, now.
[radio chatter]
[man on radio]
We offer a downloadable e-book
that outlines all our notes
and Bible studies today.
It's called "Reading Your Bible."
It's available at DIB-radio.org.
[woman on radio] You are listening
to His Voice Radio, KWTZ, FM 91.4.
Serving the Body of Christ.
Morning, sunshine. [laughs]
[she sighs]
You take your time.
No rush, okay?
[drumming]
- ♪ Hallelujah ♪
- [man] He said, "I am the Lord, thy God,
from the land of Egypt.
Thou shalt know no God but me,
- for there is no Savior beside me."
- ♪ Hallelujah ♪
And yet you all gather here
to worship another in His name..."
"God despises..."
[group] ♪ Oh ♪
It... It's like Coachella went to church.
- What are we doing here?
- We're looking for an angle.
- You ditched that back in Israel.
- Yeah, you let me know
how that Israeli-Palestine
disagreement works out.
- In the meantime...
- In the meantime,
I'm getting reamed by the network.
It's Journalism 101, Ruben.
Follow the story.
He's the story, the story's here.
- Where, exactly?
- [sighs]
[sighs]
[Felix] Hey, Jen,
the storm shelter's full.
You'll have to try my office
in the back of the church.
- Why don't we meet after lunch?
- Yeah, all right.
- Reverend?
- Just give me a minute, okay? Thanks.
[mother] Reverend?
- How can I help?
- I'm Staci.
This is my daughter, Raeah.
It's so nice to meet you.
I saw you on the TV.
Well, welcome. Glad to have you.
- [laughs]
- Just, uh... make yourselves at home...
- [woman] I mean, how do I even...
- ...wherever you can.
I just... When can we see him?
We've come all the way from Denver.
Definitely soon.
I'll get your names on the list.
There's a list?
Don't worry.
Bye.
[Samer, in Arabic] "There were on the
planet where the Little Prince lived...
as on all planets...
good plants and bad plants."
"In consequence,
there were good seeds from good plants,
and bad seeds from bad plants."
"But seeds are invisible.
They sleep deep in the heart
of the earth's darkness.
Until someone among them is seized...
with the desire to awaken."
[baby crying]
[radio chatter]
[sighs]
[man] Yep, take that water down
to the other camp...
It's me.
Felix.
[al-Masih] Come in.
I'm sorry for interrupting.
There was a frost on the ground
this morning.
Do you need some blankets?
It can get cold at night.
I watched a bird...
drinking the melting frost.
A person might have wondered
where the frost came from
in the middle of summer.
But the bird drank what it could and left.
The people, your followers,
I don't know if you've seen, but...
there are so many now.
They keep askin' to see you,
to know what's next.
Who can know what's next?
I...
I thought you might.
- No, I don't.
- But...
You brought me here, Felix.
What told you to do that?
I don't know. I just did it.
Just like the bird.
Be like the bird, Felix.
[Felix sighs]
[baby crying]
[footsteps approaching]
Bum one?
Thanks.
Been here long?
Too long.
A local?
I came from a small town.
All I wanted to do was leave too.
And did you?
- Leave?
- Eventually.
So you were here from the start?
Before all this fuss.
I knew somethin' was comin'.
You knew?
How?
[chuckles] It's stupid.
Try me.
Sometimes I see things in my head.
[sighs] I have epilepsy.
My parents don't like to call it that,
but that's what it is.
They're...
in denial.
About what?
[Rebecca snorts]
Everything.
Themselves, me.
What about him?
Are they believers?
- They think they are.
- What do you think they are?
Lost.
They don't have a clue.
[guitar playing]
Felix, it's the middle of the night.
Go to sleep.
What is it?
He doesn't have a plan.
[knocking]
I know it's late,
but I got something to show you.
Give me a minute.
[chuckles]
Sit down.
[al-Masih] ...ignore
your personal problems
and drag yourself here on a Sunday.
It's what you worship.
[Eva] Worship?
[al-Masih] Everybody worships.
The only choice is what we worship.
Some people kneel to money.
Some to power, to intellect.
You recorded me.
You are an acolyte of the C...
I was doin' my job.
Like you.
Don't take it personally.
I'm not.
You ever heard of the radical,
Oscar Wallace?
Guy who hacked the stock exchange.
Yeah. You know, he wrote a book,
Cultural Terrorist,
and it received a lot of heat,
but he basically became a magnet
for radicals and extremists.
Now, he uses our friend's
exact words in the book.
[clears throat]
"Everybody worships.
The only choice is what we worship.
Some people kneel to money,
some to power, some to intellect."
And then he goes on to question
the society that we live in,
and the society that is driven
by the world of greed and money and power.
He does go on to say
that the only way to combat this
is to create a healthy confusion
that sparks the need to question.
Confusion, causing fear,
making us question everything
in search of some sense.
If you're asking what our guy's agenda is,
then maybe he's basing it
on Wallace's manifesto.
Create confusion.
'Cause he's certainly doin' that.
- [Eva sighs]
- [car door closes]
[engine starts]
That's it.
I just thought you needed to know.
Thank you for the information.
You, uh...
You have a good night.
You, too.
Allahu akbar
Allah
[men muttering]
[Samer, in Arabic]
You're too weak. Let me help.
[Jibril] I can manage.
[Samer] Let me help.
Allahu akbar
[reciting salat]
[fly buzzing]
Allahu akbar
[sighs]
Brothers! He's dead!
- He's dead!
- [Mullah praying]
- He's dead.
He's dead.
O God, forgive our living and our dead...
[prayer continues]
[Samer] We should go back to Syria.
No.
At least there
you'll be able to see a doctor.
I won't go. I'm staying!
To die here? You can't want that.
I won't die.
You don't know what you're saying.
- You're delirious.
- You don't know!
You don't know Him! Not like I do!
He betrayed you!
You think you're special?
You think you are the chosen one?
Then why aren't you with him?
Because he's in America!
Because he's a fake!
- That's bullshit!
- It's true!
You can't see it.
You can't see it because you're mad!
You can't see it because you love him.
[Samer sighs]
[Ellie, in Hebrew] Mommy?
What are you doing, little goose?
[Ellie] Where's Daddy?
He's probably working.
Now come eat your food.
Then why is his car here?
[Mika sighs]
- [Ellie] Let me do it!
- [Mika whispers]
- [rings doorbell]
- Oh!
Uncle Zev!
[Zev] Hey, Ellie.
How are you?
Okay.
- What's up?
- Sorry for showing up unannounced, but...
[dog barks]
Go play with Cookie...
Cookie, come.
[barking and whimpering]
I feel stupid.
It's probably nothing. It's just...
[in English] With everything going on
in the West Bank...
do you know where Aviram is?
I can't get ahold of him.
I figured maybe you had him
on assignment or something.
He didn't tell you.
I had no choice, I had to suspend him.
Suspend him?
What did he do?
I can't talk about it.
What I can tell you is that
he's due to go in front of a committee
this week to testify.
I'm sure he's fine. He wouldn't miss that.
[in Hebrew] His car's been
out front of our house for three days.
They booted his wheels.
I'll put out some feelers for him.
I'm sure it's nothing to worry about.
Thank you, Zev.
Ellie... time to go.
- [barking]
- [Ellie giggling]
Ellie?
- Ellie?
- [sighs]
[country music playing on radio]
- ♪ Forgive and forget ♪
- [car door opens]
- [shop door bell rings]
♪ Now, I regret ♪
♪ Don't be upset ♪
♪ Forgive and forget ♪
Hey, buddy.
[clerk] Help you?
Yep.
♪ Forget what I did ♪
Take this one.
All righty.
Can I see your ID?
♪ Forgive and forget ♪
Resnick.
Whereabouts in Texas?
- My wife's from Austin.
- Oh?
That's nice.
Huh.
Obviously,
you're not from there originally.
No. Moved there a few years ago.
How do you want to pay?
♪ You'll have no regrets ♪
"Jacob dreamed
there was a ladder set up on the earth
and the top of it reached to Heaven,
and behold, the angels of God
were ascending and descending on it."
Daddy.
What, no hug?
- What are you doing here?
- You called me, remember?
I'm just surprised.
I didn't know you were coming.
Well, did you expect me
to just send a check?
No. [chuckles]
No.
You haven't asked me for money
for 20 years.
Course I'm here.
The situation's... changed...
a lot since I called.
Not necessarily for the better.
How's Felix?
He's fine.
I know you wouldn't have reached out
unless things were bad.
You two okay?
So, let me be your father.
I'm here to...
help.
[people singing]
♪ Through the darkest night ♪
♪ Below the eye of sinful men ♪
♪ Thy glory may not sleep ♪
[Anna's dad] Likes his solitude.
Ed.
It's odd to me, all these folks...
He just doesn't seem
very interested in people.
In anyone.
He is.
You're a smart man, Felix.
Studied divinity.
So, level with me.
Who do you think he is?
You didn't see what I saw.
And if I did, would I be calling him
the Second Coming?
Is that the cock crowing once?
Sometimes, no answer is the best answer.
These people have come for something.
They've left their homes, jobs, families,
to be here, at your church.
They want an answer.
I wouldn't want to be
the guy letting them down.
♪ Through the darkest night ♪
♪ Below the eye of sinful men ♪
By the third round of chemo,
we had hit the cap
on our insurance policy.
Jonah had to take another job.
It was tough.
That took him away.
It's not his fault.
You know, we had to pay the bills somehow.
At the end of the day,
it was really just...
me and her.
And that's why I brought her here.
[sobbing] You know, I just...
It just... I...
I need her to live.
[sniffling]
[mournful pop music plays
through earphones]
[rattling]
[Felix whispering]
...for you, I will pray...
[whispering]
[sighs]
[woman] Don't forget
to use the hand sanitizer...
[sighs]
[dog whining]
[scrabbling]
[howling]
[scrabbling and howling continue]
[distant howling]
[Mullah Umar, in Arabic] Listen...
This man that has led us here...
he is not the prophet Jesus returned.
- He took advantage of us.
- He turned away Daesh, we all saw it...
[Mullah Umer] We saw the sandstorm...
turn away Daesh.
He has led us to the gate of our enemies.
Tonight, we will leave for Jordan...
for true refuge...
where our Muslim brothers wait
with open arms.
I know how you must be feelin'.
And I know, too,
how many questions you have.
Why did this happen?
What's gonna happen now?
I felt I've had to sit
with these questions.
Same questions you all have.
Why did this happen?
What now?
What do we all expect?
[howling]
[howling continues]
[whimpering]
Hey, hey...
[howling]
- Hey.
- Samson?
[scrabbling and whining]
Samson?
I want to tell you a story about me.
I've never told this to anyone.
One day, I was lookin' out
over the valley I lived in...
I could see a storm on the horizon.
And I could smell the rain in the air.
Storm felt so close I could smell it.
And I imagined that...
this may be what God's like.
Somethin' that's so close
and far away at the same time.
I decided that was God.
That feelin'.
[snarling]
He's hurt. Careful, son.
- Be careful, Dad.
- I'm gonna get this off you, okay?
[panicked whining]
[howling]
And so, as long as
I could remember that feelin',
I decided that God was with me.
And he could be with me
through everything.
Even death.
Oh, shit.
[Felix] I decided that.
I chose God.
But what happens when God chooses you?
Then you have no control.
Then he's not a part of your story.
You're a part of his.
We didn't decide all this.
God did.
Only he knows what happens next.
He's come out of his tent.
- What?
- He's heading out of town.
- [woman] He's left his tent!
- [murmuring]
[woman 2] Where is he?
[dad] It's time to say goodbye, okay?
- [whimpering]
- He's really hurt.
We tried, son.
[boy] Samson.
- It's okay, boy.
- [whines]
[Samson howling]
[boy] He's hurt bad.
Please, help him.
I know you can.
[howling]
- [gunshot]
- [all gasp]
[gasps]
[boy] No! Samson!
You were supposed to save him.
No, I wasn't.
He's not suffering now.
[sobbing]
Hey! What just happened?
What are you doing here?
I said, what the hell are you doing here?
Answer me.
- None of your business.
- The hell it isn't.
Talk to me.
You know, the last time I looked, Shin Bet
doesn't have jurisdiction in the USA.
Neither does the CIA.
Having trouble letting go of him?
Clearly not as much as you.
I came here to kill him.
You were sent to assassinate him.
They have no clue you're here.
He got under your skin, didn't he?
That's why you erased the tape.
Don't judge me till you face him yourself.
I have.
[in Arabic]
Wanting to live is not a crime.
I promised my father
his name would live on.
[Jibril] Read to me.
[Samer] "'Were they not satisfied
where they were?'"
"asked the Little Prince..."
"'No one is ever satisfied
where he is, '
said the switchman."
[footsteps approaching]
What are you doin' here?
I came for you.
[Samer, in Arabic]
"'All men have the stars..."
"...but they are not the same things
for different people."
"For some, who are travelers,
the stars are guides..."
"For others, they are no more
than little lights in the sky..."
"But you...
you alone will have the stars
as no one else has them."