[horn beeps]
[in Arabic] Careful... put it down there.
Good boys. Did anyone follow you?
Stop! Hands up!
[Aviram] Stop!
- [whimpering]
- [grunts]
[muffled whimpering]
Well...
"baker boy"...
Everyone who meets me...
- talks.
- [glass breaks]
Do you know why?
I am...
prepared to go the extra mile.
[boy gulps]
The sensible ones...
they talk right away.
But the stupid ones...
they suffer...
for nothing.
Now...
[gasping]
are you going to be sensible...
- [whirring]
- or stupid?
[crying]
Please... please...
- I'm not the one you beg to.
- I'll talk!
[panicked breathing]
[yelps]
Relax, man! Relax...
Take it easy.
[boy talking]
[Alon talking]
[footstep]
Well?
Spit it out.
[Alon sighs]
His name is Rashid Khalid Al Nuaimi.
His father is Nuaimi.
Avi...
[in English] The guns are not necessary.
[Aviram, in English] I know.
You're welcome.
Yes, take a good last look.
You will be forgotten in a week.
They won't remember a thing about you.
America,
it's like a silly schoolgirl.
But you know that already, don't you?
[woman screams]
[sirens wailing]
[shouting]
[radio chatter]
[baby crying]
[Felix] She's still seizing.
Anna, listen, just get in the cab.
- What hospital?
- [woman] Providence, on 12th.
Providence, on 12th.
[Eva] Switch to that lower camera.
Can you zoom in?
Fuck.
Get close on that number plate.
Fucking idiot.
[distant sirens wailing]
[Eva] So why wasn't the FBI at the church?
I told you. Order came
from the head office for us to stand down.
- We were taken off the detail.
- So you didn't think to check?
[scoffs]
We got a ping on that E-ZPass,
for the license plate.
Where?
Uh... I-95 turnpike, entering Delaware.
Delaware.
I need a map.
There's another ping.
Uh, Memorial Highway One, headed south.
What airfields are out here?
Uh, Dover, Georgetown,
Wilmington are all north.
- No, smaller.
- There's Chorman airfield,
but that's government.
When was that ping?
It's two hours ago.
Access the State Department server,
and get all flight clearances
for Chorman airfield this evening,
including diplomatic planes.
I want tail numbers and flight plans.
Okay, what's your thinking?
I don't have time to explain it,
just do it.
Do it.
Yes, ma'am.
[ringing tone]
[phone chiming]
Damn it.
There's only one flight out of Chorman.
Just took off.
Where's it headed?
Says its flight plan's classified...
So's the tail number.
Asshole.
- [agent] Where are you going?
- Flight's just gone international.
Need-to-know basis.
[bells jangling]
[bleating]
[speaking Arabic]
Go... Get in there...
Come on! You're making me late!
Get in! Go on!
[woman, in French] Italy is just across
the Mediterranean from Algeria.
Malik, there you are.
Yes. And I'm sorry I was late.
I was bringing the goats in
to be milked, and one got away.
That's okay.
But that's not the worst part...
This goat, he was taken by a lion!
[laughter]
A lion? Really?
[in Arabic] There are no lions here.
Malik is always telling stories.
There was a lion,
the most ferocious one I've seen.
[in French] But don't worry, Mademoiselle,
I had my stick...
and chased him away,
and saved my goat.
[in Arabic] Last week, he saw a spaceship.
[laughter]
[machines beeping]
[Anna gasps]
Sweetheart.
How are you feeling? Are you okay?
You had us so worried.
Mom.
[Felix] Rebecca.
We need the nurse. Get the nurse.
[call bell rings]
- What do you... remember?
- Let her be a moment, Felix.
I was dreamin'.
It was terrible.
I was standin' in front of everyone.
- That wasn't a dream, honey.
- [Anna] It's okay, sweetheart.
- What made you go out there?
- This can wait.
He left.
[Felix] You saw him leave?
- Where'd he go?
- Is that all you can think about?
- I just need to know.
- Your daughter almost died, Felix.
Where's your goddamn perspective?
He's gone, Dad.
I don't know where,
but I don't think he's comin' back.
[speaking quietly]
Thank you.
It's only water,
but feel free to turn it into wine.
I'm glad we're having
this time together, Aviram.
We'll have plenty of time together,
you and me.
When we land, they are going to put us
in a very deep, dark cell,
and throw away the key, and there will be
no guard to convince to let you out.
From now on, my job...
is you.
Yes.
It is.
[crowd cheering]
[man, in Arabic] Hey... Stay awake!
Stay awake. Stay awake.
[reporter speaking Arabic]
[Arabic commentary continues]
- [Eva] Is this stream live?
- [Bailey] Yes.
Who's claiming responsibility?
No one yet.
Qamar was there. Is he okay?
No word from him yet.
I should have been there.
Yes, you should have.
I've been telling you to stay on this.
- This should never have happened.
- You're right.
I'm sorry.
Where's Golshiri?
- Eva.
- We need to talk.
The car that took Golshiri, we traced it
to a government airfield in Delaware.
- Government?
- Details of the flight are classified,
but I'm guessing
you know nothing about this.
- Of course not.
- No prizes for guessing who does.
This goes to air in 20 minutes.
You need to cut your VO.
It's written,
I just need to read it. Relax.
[man] ...West Bank.
Ah, we're hearing that people are injured,
and unfortunately,
we do not have any numbers.
That shot of the stretcher with the kid,
put that in the bin.
...Hassan speak.
Now, he's the boy
who recently rose to fame
after crossing the Syrian...
- [notification]
- [sighs]
...do not have any confirmations as yet
as to what caused the explosion.
But Palestinian authorities have been...
...terrorist attack...
We will be crossing live
to our correspondents in Israel...
- [sighs]
- We are starting to get...
[Bailey] Your department
gave clearance for that plane to land.
We need to know where it's going.
What are you gonna do?
Arrest him when he lands?
It's over. The deal is done.
We need to know where
in Israel it's landing.
We need the tail number
and the flight plans.
Do I need to wake the president, Danny?
It's approaching Spanish airspace.
- Keep a lock on that.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Why can't we force the plane to land?
- [Bailey] Diplomatic jet. It's sovereign.
He was taken against his will.
We're sending him back into that.
It's all connected.
It all goes back to him.
We wait till he lands.
And then what?
You create an opportunity.
I'll scramble a team.
The fuck you're looking at?
We never finished our conversation
about Megiddo.
Don't you want to get it off your chest?
Secrets are so heavy to carry around.
God knows your secrets.
And loves you anyway.
Sin.
Sin is just a failure
to choose goodness, that's all.
Goodness is a choice.
Every moment is an opportunity
to make a choice.
The choice to think a good thought,
to think a bad thought,
to act on it, to let it pass.
That is God's great blessing.
That in every moment,
we can create ourselves again.
Aviram.
Make a choice.
Isn't that convenient, huh?
We can all be forgiven
and start fresh again.
People have been hating and killing
since we came down from the trees.
If there's a God,
he should be ashamed of himself.
"Made in the likeness of Him."
[in Hebrew] You're unredeemable.
That's what you think.
So you project your shame onto God.
[in English]
Why don't you shut the fuck up now?
[in Hebrew] Our sins have a way
of punishing us when we ignore them.
That boy.
He'll be the last thing
you see before you die.
[Miriam] This better be worth it.
You'll need to be nicer than that.
Can we cut the bullshit?
It's late and I've got a story to update.
This is gonna blow your story
off the front page.
I don't work in print,
but I'll forgive the analogy.
Oh, you're gonna be thanking me,
not just forgiving me.
His real name is Payam Golshiri.
Whose real name?
Your messiah.
There's enough in there
to get you started.
You got a busy night ahead of you.
Why are you doing this?
I owe you.
What's the real reason?
Run with it. You'll see.
[beeping]
[PA] Calling the flight deck. Emergency.
Fasten your seat belts.
[alarms wailing]
[gasping]
[Rashid] Please!
Please.
Please. I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
For everything.
[Aviram] Everything?
You're sorry for everything?
You're sorry
for all the wrong in the world?
No... no.
I'm sorry for what I...
I don't care what you did.
I care who you are.
[Rashid] I told you my name.
[Aviram] Yes.
I know your father.
He's had a lot to do with my life.
He shaped me.
He gave me my conviction.
He's had more influence over me
than any other person.
He's killed many people...
and boasted about it.
Including...
my mother.
[Rashid gasping]
[Aviram] You weren't even born...
but you've inherited his sin.
[Rashid] No, no! Please!
I'm only 14!
My mother doesn't even know where I am.
Please! Her heart will be broken!
I bear witness that there is
no God but Allah...
and Muhammad is his messenger!
[Rashid continues praying]
[in Hebrew ]I'm sorry.
There's four passengers, one's Golshiri,
so we'll at least need a team of six.
- We've lost it.
- What?
The plane.
What do you mean?
Just dropped off. No signal. It was
right there and then it disappeared.
What are you saying?
They're flying under radar?
That type of plane can't fly
at those low altitudes.
So what, then?
[phone buzzing]
Yes.
Thank you.
[door closes]
[breathing heavily]
[sighs]
Sweetie?
Rae.
Raeah. Honey?
Raeah.
Jonah!
[Miriam] It's being called
the hoax of the century,
or maybe the millennium.
The man they call the Messiah is mortal.
He was born Payam Golshiri,
an Iranian national,
orphaned at an early age
during the Kuwaiti crisis of 1991.
He and his brother Adar were raised
by their uncle, a street performer,
who apparently taught them
the art of illusion.
It seems Golshiri also has suffered from
psychological issues throughout his life,
being committed to a mental institution
during his 20s.
This startling news
came to light this morning
from a document leaked
by undisclosed sources in the White House
that reveals Golshiri has been
under investigation by the CIA
for the past several weeks.
The exhaustive report also mentions
concerning links
to radical thinker
and dissident Oscar Wallace,
an outspoken opponent of capitalism
and proponent of civil disobedience,
who was apparently Golshiri's mentor
during the fall semester of 2008.
As of this morning,
Golshiri cannot be located.
He was residing in a Washington DC
luxury hotel until last evening,
when he went missing after failing
to appear at a broadcast service
with millionaire televangelist Edm...
[Rebecca] Dad.
- Reverend, please, just one question!
- [clamoring]
- Excuse me.
- Reverend!
- [Felix] Excuse me, please.
- [woman] Reverend!
- Excuse me.
- [man] Will you go back to Texas?
- Tell us something!
That's his real name.
[chiming]
Daddy.
Yes. We saw.
Course not.
[woman, in Arabic] His brother,
Adar Golshiri, confirmed the report...
speaking to the press
in Tehran this morning...
[Adar, in Farsi]
You know I'm doing a trick...
but you're still amazed when I do it.
At worst, you're entertained...
you want to figure out how I did it.
But the best magicians make you
a part of it, they bring you in.
- [bleep]
- Baby?
Rae?
[sobs]
Baby?
[sobbing]
- What do you want?
- An explanation.
Here's my explanation. I outrank you.
You don't have any jurisdiction over me.
- Really? I'll bury you in a second.
- You just burned a whole operation.
And I saved my president.
That information was classified.
Look.
I know you.
I know who you are.
I know who your father was.
That holds no currency here anymore.
- He has nothing to do with this.
- That's right.
Your job is
to give the administration information.
Our job is to do stuff with it.
You brought down a diplomatic plane.
That's a very serious accusation.
I'd watch what I was saying,
if I were you.
[door opens]
Go home, Eva.
[whooshing]
[groans]
[Malik, in Arabic] Here... drink.
How did he do it?
Who are you?
Malik.
You were dead.
What?
You were dead. He raised you.
The man...
...he is magic.
He put his hand on your heart
and you began to breathe.
What are you talking about?
You and that other man there...
[coughing]
You were both dead.
Your skin was gray.
You had flies crawling in your mouth...
and then he touched you
and you came back.