[wind chimes tinkling]
[sighs]
[creaking]
[breathing heavily]
[wind whistling]
[sighs]
[snoring]
[phone buzzing]
Felix, someone's texting you.
[buzzing persists]
Felix.
[wind chimes jangling]
[sighs]
[thumping]
Rebecca?
Tornado alert.
Tornado warning, wake up.
[knocking on door]
Rebecca?
[animal howling]
[howling continues]
[rock music blaring]
Oh, shit.
That's shit's foul, dude.
- It always sobers me up.
- Mm.
[zip closing]
[thunder rumbling]
[door opens]
Felix! There's a tornado warning.
We gotta get...
Where's Rebecca?
Is she here?
No. She's not in bed?
No.
[warning siren blares]
[drops canister]
[strong wind blowing]
[she gasps]
Go, go, go!
[gasps]
[siren blaring]
[Anna panting]
- [Anna] Rebecca!
- [Felix] Becca?
Oh, shit, man.
[boy] Shit! Step on it, man.
Faster, man, faster!
[engaged signal]
Rebecca!
[Anna] Rebecca?
- [whimpers]
- [Felix] Rebecca!
[moans]
[Anna] She's not answering!
- Rebecca!
- Anna!
We gotta get down there.
- [Anna] Oh... Right.
- [Felix] Let's go!
[boy] Turn! Down the main street!
It's right behind us, man!
Right behind us!
Holy shit!
[tires squeal]
[yells]
- [Felix] Let's go!
- [people yelling]
[Anna] Rebecca!
Get in! Hurry!
[Felix] Watch your step. Careful!
- Take it slow, nice and slow.
- [Anna whimpering]
Let's go! All the way in!
[gasping]
[Felix] Come on!
Anna!
[Anna] Rebecca!
We gotta get inside! Come on!
No!
Oh, God!
- Come on!
- Oh!
[Anna] God!
- I'm safe, I'm in the church shelter.
- Don't worry. She's a smart girl.
She knows what to do.
Rebecca?
[man] Felix!
Get down here!
Rebecca!
[man] We gotta close those doors!
[typing]
The timestamp says 5:30, he could be
on the other side of Jordan by now.
- The bus lines have cameras.
- [Eva sighs]
- We could hack the footage.
- [Eva] That'll take forever.
- [beeping]
- If he was part of a cell,
they'd send some kind of escort by now.
[Anna] Rebecca!
- [Rebecca] Mom!
- [Anna] Oh!
- Mom!
- Oh, my God! Are you okay?
- There you are!
- [Felix] Rebecca!
Need to start looking at flight manifests.
Start with Amman and work your way out.
- [Rebecca] I'm okay. I'm fine.
- [Anna] Where were you?
- [Anna sobbing]
- [Rebecca] I'm fine.
- He found me...
- Rozen.
- He found me under the railway tracks.
- Are you listening?
- Um...
- I'm okay.
- You need to see this.
- [Anna] Rebecca!
- Mom!
- What?
- Keep watching.
Oh, my God. Are you okay?
- What am I watching?
- Just keep...
[Anna] Oh!
- [Please...
- {Rebecca] I'm okay.
- Where were you? [sobs]
- I'm fine.
I'm fine.
- Wait.
- He found me.
It's okay. He found me
under the railway tracks.
No, I'm fine. I'm... I'm okay.
- [Eva] When did this post?
- 45 minutes ago.
- Some town in Middle...
- America. Is this the only one?
- I'm not sure.
- Scrub it.
Freeze her accounts. Facebook, Instagram,
all of it, and any other videos like it.
Last thing we need is this going viral.
- Bury it for as long as you can.
- Mm-hm.
Get me home.
[radio] ♪ I beg your pardon ♪
- ♪ I never promised you a rose garden ♪
- [sings along]
♪ Along with the sunshine ♪
♪ There's gotta be
A little rain sometime ♪
[whistles melody]
♪ When you take, you've gotta give ♪
♪ So live and let live
♪ Oh, let go-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ I beg your pardon ♪
♪ I never promised you a rose garden ♪
[man] Samson! Here, boy!
Samson!
Here, boy! Samson!
Come here, boy!
[man on radio] We're up
at the high school, we got folks...
[Felix] We've got other stuff
in the fridge if you want.
There’s a bunch of sodas... milk.
This is good, thank you.
Listen. I know...
I know who you are.
I saw what you did.
In Jerusalem.
That boy who was shot.
And then... the tornado.
How... did you...
This is your church?
Yeah, it is.
[al-Masih] It's a good church.
[Felix] Thank you.
It's a miracle it's...
still standing.
S...
So, if you are...
Why are you here?
I go where God takes me.
Where God takes you?
"He is coming with the clouds."
"And every eye will see him,
even those who pierced him."
"And all the tribes of the earth
will mourn because of him."
"So shall it be."
"So shall it be. Amen."
"I am the Alpha and the Omega...
says the Lord who is and was..."
"And is to come."
[Felix sighs]
Did you come to stop me?
[door opens]
Hello.
[Felix] Hello, can I help you?
[Felix] Wait! Wait!
You can't just...
Sir!
You don't fully understand
who this man is.
He isn't a criminal. He saved my daughter.
- You can't do this.
- Where are they taking him?
- I don't know.
- [Felix] What's he being charged with?
Title 8, United States Code, Section 1325.
Improper entry by an alien.
I'll get you out.
[whimpering]
[in Arabic] I can see you're thirsty.
What's your name?
Jibril... [coughs]
Jibril Hassan.
[Aviram] Well, Jibril Hassan...
I have some questions for you...
and hopefully you have
some answers for me.
Last night...
at the edge of your camp...
you met someone from...
Nazareth.
No?
Yes.
Palestinian?
Why?
She gave me food.
She...
What did she ask you to do?
Nothing.
She just wanted to help.
We have nothing.
People are getting sick.
People are getting sick?
People are getting killed.
A war has started...
because of your friend.
Your leader.
Where is he?
I don't know.
I'm telling you, I don't know.
You really should stop
saying, "I don't know."
He was arrested. That's it.
The girl?
- Did she say where he is?
- No.
No?
Your leader.
What's his name?
al-Masih.
That's not a real name.
What's his real name?
- [gasps]
- What's his name?
What's his name?
I swear I don't know.
No one knows anything about this man,
and yet they risk their lives
and trek across deserts for him.
Why?
Because he is sent from God.
Say that again.
He is sent from God.
I want to prove something to you...
Jibril Hassan.
[Jibril groans]
I want to prove to you...
that there is no God.
Our Lord, give us goodness
in this world...
[in English] It's empty here.
Sure is.
Real empty.
[radio chatter]
Kip?
Yeah, it's Felix Iguero.
Yeah, I know, long time.
[baby babbling]
[music playing quietly]
- [Anna] So he was just standing...
- I told you everything.
I know, I just thought,
maybe now that you'd rested...
[sighs] I hid under the rail overpass
in the drains.
I saw the tornado comin',
and when I woke up, he was just...
He was kinda just there.
- Did you have another episode?
- I don't...
Probably.
It's all kind of a blur.
- Where are you going?
- I'm just goin' to the bathroom.
[sighs] I'm okay, Mom.
- [kettle whistling]
- [murmur of conversation]
[sighs]
- Hey.
- Oh, hey.
I was... just...
- Everything all right in there?
- Mm.
As well as can be expected...
- under the circumstances.
- How are you? You holdin' up okay?
- I'm fine.
- And Rebecca, is she...
She's... good.
- Better.
- Good, good. That's good.
We were lucky, huh?
So lucky.
The church is the only building
still standin'.
The only one.
Yeah.
- We were lucky.
- Just goes to show you, you can't ever...
You just...
You can't ever give up.
You can't.
- Felix...
- I got him a lawyer.
- What?
- Won't cost us a cent.
She's pro bono. ACLU.
Old friend made some calls.
You remember Kip?
- Kip from Princeton?
- Yeah, no, I know who he is.
I'm just... I'm havin' a hard time
keepin' up with you.
Somethin' happened here.
Somethin' big.
None of this is a coincidence.
It was meant to happen, Anna.
It was meant to happen.
All of this.
[mournful pop music
playing through headphones]
[phone alert]
[sighs]
[jet engine roaring]
[Bailey] You're not
where you're supposed to be.
I... I just need some time with him, ma'am.
JTTF already have him.
Then you need to leave that to the FBI.
This is our only opportunity to get intel.
He didn't just click his heels
and end up here.
He clearly had help.
This is bigger than just him.
It's only a matter of time
before everybody knows where he is.
I need to talk to him now,
before this whole thing blows up.
You have two days.
Thank you, ma'am.
[man on PA] Thank you for using
San Antonio Airport.
[woman on radio] Badge 14,
you available to do a pickup
on the corner of Trent and Highway?
[sighs]
[gasps]
- [phone chiming]
- [gasps]
What do you got?
A private jet from here in Amman.
It was forced to land
at Quetzalcóatl International in Mexico
due to bad weather.
[sighs]
- Did you get that?
- Yeah, I heard.
Amman, Jordan to Quetzalcóatl, Mexico.
He must have crossed over from there.
It's five miles from the airport.
What is?
The US border.
We've got the tail number.
The plane belongs to a charter company.
They won't reveal their client list,
so it's going to take a little more time.
- Let me know what you find.
- Okay.
Can you please pull over?
[man] Officer Geller,
they told me you were comin'.
Will Mathers, Joint Terrorism Task Force.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Sure got down here fast.
I need to speak to the detainee.
Yeah, I heard.
Not gonna happen, I'm sorry.
Actually, it is going to happen.
He crossed the border after landing
in Mexico on a private plane from Jordan.
Well, that doesn’t matter much now.
The scope of this goes
well beyond domestic.
This is foreign intelligence.
My jurisdiction.
The boys over in the counter-terrorism
division might beg to differ.
I’ve been covering this guy
from the beginning.
The longer you stand in my way,
the worse things are gonna get.
Well, I’m not standing in your way.
His ACLU lawyer is.
- Your boy's been busy.
- [sighs]
When are they transporting him
to the detention center?
Tomorrow mornin'.
[Will sighs]
[phone chiming]
[Eva grunts]
[wind gusting]
[man] Holy shit.
Shit...
[chiming]
Hey.
Yeah, but so far
it's just a couple of personal posts.
What?
Hold on.
[phone ringing]
[woman] Ma'am,
it's the chief of staff, on one.
Put him through.
[bleeping]
More dramatic footage out of Texas today
showing the tornado that ripped
through the border town of Dilley.
This viral video appears
to show the Miracle Man
from Friday's incident
at Temple Mount in Jerusalem
seemingly standing
in the path of the tornado.
His appearance in Texas
has sparked rumors of another miracle
as this devastated town's
- only surviving structure is its church.
- [phone chiming]
Dad, something wrong?
No, no, nothing's wrong.
Something wrong with you?
No, I'm fine.
Well, I thought I'd catch you
before you get to work.
It's... one a.m.
[chuckles] No, it's not.
According to my phone, in Tel Aviv, it's...
I'm in Texas now.
Oh, did you already tell me that?
Uh... No, I just got in.
Last minute flight. Work's crazy.
Well, are you managing to get some rest?
I would be,
if it weren't for these late night calls.
Well, uh, you know,
since you're awake now anyway,
there's something
I've been wanting to ask you.
Is there anything that you need?
You know, like... um...
anything I can... do for you?
To help out?
Help out?
Yeah, just things. Anything.
I'm good, Dad.
You know, I've got the gun out.
What?
Yeah, I'm cleaning it.
- Oh.
- Yeah, the damn thing is jamming.
Uh, I think it's the extractor spring.
These old things,
they can become a nuisance.
[she sighs]
Maybe I should take the hint, right?
[sighs and chuckles]
You're not old, but you are a nuisance.
Well, I’m the only nuisance you got.
Dad, I was joking.
No, I know, I'm just...
I'm tougher than that.
- I should let you go.
- Yeah.
Good night, sweetheart.
Night.
[sighs]
[gasps]
[in Hebrew] Morning, princess.
What's this?
I don't want you to be cold out here.
Thank you.
Now I will stay nice and warm. Thank you.
Daddy, why are you sleeping in your car?
Well...
I had to work...
I had to work late last night,
but I wanted to see you.
Daddy, you're hurt.
Ellie! Ellie!
Don't come outside like that
without telling me, understand?
Why can't Daddy come inside?
Oh, Ellie,
Daddy doesn't live here anymore.
You're not where you're supposed to be.