[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.08,0:00:06.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说  扩散率等于什么鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So the rate of diffusion equals something
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.34,0:00:10.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乘以什么鬼的平方根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}times the square root of...something...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.66,0:00:12.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放弃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I give up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.35,0:00:13.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就快了嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aw, so close.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.87,0:00:15.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给姐闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.43,0:00:16.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别着急  你能学会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, don't worry. You'll get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.93,0:00:18.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实很多著名的科学家都是女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, a lot of famous scientists are women.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.68,0:00:20.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但都是肥婆  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're fat, though, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.58,0:00:23.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  艾丽克斯  要去上大提琴课了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, Alex. It's time for your cello lesson.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.43,0:00:24.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辅导得怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How's the tutoring going?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.44,0:00:25.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听说过这么一句话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you familiar with the term
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.61,0:00:27.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"赔了夫人又折兵"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"throwing good money after bad"?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.41,0:00:28.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听说过这么一句话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you familiar with the term
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.63,0:00:29.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"邓菲小姐  孤独终老"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Dunphy, party of one"?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.81,0:00:31.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这就是你的下场  -姑娘们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Because you will be.  - Girls.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.91,0:00:33.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉其实学得不错  邓菲夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley's coming along really well, Mrs. Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.78,0:00:34.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good. Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.49,0:00:36.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关键是你要时不时地歇一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, the key is to take a lot of little breaks
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.41,0:00:37.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你就不会郁闷得想要放弃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so you don't get frustrated and want to quit.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.91,0:00:38.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.27,0:00:40.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在和戴维说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was talking to David.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.75,0:00:41.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  宝贝儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, sweetie.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.60,0:00:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是说  她以后肯定找不到工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just saying -- she's never gonna get a job,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.85,0:00:48.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过没准她能傍上某个中东富豪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and how do we know the right middle-eastern businessman
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.56,0:00:49.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对她很好呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}wouldn't treat her great?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.02,0:00:51.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把购物清单落家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I left my shopping list inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.42,0:00:53.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你  我们计划让她以后跟你蹭吃蹭喝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For the record, we thought she could live with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.95,0:00:56.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们别指望能找得到我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like I'm gonna tell any of you where I live.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.45,0:00:59.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.62,0:01:02.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.46,0:01:04.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做对题以后才有得亲呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We only do this when I get one right.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.94,0:01:05.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪早该到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Momma should be here by now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.77,0:01:07.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会出啥岔子了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wonder what's keeping her.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.24,0:01:09.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  这就要看她是开那辆老破车来呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, Cam, that depends. Did she take her jalopy
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.77,0:01:11.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是开什么新式小灰机呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or one of them new fancy flyin' machines?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.84,0:01:13.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,呸  人家密苏里州\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, Missouri is more cosmopolitan
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.51,0:01:14.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比你说的要现代化得多  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}than you give it credit for, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.61,0:01:17.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,充满了活灵活现的牛仔田园风情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's got a very vibrant cowboy-poetry scene.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.76,0:01:19.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上下两句话都不是同一个意思诶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not sure you're making the point that you think --
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.86,0:01:22.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来了  过来  热情点  热情点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's her. Come on. Look alive. Look alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.89,0:01:24.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈咪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Momma!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.99,0:01:26.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心肝宝贝儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my baby!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.05,0:01:28.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲亲小淘气  过来香一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my little bomber. Puppy kiss.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.62,0:01:30.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  快过来啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, get over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.76,0:01:31.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布  你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Aah, hey, Barb!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.76,0:01:32.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我宝贝的宝贝  你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my baby's baby! How are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.72,0:01:37.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我自吹自擂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I don't want to overstate this,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.15,0:01:39.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过我妈是世界上最棒的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but my mom is the greatest woman that ever lived.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.81,0:01:41.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡爱死他妈了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam loves his mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.38,0:01:42.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一人养活了四个娃  俩农场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She raised 4 kids, 2 barns,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.84,0:01:44.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有很多其它乱七八糟的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and a whole lot of hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.02,0:01:45.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着跟乡村歌曲似的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that sounds like a country song.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.92,0:01:47.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  歌名就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that song would be called
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.17,0:01:48.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"世界上最棒的女人"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"The Greatest Woman that ever Lived".
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.94,0:01:51.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡爱死他妈了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam loves his mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.19,0:02:05.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从我第一次见到巴布起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}From the minute I met Barb,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.32,0:02:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就一直开明  热情  并且体贴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she has been open and loving and -- and caring.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.80,0:02:13.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想死你这对小肩膀了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I have missed these shoulders!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.99,0:02:18.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过要是我有任何意见的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I had one complaint --
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.34,0:02:20.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来我还真有个意见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I do --
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.19,0:02:26.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是  她老对我动手动脚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it's the...inappropriate putting of her hands on my body.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.05,0:02:30.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布  我买了你做馅要用的小红莓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Barb. I got you the cranberries you wanted for the stuffing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.04,0:02:33.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太贴心啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, bless your heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.10,0:02:37.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来帮你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me get in there and help ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.04,0:02:43.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,捏捏更健康\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And a horsey bite.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.65,0:02:45.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好喜欢这样粘在一起哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is how I like to cuddle.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.32,0:02:51.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个现象已经  已经有些日子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's been -- it's been going on a long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.21,0:02:55.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  陪我去逛商场吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, you want to go to the mall with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.39,0:02:57.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了  我今天胃有点不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, actually, my stomach's a little funny today.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.09,0:02:59.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不得了呀  小宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I am so sorry, papi.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.09,0:03:01.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不咱先买个婴儿床\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe we'll stop first at the crib store,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.37,0:03:04.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你放进去  再配条小裙子  好不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you lay down, and I buy you a little dress, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.49,0:03:06.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚觉得我们美国人都很娇气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gloria thinks Americans are babies.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.86,0:03:09.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在俺们哥伦比亚  像是小感冒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, in Colombia, we couldn't go running to the hospital
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.67,0:03:12.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者肩膀脱臼什么的  根本用不着去医院\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for every little sniffle or dislocated shoulder.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.51,0:03:19.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好咧  搞定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.94,0:03:22.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五比六  我发球  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}5-6. I serve. Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.47,0:03:27.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  你都有什么症状\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, what are your symptoms?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.26,0:03:30.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心  腹胀吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nausea, bloating?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.05,0:03:31.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  我不是跟你说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, what did I say about getting off
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.80,0:03:33.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少上那个医疗网站吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that crazy doctor website?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.22,0:03:34.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是担心杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just worried about Jay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.81,0:03:36.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胃痛可能是多种疾病的征兆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stomach pains can mean a lot of things --
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.88,0:03:37.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是肠梗阻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}intestinal blockage...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.00,0:03:39.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你发烧吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you have a fever?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.65,0:03:42.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  曼尼  他好着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stop it! Manny, he's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.11,0:03:43.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-跟他说你好着呢  -我好着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Tell him you're fine.  - I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.31,0:03:44.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  上车去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, good. Get in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.71,0:03:46.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在家没事  逛街就得发病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, home fine, not mall fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.81,0:03:49.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  你知道我生着气去逛街的后果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay, you know what happens when I shop angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.60,0:03:51.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会帮你挪出地儿来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll clear a space.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.40,0:03:57.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你脸色蜡黄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not loving your color.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.16,0:03:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一边儿玩去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go play.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.35,0:04:01.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别逞强哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't be a hero.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.40,0:04:03.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弱智男配弱智女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, dumb guys go for dumb girls,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.14,0:04:05.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聪明男也要配弱智女吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and smart guys go for dumb girls?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.59,0:04:06.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那聪明女配谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do the smart girls get?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.80,0:04:08.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,配猫吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cats mostly.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.31,0:04:10.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  我为你们俩的胡搞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Haley, how long have I been paying this guy
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.15,0:04:10.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买单多久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to make out with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.89,0:04:12.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概一个礼拜了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, about a week.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.70,0:04:14.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一开始亲他只是想让他闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}First it was just to shut him up,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.87,0:04:15.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在我真有点动心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but now I'm starting to like him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.92,0:04:17.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是真喜欢他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you really like him, though,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.16,0:04:18.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就赶紧把迪兰甩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you have to break up with Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.46,0:04:20.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  不要啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? No!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.36,0:04:21.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Believe me --
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.69,0:04:23.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早死早超生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it's best for everybody if you just do it quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.71,0:04:25.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信你们居然这样说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe we're having this conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.31,0:04:27.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就像自家人一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's like part of the family.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.67,0:04:30.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  这是百利而无一害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Trust me -- it's the right thing to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.69,0:04:31.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧把他甩了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just end it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.83,0:04:34.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  但是要温柔点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, but be gentle.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.13,0:04:36.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,青春期的男孩都很敏感的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Boys are surprisingly sensitive at that age.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.81,0:04:38.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了  水球女的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Water-polo-girl story.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.04,0:04:39.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我就要讲水球女的故事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, I'm gonna tell the water-polo-girl story,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.36,0:04:41.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为人家真的很伤心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause it hurt!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.18,0:04:44.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时候我在校长办公室工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, so I'm working in the principal's office.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.72,0:04:45.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她就那么走进来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She walks in,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.68,0:04:47.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头发因刚游完泳而闪闪发亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}hair all silver from the chlorine...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.83,0:04:50.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说她想把棒球外套拿回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}tells me she wants her varsity jacket back.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.87,0:04:52.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一听这个眼睛就湿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I tear up a little,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.18,0:04:53.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着嚎啕大哭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then I tear up a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.37,0:04:55.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我求她  求她不要这样对我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm begging, I'm begging --
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.78,0:04:56.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果我突然发现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}at some point I realize
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.99,0:04:58.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我屁股底下坐着的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sitting on the button
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.44,0:05:00.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全校广播的开关\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to the high-school intercom system.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.38,0:05:01.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yuk it up, ladies.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.64,0:05:04.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从前不好笑  现在更不好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wasn't funny then, is not funny now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.10,0:05:06.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那完全就是杯具啊  海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was traumatic, Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.18,0:05:10.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要像"大炮"琳达对我那样对待迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't do Dylan like Linda "the cannon" Concannon did me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.20,0:05:12.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.14,0:05:14.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都过去那么久了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that was a long time ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.01,0:05:16.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的爱过她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I loved her.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.39,0:05:18.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.86,0:05:20.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.11,0:05:22.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许海莉跟迪兰分手以后  我可以打给他聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe I'll call Dylan after he talks to Haley.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.11,0:05:23.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他肯定需要找个人来依靠一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's gonna need someone to lean on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.75,0:05:26.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那个人不该是他前女友的老爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that someone should not be his ex-girlfriend's father.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.75,0:05:28.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  迪兰跟海莉分手以后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, when Dylan is out of her life,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.79,0:05:30.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就应该跟咱们都分手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}he should be out of ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.09,0:05:31.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一向讨厌迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You've always hated Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.56,0:05:32.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有一向讨厌迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have not always hated Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.93,0:05:35.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是一向认为海莉可以找个更好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have always thought that Haley could do better.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.19,0:05:37.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说  这个新男友超聪明呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Plus, the new boyfriend is so smart.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.62,0:05:40.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞掂了  我们分手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's done. We broke up.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.80,0:05:41.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.57,0:05:43.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发了短信给迪兰  分了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I texted Dylan. It's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.15,0:05:45.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll bet that's him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.35,0:05:49.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哭丧着脸的表情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sad-face emoticon!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.25,0:05:51.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,透过电话都知道他有多伤心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You can feel the hurt through the phone!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.70,0:05:58.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃晚餐时  小卡的妈妈有一半的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam's mom's been half of the dinner with her hands
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.40,0:05:59.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都在对我上下其手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}all over me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.48,0:06:00.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像她是个瞎子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was like she was blind
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.93,0:06:03.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后想知道我的大腿长什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and wanted to know what my thighs looked like.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.14,0:06:05.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.24,0:06:07.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对这种事情真的有评论权吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, are you really the best judge of this kind of a thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.92,0:06:10.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从小就对界限模糊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You've had boundary issues since you were a kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.11,0:06:11.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have not!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.31,0:06:13.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  对不起  是我的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Sorry. My mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.45,0:06:17.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是小卡母亲的错  是她有问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Must be Cam's mom...her issues.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.42,0:06:18.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.37,0:06:19.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没干吗  拿个勺子而已  -别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Nothing -- just getting a spoon.  - Stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.62,0:06:20.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你觉得不舒服吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is it bothering you?  - Yes, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.97,0:06:22.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-嘿  米奇尔  -克莱尔  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hey, Mitchell  - Claire, stop it! Stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.21,0:06:23.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔  米奇尔  米奇尔  -别逼我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mitchell, Mitchell, Mitchell, Mitchell --  - Force field!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.06,0:06:26.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是那么好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That never stops being fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.89,0:06:27.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.47,0:06:30.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听好了  这不是我瞎想的  克莱尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, this is -- this is not in my head, Claire.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.05,0:06:31.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且她愈演愈烈了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And it's actually getting worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.78,0:06:32.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡怎么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What does Cam say?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.74,0:06:34.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他根本就没注意到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, he never seems to notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.38,0:06:35.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我肯定不能告诉他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I certainly can't talk to him about it
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.02,0:06:38.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我绝对不能说他妈坏话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}because God forbid I say anything negative about his mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.96,0:06:41.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一次我在她的砂锅炖肉里加了盐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One time I added salt to her casserole...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.29,0:06:44.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果他冲进车库砸了我的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}...and he went into the garage and punched the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.10,0:06:45.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  米奇尔  如果这一切是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, Mitchell, if this is happening --
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.70,0:06:47.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我很确定这是你的幻觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm pretty sure it isn't --
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.08,0:06:48.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  你还真是挺我呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you. Supportive.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.53,0:06:50.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你就要让小卡看到他妈妈摸你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then you need Cam to see his mom feeling you up
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.40,0:06:52.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后交给他去处理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then make Cam deal with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.18,0:06:55.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好想想吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.82,0:06:58.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.01,0:06:59.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邓菲太太\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Mrs. Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.32,0:07:02.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过现在我跟海莉分手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Or, I guess, now that Haley and I broke up,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.21,0:07:03.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我该叫你"克莱尔"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I should call you "Claire".
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.23,0:07:04.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是继续叫我邓菲太太吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, I think we're gonna stick with "Mrs. Dunphy".
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.00,0:07:06.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进来吧  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on in. How are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.57,0:07:07.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not so good.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.24,0:07:11.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不管去哪  都能见到她的脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, everywhere I look, I see her face.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.56,0:07:16.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是呀  迪兰  你看的是我们的全家福\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To be fair, Dylan, that is a family portrait.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.32,0:07:18.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要上去拿我的东西  可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got to go get some of my stuff. Is that cool?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.27,0:07:19.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, sure. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.88,0:07:24.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There she is again!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.51,0:07:28.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别往书架上看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, don't look on the bookshelf!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.78,0:07:30.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会让你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're just gonna...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.00,0:07:33.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子  有时间吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, kid, you got a minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.45,0:07:35.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要那个医学网站的网址\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I need the name of that medical website.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.87,0:07:37.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能等我回家再说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can this wait until I'm home?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.46,0:07:38.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正赢得爽着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm having the round of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.98,0:07:40.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在想  我可能有一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've been thinking, I might have a couple of those, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.63,0:07:42.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前说的那些症状\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}those symptoms you were talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.85,0:07:44.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.90,0:07:46.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别等我了  你继续打吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You might as well play through.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.30,0:07:47.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还要耽搁一会呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's gonna be a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.75,0:07:48.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能是多想了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I'm probably wrong,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.88,0:07:50.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我只是想确认一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but, you know, I just, uh, want to make sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.41,0:07:53.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是曼尼吗  -是工作电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Is that Manny?  - Work.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.30,0:07:55.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  告诉他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, uh, tell them I'll --
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.23,0:07:57.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天下午就发货  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll get that order out this afternoon, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.34,0:07:58.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她信了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did she buy that?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.33,0:07:59.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为就连我听起来都觉得有点假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because it sounded fake on this end.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.98,0:08:01.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚点聊  汤姆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll talk to you later, Tom.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.96,0:08:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是汤姆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tom.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.90,0:08:06.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.21,0:08:08.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  迪兰  迪兰  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Dylan, Dylan, Dylan, Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.41,0:08:10.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,邓菲先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Mr. Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.53,0:08:12.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩现在既然分手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, now that you guys are broken up,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.08,0:08:13.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你随便怎么叫我都行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you can call me whatever you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.58,0:08:16.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  维他命菲  菲老爸  都行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, Vitamin P., P. Daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.47,0:08:17.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.57,0:08:18.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.75,0:08:21.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会想念这个臭小子的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna miss that bad boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.73,0:08:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候我手痒痒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When I forget my own axe,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.29,0:08:25.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就进来拨弄一下它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}sometimes I come in here and noodle on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.97,0:08:28.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,实际上  我最近也在写首歌呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, I've been writing a little song of my own.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.28,0:08:30.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我可以给你弹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Might be able to pluck out a few...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.63,0:08:33.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直希望这一切只是个梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I keep on hoping that this is just a dream,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.35,0:08:35.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉其实没有跟我分手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that Haley and I didn't really break up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.28,0:08:37.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这不是梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But it's not a dream...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.38,0:08:39.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非整件事都是个梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}unless the whole thing was a dream
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.37,0:08:41.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从一开始就没在一起过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and we never even dated in the first place.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.30,0:08:43.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪  这跟我写的歌差不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Weird -- this is kind of what my song's about.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.01,0:08:44.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  真奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.19,0:08:51.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这不好受  但是你会好起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know this is tough, but you're gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.60,0:08:53.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我高中的时候跟你很像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, I was a lot like you in high school...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.40,0:08:55.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了我的头发短点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}except my hair was shorter
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.91,0:08:57.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我玩的不是吉他而是长笛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and my guitar was a flute.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.84,0:09:01.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想要把吉他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, if you want your own guitar,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.08,0:09:02.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱俩可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, we could --
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.15,0:09:03.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱俩可以一块去买\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We could go out and we'd pick you one.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.68,0:09:06.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不  这样好像不太好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I don't -- I don't know if that's such a good idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.34,0:09:09.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Totally.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.43,0:09:10.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.97,0:09:12.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看我还是走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess I'll get going.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.16,0:09:13.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样一来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.13,0:09:17.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就能  孤独终老了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can...well, be alone forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.66,0:09:21.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管它的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, what -- what the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.73,0:09:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱俩去买吉他吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go guitar shopping.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.73,0:09:25.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Awesome.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.12,0:09:28.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答应我件事  别  别告诉邓菲太太好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, do me a favor. Don't -- don't tell Mrs. Dunphy?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.99,0:09:31.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是一定的  没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Definitely. You got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.09,0:09:32.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.49,0:09:33.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那回头见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I guess I'll see ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.58,0:09:35.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. You --
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.29,0:09:38.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以直接\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you, uh, you can go ahead and exit
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.21,0:09:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从  正门出去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}through the...front door.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.92,0:09:41.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对哦  我都习惯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, right. Habit.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.90,0:09:46.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的旧年鉴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My old yearbook!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.56,0:09:48.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我把它们都存下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know I saved them all.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.36,0:09:50.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看呀  -是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, look.  - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.98,0:09:52.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是全校最可爱的男生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"You're the cutest boy in school.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.50,0:09:54.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你将拥有一个美妙绝伦的夏天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're gonna have an awesome summer.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.16,0:09:56.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲亲  布兰达\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Smooches -- Brenda."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.83,0:09:58.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可怜的布兰达  你将拥有一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Brenda, you are about to have
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.57,0:10:01.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,史上最郁闷的夏天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the most confusing summer of your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.43,0:10:03.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.57,0:10:04.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, there's Mitchell!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.96,0:10:07.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小亲亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My little corn silk!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.21,0:10:12.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布  你的拥抱真带劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Barb, oh, you are such a good hugger.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.63,0:10:14.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的拥抱是最带劲的不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Isn't she the best hugger?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.54,0:10:16.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.85,0:10:19.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看我给你带了什么  巴布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, and look what I -- I got you, Barb.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.31,0:10:19.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.95,0:10:21.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是刮奖彩票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scratchers!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.51,0:10:23.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-亲亲  -谢啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mmm...  - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.39,0:10:25.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.24,0:10:27.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的茶好了  我去给你沏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's your tea. I'm gonna get your tea.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.48,0:10:28.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.43,0:10:29.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要个硬币\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I need a quarter.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.59,0:10:31.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来找找看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Let me have that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.57,0:10:33.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  请随便摸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, wow, yeah, feel free to fish around in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.48,0:10:34.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  小卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam? Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.05,0:10:36.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也给我来一杯  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd like a cup, too, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.24,0:10:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.84,0:10:39.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布  我跟你讲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ohh, Barb, ohh. You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.78,0:10:42.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我今天扭伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I-I strained myself so bad today.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.12,0:10:44.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, what's hurtin' on ya?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.28,0:10:46.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在  后背下面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's this area between my, uh, lower back
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.63,0:10:47.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大腿上面这块\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and upper thigh.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.15,0:10:49.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来像是屁股\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sounds like your fanny.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.08,0:10:49.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  就是屁股\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's my fanny.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.96,0:10:51.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼得不得了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's really knotted up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.72,0:10:53.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得找个医生看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you need someone to work on that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.63,0:10:56.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是想  只是我疼得走不动了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ohh, I would love that. Just -- it's really seized up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.63,0:10:58.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只要你来捏捏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just put your fingers all over my...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.22,0:10:58.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的屁股就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}my fanny.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.43,0:11:01.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你的回春之手  巴布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your magic fingers...Barb.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.94,0:11:04.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老妈  你的茶好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Momma? Your tea.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.53,0:11:05.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔  -谢谢  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Mitchell?  - Thanks, sweetie.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.00,0:11:07.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能否借一步说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See you in the room for a minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.31,0:11:08.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  茶还很烫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you. It's very hot.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.83,0:11:11.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别烫着舌头  -好的  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Don't burn your tongue.  - All right, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.95,0:11:16.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我不会哭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I am not gonna cry,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.38,0:11:17.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我想知道为什么  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I want to know why, Mitchell,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.95,0:11:20.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么在我妈面前表现得跟只狒狒一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why you are presenting to my mother like a baboon.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.55,0:11:22.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让你看看她是怎么摸我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wanted you to see her fondling me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.60,0:11:23.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来你就是承心要弄哭我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, you do want me to cry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.96,0:11:25.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  小卡  只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, Cam, it's just that...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.12,0:11:26.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她总是对我动手动脚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}she's always touching me inappropriately,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.86,0:11:29.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你似乎从来没有注意到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you never seem to notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.30,0:11:30.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做给我看  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Show me, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.39,0:11:33.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用莉莉的娃娃做给我看  我妈摸你哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Show me on Lily's doll where my mother is touching you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.78,0:11:36.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你不爱听  但是她确实动手动脚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know that you don't want to hear this, but she's handsy,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.61,0:11:38.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我觉得很不自在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it makes me uncomfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.10,0:11:41.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我知道这是怎么回事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my god. I know what this is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.15,0:11:43.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈太关心你了  你一时适应不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're just not used to having a mother that shows affection.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.12,0:11:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别又把我妈扯进来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, do not make this about my mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.99,0:11:45.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.00,0:11:48.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是跟母亲的肢体接触是难免的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But it is normal for a mother to be physical.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.68,0:11:50.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔的拥抱或者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And it is not strange
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.53,0:11:53.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍拍屁股是很正常的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for an occasional hug or a little pat on tanny.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.20,0:11:55.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不只是拍  小卡  根本不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, these aren't pats, Cam -- no.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.33,0:11:58.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一直揪来揪去不放手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She squeezes and lingers!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.64,0:12:00.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我示范下她怎么揪来揪去不放手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Show me where she squeezes and lingers.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.22,0:12:02.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  把娃娃放下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, put the doll down.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.64,0:12:07.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道她是开放还是疯掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know if this is just sexual or -- or crazy town,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.62,0:12:10.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她老是对我下咸猪手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but your mother cannot keep her hands off of me,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.23,0:12:11.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经受不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it's creeping me out
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.25,0:12:13.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.81,0:12:15.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Barb...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.86,0:12:19.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你示范\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me show you
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.46,0:12:21.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪捅了我妈一刀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where you stabbed my momma.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.21,0:12:25.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你帮我挑吉他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks for helping me pick out my axe.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.95,0:12:26.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You were so right, by the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.00,0:12:28.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双颈吉他的确是太过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The one with two necks would have been overkill.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.72,0:12:30.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想吃就吃吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you want, you can have some of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.05,0:12:31.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天开始节食\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Diet starts tomorrow!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.46,0:12:33.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也不能告诉邓菲太太哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't tell Mrs. Dunphy about this, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.77,0:12:36.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  一直想跟海莉来这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I, uh, I always wanted to go to this place with Haley,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.14,0:12:37.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是她觉得很傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but she said it looked stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.49,0:12:39.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她为人太主观了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's a girl with strong opinions --
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.36,0:12:40.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟她妈妈一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like her mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.03,0:12:42.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克莱尔总是对我买的这件运动衫指指点点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire hates this new sweatshirt I bought.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.88,0:12:43.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说这看上去像是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She says it looks like something
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.84,0:12:44.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女生去沙滩时穿的衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a girl would wear to the beach.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.87,0:12:46.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实很像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, it does.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.20,0:12:48.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是穿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I wear it anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.01,0:12:48.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白我的意思吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.99,0:12:51.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得吧  一个人要是不能做喜欢的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I figure, why be alive if you can't do the things
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.06,0:12:52.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活着还有啥意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you're passionate about?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.58,0:12:54.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么你热衷于什么呢  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you passionate about, Dylan?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.47,0:12:58.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}格雷斯兰  猫王宅邸  位于田纳西州的孟菲斯
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.47,0:12:58.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,额  我一直想开车去格雷斯兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, I always wanted to drive to Graceland.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.39,0:13:00.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错  还有呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fun! What else?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.34,0:13:02.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识一个人能给我搞到一只美洲山猫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know a guy who can get me a pet bobcat.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.31,0:13:05.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  你根本不知道它们多厉害\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah! No, you don't really know what they're gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.43,0:13:07.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重点是  你人生道路还长着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The point is, you got your whole life ahead of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.37,0:13:10.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,享受单身吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Enjoy being single.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.40,0:13:11.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我应该给你弹一下这首歌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I really got to play that song for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.92,0:13:13.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我突然来感觉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is all in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.06,0:13:13.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.96,0:13:16.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷毙了  我马上回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Awesome. Be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.33,0:13:26.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hey, come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.27,0:13:29.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边那家伙是跟别人一起来的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that guy over there with someone?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.15,0:13:31.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他们在搞什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could you tell if there was anything going on between them?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.93,0:13:32.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don'know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.95,0:13:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像在说一起去格雷斯兰什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They were talking about taking a trip to Graceland together.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.68,0:13:38.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想去是因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He just wants to go
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.10,0:13:40.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得那是一个游乐园\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause he thinks it's an amusement park!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.06,0:13:46.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得跟你说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got to tell you,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.44,0:13:48.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}憩室  消化道粘膜向管壁外突出的局限性袋形扩张或囊样突出
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.44,0:13:48.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这症状越来越像憩室炎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}this is looking more and more like diverticulitis.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.57,0:13:50.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有没有说如何治疗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do they say how to treat it?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.05,0:13:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是用电热毯或者  又疼了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like a heating pad or -- ohh -- there it is again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.66,0:13:53.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说你是怎么个疼法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, describe the pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.96,0:13:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像被捅了一刀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's like I'm being stabbed,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.14,0:13:58.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但又像是被我吃掉的扇贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but also like I ate a bad scallop
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.08,0:14:00.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从里面捅了我一刀一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's stabbing me from the inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.22,0:14:02.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很形象  但网站上没这些选项\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's colorful, but there's no box for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.57,0:14:03.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们爷俩干啥捏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you guys looking at?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.75,0:14:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}赫芬顿邮报  美国最著名的政治博客
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.75,0:14:05.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-看美女  -赫芬顿邮报  美女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Girls!  - Huffington post...girls.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.71,0:14:08.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  让老娘看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Manny, let me see that screen.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.95,0:14:10.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是叫你不要上这个网站的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What did I tell you?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.15,0:14:12.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是他的错  是我让他看的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not his fault. I asked him to look.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.20,0:14:14.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开始觉得我的病严重起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm starting to think I have a serious problem here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.05,0:14:15.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  就是这破电脑惹的祸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, you do! That computer!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.96,0:14:17.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看了网页  就开始想入非非\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You read it there, you think it here,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.69,0:14:18.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就无病呻吟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you feel it here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.62,0:14:20.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想好受点吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You want to feel better?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.30,0:14:23.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  你痊愈了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There -- you're cured.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.24,0:14:26.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帮我争取15分钟时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give me 15 minutes,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.72,0:14:29.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弗罗伦斯·南丁格尔女士要是问起来就说我去医院了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}then tell Florence Nightingale I went to the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.72,0:14:29.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}弗罗伦斯·南丁格尔  近代护理事业的创始人  5.12护士节就是为了纪念她  这里是挖苦歌洛莉亚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.39,0:14:42.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要杀了她  我还要杀了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna kill her! I'm gonna kill him!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.40,0:14:43.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要杀了这对狗男女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna kill both of them!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.95,0:14:44.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.73,0:14:46.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰找了个新女友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dylan has a new girlfriend!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.58,0:14:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When did that happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.01,0:14:49.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who cares?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.01,0:14:51.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他什么都没跟你说么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just surprised he didn't say anything...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.24,0:14:52.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.28,0:14:54.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也不回我短信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's not answering my texts.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.56,0:14:56.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么能这么对我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How could he do this to me?!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.10,0:14:58.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  是你把他甩了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey, you were the one who broke up with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.07,0:15:00.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想到他那么快又找了一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't think he was gonna find someone so fast!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.46,0:15:03.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能他比我想的要好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe he's better than I thought.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.09,0:15:06.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不会  绝对不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, he's not. What? No, he's not better!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.21,0:15:07.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道谁更好么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, you know who's better?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.59,0:15:09.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴维  家教哥戴维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}David -- David the tutor.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.77,0:15:10.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聪明的戴维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Smart, smart David?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.52,0:15:13.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是他来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe that's him right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.31,0:15:14.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想跟他单独相处吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you want the house to yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.88,0:15:16.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就一会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}For just a little while.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.28,0:15:22.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收到你的短信了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got your texts.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.99,0:15:23.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你骂得还真狠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You swore a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.96,0:15:24.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.81,0:15:25.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who is who?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.55,0:15:26.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的新女友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your new girlfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.85,0:15:28.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要她的名字和地址  好去找她算账\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I need her name and address, so I can mess her up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.59,0:15:30.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪有新女友了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't have a new girlfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.46,0:15:31.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装傻了  迪兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't play dumb, Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.88,0:15:34.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有  我从来不装傻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not. I'm never playing dumb!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.17,0:15:37.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在那个傻逼餐厅看到你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I saw you at that stupid restaurant,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.17,0:15:39.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟她椅子上的恶心运动衫同吃一个圣代\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}sharing a sundae with her ugly sweatshirt on the chair.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.10,0:15:42.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个贱人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, is that the skank?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.14,0:15:44.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  没有 没有什么荡妇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No...no, there's -- there's no skank.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.53,0:15:46.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么不接电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, then why aren't yo answering it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.50,0:15:48.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我想跟你谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause I want to talk to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.37,0:15:49.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒是想跟她谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I want to talk to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.91,0:15:51.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要给她打回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna call her back
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.14,0:15:52.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她把她的爪子从属于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and tell her to keep her hands off
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.48,0:15:53.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的东西上拿开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}of what belongs to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.56,0:15:55.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-海莉  -喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Haley...  - Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.51,0:15:59.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-爸  -海莉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Dad?  - Haley?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.57,0:16:04.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天  那件运动衫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh...my...god -- the sweatshirt?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.43,0:16:06.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟迪兰在一起的人是你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was you with Dylan?!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.08,0:16:08.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等一下  你就是那个新女友吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait, you're the other girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.25,0:16:09.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们只是朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, we're just friends!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.28,0:16:10.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  你搞什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, what are you --
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.86,0:16:12.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  把电话挂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, put the phone down.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.34,0:16:13.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}what is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.70,0:16:15.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他需要一个可以倾诉的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He needed someone to talk to.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.63,0:16:17.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的心都快碎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He took the break-up pretty hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.65,0:16:19.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是  -真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- But --  - You did?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.50,0:16:23.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直希望我们能重归于好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I kept on hoping that we'd get back together.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.18,0:16:25.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一想到你跟别人在一起我都快疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thinking of you with someone else just drove me crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.89,0:16:27.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Me too, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.93,0:16:29.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你爸帮我认识到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But then your da helped me figure out
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.84,0:16:31.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许分开才是最好的选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}maybe it's best if we're apart.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.73,0:16:32.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.36,0:16:34.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I think I just need
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.88,0:16:37.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要一点时间去跟迪兰约会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a little time to date...Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.64,0:16:40.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是说我自己啦  不是另一个叫迪兰的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I mean me, not another guy named Dylan.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.73,0:16:43.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  我们还是要分手吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, we're still broken up?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.74,0:16:45.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我想是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.85,0:16:52.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那就  再见吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow. Okay...um...I don't know -- I'll see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.63,0:16:55.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.88,0:16:59.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you okay, baby?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.94,0:17:01.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还要垫多个枕头吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you need another pillow?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.82,0:17:03.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你觉得我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know you think this is nothing,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.13,0:17:04.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但医生的确说有可能是溃疡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but he did say it could be an ulcer.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.64,0:17:06.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还说有可能是胀气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He also said it could be gas.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.81,0:17:09.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我帮你拍拍背吗  过来  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you want me to burp you? Come here. Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.54,0:17:12.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十有八九是憩室炎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dollars to doughnuts, it's diverticulitis.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.11,0:17:13.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是憩室炎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, it's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.51,0:17:15.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得了急性阑尾炎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have acute pendicitis.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.76,0:17:17.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要马上给你动手术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We need to get you into surgery right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.43,0:17:19.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,紧急手术  我跟你说了不是小毛病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Emergency surgery. I told you it was something.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.91,0:17:22.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能  你得再复查一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That can't be right. You have to check again!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.63,0:17:23.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经确诊了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The tests are conclusive.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.95,0:17:25.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会没事的   普里契特先生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Everything will be all right, Mr. Pritchett.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.58,0:17:26.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.41,0:17:27.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  杰  如果是真的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, jay, if that's true,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.93,0:17:29.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就是全世界最恶毒的老婆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}yhen I'm the worst wife in the whole wide world!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.98,0:17:31.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让你忍了整整两天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I made you suffer for two whole days!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.74,0:17:32.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.85,0:17:34.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  怎么会没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's not okay!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.23,0:17:36.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  为什么我总是差点害死我老公\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why?! Why do I always almost kill my husbands?!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.60,0:17:38.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找时间再听这个故事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I want to hear this story sometime,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.35,0:17:40.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我现在要准备割阑尾了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I'm sort of counting down to a rupture here!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.25,0:17:43.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你不能带着对我的怨恨离开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No!! You can't go without forgiving me!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.00,0:17:44.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是死在手术室里了怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What if you die in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.44,0:17:45.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有你我该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do I do without you?!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.36,0:17:46.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我原谅你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I forgive you,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.38,0:17:48.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是没人会死于阑尾炎手术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but nobody dies of an appendectomy!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.37,0:17:50.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  通常都是麻醉出问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}True, it's usually the anesthesia that gets you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.00,0:17:52.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你六十多岁了  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're over 60, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.54,0:17:55.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我永远不会忘了你的  杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I will never forget you, Jay!!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.09,0:17:58.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是保持铁石心肠吧  拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could you go back to not caring, please?!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.42,0:17:59.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇尔  我是巴布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mitchell, it's Barb.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.86,0:18:02.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ohh, Barb. I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.41,0:18:04.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  亲爱的  听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, no, no, honey, you hush.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.17,0:18:05.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.62,0:18:08.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在想关于我听到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've been thinking about what I heard, and...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.98,0:18:11.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我是摸你摸得的有点过分了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}maybe I do touch you too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.15,0:18:14.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说我这么做是因为咱们是一家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I could say it's 'cause we're a family,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.28,0:18:17.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  事实上  我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but, you know, I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.72,0:18:20.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜我跟你在一起很开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess I have been having some fun with you,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.28,0:18:23.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我以为摸两把没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I...I thought that it was harmless,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.45,0:18:26.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我从来没想让你觉得不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I would never want to make you uncomfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.92,0:18:28.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴布  这也是我的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Barb, it's my fault, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.23,0:18:30.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们和好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So we're okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.38,0:18:32.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  是的  当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, yes, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.05,0:18:33.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank god.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.42,0:18:36.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果咱俩之间有芥蒂的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause I couldn't live with myself
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.58,0:18:39.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会难受死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if things stayed weird between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.81,0:18:42.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小卡  小卡  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Uh, Cam? Cam?  - What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.78,0:18:45.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经和好了  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, we got it all worked out, sweetie!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.08,0:18:46.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  我去拿相机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, great. Let me get my camera!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.80,0:18:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要吧  不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that's not necessary -- no!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.61,0:18:51.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从现在开始  如果我做得过分了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}From now on, if I go too far,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.43,0:18:53.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-拜托你直接告诉我  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- please, you just tell me about it.  - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.88,0:18:56.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is that? Oh -- ohh!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.45,0:18:57.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点把手镯丢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Almost lost my bracelet.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.85,0:19:00.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-掉在那还好  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- That would be an area that's okay.  - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.63,0:19:02.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-要命  -我来捡  我来捡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Oh, dang it!  - I'll get it. I'll get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.28,0:19:03.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我看见它掉在哪儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no, I saw where it fell.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.90,0:19:05.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别逼我  别逼我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Force field! Force field!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.54,0:19:07.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.61,0:19:09.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我把手镯掉进去了  -妈咪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I lost my bracelet in here.  - Momma!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.97,0:19:13.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我想这种就是米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, I think this might be one of those situations
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.37,0:19:16.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得你做的过分的情形之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where Mitchell feels like you're crossing a boundary.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.11,0:19:18.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.74,0:19:20.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像  这样也算吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like, this too?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.84,0:19:25.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我要好好想一想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well...I...I got to have a good long think
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.70,0:19:27.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的行为举止问题了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}about how I conduct myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.50,0:19:30.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很抱歉  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm truly sorry, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.25,0:19:31.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's okay! It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.59,0:19:34.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那咱们赶紧照张相\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, let's take one quick picture,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.76,0:19:36.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后我们就出去  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- and we'll get out of his way.  - Yeah. Absolutely.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.84,0:19:38.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-靠近一点  -这样行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Scooch together there.  - This all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.96,0:19:39.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.91,0:19:48.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I miss him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.45,0:19:52.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是你第一个真正意义上的男朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He was your first real boyfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.96,0:19:55.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直希望他能出现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I keep expecting him to show up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.91,0:19:57.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他以前都是晚上过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He used to come by at night,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.42,0:19:59.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我偷偷溜去跟他见面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'd sneak out to see him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.21,0:20:01.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是  我知道  -你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah, I know.  - You knew?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.10,0:20:04.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他开一辆没有消音器的三十年前的旧车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}His car is 30 years old and doesn't have a muffler.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.52,0:20:06.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他居然还按喇叭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And he honked.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.77,0:20:10.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我超爱那台车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I loved that car.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.54,0:20:13.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坐着它去吉他店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I rode in it to the guitar store.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.64,0:20:16.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉自己快飞起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I felt like I was flying.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.75,0:20:22.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你现在很难过  宝贝  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know it hurts now, sweetheart, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.20,0:20:26.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你才明白这段感情是值得拥有的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's how you know it was a relationship worth having.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.25,0:20:39.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks, dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.05,0:20:59.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  猫王家好玩吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So Dylan, you love the Graceland?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.97,0:21:02.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, that's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.33,0:21:05.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们有过山车就更酷了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Probably would be cooler if they had roller coasters.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.77,0:21:08.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过  能看到国王住的地方还是很有趣对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Still, it's fun to see where the king lived, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.89,0:21:10.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.78,0:21:13.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是一个比喻  美国没有国王\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's just an expression. America doesn't have a king.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.54,0:21:21.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  好呀  什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Oh, sure. Uh-huh. When?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.18,0:21:25.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不总是那样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that's not always the case.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.72,0:21:27.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪兰  你有机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Dylan, did you get a chance
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.44,0:21:29.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我发给你的歌吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to listen to that song I sent you?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.02,0:21:32.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有吗   你有七分钟时间吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No? You got seven minutes?

