[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.10,0:00:07.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰一下  真是不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me, I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.43,0:00:09.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从不跟名人打招呼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never do this for celebrities.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.13,0:00:11.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你是不是新视野不动产广告\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But are you by any chance the foxy mom
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.19,0:00:13.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面那位性感迷人的辣妈呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}on the New Horizon realty ad.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.25,0:00:14.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会后悔做这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Am I gonna regret doing that?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.70,0:00:17.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拍万宝路广告那个人后悔过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did the marlboro man have any regrets?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.65,0:00:19.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个广告太完美了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This ad is perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.25,0:00:20.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  我不只是在卖房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, I'm not just selling houses,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.52,0:00:21.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在宣传我自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm selling myself,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.67,0:00:23.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最让我引以为傲的就是我的家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and the best part about me is my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.03,0:00:25.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有我的牙齿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And my teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.76,0:00:30.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这些  都将呈现在这则广告上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And both...are on display in this ad.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.20,0:00:33.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"您满意  我满足"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"I can't be satisfied until you're satisfied"?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.17,0:00:34.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你即将在巴士候车亭看见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Coming soon to a bus bench near you,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.00,0:00:36.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更别说我们的小货车了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}not to mention our minivan.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.67,0:00:38.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你是来真的咯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So that's really happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.47,0:00:40.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我们的小货车怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait. What's happening to our minivan?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.07,0:00:42.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要被这个坏家伙贴身黏上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Having this bad boy shrink-wrapped on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.21,0:00:43.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-漂亮  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Classy. - Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.49,0:00:46.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就算你妈开车瞎晃  也能干点正事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now all that driving around your mom does will serve a purpose.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.46,0:00:48.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好  亲人们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good morning, family.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.07,0:00:49.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个美好的日子里  你们过得怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How are you all doing on this beautiful day?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.97,0:00:51.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  这是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. What's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.40,0:00:53.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉的高考成绩可以在网上查询了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley's S.A.T. scores are available online.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.37,0:00:53.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.94,0:00:55.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天可是个大日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh! ! Today's the big day.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.87,0:00:58.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来看看  她考的怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's take a look, see how she did.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.28,0:01:00.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真的要现在就看么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do we really have to look at them now?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.09,0:01:00.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.63,0:01:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不期望会有奇迹发生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're not expecting any miracles.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.09,0:01:03.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.13,0:01:05.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是海莉的分数吗  你确定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are those Haley's scores? Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.36,0:01:06.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  很低么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why? Are they bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.80,0:01:08.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  它们不低\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, they're not bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.21,0:01:08.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那很高吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are they good?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.01,0:01:11.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不  中等水平\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, they're average.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.25,0:01:13.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我们成功了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, we did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.17,0:01:14.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的孩子是中等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Our baby's average.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:15.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中等万岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Medium five!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.32,0:01:17.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只是一个偶然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is just a fluke.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.42,0:01:18.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她还可以再考一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She can take them again.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.93,0:01:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  她或许还能考得更好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, and she'll probably do even better.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.40,0:01:21.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到时候你就可以有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are gonna have your choice
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.67,0:01:24.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好几个很好的大学可供选择了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}of some pretty good colleges when the time comes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.27,0:01:25.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前提是我得去大学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I go to college.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.80,0:01:26.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.80,0:01:28.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最近一直在想这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've been thinking about it lately,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.64,0:01:31.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我或许  不会去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I might...not.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.77,0:01:33.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Later!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.83,0:01:36.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然成绩出乎意料的不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, we took the scenic route,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.01,0:01:38.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但烂泥终究扶不上墙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but we ended up in the same place.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.82,0:01:54.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从津巴布韦到阿尔及利亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}From Zimbabwe to Algeria
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.36,0:01:55.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  让我听到你的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, let me hear ya
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.92,0:01:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这些国家了  就是这些国家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These are the countries, these are the countries
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.34,0:02:01.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡最近成了富兰克林中学的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam recently became Franklin middle school's
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.06,0:02:02.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,临时音乐总监\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}interim musical director.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.09,0:02:03.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加油  富兰克林\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Go, Franklin!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.36,0:02:07.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自告奋勇为他们的春季音乐会效力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was volunteering for their spring musical festival
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.23,0:02:08.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他们的常规总监\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when their regular director
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.77,0:02:10.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,突然莫名其妙的病了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}suddenly and mysteriously became ill.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.94,0:02:12.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.74,0:02:14.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可能是他们的福分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It may have been a blessing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.64,0:02:16.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们的演出没什么重点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Their show lacked focus.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.11,0:02:18.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我为它制定了一个主题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I gave it a theme --
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.44,0:02:20.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"环球音乐之旅"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"A musical trip around the world."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.61,0:02:22.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  瞧  他的重点就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, see, he focused it
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.31,0:02:24.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它跟世界联系起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}by making it about the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.28,0:02:25.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不喜欢这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.38,0:02:27.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  小卡  我喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No -- Cam. I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.25,0:02:28.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认为那些孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you -- do you think that the kids, though,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.62,0:02:30.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚就能学会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}are gonna be able to learn it by tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.86,0:02:31.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  或许你可以着重于\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, maybe you should stick
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.02,0:02:32.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们之前排练好的节目\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with something that they already know.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.03,0:02:33.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道会这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I knew this would happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.83,0:02:35.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你总是要浇熄我炙热的梦想呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do you have to throw a wet blanket on my dreams?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.97,0:02:37.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没有  -你一直都这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- I do not. - You do it all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.77,0:02:40.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我是以什么告终的么  梦遗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you know what I end up with? Wet dreams.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.07,0:02:41.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这词一脱口而出我就后悔了  不要管它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I heard it as soon as I said it. Just leave it alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.64,0:02:44.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  小卡  只不过有时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, well, Cam, it's just that sometimes
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.04,0:02:47.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有点小小的过分热情了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you can be a little, you know, overenthusiastic.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.51,0:02:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让它变成世界上最好的演出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is it really that big of a deal
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.81,0:02:50.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真有那么大的关系么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that I want this to be the best show in the world?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.82,0:02:52.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该说的我都说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, as long as you heard me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.68,0:02:55.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站在我这一边  不要这么吹毛求疵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Be in my corner. Don't be so critical.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.42,0:02:57.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的是这么看我的么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We-- is that really how you see me?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.36,0:02:58.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候我确实是这么看你的  米奇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes, yeah, I do, Mitchell.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.99,0:03:02.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡  如果这是真的  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cam, well, if -- if that's true, then I'm -- I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.46,0:03:04.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  好的  从现在开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, you know, okay, from now on,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.53,0:03:06.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我百分百站在你那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am in your corner 100%.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.87,0:03:09.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这首歌一定会艳惊四座\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, that song is gonna knock everyone out.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.30,0:03:10.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  不过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I don't know, but
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.01,0:03:11.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你看了我准备的舞蹈再说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}wait till you see the dance I have prepared.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.40,0:03:13.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,舞蹈  舞蹈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A dance? A dance!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.61,0:03:17.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一些吐司么  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}More toast, Manny?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.12,0:03:19.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么不给我打电话呢  艾玛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why won't you call me, Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.09,0:03:20.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一些吐司么  艾玛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}More toast, Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.69,0:03:22.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有必要什么时候都来掺一脚么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you have to be on all the time?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.52,0:03:25.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  对不起  谁是艾玛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I'm sorry. Who is this Emma?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.13,0:03:26.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我今晚表演的同伴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's in the show with me tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.66,0:03:28.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在考虑追她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm thinking of taking a run at her.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.30,0:03:30.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该"追"女生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't "Take a run" at a woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.20,0:03:32.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得取悦她  让她觉得她是特别的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You woo her. You make her feel special.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.30,0:03:33.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  看看这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, hon, take a look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.00,0:03:35.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我屁屁的照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a picture of my butt.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.50,0:03:36.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把她拿下之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then when you get her,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.00,0:03:38.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就可以随心所欲了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you can tell her whatever you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.94,0:03:40.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do you do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.41,0:03:42.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我哥哥唐尼一打电话来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I programmed it so my butt pops up
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.11,0:03:43.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的屁屁就会跳出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}when my brother donnie calls.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.54,0:03:45.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,借用屁屁来鄙视我哥  只用聪明人才会的招数呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a clever way of saying my brother's an ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.78,0:03:46.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.68,0:03:48.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他来了  淡定淡定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's him. Compose yourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.82,0:03:50.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忘了我给你们看过这张照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Forget I showed you this picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.25,0:03:51.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我尽力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm trying.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.20,0:03:54.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你过得咋样  婊子养的傻儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How you doing, you dumb son of a bitch?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.93,0:03:57.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个老不死的  看起来你又胖了几磅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You old mick. Looks like you've put on a few pounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.74,0:03:58.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,彼此彼此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.54,0:03:59.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是连你头发都给吃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, are you eating your hair?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.98,0:04:01.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Gloria. Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.71,0:04:03.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么还在这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you still doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.32,0:04:05.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿绿卡的办法多了  肯定还有更容易的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's got to be an easier way to get a green card.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.17,0:04:06.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唐尼伯伯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, uncle Donnie,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.19,0:04:08.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今晚会来我的校园音乐会么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}are you coming to my school concert tonight?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.29,0:04:09.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这个嘛  -最多就一个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Well... - It's an hour, tops.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.49,0:04:10.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}...wouldn't miss it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.66,0:04:12.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找不到我的电话了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, you know, I think I misplaced my phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.36,0:04:13.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能用你的手机打我的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Could you call me on yours?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.50,0:04:14.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我手机在包的最底下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My phone's at the bottom of my bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.67,0:04:15.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不用你家里的电话打呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why don't you use your home phone?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.80,0:04:16.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  这很简单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, come on. It's simple.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.87,0:04:17.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.76,0:04:18.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.30,0:04:19.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你放手怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How about you let go, you --
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.47,0:04:20.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把电话给我  唐尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Give me the phone, Donnie!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.57,0:04:22.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还以为你能放倒我么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You still think you can take me?!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.27,0:04:23.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  你就这种水平吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What? Is this all you got, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.94,0:04:25.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你的嘴尝尝老子拳头的滋味\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna wash your mouth out with fist.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.45,0:04:30.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不明白这种兄弟情  艾玛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't understand this relationship, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.88,0:04:39.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾玛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.32,0:04:41.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做这场表演  就像是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Doing this show, it feels like
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.42,0:04:43.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们成为了一个小家庭  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we've become like a little family, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.36,0:04:44.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说你就像是我兄弟一样么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean like you're my brother?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.89,0:04:47.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. N-no, I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.23,0:04:48.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.66,0:04:52.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们回来了  恐龙武器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're back -- dinosaur arms!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.16,0:04:54.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在可不是个好时候  卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This isn't a good time, Luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.07,0:04:55.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可真是搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.57,0:04:58.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,半人半恐龙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Half boy, half t-rex.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.37,0:05:00.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,身处人兽两界之间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}One foot in both worlds,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.51,0:05:02.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而为两界所不容\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wanted by neither.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.51,0:05:05.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  你把衣服撑大的方法真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, that's a great way to stretch out a shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.58,0:05:08.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了  休息结束了  大家伙儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, okay! Break's over, everyone!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.45,0:05:09.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们从头再来一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's take it from the top.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.71,0:05:11.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  因为演出时间是20分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, we're running 20 minutes long,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.55,0:05:13.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们要去掉宝莱坞部分继续演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So we're gonna go ahead and cut the Bollywood number.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.95,0:05:15.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能离开了吗  我足球练习迟到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can I go? I'm late for soccer practice.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.99,0:05:18.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道还有谁错过了足球练习吗  德尔罗伊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know who else missed soccer practice, Delroy?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.59,0:05:20.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《吉屋出租》的演员们  而他们赢得了东尼奖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The cast of "Rent." And now they have a Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.59,0:05:20.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东尼奖是美国百老汇舞台剧界最高荣誉奖
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.03,0:05:22.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也有一位东尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We have a Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.79,0:05:25.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太搞笑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are so funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.53,0:05:26.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.62,0:05:28.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.38,0:05:30.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甜心  他们把车开来了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, honey. Did they drop the van off yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.36,0:05:31.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚开来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, a little while ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.56,0:05:32.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How's it look?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.63,0:05:33.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,信不信由你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, well, believe it or not,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.83,0:05:35.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忍住了不去看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have resisted the temptation to look.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.70,0:05:38.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉的事情搞得我有点头大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This whole Haley thing has got me a little preoccupied.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.23,0:05:40.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正要去吃饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're on our way out to lunch right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.17,0:05:41.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于那个我有个看法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}About that, I've been thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.77,0:05:43.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大学还早着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}College is still a ways away.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.27,0:05:44.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得应该让海莉自己考虑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I say we leave Haley alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.71,0:05:46.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们越是给她压力  她越是反抗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The more we push, the more she'll push back.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.77,0:05:47.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是要给她压力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna push.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.78,0:05:48.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我坚决支持\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I support that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.91,0:05:52.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也只有老爹能把我们的车搞得更丑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Only dad can make our minivan even lamer.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.91,0:05:54.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  你在搞啥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me. What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.75,0:05:56.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把这车开到水库里面去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm driving this thing to the reservoir.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.38,0:05:57.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你跳车  你就跳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just jump when I say jump.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.45,0:05:59.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  坐过去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Honey, slide over.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.89,0:06:05.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠这种蹩脚广告怎么能卖出房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How is this stupid ad supposed to sell houses anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.43,0:06:06.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也听你爸说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You heard your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.59,0:06:08.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不只是在卖房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's not just selling houses...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.33,0:06:10.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是在宣传我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's selling us.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.27,0:06:13.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的朋友会怎么想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are my friends gonna think?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.10,0:06:14.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They are gonna think
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.60,0:06:17.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在帮你老爸捞钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that you're helping your father put food on the table.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.88,0:06:23.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,- 椅子坏了吗  -算是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Ay, is the chair broken? - Almost.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.42,0:06:25.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我那个贪便宜吃白食的哥哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That cheap, freeloading brother of mine
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.59,0:06:27.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老是对我的上好苏格兰威士忌恋恋不忘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}can't keep his hands off my good Scotch,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.16,0:06:28.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  我把威士忌放那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, you see, I placed that Scotch there.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.99,0:06:31.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我哥哥一屁股坐上面  椅子就会立马散架\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My brother sits in this chair, goes out from under him --
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.80,0:06:33.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啪嗒  杰作呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bam! -- Masterpiece.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.36,0:06:36.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就让你兄弟摔倒  把酒洒了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you make your brother fall and spill his drink?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.33,0:06:37.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想让酒跟着遭殃  但计划就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I don't want to jinx it, but that's the plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.77,0:06:39.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩怎么都那么小气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you both so mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.67,0:06:42.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我长大的地方  兄弟互相尊敬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where I come from, brothers respect each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.77,0:06:44.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以说哥伦比亚才是"世外桃源"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's why Colombia is such a peaceful utopia.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.98,0:06:46.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两位小姐  你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello, ladies.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.28,0:06:47.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  衣服不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, nice shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.91,0:06:49.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去买衣服的地方有卖男人衣服吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do they sell men's clothes where you got that?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.75,0:06:51.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思  因为妇女一向地位低下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's funny because women are so inferior.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.41,0:06:52.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真没品位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got no taste.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.45,0:06:54.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我专门为了梅莱尼的洗礼买的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I bought this for Melanie's baptism.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.32,0:06:55.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梅莱尼是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who's Melanie?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.10,0:06:56.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克的孩子  我的孙女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Michael's kid, my granddaughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.82,0:07:00.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  忘了跟艾琳说我平安抵达了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I forgot to tell Irene I landed safely.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.14,0:07:01.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.87,0:07:03.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How could you not know
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.24,0:07:04.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己的兄弟有孙女了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that your own brother had a granddaughter?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.94,0:07:05.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我好像知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I probably knew.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.68,0:07:07.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能连家人的事情都不记得了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How can you forget when he's family?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.61,0:07:09.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有29个堂兄弟姐妹  我能一一道来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have 29 cousins, and I know them all --
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.78,0:07:11.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗莎·玛琳娜  歌洛莉亚·玛琳娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Rosa Marina, Gloria Maria,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.42,0:07:14.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-维罗妮卡·玛琳娜  何塞·维森特  -够了够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Veronica Maria, Jose Vicente - Okay, okay, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.05,0:07:14.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's your point?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.95,0:07:17.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你破坏椅子  你跟他打架\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You do the chair, you do the fighting,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.32,0:07:19.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你们就是不了解对方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But you don't know each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.36,0:07:20.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悲剧啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.88,0:07:22.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  虽然我跟我哥哥的交流方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I may not talk to my brother
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.08,0:07:23.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与你和你的姐妹的不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the way you talk to your sisters,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.25,0:07:26.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是相信我  我们有我们的友爱方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But believe me, we're close in our own way.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.16,0:07:28.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上次见他是什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}When was the last time that you saw him?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.26,0:07:30.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们见面没那么容易  因为他住在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that's not easy, 'cause he lives up...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.93,0:07:33.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  我想说水牛城来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See, I want to say Buffalo.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.57,0:07:37.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想说的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All I'm saying
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.77,0:07:40.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多接受点教育没什么不好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is that there's no downside to more education.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.89,0:07:42.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早就知道你开车带我出来另有所图\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I knew this car ride was a trap.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.39,0:07:43.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See that?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.66,0:07:46.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从这句话我就知道你有多聪明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That right there shows me just how smart you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.50,0:07:48.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没搞错吧  又来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? Again?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.83,0:07:49.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.93,0:07:50.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那个蹩脚广告\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's the stupid ad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.98,0:07:52.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些人也跑到我这边按喇叭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're honking on my side, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.24,0:07:55.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  广告上就是我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, we're the people in the ad.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.71,0:07:57.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.29,0:08:00.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大学还有另外一大好处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Another great thing about college
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.69,0:08:02.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全的自由\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}complete independence.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.10,0:08:03.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我外面住公寓一样自由\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'd have that in an apartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.83,0:08:07.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你要租公寓  必须得有工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, because to have an apartment, you would need a job.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.03,0:08:08.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道在学校你的工作是什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You want to know what your job is in college?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.80,0:08:11.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上上课啦  做做作业啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's a little bit of class and homework.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.13,0:08:13.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交许许多多的朋友啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And it's a whole lot of new friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.37,0:08:15.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各种各样的体验呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And experiences.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.04,0:08:18.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男孩觉得你可爱  而你确实处于可爱的青春年少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And the boys think you're cute and you are cute,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.67,0:08:20.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  青春转瞬即逝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And, oh, trust me, that doesn't last forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.81,0:08:24.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打电话就是了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Call the number!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.62,0:08:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.05,0:08:28.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好输球了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You in the mood to lose?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.62,0:08:29.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哥我还没输过球呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}First time for everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.85,0:08:31.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You break.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.59,0:08:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, how's work?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.42,0:08:35.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用着急  有钱哥  我不是来借钱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry, moneybags. I'm not here for a loan.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.19,0:08:36.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开得好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice break.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.96,0:08:38.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啦  全色球归你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, you're solids,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.23,0:08:40.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过估计你得半天才能动杆子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which you won't be able to eat in a few years.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.50,0:08:41.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.70,0:08:43.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  你最近过得如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, though, how are things going with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.17,0:08:44.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好得很\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Swell.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.34,0:08:46.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就在台球桌上教训一个胖子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm beating a fat guy at pool right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.54,0:08:47.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唐尼  我试图和你交谈呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Donnie, I'm trying to talk to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.91,0:08:48.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.84,0:08:50.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么  因为普通人都这样做吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why? 'cause that's what people do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.01,0:08:53.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谈天说地  比如说他们的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Talk about things, like their lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.08,0:08:58.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾琳原来是下我套来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Irene opened her big trap.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.45,0:08:59.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Look, I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.48,0:09:01.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不是要死掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not like I'm gonna die.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.29,0:09:02.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.35,0:09:03.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医生发现得早\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, they caught it early.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.59,0:09:05.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化疗过后  现在好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I took the treatment. I'm clear for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.26,0:09:06.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  该你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. It's your shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.39,0:09:07.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诊断出啥了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Caught what early?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.19,0:09:11.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唐尼  你是不是说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Donnie, are you talking about...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.50,0:09:12.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,癌症\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}cancer?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.63,0:09:14.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么好避讳的  我知道我得癌症了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't have to whisper. I know I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.99,0:09:17.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的前列腺检查是医生做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You just get your prostate checked -- by a doctor,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.32,0:09:18.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不是在网上认识的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}not some guy you met on the internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.89,0:09:20.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不敢相信你居然瞒着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe you didn't tell me this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.36,0:09:21.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这又没什么大不了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because it's not a big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.76,0:09:24.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  这件事就咋俩知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, listen. It's just between us.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.93,0:09:27.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, god.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.37,0:09:34.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾琳  我怎么知道你的破眼镜在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Irene, how the hell do I know where your glasses are?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.00,0:09:41.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有飞盘高尔夫啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And there's frisbee golf,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.24,0:09:43.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还可以用自助餐厅的大盘子当雪橇滑雪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And -- and you go snow-sledding on cafeteria trays.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.90,0:09:45.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和室友还可以一起养条狗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, and you all get a dog together.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.57,0:09:47.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道暑假的时候是谁照顾它的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't really know who takes care of the dog during the summer,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.84,0:09:49.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正你回去的时候它肯定在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but he's there when you get back.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.31,0:09:51.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有完没完  或许你应该回去念大学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Geez, maybe you should just go back to college.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.24,0:09:54.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  如果时光能倒流我真的什么都愿意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, honey, do you know what I would give to go back?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.28,0:09:57.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那一刻你所有的生活都在你跟前  由你随心所欲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's this moment when your whole life is in front of you,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.58,0:10:00.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太神奇了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and it's a magical time.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.32,0:10:01.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对不会想错过的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't want to miss that,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.35,0:10:03.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为光阴一去不复返\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because when it's gone, it's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.36,0:10:06.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别烦  别烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.03,0:10:11.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  艾丽克斯  车要开了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, Alex. Bus is leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.83,0:10:13.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  你手机震个不停\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dad, your phone's been buzzing like crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.80,0:10:16.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我滴个乖乖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweet lorna doone!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.69,0:10:17.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十九个未接来电\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}19 missed calls?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.92,0:10:19.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底是谁...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wonder who's --
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.62,0:10:23.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔·邓菲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil Dunphy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.19,0:10:24.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看过那个广告啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You saw the ad?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.55,0:10:25.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.99,0:10:27.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想找什么样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you know what you're looking for?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.39,0:10:29.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小的那个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The little one?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.23,0:10:30.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白你说的是哪个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I know which one you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.89,0:10:31.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你感兴趣的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, if you're interested,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.93,0:10:34.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个品质尚佳的老款\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I also have an older model with a lot of character.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.90,0:10:35.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.87,0:10:37.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得地毯和窗帘很配啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think the carpet matches the drapes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.93,0:10:39.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有段时间没看过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I haven't checked in a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.27,0:10:41.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两个都想要啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Both of them?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.40,0:10:42.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.84,0:10:45.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你打算要一个的话  我还能理解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I guess that makes sense if you're planning to flip one.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.64,0:10:47.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧  我等会回你好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, um, why don't I call you back?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.48,0:10:48.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们约个时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll set up an appointment.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.94,0:10:51.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会抓紧时间把它们都清洗干净\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It'll give me a chance to give them both a good scrubbing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.61,0:10:53.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.55,0:10:54.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.65,0:10:55.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bye-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.79,0:10:57.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How about that, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.26,0:11:00.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看这些电话都是问那个广告的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You think all these calls are about the ad?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.29,0:11:03.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.06,0:11:05.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友妮可刚把咱们家小货车的照片发给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My friend Nicole just sent me a picture of the van.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.16,0:11:07.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你老妈要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess I'll be seeing you wednesdays
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.83,0:11:10.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气得跟我离婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and every other weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.10,0:11:11.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.84,0:11:14.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的  听上去你很生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, um, you sound very angry,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.34,0:11:15.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我完全理解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which is completely understandable.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.94,0:11:17.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没生气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.14,0:11:18.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是坐在这里  回想我的大学生涯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just sitting here thinking about college
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.01,0:11:20.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回忆曾经的青春年少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and how life has passed me by.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.71,0:11:22.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地  我们表演会上见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thank god. I'll see you at the show.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.21,0:11:23.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱你  拜拜  快走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Love you. Bye. We got to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.28,0:11:27.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音乐到达高潮的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And as the music swells,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.45,0:11:29.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们举起手里的字母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}we reveal our letters
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.41,0:11:31.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拼成"我们爱世界"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}spelling "We love the world."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.05,0:11:32.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好很强大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Powerful stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.59,0:11:35.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后宏伟的富兰克林中学的标志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then the majestic Franklin middle school insignia
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.65,0:11:37.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会缓缓就位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}will drop into position
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.52,0:11:40.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过前提是鲁本能把标志画完\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if Reuben ever finishes painting it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.55,0:11:41.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是艺术殿堂  鲁本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not the sistine chapel, Reuben.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.92,0:11:44.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惊喜吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Surprise! Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.72,0:11:47.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼎力支持的男友顺路带点心给你吃啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your supportive boyfriend dropped by to bring you a snack.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.03,0:11:49.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨梨  小布里和肉肉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}P.B. And J.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.06,0:11:50.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梨子  布里干酪配火腿  我最爱啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pear, brie, and jambon. My favorite!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.96,0:11:53.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同志们  休息五分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, people, let's take five.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.10,0:11:54.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就五分钟哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A true five.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.34,0:11:57.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曼尼  怎么样啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Manny. How's it going?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.40,0:11:59.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  很好  好得不能再好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good, great, couldn't be better.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.40,0:12:02.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能不能...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can we, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.07,0:12:05.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  当然  没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, we can, uh -- all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.31,0:12:06.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.99,0:12:08.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  你需要跟小卡谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, you got to talk to Cam.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.66,0:12:09.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要把我们逼疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's driving us crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.86,0:12:11.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯文又开始咬指甲了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Kevin is biting his nails again,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.66,0:12:14.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲁本一周都没有拉便便了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And Reuben hasn't had a bowel movement in a week.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.26,0:12:16.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别笑  猫王就是被逼死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't laugh. That's how Elvis died.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.00,0:12:18.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  曼尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, um, Manny,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.36,0:12:20.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我不能参与进去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I can't get involved.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.44,0:12:22.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但  好吧  要是你想反映情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, all right, if you have to say something,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.61,0:12:25.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就去告诉犀利哥  说他做过头了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just tell Bob Fussy that he's overdoing it
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.71,0:12:26.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他你们想回到原来那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you want to go back to your old stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.90,0:12:28.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  休息结束  同志们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, break's over, people!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.17,0:12:30.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们再来次法国大革命那一段\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I want to do the french revolution number again.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.97,0:12:32.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把断头台拿上来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's bring out the guillotine.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.57,0:12:34.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这次用点心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Carefully this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.31,0:12:36.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  不要  不要了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.50,0:12:37.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.91,0:12:41.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不想做这个新玩意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We don't want to do the new stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.28,0:12:42.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不想继续排练\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We want to stop rehearsing
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.88,0:12:45.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想用原来的方式演绎  犀利哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and go back to the old way, Bob Fussy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.39,0:12:48.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我  我不知道那词哪来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I-I don't know where this is coming from.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.89,0:12:51.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都这么认为吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You all feel this way?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.86,0:12:53.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  是的  是的 是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.73,0:12:56.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I had no idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.36,0:13:00.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我周围是一群懒人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had no idea I was surrounded by a bunch of quitters.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.97,0:13:03.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要不是我把音乐剧大师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This production was a joke
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.17,0:13:04.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯恩斯坦和桑坦介绍给孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}until I introduced these children
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.84,0:13:06.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个破音乐剧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to the musical-theater greats --
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.37,0:13:07.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还只是个大笑柄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bernstein, Sondheim.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.41,0:13:08.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几年后  有个别孩子就会谈论\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Years from now, some of these kids
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.91,0:13:11.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当初我如何将他们桑坦化的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}will still be talking about the way I sondheim-ized them.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.28,0:13:14.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得那样说不太好...好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ooh, I'm don't think that's a good way of saying -- okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.18,0:13:15.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想用原来的方式吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You want to do it the old way
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.65,0:13:18.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这首没新意老歌和死气沉沉的编舞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with the same tired songs, the same drab choreography,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.39,0:13:20.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后得到父母敷衍的欢呼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the same tepid applause from mom and dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.59,0:13:22.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们真的想吗  回答我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is that what you want? Just say the word.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.82,0:13:23.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就是那样想的  是的  是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what we want. Yes. Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.89,0:13:24.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  伙计们  很遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, too bad, people!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.96,0:13:27.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了算  重来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're doing it my way! From the top!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.36,0:13:29.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是封闭式彩排  闪开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is a closed rehearsal. March.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.75,0:13:35.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你在外面干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi, honey. What are you doing out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.39,0:13:37.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你啊  因为我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, just waiting for you 'cause I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.66,0:13:38.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,海莉  从这边下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Haley, come out this side.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.93,0:13:39.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.62,0:13:40.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为很好玩啊  试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'Cause it's fun. Try it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.60,0:13:45.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滑动门  移动坐垫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, the doors slide, the seats slide.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.54,0:13:46.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这车无所不能啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What can't the sienna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.67,0:13:47.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.64,0:13:48.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  去看表演吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right? Let's go see a show!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.91,0:13:50.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我们应该把门关上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sweetie, we need to close the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.54,0:13:51.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  用钥匙就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, with the key.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.84,0:13:53.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看看走多远\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I like to see how far I can get from the car
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.34,0:13:54.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还能控制这车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and still make it work.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.38,0:13:55.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  亲爱的  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Listen, honey, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.55,0:13:57.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么  -我要问你些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Yeah? - Let me ask you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.18,0:13:58.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要实话实说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I need you to be really honest with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.98,0:14:02.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊  你可...行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, you ca-- yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.19,0:14:03.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是人老珠黄了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are my best years behind me?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.71,0:14:04.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.74,0:14:06.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.21,0:14:09.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,秘诀就是向前看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The trick is to keep looking forward.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.12,0:14:10.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.08,0:14:11.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.08,0:14:12.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的是的  千真万确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, yes, for sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.82,0:14:13.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好些没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You feel good?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.85,0:14:14.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.32,0:14:22.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好  欢迎各位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello, and welcome, everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.19,0:14:23.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及迟到的人们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And latecomers.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.03,0:14:24.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望大家能喜欢今晚的表演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I hope you enjoy the show tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.70,0:14:27.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们一定赞同这个舞台已经多年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think you will agree it has a certain flair
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.37,0:14:29.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有高水准高质量的表演了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that has been lacking from this stage in years past.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.97,0:14:33.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  请容许我邀您坐稳当  放轻松\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, please, I invite you to sit back, relax,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.61,0:14:38.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情享受这趟世界音乐旅程吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and enjoy this musical trip around the world!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.18,0:14:45.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wow.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.48,0:14:48.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在美国长大是很不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Growing up in America sure is great,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.09,0:14:50.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还想对世界了解的更多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I wish I knew more about the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.43,0:14:51.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.89,0:14:53.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I've got an idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.66,0:14:55.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会见  朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See you later, friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.43,0:14:56.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.87,0:14:59.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去见见世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To see the world!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.72,0:15:03.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国看上去很有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}China looks interesting.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.19,0:15:04.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在这里着陆吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think I'll land here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.96,0:15:07.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放他下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bring him down!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.16,0:15:08.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放他下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bring him down!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.86,0:15:11.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续  继续演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just go with it. Go with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.60,0:15:16.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  搞什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Hey. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.66,0:15:18.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  搞什么呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Geez, come on,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.11,0:15:19.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰  你在剧院里呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Jay. You're in the theater.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.42,0:15:20.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你夹克的口袋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Try your jacket pocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.55,0:15:21.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry, folks.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.34,0:15:23.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厉害 他用胶带把手机封死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nice. He taped it shut.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.28,0:15:24.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that's enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.42,0:15:29.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,傻子啊  你也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ay! Stupid! You too!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.81,0:15:31.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打他  他得癌症了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't hit him. He has cancer.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.18,0:15:32.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What --
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.99,0:15:41.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  卢克是被卡在那儿了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, my god, is Luke stuck up there?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.16,0:15:45.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.60,0:15:47.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.03,0:15:48.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.73,0:15:50.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对--  别  哦不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ye-- oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.07,0:15:51.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.80,0:15:53.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,中国是挺有意思的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}China sure was fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.77,0:15:57.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看啊  那儿还有快乐的老英格兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and look, there's merry old England.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.14,0:15:59.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道看表演的人都没见过地球仪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Has anyone here ever seen a globe?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.28,0:16:02.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全速前进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Full steam ahead!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.58,0:16:04.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是前进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ahead!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.81,0:16:06.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管那个了  你就唱吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just sing.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.28,0:16:08.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哦  睁开被海风吹拂的眼睛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, joy to salt-swept eyes
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.97,0:16:11.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我欣喜地看见了  那美丽的英格兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fair England, do I see
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.66,0:16:21.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉我告诉了歌洛莉亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry about what I said to Gloria, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.87,0:16:24.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是一时脱口而出了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just came out.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.14,0:16:25.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们进去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's go back inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.57,0:16:27.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-打我一下  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hit me. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.71,0:16:28.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听见我说的了  打我一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You heard me. Hit me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.94,0:16:30.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会打你的  唐尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not gonna hit you, Donnie.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.48,0:16:32.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  这就是重点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, well, that's the whole damn point.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.44,0:16:33.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一听说我病了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As soon as you heard I was sick,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.53,0:16:34.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对待我的方式就不一样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you treated me different.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.01,0:16:37.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你吧  那些我在家就受够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let me tell you, I get enough of that at home.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.32,0:16:39.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.79,0:16:41.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是有点儿替你难过  行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I feel a little bad for you, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.22,0:16:46.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我们不常说这些  可是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know we don't say this much, but, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.86,0:16:49.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是关心你的  你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I care for you, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.63,0:16:52.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我不知道这点屁事儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you think I don't know that crap?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.16,0:16:54.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从我八岁你十岁那年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have known you cared about me
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.60,0:16:56.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个蠢货乔伊·可列里偷了我的自行车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}since we were 8 and 10 years old
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.74,0:16:59.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把他的头埋进冰里之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and that mook Joey Calieri stole my bike
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.91,0:17:01.77,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道你是关心我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you put his head in the ice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.05,0:17:06.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他当时说什么来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What was that he said again?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.58,0:17:08.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我再也听不见了"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, "I can't hear no more."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.29,0:17:13.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我再也听不见了"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"I can't hear no more!"
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.25,0:17:14.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}oh, Don.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.82,0:17:16.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的舞台装饰被弄得到处都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your stage is all over the place.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.72,0:17:17.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们都累疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The kids are exhausted.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.25,0:17:19.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就在那儿照自己的意思演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're making all about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.13,0:17:19.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连幕间休息都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No intermission.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.89,0:17:21.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把我们当动物了是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, are we animals?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.06,0:17:22.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I --
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.48,0:17:29.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.92,0:17:30.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有很好的医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I got great doctors.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.87,0:17:32.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们每天都给我打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The kids call me every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.68,0:17:35.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾琳因为压力过大  还瘦了20磅呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Irene even lost 20 pounds due to stress.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.22,0:17:36.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.56,0:17:41.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你答应我你会好好做个肝区检查\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You promise me you'll get that liver checked out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.17,0:17:43.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎呀  根本没--\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, there's nothing wrong--
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.10,0:17:45.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  唐  您老就忍着点吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, Donna. Suck it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.51,0:17:46.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都错过我儿子的演出了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're missing my kid's show.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.97,0:17:48.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.38,0:17:50.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.14,0:17:52.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我再也听不见啦"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"I can't hear no more!"
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.71,0:17:55.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.82,0:17:56.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那个是我的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That one was my fault,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.88,0:17:58.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过圣女贞德会没事儿的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But Joan of Arc's gonna be just fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.52,0:18:00.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这剧没了艾玛就没意思了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not gonna be much fun doing the show without Emma.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.89,0:18:02.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们应该到此为止\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe we should just stop this.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.99,0:18:05.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别  不行  在戏剧界有句俗话叫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No. There is a saying in the theater world that --
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.12,0:18:06.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"为它丧命实属不智"吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"It's not worth dying for"?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.69,0:18:08.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是"结尾成就一切"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's that "Endings make shows."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.29,0:18:09.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说我们那个结尾那么好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And we've got a great ending.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.60,0:18:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以现在赶紧出去给我充满感情地唱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now get out there and sing your hearts out.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.53,0:18:14.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的你就别唱了  你对口型就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, not you, sweetie. You just mouth the words. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.17,0:18:16.74,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡叔叔  我两条腿都疼了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uncle Cam, both my legs are tingly.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.74,0:18:18.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  我们马上就把你放下来行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, we'll cut you down in just a second, Luke, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.61,0:18:20.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演出得继续  要乐在其中哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The show must go on. Have fun with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.18,0:18:24.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,了解这个世界的确很有趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Learning about the world sure was fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.71,0:18:27.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是能够重新两脚着地  我也挺高兴的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But I'm glad to have my feet back on the ground again.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.92,0:18:31.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,埃及土地  金字塔耸立\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Egypt is a land where the pyramids stand
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.84,0:18:35.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勤劳的犹太人  把它们全部建起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which were built by industrious jews
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.25,0:18:39.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风车们在荷兰的村庄  随处可见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And windmills go around in Holland town
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.08,0:18:43.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里的人们  都穿着木头做的鞋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where they all wear wooden shoes
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.94,0:18:47.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们学了很多东西  在今天这一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}These are the things we learned today
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.96,0:18:53.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千言万语  只剩一句\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And there's one last thing we want to say
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.97,0:18:58.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我们爱这个词"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"We love the word"
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.18,0:19:00.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么少一个字母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where's the "L"?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.08,0:19:02.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是卢克拿着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's luke.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.05,0:19:03.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那个标志牌放低点儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lower the insignia.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.21,0:19:04.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,低点儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lower it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.48,0:19:05.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我们爱操蛋这个词"
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.48,0:19:05.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们爱...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"We love the --"
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.38,0:19:08.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What the hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.95,0:19:10.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不对  不是  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no. No, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.65,0:19:12.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.12,0:19:14.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. No, no, no. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.30,0:19:20.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太精彩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Brava!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.00,0:19:22.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔  你去哪儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Phil, where have you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.98,0:19:24.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是呼吸点儿新鲜空气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, just getting some fresh air.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.48,0:19:25.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-亲爱的  -呼吸完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Honey. - Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.78,0:19:27.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要走了吗  嘿  看看月亮吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ready to go? Hey, look up at the moon.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.42,0:19:29.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说这是满月呢  还是弦月呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you say that's waxing or waning?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.15,0:19:30.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他呢  我们能花一晚上看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who cares? We can spend all night looking --
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.99,0:19:33.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我不能被满足"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"I can't be satisfied"?!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.79,0:19:34.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊  菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}My God, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.83,0:19:36.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话让我看起来跟个妓女一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That makes me look like a prostitute.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.93,0:19:37.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.76,0:19:38.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有  就有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. Yes, it does.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.96,0:19:40.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实更像个三陪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}More of an escort, really.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.40,0:19:41.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三陪的只是出卖时间而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're just selling your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.57,0:19:43.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是妓女是--  -行了菲尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Whereas a prostitute just-- - Okay, Phil.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.40,0:19:46.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天一整天都开着这车跑来跑去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have been driving around in this all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.54,0:19:49.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  既然你已经生气了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, since you're mad already,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.41,0:19:51.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你不到这边来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}why don't you just step over here
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.86,0:19:53.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这个呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and have a look at that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.46,0:19:55.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝啊  我的宝贝女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, God. My baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.43,0:19:57.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝不再坐那辆车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am not getting back in that car!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.40,0:19:59.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧  亲爱的  那你怎么回家呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, how do you think you're gonna get home, honey?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.33,0:20:01.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无所谓  我随便跟谁回家都行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It doesn't matter! I'll go home with anyone!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.07,0:20:02.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这话才应该写在车上呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what it should say on the van.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.67,0:20:04.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.86,0:20:05.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't believe we trusted you
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.97,0:20:06.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过上次失败的照片教训\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to put this on the car
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.96,0:20:08.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还敢让你把照片贴车上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}after the debacle of that last picture.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.59,0:20:09.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.83,0:20:11.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你--  是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And that -- who was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.53,0:20:13.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是另一个...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Probably another...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.10,0:20:15.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你想说的可能是"路人甲"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think the word you're looking for is "John."
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.13,0:20:17.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get in the minivan.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.47,0:20:18.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想告诉我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean to tell me that
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.41,0:20:20.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确有人打电话来要特殊服务是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}people have actually been calling about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.21,0:20:21.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,变态多得是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There are a lot of creeps out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.54,0:20:23.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也太恶心了  她还是个孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's disgusting. She's a child.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.51,0:20:25.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公平点儿说  大部分是打来要你服务的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, to be fair, most of them were for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.01,0:20:28.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也很恶心好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, it's still sick.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.58,0:20:30.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说"大部分"  是多少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What do you mean, "Most"?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.78,0:20:33.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  差不多有三十通电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I don't know. There were 30 calls.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.09,0:20:35.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二十多个都是找你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got 20 or 25 of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.32,0:20:37.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他们...点名找我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And they...ask for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.32,0:20:38.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要那个金发辣妹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They asked for the hot blonde.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.96,0:20:42.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人都是色情狂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hmm. Men are pigs.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.29,0:20:43.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了金发辣妹  他们还叫我什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did they call me anything else?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.96,0:20:46.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  谢谢城里的所有变态\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, thanks to all the perverts in town,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.10,0:20:48.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我发现我的青春年华还剩好几年呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I realized I still have a few good years ahead of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.87,0:20:52.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们为此要感谢谁的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And if we have one person to thank for that,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.17,0:20:53.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那肯定是我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It would be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.57,0:20:54.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.21,0:21:07.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,演出和我想的一样烂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was it as awful as I think?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.24,0:21:08.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收下这花儿吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Take the flowers.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.05,0:21:12.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你在我像个傻子一样出尽洋相的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It must have been really hard for you to be supportive
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.52,0:21:14.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还那么支持我一定很难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}while I made a fool out of myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.08,0:21:16.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来抱抱吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.03,0:21:21.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  你能不能安静点儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Luke, do you mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.09,0:21:21.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正浓情蜜意呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're trying to have a moment here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.00,0:21:24.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的眼睛都能感觉到心跳了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can feel my heartbeat in my eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.47,0:21:25.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他的眼睛  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- In his eyes? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.00,0:21:27.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去找工人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. We'll get a janitor.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.40,0:21:28.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.

