1
00:00:10,000 --> 00:00:15,010
{\pos(120.2,219.2)}m 330 133 l 343 133 l 343 125 l 330 125 m 330 122 l 343 122 l 343 115 l 330 115 m 330 112 l 343 112 l 343 104 l 330 104 m 322 136 l 322 133 l 327 133 l 327 101 l 346 101 l 346 133 l 350 133 l 350 136 m 316 121 b 316 121 316 121 316 121 b 316 121 320 121 323 121 b 323 121 323 123 323 123 b 318 124 315 124 311 125 l 311 122 b 311 122 317 114 317 114 b 317 114 317 114 317 114 b 316 113 310 115 310 115 l 310 112 b 310 112 317 99 317 99 l 320 100 b 317 105 316 107 314 112 b 313 112 314 112 313 112 b 320 112 322 105 322 105 l 325 107 b 325 107 316 121 316 121 m 310 131 b 313 131 318 130 324 129 l 324 131 b 319 132 315 133 310 134 m 296 126 b 296 125 293 124 293 123 l 288 123 l 288 126 m 281 123 b 280 123 277 126 277 126 l 285 126 l 285 123 m 276 116 l 298 116 l 298 113 l 276 113 m 276 111 l 298 111 l 298 109 l 276 109 m 291 99 l 294 99 l 294 101 l 306 101 l 305 104 l 294 104 l 294 106 l 291 106 l 291 104 l 282 104 l 282 106 l 279 106 l 279 104 l 268 104 l 268 101 l 279 101 l 279 98 l 282 98 l 282 101 l 291 101 m 268 120 l 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 280 119 l 272 119 l 272 106 l 301 106 l 301 118 l 287 118 b 285 118 284 119 283 120 l 305 120 l 305 123 l 297 123 b 299 123 297 123 307 128 b 306 128 307 128 305 131 b 301 128 300 128 300 128 l 300 130 b 300 134 297 135 297 135 l 291 135 b 291 135 291 135 291 132 b 291 132 291 133 291 133 b 292 132 292 132 297 132 b 297 130 297 130 297 131 l 297 129 l 288 129 l 288 138 l 285 138 l 285 129 l 277 129 l 277 136 l 274 136 l 274 127 b 274 127 274 127 268 131 b 268 131 268 131 266 129 b 266 129 272 125 276 123 l 268 123 m 244 98 l 244 98 b 244 98 246 103 247 104 l 244 104 l 263 104 l 263 112 l 259 112 l 259 108 l 229 108 l 229 113 l 225 113 l 225 104 l 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 241 99 m 242 119 l 251 115 l 231 115 l 231 112 l 256 112 l 256 116 l 246 121 l 246 122 l 264 122 l 264 125 l 246 125 l 246 129 b 246 134 246 137 243 138 l 235 138 b 235 138 234 134 234 134 b 236 134 236 134 242 134 b 242 134 242 130 242 130 l 242 125 l 224 125 l 224 122 l 242 122 m 210 58 l 192 58 l 192 54 l 210 54 m 225 55 l 239 56 l 261 28 l 245 28 l 225 53 b 224 49 221 45 216 46 l 178 46 l 178 66 l 193 66 l 193 77 l 189 77 l 191 68 l 178 68 l 174 87 l 188 87 l 190 81 l 193 87 l 209 87 l 209 66 l 225 66 m 192 19 l 210 19 l 210 21 l 192 21 m 192 9 l 210 9 l 210 12 l 192 12 m 228 34 l 210 34 l 209 31 l 226 31 l 226 27 l 238 27 l 261 0 l 244 0 l 226 22 l 225 22 l 225 6 b 225 3 224 0 217 0 l 177 0 l 176 30 l 193 30 l 193 34 l 174 34 l 174 43 l 227 43 m 246 57 l 226 79 l 224 69 l 212 69 l 215 85 l 223 84 l 222 87 l 238 87 l 261 57 m 336 77 l 336 59 l 329 58 l 329 14 l 315 14 l 315 49 l 291 87 l 306 87 l 324 58 l 324 87 l 346 87 l 350 77 m 310 10 l 334 10 l 335 56 l 345 56 l 345 6 b 345 4 343 0 339 0 l 298 0 l 298 56 l 310 56 m 295 36 l 286 36 l 295 21 l 295 10 l 288 10 l 284 0 l 267 0 l 272 10 l 261 10 l 261 20 l 279 20 l 260 51 l 270 51 l 270 86 l 283 87 l 283 42 l 285 39 l 287 64 l 297 64 m 155 87 l 129 35 l 104 87 l 84 87 l 128 0 l 146 0 l 132 30 l 146 30 l 174 87 m 66 87 l 39 35 l 14 87 l -5 87 l 38 0 l 56 0 l 42 30 l 56 30 l 84 87 m 203 138 l 199 138 l 190 111 l 194 111 l 201 133 b 201 134 201 134 201 133 l 209 111 l 213 111 m 188 135 l 188 137 b 183 137 188 137 183 137 b 183 137 179 138 179 134 l 179 115 l 176 115 l 176 111 l 179 111 l 179 104 l 183 103 l 183 111 l 187 111 l 187 115 l 183 115 l 183 135 b 183 135 183 135 188 135 m 166 132 l 171 132 l 171 137 l 166 137 m 154 111 l 158 111 l 158 137 l 155 137 l 155 133 b 153 136 151 138 145 137 b 143 138 139 137 136 132 l 136 111 l 140 111 l 140 127 b 140 131 139 134 146 135 b 151 135 153 132 154 128 m 110 134 l 132 134 l 132 137 l 104 137 l 104 135 l 126 105 l 107 105 l 107 102 l 131 102 l 131 105 m 96 111 l 100 111 l 100 137 l 97 137 l 97 133 b 94 135 93 138 88 138 b 85 138 81 136 79 130 l 79 111 l 83 111 l 83 130 b 84 133 86 135 89 135 b 94 135 97 130 96 123 m 69 107 l 57 137 l 54 137 l 42 107 l 42 137 l 38 137 l 38 102 l 43 102 l 56 132 l 67 102 l 73 102 l 73 137 l 69 137 m 27 111 l 31 111 l 31 137 l 27 137 m 27 102 l 31 102 l 31 106 l 27 106 m 0 135 l 23 135 l 23 137 l -5 137 l -5 135 l 17 105 l -3 105 l -3 102 l 22 102 l 22 104 

2
00:00:10,000 --> 00:00:15,010
{\pos(63.2,210.173)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

3
00:00:10,000 --> 00:00:15,010
{\pos(74.6,219.373)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

4
00:00:10,000 --> 00:00:15,010
{\pos(60.2,205)}m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 

5
00:00:11,000 --> 00:00:15,010
{\pos(238.2,237.8)}仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv

7
00:00:11,000 --> 00:00:15,010
{\pos(106.2,237.8)}原创翻译  双语字幕

8
00:00:15,000 --> 00:00:20,000
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  丁小七  芝小士  阿朱

10
00:00:19,970 --> 00:00:24,970
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  亲爱的小饭    moonshine

11
00:00:24,930 --> 00:00:29,930
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}校对:  慕容龙飞

12
00:00:29,900 --> 00:00:34,900
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}时间轴:  掌人仙

13
00:00:34,900 --> 00:00:39,900
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}后期:  瓜瓜2016版    总监： 瓜瓜

14
00:00:40,000 --> 00:00:50,000
{\an7}{\pos(22.2,180.8)} m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340

15
00:00:40,000 --> 00:00:45,000
{\an4}{\pos(70,211.2)}打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息

17
00:02:22,440 --> 00:02:23,510
{\pos(183,74)}摩  登

18
00:02:22,440 --> 00:02:23,510
{\pos(183,240)}家  庭

19
00:02:22,930 --> 00:02:25,390
{\pos(304,242)}第七季 第十九集

20
00:10:46,490 --> 00:10:59,490
{\an5}{\pos(338,27)}最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv

21
00:10:46,490 --> 00:11:11,490
{\pos(280.4,34.773)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

22
00:10:46,490 --> 00:11:11,490
{\pos(295.4,43.173)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

23
00:10:46,490 --> 00:11:11,490
{\an9}{\pos(293.4,-2.4)}m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 

31
00:10:59,490 --> 00:11:11,490
{\pos(342.8,43.2)}m 330 133 l 343 133 l 343 125 l 330 125 m 330 122 l 343 122 l 343 115 l 330 115 m 330 112 l 343 112 l 343 104 l 330 104 m 322 136 l 322 133 l 327 133 l 327 101 l 346 101 l 346 133 l 350 133 l 350 136 m 316 121 b 316 121 316 121 316 121 b 316 121 320 121 323 121 b 323 121 323 123 323 123 b 318 124 315 124 311 125 l 311 122 b 311 122 317 114 317 114 b 317 114 317 114 317 114 b 316 113 310 115 310 115 l 310 112 b 310 112 317 99 317 99 l 320 100 b 317 105 316 107 314 112 b 313 112 314 112 313 112 b 320 112 322 105 322 105 l 325 107 b 325 107 316 121 316 121 m 310 131 b 313 131 318 130 324 129 l 324 131 b 319 132 315 133 310 134 m 296 126 b 296 125 293 124 293 123 l 288 123 l 288 126 m 281 123 b 280 123 277 126 277 126 l 285 126 l 285 123 m 276 116 l 298 116 l 298 113 l 276 113 m 276 111 l 298 111 l 298 109 l 276 109 m 291 99 l 294 99 l 294 101 l 306 101 l 305 104 l 294 104 l 294 106 l 291 106 l 291 104 l 282 104 l 282 106 l 279 106 l 279 104 l 268 104 l 268 101 l 279 101 l 279 98 l 282 98 l 282 101 l 291 101 m 268 120 l 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 280 119 l 272 119 l 272 106 l 301 106 l 301 118 l 287 118 b 285 118 284 119 283 120 l 305 120 l 305 123 l 297 123 b 299 123 297 123 307 128 b 306 128 307 128 305 131 b 301 128 300 128 300 128 l 300 130 b 300 134 297 135 297 135 l 291 135 b 291 135 291 135 291 132 b 291 132 291 133 291 133 b 292 132 292 132 297 132 b 297 130 297 130 297 131 l 297 129 l 288 129 l 288 138 l 285 138 l 285 129 l 277 129 l 277 136 l 274 136 l 274 127 b 274 127 274 127 268 131 b 268 131 268 131 266 129 b 266 129 272 125 276 123 l 268 123 m 244 98 l 244 98 b 244 98 246 103 247 104 l 244 104 l 263 104 l 263 112 l 259 112 l 259 108 l 229 108 l 229 113 l 225 113 l 225 104 l 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 241 99 m 242 119 l 251 115 l 231 115 l 231 112 l 256 112 l 256 116 l 246 121 l 246 122 l 264 122 l 264 125 l 246 125 l 246 129 b 246 134 246 137 243 138 l 235 138 b 235 138 234 134 234 134 b 236 134 236 134 242 134 b 242 134 242 130 242 130 l 242 125 l 224 125 l 224 122 l 242 122 m 210 58 l 192 58 l 192 54 l 210 54 m 225 55 l 239 56 l 261 28 l 245 28 l 225 53 b 224 49 221 45 216 46 l 178 46 l 178 66 l 193 66 l 193 77 l 189 77 l 191 68 l 178 68 l 174 87 l 188 87 l 190 81 l 193 87 l 209 87 l 209 66 l 225 66 m 192 19 l 210 19 l 210 21 l 192 21 m 192 9 l 210 9 l 210 12 l 192 12 m 228 34 l 210 34 l 209 31 l 226 31 l 226 27 l 238 27 l 261 0 l 244 0 l 226 22 l 225 22 l 225 6 b 225 3 224 0 217 0 l 177 0 l 176 30 l 193 30 l 193 34 l 174 34 l 174 43 l 227 43 m 246 57 l 226 79 l 224 69 l 212 69 l 215 85 l 223 84 l 222 87 l 238 87 l 261 57 m 336 77 l 336 59 l 329 58 l 329 14 l 315 14 l 315 49 l 291 87 l 306 87 l 324 58 l 324 87 l 346 87 l 350 77 m 310 10 l 334 10 l 335 56 l 345 56 l 345 6 b 345 4 343 0 339 0 l 298 0 l 298 56 l 310 56 m 295 36 l 286 36 l 295 21 l 295 10 l 288 10 l 284 0 l 267 0 l 272 10 l 261 10 l 261 20 l 279 20 l 260 51 l 270 51 l 270 86 l 283 87 l 283 42 l 285 39 l 287 64 l 297 64 m 155 87 l 129 35 l 104 87 l 84 87 l 128 0 l 146 0 l 132 30 l 146 30 l 174 87 m 66 87 l 39 35 l 14 87 l -5 87 l 38 0 l 56 0 l 42 30 l 56 30 l 84 87 m 203 138 l 199 138 l 190 111 l 194 111 l 201 133 b 201 134 201 134 201 133 l 209 111 l 213 111 m 188 135 l 188 137 b 183 137 188 137 183 137 b 183 137 179 138 179 134 l 179 115 l 176 115 l 176 111 l 179 111 l 179 104 l 183 103 l 183 111 l 187 111 l 187 115 l 183 115 l 183 135 b 183 135 183 135 188 135 m 166 132 l 171 132 l 171 137 l 166 137 m 154 111 l 158 111 l 158 137 l 155 137 l 155 133 b 153 136 151 138 145 137 b 143 138 139 137 136 132 l 136 111 l 140 111 l 140 127 b 140 131 139 134 146 135 b 151 135 153 132 154 128 m 110 134 l 132 134 l 132 137 l 104 137 l 104 135 l 126 105 l 107 105 l 107 102 l 131 102 l 131 105 m 96 111 l 100 111 l 100 137 l 97 137 l 97 133 b 94 135 93 138 88 138 b 85 138 81 136 79 130 l 79 111 l 83 111 l 83 130 b 84 133 86 135 89 135 b 94 135 97 130 96 123 m 69 107 l 57 137 l 54 137 l 42 107 l 42 137 l 38 137 l 38 102 l 43 102 l 56 132 l 67 102 l 73 102 l 73 137 l 69 137 m 27 111 l 31 111 l 31 137 l 27 137 m 27 102 l 31 102 l 31 106 l 27 106 m 0 135 l 23 135 l 23 137 l -5 137 l -5 135 l 17 105 l -3 105 l -3 102 l 22 102 l 22 104 

39
00:00:02,940 --> 00:00:05,610
宅度假胡子非常有型啊  老爸
That staycation beard's really taking shape, dad.

40
00:00:05,610 --> 00:00:06,650
开始会黏吃的了 
It's starting to trap food.

41
00:00:06,660 --> 00:00:07,250
是啊
Yep.

42
00:00:07,250 --> 00:00:08,700
已经从痒变得难受了
It's gone from itchin' to bitchin'.

43
00:00:08,710 --> 00:00:10,180
你还在穿这身运动服
And you're still rocking the sweats.

44
00:00:10,180 --> 00:00:11,450
一周都没换
Every day this week. 

45
00:00:11,450 --> 00:00:12,360
内裤都不换吗
Same underwear?

46
00:00:12,360 --> 00:00:13,440
什么内裤
What underwear?

47
00:00:13,960 --> 00:00:14,760
等下继续聊
Hold that thought. 

48
00:00:14,760 --> 00:00:15,790
还要继续聊吗
Do I have to?

49
00:00:15,790 --> 00:00:17,640
菲城市长办公室
Mayor's office. City of Phila-Dunphy-a.

50
00:00:17,640 --> 00:00:19,030
抱歉  我刚下班
I'm sorry. I just got done.

51
00:00:19,030 --> 00:00:20,180
我的电脑坏了
My computer crashed,

52
00:00:20,180 --> 00:00:23,040
共从台湾运来的四架板转轴
and we got four pallets of hinges from Taiwan

53
00:00:23,040 --> 00:00:24,220
铆接又出了问题
with faulty riveting.

54
00:00:24,220 --> 00:00:25,710
至少你的故事很吸引人[铆接]
At least your story's riveting.

55
00:00:25,710 --> 00:00:27,160
好搞笑  等下给你解释
It's clever. I'll tell you later.

56
00:00:27,340 --> 00:00:29,120
为什么小货车停在咱家停车道上
Hey, why is the minivan in the driveway?

57
00:00:29,120 --> 00:00:30,340
你今天早上把我堵在里面了
You parked me in this morning.

58
00:00:30,340 --> 00:00:31,340
我那时候开会快迟到了
I was running late for a meeting,

59
00:00:31,340 --> 00:00:32,660
所以我就开了海莉的花冠去的
so I just took Haley's Corolla.

60
00:00:32,660 --> 00:00:33,200
好玩
Fun.

61
00:00:33,200 --> 00:00:34,420
要是闻起来不像
It would be if it didn't smell like

62
00:00:34,420 --> 00:00:36,810
鲍勃·马利的洗衣篮那就真还不错
the inside of Bob Marley's laundry hamper.

63
00:00:36,810 --> 00:00:38,440
总之我还得再打好几个电话
Anyway, I've got a bunch more calls to make.

64
00:00:38,440 --> 00:00:40,060
今天晚上没时间做饭了
I'm not gonna have time to cook tonight.

65
00:00:40,070 --> 00:00:40,740
我们可以去外面吃
We could go out.

66
00:00:40,740 --> 00:00:42,080
新开了家餐馆叫滑板鞋
There's that new restaurant -- Sliders.

67
00:00:42,090 --> 00:00:43,610
噱头就是餐馆开在一个斜坡上
The gimmick is they built it on a slant,

68
00:00:43,610 --> 00:00:45,430
所有服务员都只穿袜子
and the waiters all wear socks.

69
00:00:45,580 --> 00:00:47,500
听起来不怎么样啊
That doesn't sound good at all.

70
00:00:47,510 --> 00:00:48,850
你能叫点外卖吗
Can you just order something?

71
00:00:48,850 --> 00:00:49,730
好啊  没问题
Yeah, you got it. 

72
00:00:49,740 --> 00:00:50,770
太好了
Great.

73
00:00:54,860 --> 00:00:55,850
你在干嘛
What are you doing? 

74
00:00:56,230 --> 00:00:57,400
走开  小狗
Run away, little dog.

75
00:00:57,760 --> 00:00:59,510
好吧  我绕开就是了
Fine. Go around you.

76
00:00:59,810 --> 00:01:01,130
你不会走的
You're not gonna move.

77
00:01:01,300 --> 00:01:03,730
因为我不会为你停车的
'Cause I'm not stopping for you.

78
00:01:04,240 --> 00:01:06,710
我会为你停车的
I'm stopping for you.

79
00:01:06,770 --> 00:01:07,620
该死
Damn.  

80
00:01:10,690 --> 00:01:11,540
快走啊
Move it!

81
00:01:12,360 --> 00:01:13,790
真不走吗
Seriously?

82
00:01:18,730 --> 00:01:21,670
别忘了客人来的时候  你要照看乔哦
Don't forget you have to watch Joe while we have company.

83
00:01:21,670 --> 00:01:22,260
又要吗
Again? 

84
00:01:22,260 --> 00:01:23,320
对  又要
Yes, again.

85
00:01:23,330 --> 00:01:24,450
有什么问题吗
What is the problem?

86
00:01:24,460 --> 00:01:26,010
他老想看他的节目
He always wants to watch his show 

87
00:01:26,010 --> 00:01:27,800
《神秘孩纸》  是"纸"哦
"Mystery Kidz," With a "Z."

88
00:01:27,800 --> 00:01:28,610
太让人受不了了
It's insufferable.

89
00:01:28,610 --> 00:01:29,600
现在你明白
Now you know what I felt

90
00:01:29,600 --> 00:01:31,980
我陪你看你最喜欢的节目时的感受了吧
when I had to watch your favorite show.

91
00:01:31,980 --> 00:01:33,100
《经典剧场》吗
"Masterpiece Theater"?

92
00:01:33,100 --> 00:01:35,080
节目主持人是一只可怕的木偶
It was hosted by a creepy puppet.

93
00:01:35,080 --> 00:01:36,510
那是艾伦·卡明
That was Alan Cumming.

94
00:01:36,810 --> 00:01:39,530
杰  你得再多搬两把椅子出来
Ay, Jay, you have to add two more chairs.

95
00:01:39,530 --> 00:01:40,440
给谁
For who?

96
00:01:40,440 --> 00:01:41,960
我们俩  麦克克劳兹夫妇  夏普斯夫妇
It's us, the McClouds, and the Sharps.

97
00:01:41,960 --> 00:01:45,100
我还请了我朋友戴娜和她丈夫瑞斯
I also invited my friend Dana and her husband, Reece.

98
00:01:45,110 --> 00:01:46,920
瑞斯  瑞斯是谁
Reece? Who's Reece?

99
00:01:46,920 --> 00:01:48,890
我刚跟你说了啊  戴娜的老公
I just told you. Dana's husband.

100
00:01:48,890 --> 00:01:50,540
我在家长教师联谊会午餐时认识她的
I met her at the PTA lunch,

101
00:01:50,540 --> 00:01:53,170
她是反欺霸社团中唯一一个
and she's the only woman in the anti-bullying campaign

102
00:01:53,170 --> 00:01:54,850
我不想揍的女人
that I don't want to punch in the face.

103
00:01:54,860 --> 00:01:56,660
我为什么要请那俩人来我家里
Why would I want these people in my house

104
00:01:56,670 --> 00:01:58,270
搅了我的扑克局
messing up my poker game?

105
00:01:58,270 --> 00:01:59,770
这样你就可以认识新朋友了啊
Maybe you'll meet new friends.

106
00:01:59,770 --> 00:02:02,490
我们以前就说过了啊  我不想认识什么新朋友
We've been over this before. I don't want any new friends.

107
00:02:02,500 --> 00:02:05,180
我的朋友数量刚刚好
I have the exact-right number of friends.

108
00:02:05,180 --> 00:02:07,170
杰  你的朋友都是
Jay, your friends have been around

109
00:02:07,170 --> 00:02:09,390
从默片时代过来的了
since before the movies could talk.

110
00:02:09,390 --> 00:02:10,780
我觉得开始找一些备胎
I don't think it's the worst idea

111
00:02:10,780 --> 00:02:12,880
也不失为一个好主意
to start getting some backups.

112
00:02:26,320 --> 00:02:28,550
老爸  什么是最小公分母[特征人群]啊
Hey, Daddy, what's a lowest common denominator?

113
00:02:28,550 --> 00:02:30,400
-真人秀  -好好笑
- Reality TV. - That's hilarious,

114
00:02:30,410 --> 00:02:32,260
但我明天要考试了
but I've got a quiz tomorrow.

115
00:02:34,760 --> 00:02:35,700
什么声音
What is that noise?

116
00:02:35,700 --> 00:02:37,470
我提醒你一下  已经有好几周
Let me remind you that it's been weeks

117
00:02:37,470 --> 00:02:38,910
楼上没人租了
since we've had a tenant up there.

118
00:02:38,910 --> 00:02:40,910
所以你就租给一个摇滚乐队
So you rented it to a rock band?

119
00:02:40,910 --> 00:02:42,280
一个基督教摇滚乐队
A Christian rock band.

120
00:02:42,290 --> 00:02:44,640
这下好了  所以他们又吵又爱评论人
Oh, good. Okay, so they're noisy and judge-y.

121
00:02:44,640 --> 00:02:47,020
你和你这种狭隘的城市优越感太不要脸了
Shame on you and your narrow, big-city attitude.

122
00:02:47,020 --> 00:02:49,450
我也认识很多有信仰的开明人士
I've known many accepting people of faith.

123
00:02:49,450 --> 00:02:51,280
我被传教士追到了一片湖里
And I've been chased into a lake.

124
00:02:51,280 --> 00:02:53,470
所以我们都有权维持自己的观点
So I guess we're both entitled to our opinion.

125
00:02:55,170 --> 00:02:55,910
不
No!

126
00:02:55,910 --> 00:02:57,700
绝对不行
Absolutely not.

127
00:02:59,420 --> 00:03:00,240
进
Come in.

128
00:03:01,980 --> 00:03:04,000
这是米奇尔  音乐太棒了
This is Mitchell, and the music sounds great.

129
00:03:04,000 --> 00:03:06,390
就是想问问你们有没有可能稍微小点声
Just wondering if you could turn it down a-a skosh.

130
00:03:06,390 --> 00:03:08,190
当然可以  很抱歉
Yeah, of course. We're sorry.

131
00:03:08,190 --> 00:03:11,490
只是想给楼上的哥们感受一下我们的新歌
Just giving the guy upstairs a taste of our new song.

132
00:03:11,640 --> 00:03:12,370
他是说上帝
He means God. 

133
00:03:12,370 --> 00:03:14,550
是吗  真的没有我不知道的三楼吗
Really? There's no third floor I don't know about?

134
00:03:14,570 --> 00:03:17,070
顺便提一嘴  我们很喜欢这里
We love the place, by the way.

135
00:03:17,070 --> 00:03:19,130
真的非常漂亮
It's just scrumptious.

136
00:03:19,780 --> 00:03:21,100
很好  很好
Good! Good!

137
00:03:21,460 --> 00:03:24,620
所以你们是基督教摇滚乐队是吧
So, you guys are a Christian rock band?

138
00:03:24,900 --> 00:03:26,870
化水为酒乐队  没错  就是我们
Water to Wine. Yeah, that's us.

139
00:03:26,870 --> 00:03:27,850
我希望你们不会把
Well, I hope you're not expecting

140
00:03:27,850 --> 00:03:29,730
你们的粉丝们都带来这里吧
to bring all your groupies back here.

141
00:03:30,750 --> 00:03:31,320
别担心
Don't worry.

142
00:03:31,320 --> 00:03:33,380
羔羊教堂的士兵
The Soldiers of the Lamb Church

143
00:03:33,380 --> 00:03:34,720
禁止婚前关系
forbids premarital relations.

144
00:03:34,720 --> 00:03:36,730
当然  但是我也能想到几个
Of course. But I can think of a few ladies

145
00:03:36,740 --> 00:03:38,330
在我们长老给过祝福后
I wouldn't mind multiplying with

146
00:03:38,330 --> 00:03:40,340
我愿意与她生小孩的姑娘
after our elders give us their blessings.

147
00:03:40,340 --> 00:03:41,500
我听到了哦
I heard that.  

148
00:03:41,820 --> 00:03:43,820
我们爱姑娘
We love girls!

149
00:03:44,070 --> 00:03:47,280
正巧你们来了  我需要点外人的意见
As long as you guys are here, I need an outsider's opinion.

150
00:03:47,280 --> 00:03:48,340
我在写一首歌
I'm working on a song,

151
00:03:48,340 --> 00:03:51,110
但是这些家伙觉得这歌太温柔了
but these guys think it's too soft.

152
00:03:52,250 --> 00:03:53,460
介意听一下吗
Do you mind?

153
00:03:55,180 --> 00:03:56,350
来吧  兄弟
Lay it on us, bro.

154
00:03:57,070 --> 00:03:59,600
*隐藏已久*
*Hiding for so long*

155
00:03:59,730 --> 00:04:02,670
*不属于我的真实自我*
*The real me, I don't belong*

156
00:04:02,680 --> 00:04:05,810
*我不是自己  从未曾是*
*I'm not myself, I never was*

157
00:04:05,810 --> 00:04:08,950
*我在黑夜哭泣  都因为*
*I cry at night and all because*

158
00:04:08,950 --> 00:04:11,770
*我困在一条秘密的小路中*
*I'm trapped on a secret path*

159
00:04:11,790 --> 00:04:14,160
*我需要圣浴*
*I need a holy bath*

160
00:04:14,160 --> 00:04:17,110
*洗刷我隐藏的罪孽*
*To wash away the sins I hide*

161
00:04:17,110 --> 00:04:20,610
*浇熄我内心深处的小火焰*
*To douse the fire I feel inside*

162
00:04:20,610 --> 00:04:22,620
该死  戴克斯  你这样我很不爽
Aw, dang it, Dex, you're bumming me out!

163
00:04:22,620 --> 00:04:24,070
冷静 库普
Calm down, Coop.

164
00:04:24,070 --> 00:04:25,100
我们进了城
Just 'cause we're in the city

165
00:04:25,100 --> 00:04:27,080
不代表我们就能随心所欲说话
doesn't mean we got to talk like it.

166
00:04:28,030 --> 00:04:29,270
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.

167
00:04:29,940 --> 00:04:32,370
你知道吗  戴克斯  我喜欢这首歌
You know what, Dex, I like that song.

168
00:04:32,370 --> 00:04:34,110
是啊  歌名是什么
Yeah. What's the title?

169
00:04:34,520 --> 00:04:36,870
我叫它《求助》
I call it "A Cry for Help."

170
00:04:36,870 --> 00:04:38,870
-你听到了吗  -当然  我就在这呢
- Did you hear that? -Yeah, I'm standing right here.

171
00:04:41,760 --> 00:04:42,910
你又回来了吗
You're back again?

172
00:04:43,120 --> 00:04:44,300
我也想你了
Missed you, too.

173
00:04:45,400 --> 00:04:46,780
桑杰这周末回家了
Sanjay's home this weekend.

174
00:04:46,780 --> 00:04:50,110
今天是我们一个重要的日子  一周年纪念日
It's kind of a big day for us -- our first anniversary.

175
00:04:50,280 --> 00:04:51,300
看看我给他准备了什么
Look what I got him.

176
00:04:51,840 --> 00:04:53,340
这是一支鸭嘴龙掌骨
It's a hadrosaur metacarpal

177
00:04:53,340 --> 00:04:55,230
他喜欢收集恐龙骨头
for his dinosaur bone collection.

178
00:04:56,010 --> 00:04:56,810
太过了吗
Too much?

179
00:04:56,810 --> 00:04:59,110
如果你们都是正常人这是什么等级的礼物
Well, what's the equivalent gift if you guys were normal?

180
00:04:59,110 --> 00:05:01,440
是星巴克礼品卡还是劳力士
Like, a Starbucks card or a Rolex?

181
00:05:01,800 --> 00:05:04,380
大概相当于一架很棒的显微镜吧
Kind of like a really nice microscope.

182
00:05:04,380 --> 00:05:05,590
说了也白说
You're not helping.

183
00:05:05,590 --> 00:05:09,330
我还以为书呆子的周年纪念应该是呼吸器
I thought the gift for a first nerd anniversary was inhaler.

184
00:05:11,440 --> 00:05:12,360
你们老爸呢
Where's your dad?

185
00:05:12,360 --> 00:05:13,850
在楼上  怎么了
Upstairs. Why?

186
00:05:15,720 --> 00:05:16,700
你给我们买了狗
You got us a dog?!

187
00:05:16,700 --> 00:05:18,540
不  它只是迷路了
No, no! It's a stray,

188
00:05:18,540 --> 00:05:19,620
我们不会留下它的
and we are not keeping him.

189
00:05:19,620 --> 00:05:20,500
安静点
Be quiet.

190
00:05:20,500 --> 00:05:22,350
别让你们老爸知道
Your dad cannot know he's here.

191
00:05:22,730 --> 00:05:24,090
他要是看到一定会喜欢上它
If he sees him, he'll get all attached,

192
00:05:24,090 --> 00:05:25,370
我们就不可能把它送走了
and there's no getting rid of it.

193
00:05:25,370 --> 00:05:27,230
就跟卢克一样
Oh, it'll be like Luke all over again.

194
00:05:27,230 --> 00:05:29,160
至少他们有我的时候已经结婚了
At least they were married when they had me.

195
00:05:29,160 --> 00:05:30,320
你毁了妈妈的生活
You ruined mom's life.

196
00:05:30,320 --> 00:05:33,670
停  我现在很高兴有你们
Stop. I am now very happy I have all of you.

197
00:05:33,670 --> 00:05:35,490
可是我没办法再多照顾一个生物了
But I just can't take care of another living creature.

198
00:05:35,490 --> 00:05:36,630
那你为什么还带它回家
Then why'd you bring it home?

199
00:05:36,630 --> 00:05:38,140
我没法把它留在街上
I couldn't leave it in the street.

200
00:05:38,140 --> 00:05:39,670
克莱尔  是你吗
Claire, is that you?

201
00:05:39,860 --> 00:05:40,530
照顾好它
Take care of it.

202
00:05:40,530 --> 00:05:42,270
我不会把狗狗养死的
I'm not gonna kill a dog.

203
00:05:42,510 --> 00:05:43,890
把它藏进你房间
Hide it in your room.

204
00:05:44,630 --> 00:05:45,690
是像我想的一样吗
Is that what I think it is? 

205
00:05:45,690 --> 00:05:47,310
不是
Uh, no.

206
00:05:47,310 --> 00:05:49,010
没错  披萨到了
Yeah, pizza's here.

207
00:05:49,840 --> 00:05:50,630
你好
How you doing?

208
00:05:52,700 --> 00:05:53,570
你们干嘛呢
What was that?

209
00:05:55,640 --> 00:05:57,940
我是披萨怪
I'm the pizza monster!

210
00:05:57,950 --> 00:05:59,950
这是我的新角色
It's this new character I'm doing.

211
00:06:00,000 --> 00:06:02,760
我喜欢  我真的很喜欢
I love it. I really love it.

212
00:06:02,780 --> 00:06:04,370
我其实不怎么喜欢
I didn't really love it.

213
00:06:04,370 --> 00:06:06,920
感觉跟我的"鸡锅海盗"有点像
It felt a little close to my Chicken Pot Pirate.

214
00:06:07,330 --> 00:06:09,250
那是个不解之谜
It's a mystery.

215
00:06:10,140 --> 00:06:11,010
那是谁
Who's that?

216
00:06:11,560 --> 00:06:14,780
诺尼  可以隐身
Noni. She can be invisible.

217
00:06:14,790 --> 00:06:15,640
那又是谁
Who's that? 

218
00:06:15,640 --> 00:06:16,670
勾勾
Gogo.

219
00:06:16,670 --> 00:06:19,680
他能跳下高楼
He can jump off of buildings.

220
00:06:19,960 --> 00:06:22,670
这是我看过最不现实的节目
This is the most unrealistic show I've ever seen.

221
00:06:23,120 --> 00:06:24,220
那又是谁
Who's that?

222
00:06:24,300 --> 00:06:26,370
是  太好了  我现在开大门
Yes, great. I will open the gate.

223
00:06:26,870 --> 00:06:29,000
瑞斯  可能连修门都不会
Reece. Probably can't even work a gate.

224
00:06:29,010 --> 00:06:30,090
你可能会喜欢他
Maybe you'll like him.

225
00:06:30,090 --> 00:06:31,530
他是国王的牙医
He's the Kings' dentist.

226
00:06:31,530 --> 00:06:34,270
那我还是皇帝的橱柜制造商呢
Well, hoity-toity. I'm the emperor's closet maker.

227
00:06:34,270 --> 00:06:36,270
洛杉矶国王冰球队
The L.A. Kings hockey team.

228
00:06:34,270 --> 00:06:36,270
{\an8}冰球规则允许打架  运动员也因此经常缺牙烂嘴

229
00:06:36,270 --> 00:06:37,660
国王的牙医  为什么他要这么说
Kings' dentist. Why does he say it like that?

230
00:06:37,660 --> 00:06:39,080
因为这样听起来很酷炫吗
What, is he trying to be all fancy?

231
00:06:39,080 --> 00:06:41,280
他什么都没说  是我说的
He didn't say anything. I said it.

232
00:06:43,620 --> 00:06:44,540
-你好  -你好
- Hello. - Hi.

233
00:06:44,540 --> 00:06:47,560
戴娜  瑞斯  这是我先生杰
Dana, Reece, this is my husband, Jay.

234
00:06:47,590 --> 00:06:49,040
-你好  瑞斯  -你好  杰
- Hi, Reece. How are you? - Hey, Jay.

235
00:06:49,040 --> 00:06:50,460
戴娜  跟我来厨房吧
Dana, come with me to the kitchen

236
00:06:50,470 --> 00:06:52,550
让男生们互相了解一下
while the boys get to know each other.

237
00:06:52,550 --> 00:06:53,380
好
All right.

238
00:06:53,740 --> 00:06:54,840
你听说了吗
Did you hear they're thinking

239
00:06:54,840 --> 00:06:57,070
他们在考虑在学校里禁脏话
of eliminating cursive at the school?

240
00:06:57,070 --> 00:06:59,060
所有脏话  还是艹字头那个
All of it, or just the "F" Word?

241
00:06:59,060 --> 00:07:00,640
我给你带了瓶威士忌
I brought you some Scotch.

242
00:07:01,070 --> 00:07:02,840
这瓶是好酒  谢谢
That's quite a bottle. Thank you.

243
00:07:04,320 --> 00:07:06,160
歌洛莉亚跟我说你是国王队的牙医
Gloria tells me you're the Kings' dentist.

244
00:07:06,160 --> 00:07:09,360
你提到这个的态度感觉好拽
Well, when you say it like that, it sounds so hoity-toity.

245
00:07:09,360 --> 00:07:10,620
不如把酒开了吧
Why don't we crack that open?

246
00:07:10,630 --> 00:07:12,740
你这有古巴高希霸罗拔图雪茄吗
And do you have any Cohiba Robustos?

247
00:07:12,740 --> 00:07:15,380
我也想有  可是这牌子基本找不到了
Oh, I wish, but, you know, they're impossible to find.

248
00:07:15,600 --> 00:07:17,420
瞧瞧看
Well, look at that.

249
00:07:17,450 --> 00:07:18,910
我刚找到两支
I just found two.

250
00:07:20,160 --> 00:07:21,600
好吧  这人还挺不错的
Okay, the guy wasn't all bad, 

251
00:07:21,600 --> 00:07:23,310
可我不能让歌洛莉亚知道
but I couldn't let Gloria know

252
00:07:23,310 --> 00:07:25,810
不然她就会开始逼我去做一大堆
or it would open the door for a whole bunch of new things

253
00:07:25,810 --> 00:07:26,800
我不想做的事
I don't want to do --

254
00:07:26,800 --> 00:07:28,190
比如试新餐厅
Trendy restaurants,

255
00:07:28,190 --> 00:07:30,600
关于女性一些无聊事情感觉的电影
movies about how women feel about crap.

256
00:07:30,600 --> 00:07:31,840
谁需要那些啊
And who needs it?

257
00:07:32,930 --> 00:07:34,560
如果这周还不够惨的话
As if this week wasn't bad enough,

258
00:07:34,560 --> 00:07:37,560
我们在布鲁塞尔的硬件供应商又变卦了
now my hardware supplier in Brussels is flip-flopping.

259
00:07:37,770 --> 00:07:40,550
看来你最近吉卦不怎么多啊
Sounds like you're dealing with a real Belgian waffle.

260
00:07:42,470 --> 00:07:43,480
那是狗叫吗
Is that a dog?

261
00:07:43,490 --> 00:07:45,340
什么  不是
What? No.

262
00:07:47,250 --> 00:07:48,350
听起来像狗叫
That sounds like a dog.

263
00:07:48,350 --> 00:07:49,920
为了不听我说话
You will do anything

264
00:07:49,920 --> 00:07:52,630
你什么事情都做得出来  对吗
to avoid hearing me talk about work, won't you?

265
00:07:52,630 --> 00:07:56,540
我要下楼冷静一下
I'm -- I'm just gonna go cool off downstairs. Yep.

266
00:07:58,020 --> 00:07:58,900
亲爱的
Honey?

267
00:07:59,120 --> 00:08:00,230
她说的没错
She is right.

268
00:08:00,230 --> 00:08:02,020
有时候我不想听她说话
Sometimes I don't listen.

269
00:08:02,780 --> 00:08:05,020
她是这么说的对吧  我不听她说话
That's what she said, right? I don't listen?

270
00:08:05,520 --> 00:08:06,920
你怎么出来了
Did you get out?

271
00:08:06,930 --> 00:08:08,800
快过来
Oh, come on, now.

272
00:08:09,840 --> 00:08:10,740
亲爱的
Honey?

273
00:08:11,950 --> 00:08:12,950
甜心
Sweetheart?   

274
00:08:13,920 --> 00:08:15,450
我很抱歉
I am so sorry.

275
00:08:15,450 --> 00:08:18,160
没关系  菲尔  你回去睡吧
It's fine, Phil, really. Just go back to bed.

276
00:08:21,430 --> 00:08:24,110
我只是需要一点时间静一静
I just... need some time to myself.

277
00:08:24,480 --> 00:08:26,590
你一哭我也想哭了
Y-You know I cry when you cry.

278
00:08:27,110 --> 00:08:28,430
我会上楼的
I'll be upstairs.

279
00:08:30,440 --> 00:08:31,190
你没事吧
You okay?

280
00:08:31,190 --> 00:08:33,150
只是  最近太多事了
It's just -- It's been a lot.

281
00:08:34,080 --> 00:08:35,040
我爱你
I love you.

282
00:08:42,390 --> 00:08:43,980
戴克斯  你好吗
Hey, Dex. How are you?

283
00:08:44,750 --> 00:08:45,620
你没事吧
You okay?

284
00:08:45,620 --> 00:08:47,910
我没事  在欣赏你们的花园而已
Yeah, I was just admiring your garden.

285
00:08:47,910 --> 00:08:49,150
快进来吧
Hey, come on in.

286
00:08:49,800 --> 00:08:52,410
其他人呢
So, uh, where is the rest of the gang?

287
00:08:52,410 --> 00:08:54,370
参加祷告晨跑了
Oh, they're out on a prayer jog. 

288
00:08:54,810 --> 00:08:56,450
我不太喜欢
It's not really my thing.

289
00:08:57,100 --> 00:08:58,660
会经常发生吗
Is -- Is that something that happens a lot

290
00:08:58,660 --> 00:09:00,830
你觉得自己格格不入的情况
where -- where you feel different?

291
00:09:00,830 --> 00:09:01,810
你好吗  德克斯
Hi, Dex.

292
00:09:01,830 --> 00:09:02,420
米奇尔
Hey, Mitchell.  

293
00:09:02,420 --> 00:09:04,840
能不能过来帮我个忙  很快就好
Can I have you help me over here for just a second?

294
00:09:04,840 --> 00:09:05,970
好吧
Uh, okay.

295
00:09:08,870 --> 00:09:09,510
你在干什么
What are you doing?

296
00:09:09,510 --> 00:09:11,360
他明摆着想寻求帮助
He was clearly reaching out.

297
00:09:11,360 --> 00:09:12,790
他在欣赏我们的花园
He was admiring our garden.

298
00:09:12,790 --> 00:09:14,000
没人会欣赏我们的花园 
Nobody admires our garden.

299
00:09:14,000 --> 00:09:16,350
里面只有颗粘着购物袋的死仙人掌
It's a dead cactus with a grocery bag stuck to it.

300
00:09:16,350 --> 00:09:17,330
你怎么回事
What is going on with you?

301
00:09:17,330 --> 00:09:18,390
你不是一直不想
You're the one who never wants

302
00:09:18,390 --> 00:09:19,890
掺和别人的生活吗
to get involved in people's lives.

303
00:09:19,890 --> 00:09:20,690
你看不出来吗
Don't you see?

304
00:09:20,690 --> 00:09:22,300
他觉得被那些人困住了
He feels trapped by those guys.

305
00:09:22,300 --> 00:09:23,940
那些借《圣经》的名义干涉别人生活的坏蛋吗
Oh, the big, bad Bible thumpers?

306
00:09:23,950 --> 00:09:24,940
又来了
Here we go again.

307
00:09:24,940 --> 00:09:27,050
我只是说可以把他的歌
I'm just saying you could read his song

308
00:09:27,050 --> 00:09:28,490
《求助》
"A Cry for Help"

309
00:09:28,830 --> 00:09:29,880
解读成是求助
as a cry for help.

310
00:09:29,880 --> 00:09:33,610
米奇尔  你被传教士逼到湖里去了
Mitchell, I'm sorry you got chased into a lake,

311
00:09:34,030 --> 00:09:35,350
我认识的一些最善良最有爱
but some of the kindest, most loving,

312
00:09:35,350 --> 00:09:39,730
最慷慨的人都是信教的
generous people I've ever known were churchgoers.

313
00:09:39,900 --> 00:09:40,710
我就...
Just...

314
00:09:40,780 --> 00:09:41,600
别...
Come --

315
00:09:43,060 --> 00:09:45,880
戴克斯  我能不能发表一下个人见解
Hey, Dex, do you mind if I make a personal observation?

316
00:09:45,880 --> 00:09:48,490
如果是想说我的翘臀  怪我妈咯
If it's about my hips, blame my mother.

317
00:09:48,490 --> 00:09:50,190
不  不
No, no.

318
00:09:50,710 --> 00:09:52,730
是关于你昨天唱的歌
It's -- It's about the song that you sang yesterday.

319
00:09:52,730 --> 00:09:55,220
你似乎是想表达
It seemed like you were trying to express something --

320
00:09:55,220 --> 00:09:56,890
你的感受
some feelings you might be having

321
00:09:56,890 --> 00:09:59,060
而这些感受似乎
that you think might not be met with approval

322
00:09:59,060 --> 00:10:01,060
没有被你们的"小团体"认可
from your..."community."

323
00:10:01,060 --> 00:10:03,220
或者就只是首歌
Or it's just a song.

324
00:10:03,480 --> 00:10:06,010
跟他自身情况毫无关联
Has nothing to do with his personal situation.

325
00:10:06,010 --> 00:10:07,120
不  是有关联的
No, it does.  

326
00:10:07,850 --> 00:10:09,240
不好意思  你的痛是真真切切的
I'm -- I'm sorry. Your pain is real.

327
00:10:09,240 --> 00:10:11,130
我只是觉得好有负罪感
I just feel so guilty.

328
00:10:11,130 --> 00:10:12,710
我知道大家会很失望
I know people will be disappointed.

329
00:10:12,710 --> 00:10:14,220
别  别  不要有负罪感
No, no, don't feel guilty.

330
00:10:14,230 --> 00:10:17,590
听着  第一步就是要大声说出来
Look, the first step is to say it out loud.

331
00:10:19,300 --> 00:10:20,900
我不想当鼓手
I don't want to be a drummer.

332
00:10:21,300 --> 00:10:23,640
好  继续说
Okay, now say the other thing.

333
00:10:24,320 --> 00:10:26,630
我不想再呆在乐队里了
I don't want to be in a band anymore.

334
00:10:26,630 --> 00:10:27,800
我好想家
I miss home.

335
00:10:27,800 --> 00:10:29,630
好想我的女友
I miss my girlfriend.

336
00:10:29,630 --> 00:10:31,220
-抱歉  什么  -抱歉  你的什么
- I'm sorry. Whoa. What? - I'm sorry. Your what?

337
00:10:31,450 --> 00:10:34,070
感觉心里一下释然了
It's like a weight has been lifted.

338
00:10:35,030 --> 00:10:37,230
太感谢你们了
Thank you so much, guys.

339
00:10:37,720 --> 00:10:40,040
我今天本想呆在里面的
You know, I was just gonna stay inside today,

340
00:10:40,040 --> 00:10:43,330
还好出来了
but I'm really glad I came out.

341
00:10:45,060 --> 00:10:46,410
他才不是想说那些
He doesn't get to say that.

342
00:10:47,630 --> 00:10:48,530
乔
Oh, hey, Joe.

343
00:10:48,530 --> 00:10:50,250
现在在播新一集《神秘孩纸》
Uh, there's a new "Mystery Kidz" on.

344
00:10:50,260 --> 00:10:51,170
我不看了  谢谢
No, thanks.

345
00:10:51,170 --> 00:10:52,080
"我不看了  谢谢"
"No, thanks"?

346
00:10:52,080 --> 00:10:54,400
你难道不好奇谁偷了普可的魔法翅膀吗
Aren't you curious who stole Poco's magic wings?

347
00:10:54,400 --> 00:10:55,350
没什么兴趣
Not really.

348
00:10:55,350 --> 00:10:56,840
可是每个人都有嫌疑
But everyone's a suspect.

349
00:10:56,840 --> 00:10:58,280
钟表匠讨厌普可
The watchmaker hates Poco,

350
00:10:58,280 --> 00:11:00,290
布丁市长会不惜一切手段留任
and Mayor Pudding would do anything to stay in office.

351
00:11:00,290 --> 00:11:02,160
你怎么会不想看接下来发生了什么呢
How could you not want to see what happens?

352
00:11:06,120 --> 00:11:06,880
喂
Hello?

353
00:11:07,260 --> 00:11:08,400
对  等等
Uh, yes. Hold on.

354
00:11:08,700 --> 00:11:10,220
杰  是瑞斯
Jay, it's Reece.

355
00:11:11,260 --> 00:11:12,050
你看  歌洛莉亚
You see, Gloria?

356
00:11:12,050 --> 00:11:13,340
现在他开始给我打电话了
Now he's calling me.

357
00:11:13,520 --> 00:11:15,040
我怕的就是这个
This is what I was afraid of.

358
00:11:15,040 --> 00:11:16,000
他打电话来了
He called.

359
00:11:16,000 --> 00:11:17,480
我的新朋友打电话了
My new friend called.

360
00:11:17,630 --> 00:11:19,280
要带我去看冰球比赛
He's taking me to a hockey game.

361
00:11:19,280 --> 00:11:20,150
太棒了
Great.

362
00:11:20,360 --> 00:11:23,610
现在我非得跟瑞斯去一个什么无聊的慈善活动
Now I'm stuck going to some boring charity event with Reece.

363
00:11:23,610 --> 00:11:25,110
你看你妈给我惹的好事
You see what your mom got me into?

364
00:11:25,110 --> 00:11:26,830
杰  别这样  开明点
Jay, come on. Keep an open mind.

365
00:11:26,830 --> 00:11:29,830
我们只是觉得要给瑞斯一个机会
All we're saying is give Reece a chance.

366
00:11:32,660 --> 00:11:33,680
雷克斯
Rex.

367
00:11:33,740 --> 00:11:34,790
史都比
Scooby.

368
00:11:35,070 --> 00:11:35,890
克利福德
Clifford.

369
00:11:35,900 --> 00:11:36,730
你在干吗
What are you doing?

370
00:11:36,730 --> 00:11:38,070
猜它的名字
Trying to figure out his name.

371
00:11:38,070 --> 00:11:39,030
你考虑过老爸吗
What about Dad?

372
00:11:39,030 --> 00:11:39,830
给  老爸
Here, Dad. 

373
00:11:40,380 --> 00:11:40,910
不是
Nope.

374
00:11:40,910 --> 00:11:42,560
不用猜他的名字
You do not need to figure out his name

375
00:11:42,560 --> 00:11:44,270
因为我们要去贴启示
because we're going to put these fliers up,

376
00:11:42,560 --> 00:11:45,060
{\an8}寻主启示

377
00:11:44,270 --> 00:11:45,490
就会有人打电话来了
and someone's gonna call.

378
00:11:45,790 --> 00:11:48,400
我给桑杰的恐龙化石呢
What happened to the dinosaur bone I got for Sanjay?

379
00:11:48,400 --> 00:11:49,980
我看到史努比
I saw Snoop...

380
00:11:51,350 --> 00:11:52,800
在后院埋东西
burying something in the backyard.

381
00:11:52,800 --> 00:11:54,340
你什么都没做吗
And you didn't do anything?

382
00:11:54,350 --> 00:11:55,690
我帮它开了门
I opened the door for him.

383
00:11:55,690 --> 00:11:57,630
那块化石有6500万年的历史
That bone lasted 65 million years,

384
00:11:57,630 --> 00:11:59,400
在这个家居然撑不过一天
and it can't even last one day in this house?!

385
00:11:59,410 --> 00:12:01,500
-克莱尔  -我的天  你爸来了
- Claire. - Oh, my God, your father!

386
00:12:01,500 --> 00:12:03,380
狗  带出去  出去
The dog -- outside! Outside! Outside! 

387
00:12:03,740 --> 00:12:04,420
怎么了  亲爱的
Yeah, honey?

388
00:12:04,420 --> 00:12:06,480
甜心  昨晚的事
Sweetheart, about last night.  

389
00:12:06,570 --> 00:12:08,860
我没用这俩耳朵认真听你说话
Because I didn't listen with these two ears...

390
00:12:08,860 --> 00:12:09,370
对
Yes.

391
00:12:09,370 --> 00:12:13,190
我想用这些郁金香[俩嘴唇]道歉
I want to apologize with these tu-lips.

392
00:12:13,190 --> 00:12:15,600
太...  你太好了
Oh, that is very -- That's so sweet of you.

393
00:12:15,600 --> 00:12:16,790
谢谢你  宝贝
Thank you, baby.

394
00:12:17,830 --> 00:12:21,060
太好了  那是玉米片渣吗
Great. Oh, is that a tortilla chip right there?

395
00:12:21,060 --> 00:12:21,890
就那
Yeah --  

396
00:12:21,990 --> 00:12:23,390
你好吗  昨天的朋友
Hola, amigo from yesterday.

397
00:12:23,390 --> 00:12:24,760
你不会要吃吧
You're not gonna eat that, are you?

398
00:12:24,760 --> 00:12:26,160
才不  多恶心
No, that would be disgusting.

399
00:12:26,160 --> 00:12:27,190
这是啥
What are these?

400
00:12:27,190 --> 00:12:28,640
那个是  是
Oh, that's a -- It's a...

401
00:12:29,350 --> 00:12:30,320
蛋白质零食
It's a protein snack.

402
00:12:30,320 --> 00:12:31,280
不喜欢的话就别吃了
You don't have to eat that if you don't like it. 

403
00:12:31,280 --> 00:12:32,080
不会
No.

404
00:12:32,330 --> 00:12:33,150
我喜欢  好吃
I like it. Good.

405
00:12:33,150 --> 00:12:35,090
有肝味[活力]
It's -- It's liver-y.

406
00:12:36,550 --> 00:12:38,220
你太会照顾我们了
You take such good care of us.

407
00:12:38,220 --> 00:12:39,180
谢谢  亲爱的
Thanks, honey.

408
00:12:39,180 --> 00:12:40,450
我们应该把花放到花瓶里
We should get those flowers in a a vase.

409
00:12:40,460 --> 00:12:41,310
不  菲尔
No, Phil.  

410
00:12:41,310 --> 00:12:42,750
别用那个花瓶
Not that vase.

411
00:12:42,750 --> 00:12:43,820
看着我
Look at me!

412
00:12:44,140 --> 00:12:46,060
好好看着我
Really look at me.

413
00:12:46,460 --> 00:12:47,750
我觉得我在看啊
I feel like I am.

414
00:12:49,210 --> 00:12:50,860
你还是不明白  对吧
You're just not getting it, are you?

415
00:12:50,860 --> 00:12:53,850
对不起  我想一个人待会
I'm sorry. I need some alone time.

416
00:12:59,490 --> 00:13:01,860
抱歉一直敲你家门
Sorry for knocking on your door so persistently,

417
00:13:01,870 --> 00:13:03,820
可我们找不到戴克斯了
but we can't find Dex,

418
00:13:03,820 --> 00:13:05,300
他的行李也不见了
and all his matching luggage is gone.

419
00:13:05,310 --> 00:13:07,140
你们知道他去哪了吗
Do you have any idea where he is?

420
00:13:07,730 --> 00:13:08,610
我...  我不知道  米奇尔
I don-- I don't know, Mitchell.

421
00:13:08,610 --> 00:13:10,670
最后跟他说话的是你吧
Weren't you the last person to talk to him?

422
00:13:10,670 --> 00:13:11,910
我们的时间不多了
And we haven't got much time.

423
00:13:11,910 --> 00:13:12,730
要是我们没有鼓手
If we don't have a drummer,

424
00:13:12,730 --> 00:13:14,020
就得被迫取消演出
we're gonna have to cancel the gig.

425
00:13:14,030 --> 00:13:16,610
我主行事  凡人莫测
Well, the Lord works in mysterious ways.

426
00:13:16,610 --> 00:13:18,200
-打住...  -我...
- Don't even... - I...

427
00:13:18,910 --> 00:13:19,990
真是毁灭性打击
Aah, this is devastating.

428
00:13:19,990 --> 00:13:21,330
如果我们不演出  就拿不到报酬
If we don't play, we won't get paid,

429
00:13:21,330 --> 00:13:22,860
也就没有足够的钱回家了
and we don't have enough money to get home.

430
00:13:22,860 --> 00:13:25,070
你们不明白戴克斯正在经历什么
Hey, you don't know what Dex is going through.

431
00:13:25,070 --> 00:13:27,440
人务须遵从本性
One hath to be true to the way one was born.

432
00:13:27,440 --> 00:13:29,280
得了  你不能随便加个"务须"
Okay, you can't just add "Hath"

433
00:13:29,280 --> 00:13:30,730
就假装是《圣经》里的话
and pretend it was in the Bible.

434
00:13:30,730 --> 00:13:33,490
我想我们得打电话给音乐厅取消演出了
Well, I guess we better call the venue and cancel the gig.

435
00:13:33,490 --> 00:13:35,630
天啊  好了  你懂的
Oh, boy, well, you know.

436
00:13:36,930 --> 00:13:37,940
我可以做你们的鼓手
I could be your drummer.

437
00:13:37,950 --> 00:13:39,200
上帝啊  又来了
Oh, God, here we go.

438
00:13:39,200 --> 00:13:40,570
真的吗  你会打鼓 
Really? You play?

439
00:13:40,570 --> 00:13:41,620
我对上面那位发誓
Swear to G-dash-D.

440
00:13:42,130 --> 00:13:44,670
来几段音乐试试  我能跟上节奏
Just play me a few bars. I can pick it up, follow along.

441
00:13:45,410 --> 00:13:47,650
卡梅伦先生  太感谢你了
Mr. Cameron, thank you so much.

442
00:13:47,860 --> 00:13:50,760
你让我想起某个重要的人
You kind of remind me of another special someone

443
00:13:51,000 --> 00:13:53,170
他曾为我们做出重大牺牲
who made a pretty big sacrifice to save us.

444
00:13:53,170 --> 00:13:54,450
拜托  别把我比作你的...
Please, do not compare me to your...

445
00:13:54,450 --> 00:13:56,220
是伯尼·考夫曼先生  我们的经纪人
Mr. Bernie Kaufman, our manager.

446
00:13:56,220 --> 00:13:58,860
他烧了他的鞋店[骗保险]赞助我们首张唱片小样
He burnt down his shoe store to pay for our first demo.

447
00:14:02,550 --> 00:14:02,890
你在干嘛呢
what are you doing?

448
00:14:02,890 --> 00:14:03,770
天啊 你快把狗抱走
Oh, God, you take the dog,

449
00:14:03,770 --> 00:14:04,910
我把这收拾干净  好吗
and I'll clean this up, okay?

450
00:14:04,910 --> 00:14:05,560
好
Okay.

451
00:14:05,560 --> 00:14:08,530
亲爱的 我找了几个备选花瓶
Honey, I got some vase options.

452
00:14:10,650 --> 00:14:11,880
怎么回事
What happened?

453
00:14:13,170 --> 00:14:14,910
你觉得是怎么回事
what do you think happened?

454
00:14:14,910 --> 00:14:16,410
我觉得她认为送花道歉
I think she saw those flowers as the shallow

455
00:14:16,410 --> 00:14:17,950
是种肤浅的行为
transparent gesture they were

456
00:14:17,950 --> 00:14:20,840
她有理由一气之下把它们撕烂
and shredded them to pieces in a justifiable rage.

457
00:14:21,750 --> 00:14:22,460
没错
Yep.

458
00:14:22,860 --> 00:14:24,670
我做了什么事让她这么生气
What have I done to upset her so much?

459
00:14:24,670 --> 00:14:26,330
也许你照照镜子
Maybe you should look in a mirror

460
00:14:26,330 --> 00:14:28,080
就能回答自己的问题了
and ask yourself that question.

461
00:14:31,100 --> 00:14:33,780
我的老天啊  瞧我变成什么人了
Sweet Teen Wolf, what have I become?

462
00:14:35,670 --> 00:14:36,790
看见那家伙了吗
You see that guy?

463
00:14:36,940 --> 00:14:38,700
我在他的牙上下了不少功夫
I have done so much work on his mouth

464
00:14:38,700 --> 00:14:41,200
花费足够付我船上的热水浴缸
that he's paid for the hot tub on my boat.

465
00:14:43,520 --> 00:14:45,360
科皮塔刚才是跟你招手吗
Did Kopitar just wave to you?

466
00:14:45,370 --> 00:14:46,400
那可不
It's the least he can do.

467
00:14:46,400 --> 00:14:49,390
这周末我要带他去卡特琳娜钓鱼
I'm taking him out fishing this weekend in Catalina.

468
00:14:49,490 --> 00:14:51,030
你想来吗
Hey, hey, do you want to come?

469
00:14:51,030 --> 00:14:52,700
天啊  我当然很愿意去
Oh, my God, I'd love to go.

470
00:14:53,410 --> 00:14:54,790
-不过...  -怎么了
- Oh, but... - What?

471
00:14:54,790 --> 00:14:56,990
昨晚你来之前
Last night, before you got there,

472
00:14:57,170 --> 00:14:58,600
歌洛莉亚和我大吵了一架
Gloria and I got in a big to-do

473
00:14:58,610 --> 00:15:00,710
因为我不想认识新朋友
about me not needing new friends.

474
00:15:01,560 --> 00:15:03,610
现在你不愿意承认自己错了
And now you don't want to admit you were wrong.

475
00:15:03,830 --> 00:15:06,230
你真懂我
Wow, do you get me.

476
00:15:06,310 --> 00:15:09,650
这会儿应该是观赏鲸鱼的好天气
Well, it's supposed to be perfect whale-watching weather,

477
00:15:09,650 --> 00:15:11,060
还有  对了
and, uh, oh, yeah,

478
00:15:11,060 --> 00:15:12,380
格雷斯基也会来
Gretzky's coming, too.

479
00:15:12,380 --> 00:15:13,220
有名的那个吗
The Great One?

480
00:15:13,220 --> 00:15:15,290
他不跟人分享望远镜  这点倒臭名昭著
Not at sharing the binoculars, he isn't.

481
00:15:15,290 --> 00:15:16,950
真要命  我去不了
It's killing me I can't go!

482
00:15:16,950 --> 00:15:18,670
我有个疯狂的主意
Well, here's a crazy idea.

483
00:15:18,990 --> 00:15:21,510
你干嘛不对你妻子实话实话
Why don't you tell your wife the truth

484
00:15:21,510 --> 00:15:23,140
承认你错了
and admit you were wrong?

485
00:15:23,670 --> 00:15:25,290
你没我想的那么懂我
You don't get me like I thought you did.

486
00:15:25,290 --> 00:15:26,250
要不然呢
Or...?

487
00:15:26,360 --> 00:15:27,680
好吧  我会跟她说实话的
Fine. I'll level with her.

488
00:15:33,110 --> 00:15:34,390
你是怎么回事啊
What is going on?

489
00:15:36,880 --> 00:15:38,050
太好了  不是老爸
Ohh, good, you're not Dad.

490
00:15:38,260 --> 00:15:39,990
你和桑杰进展得怎么样
So, how'd it go with Sanjay?

491
00:15:39,990 --> 00:15:41,680
他记得你们的纪念日吗
Did he remember your anniversary?

492
00:15:41,740 --> 00:15:42,800
你说呢
You tell me.

493
00:15:42,870 --> 00:15:44,190
我把化石送给他之后
After I gave him the fossil,

494
00:15:44,190 --> 00:15:47,500
他给了我这只箱子作为斯坦福浪漫周末的礼物
 he gave me this for romantic weekends up at Stanford.

495
00:15:47,930 --> 00:15:49,740
看起来像是二手货
It looks kind of used.

496
00:15:50,010 --> 00:15:51,420
你觉得有没有可能他忘了
Do you think it's possible he forgot

497
00:15:51,420 --> 00:15:52,360
只是随手拿了一件东西...
and just grabbed the first thing that he's...

498
00:15:52,360 --> 00:15:53,380
闭嘴  他爱我的
Shut up! He loves me!

499
00:15:53,380 --> 00:15:55,940
真不敢相信连一个电话都没有
I can't believe i haven't gotten a single call.

500
00:15:55,940 --> 00:15:58,120
我已经贴出无数启示了
I must have put up a thousand fliers.

501
00:16:01,390 --> 00:16:02,690
大伙好啊
Hey, guys.

502
00:16:03,570 --> 00:16:04,740
亲爱的
Honey.

503
00:16:05,920 --> 00:16:07,690
-克莱尔  -在
-Claire. -Yeah.

504
00:16:07,690 --> 00:16:08,760
我想跟你谈谈
I want to talk to you.

505
00:16:09,490 --> 00:16:10,960
我真的很抱歉
I am so sorry.

506
00:16:11,680 --> 00:16:12,720
我不听你说话
I don't listen.

507
00:16:12,980 --> 00:16:15,120
光想靠送花解决问题
I try to solve problems with flowers.

508
00:16:15,120 --> 00:16:17,540
还在朋友面前捏造你的负面形象
I do unflattering impressions of you for my friends.

509
00:16:17,540 --> 00:16:20,130
最糟糕的是  我放任自己
And worst of all, I let myself go.

510
00:16:20,400 --> 00:16:23,070
所以我刮了胡子  换了衣服
So I shaved and put on a suit.

511
00:16:23,280 --> 00:16:24,570
亲爱的
Oh, honey.

512
00:16:24,780 --> 00:16:25,730
那是什么
What's that?

513
00:16:25,810 --> 00:16:26,670
什么
What?

514
00:16:27,690 --> 00:16:29,890
天啊  你收拾了行李
Oh, my God. You packed a suitcase.

515
00:16:29,900 --> 00:16:30,890
你要离开一段时间
You need some time away.

516
00:16:30,890 --> 00:16:32,400
我想我做这一切都...
I guess all this was...

517
00:16:32,400 --> 00:16:33,500
太不够了  也太迟了
too little, too late.

518
00:16:33,500 --> 00:16:35,480
但不包括美黑  做得时间太长  也太黑
Well, not the spray tan. That was too much, too long.

519
00:16:35,490 --> 00:16:37,190
我觉得那个喷嘴坏了
I think the nozzle was broken.

520
00:16:37,420 --> 00:16:40,640
你全都理解错了  都是我不好
You're getting this all wrong, and it's all my fault.

521
00:16:40,640 --> 00:16:41,680
好吧  听着
Okay, look,

522
00:16:41,680 --> 00:16:43,350
我一直拼命躲着你  没错
I have been trying to distract you, yes,

523
00:16:43,350 --> 00:16:46,520
可那是因为我一直在想着对我有好处的事
but because I have been thinking about what was good for me

524
00:16:46,520 --> 00:16:49,000
而不是可能会对你有好处的事
and not what might be good for you.

525
00:16:49,000 --> 00:16:51,060
我不知道
So I have no idea

526
00:16:51,060 --> 00:16:53,720
我们能不能找到它真正的主人
if we're ever gonna find out who his real owner is,

527
00:16:53,720 --> 00:16:56,180
如果找不到的话  你可以养着它
but if we don't, you can keep him.

528
00:16:57,180 --> 00:16:59,210
我为什么要养唐克斯里家的狗
Why would I want the Tanksley's dog?

529
00:16:59,330 --> 00:16:59,870
你说什么
What?

530
00:16:59,880 --> 00:17:00,680
这是巴迪
This is Buddy.

531
00:17:00,680 --> 00:17:02,160
你不知道唐克斯一家搬去克里夫顿了吗
You know the Tanksley's over on Clifton?

532
00:17:02,160 --> 00:17:03,210
我卖掉了他们的房子
I sold them their house.

533
00:17:03,210 --> 00:17:04,270
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.

534
00:17:04,270 --> 00:17:06,710
不过如果你同意我养宠物的话
But if you're open to me getting a pet...

535
00:17:06,710 --> 00:17:08,520
当然同意  养只狗吧
Yeah. Of course. Get a dog.

536
00:17:08,520 --> 00:17:09,230
不  我不想养狗
No, I don't want a dog.

537
00:17:09,230 --> 00:17:10,860
我想养只凤头鹦鹉带去滑旱冰
I want a cockatoo to take Rollerblading.

538
00:17:10,860 --> 00:17:12,540
想象一下  有只凤头鹦鹉站在我肩膀上
How cool would that be sitting on my shoulder

539
00:17:12,540 --> 00:17:13,930
我的衬衫迎风飘动  那得多酷啊
my half shirt flapping in the wind?

540
00:17:13,930 --> 00:17:15,290
你不能养鸟
You're not getting a bird.

541
00:17:15,300 --> 00:17:16,850
-你是认真的吗  -是
- Are you serious? - Yeah.

542
00:17:16,910 --> 00:17:18,330
那些养鸟的人
People that have birds

543
00:17:18,330 --> 00:17:19,680
让鸟站在他们肩膀上到处走
and walk around with them on their shoulders --

544
00:17:19,680 --> 00:17:20,380
他们看起来太可笑了
They look ridiculous.

545
00:17:20,380 --> 00:17:22,330
那完全是为了吸引别人的注意而用力过度
It's obviously a desperate cry for attention.

546
00:17:22,330 --> 00:17:23,240
好吧
Okay.

547
00:17:24,000 --> 00:17:25,950
现在轮到我需要时间静静了
Now I need some time to myself.

548
00:17:29,560 --> 00:17:30,710
你在看什么
What are you doing?

549
00:17:32,230 --> 00:17:32,860
没什么
Nothing.

550
00:17:32,860 --> 00:17:34,780
你在看《神秘孩纸》
You're watching "Mystery Kidz."

551
00:17:34,880 --> 00:17:36,260
你不是说不想看吗
You said you didn't want to.

552
00:17:36,260 --> 00:17:39,960
是不想跟你一起看  你问题太多了
Not with you. You ask too many questions.

553
00:17:40,100 --> 00:17:41,160
你这么说很过分
That's rude.

554
00:17:41,160 --> 00:17:43,300
我可是出于礼貌才看的
I was only watching as a courtesy.

555
00:17:43,430 --> 00:17:44,510
刚发生什么了
What just happened?

556
00:17:44,600 --> 00:17:45,620
等等  那是谁
Wait, who's that?

557
00:17:46,180 --> 00:17:47,220
歌洛莉亚
Gloria.

558
00:17:47,550 --> 00:17:49,080
慈善会怎么样
How was the charity event?

559
00:17:49,080 --> 00:17:50,910
我有话跟你说
I have to talk to you about something.

560
00:17:51,480 --> 00:17:52,390
怎么了
What?

561
00:17:52,500 --> 00:17:54,420
我要跟你说声对不起
I owe you an apology.

562
00:17:55,250 --> 00:17:57,250
我这周末要去克利夫兰
I have to go to Cleveland this weekend

563
00:17:57,250 --> 00:17:58,610
参加一个姑妈的葬礼
for my Aunt Bea's funeral.

564
00:17:58,610 --> 00:17:59,420
很慈祥的一个老太太
Nice old lady.

565
00:17:59,420 --> 00:18:00,410
她从悬崖上摔下去了
Fell off a cliff.

566
00:18:00,410 --> 00:18:02,790
我和你一起去  我马上去收拾行李
I'll -- I'll go with you. I'll start packing right now.

567
00:18:02,790 --> 00:18:04,870
不  你跟乔和曼尼留在这儿
No, no, no. You stay here with Joe and Manny.

568
00:18:04,870 --> 00:18:06,390
我会寄个雪花玻璃球给你
I'll send you a snow globe.

569
00:18:06,390 --> 00:18:07,870
我们有多余的望远镜吗
Hey, did we have an extra pair of binoculars?

570
00:18:07,870 --> 00:18:09,260
我看到外面有只奇怪的鸟
I saw a weird bird outside.

571
00:18:09,260 --> 00:18:10,900
别再撒谎了
Stop with the lies.

572
00:18:10,910 --> 00:18:12,690
我真搞不懂男人
I really don't understand men.

573
00:18:12,840 --> 00:18:15,730
你就不能直接承认你错了吗
Why can't you just admit that you were wrong?

574
00:18:16,130 --> 00:18:17,250
这又不是缺点
It's not a weakness.

575
00:18:17,250 --> 00:18:18,140
这是个优点
It's a strength,

576
00:18:18,140 --> 00:18:20,820
我会因此更爱你  更尊重你
and I would love you and respect you more.

577
00:18:20,830 --> 00:18:21,760
好吧
Fine.

578
00:18:22,090 --> 00:18:24,570
我喜欢瑞斯  我想和他出去玩[私奔]
I like Reece, and I want to go away with him.

579
00:18:24,570 --> 00:18:25,700
我就知道
I knew it!

580
00:18:25,700 --> 00:18:27,700
我是对的  你是错的
I was right, and you were wrong!

581
00:18:28,150 --> 00:18:31,340
从现在开始  我们要不断尝试新事物
From now on, we're gonna do new things all the time.

582
00:18:31,350 --> 00:18:33,560
明天我们去埃塞俄比亚餐厅吃饭
Tomorrow we're going to an Ethiopian restaurant,

583
00:18:33,560 --> 00:18:34,810
然后去看部电影
and then we're gonna watch a movie

584
00:18:34,810 --> 00:18:37,550
那电影讲述了一封迟到30年的情书
about a love letter that arrived 30 years late

585
00:18:37,550 --> 00:18:39,520
改变了两个女人一生的故事
and changed the life of two women.

586
00:18:41,100 --> 00:18:42,090
我能带上瑞斯吗
Can I bring Reece?

587
00:18:42,090 --> 00:18:42,990
不行
No!

588
00:18:44,300 --> 00:18:46,480
{\an8}今夜演出
化水为酒乐队

589
00:18:45,480 --> 00:18:47,490
大家好  我们来一起做表演前祷告吧
Hey, everyone, let's gather for the preshow prayer.

590
00:18:47,490 --> 00:18:49,780
就像麦当娜和她的伴舞们一样
Kind of like Madonna and her backup dancers.

591
00:18:49,780 --> 00:18:51,400
米奇尔先生  你想和我们一起吗
Mr. Mitchell, would you like to join us?

592
00:18:51,400 --> 00:18:52,850
不用了  谢谢
Oh, I'm good. Thank you.

593
00:18:52,850 --> 00:18:53,680
好的
All right.

594
00:18:55,060 --> 00:18:56,110
仁慈的上帝
Heavenly Father,

595
00:18:56,370 --> 00:19:00,790
请保佑我们的粉丝万分喜爱今晚的演出
we ask that you make this show super-amazing for all of our fans,

596
00:19:00,800 --> 00:19:02,110
我们还要为戴克斯祈祷
and we pray for Dex.

597
00:19:02,110 --> 00:19:03,760
上帝  请引导他
Lord, please guide him.

598
00:19:03,760 --> 00:19:05,220
给他力量
Give him strength.

599
00:19:05,320 --> 00:19:08,330
让他知道无论如何我们都爱他  接受他
And let him know that we love and accept him no matter what.

600
00:19:09,180 --> 00:19:11,080
米奇尔  你听到了吗
Mitchell, did you hear that?

601
00:19:11,780 --> 00:19:14,230
我要加入祷告
Hey, you know what? Let me in there.

602
00:19:14,760 --> 00:19:16,830
我以前有些武断  对吗
I have been a little judgmental, haven't I?

603
00:19:16,830 --> 00:19:17,570
所以
So...

604
00:19:18,770 --> 00:19:19,590
请继续
Go ahead.

605
00:19:20,040 --> 00:19:21,460
-阿门  -阿门
- Amen. - Amen.

606
00:19:21,460 --> 00:19:22,560
我们上台吧
Let's do this.

607
00:19:22,940 --> 00:19:25,490
-祝你们好运  -谢谢
- Break a leg! - Thank you!

608
00:19:26,490 --> 00:19:27,150
给你
Here.

609
00:19:27,390 --> 00:19:28,250
这是什么
What's this?

610
00:19:28,250 --> 00:19:28,840
如果你有兴致
If the mood strikes you,

611
00:19:28,840 --> 00:19:30,230
何不跟我们一起上台
why don't you join us onstage,

612
00:19:30,230 --> 00:19:31,750
制造些欢快的声音
make some joyful noise?

613
00:19:31,790 --> 00:19:34,720
女士们先生们  有请化水为酒乐队
Ladies and gentlemen, Water to Wine!

614
00:19:41,780 --> 00:19:43,930
一  二  三  四
One, two, three, four.

615
00:19:49,970 --> 00:19:51,550
*世界也许是平的*
*The world may be flat*

616
00:19:51,550 --> 00:19:53,570
*但它总在变化*
*But it's always changin'*

617
00:19:53,570 --> 00:19:56,660
*言语中罪恶在蔓延*
*So many sins from topics that are rangin' *

618
00:19:56,660 --> 00:19:59,630
*魔鬼用毕早餐  恶性在肆虐*
*Devil's done with breakfast, and his evil is ragin' *

619
00:19:59,630 --> 00:20:01,390
*这就是为什么  这就是为什么*
*Which is why. Which is why*

620
00:20:01,390 --> 00:20:03,380
*这就是为什么  这就是为什么*
*Which is why. Which is why*

621
00:20:03,380 --> 00:20:04,840
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*

622
00:20:04,840 --> 00:20:06,540
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*

623
00:20:06,550 --> 00:20:09,910
*人们不该对他人撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie with another man*

624
00:20:09,910 --> 00:20:11,450
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*

625
00:20:11,450 --> 00:20:13,180
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*

626
00:20:13,180 --> 00:20:16,150
*人们不该对他人撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie with another man*

627
00:20:16,150 --> 00:20:17,680
*地狱中在开派对*
*There's a party in hell*

628
00:20:17,680 --> 00:20:19,740
*酒一直在流淌*
*And the drinks are always flowing*

629
00:20:19,740 --> 00:20:23,210
*我想我们认识所有参加派对的人*
*I think we all know the kind of people that are going*

630
00:20:23,210 --> 00:20:24,670
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*

631
00:20:24,680 --> 00:20:26,430
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*

632
00:20:26,430 --> 00:20:29,420
*人们不该对他人撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie with another man*

633
00:20:29,420 --> 00:20:30,560
*除非他们相爱*
*Unless they really love each other*

634
00:20:30,560 --> 00:20:31,340
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*

635
00:20:31,340 --> 00:20:33,110
*人们不该撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie*

636
00:20:33,110 --> 00:20:36,550
*人们不该对他人撒谎*
*Man shouldn't lie with another man*

637
00:20:36,690 --> 00:20:39,720
*我所认识的耶稣博爱世人*
*The Jesus I know loves everyone*

638
00:20:39,740 --> 00:20:42,190
*不管你是直是弯*
*Even if you're gay or straight*

639
00:20:42,950 --> 00:20:46,770
*不在乎你性取向如何*
*Doesn't matter about your sexuality-y-y*

640
00:20:51,620 --> 00:20:53,310
我只是说也许
I'm just saying that maybe,

641
00:20:53,310 --> 00:20:55,040
法国革命之前
before you join the French resistance,

642
00:20:55,040 --> 00:20:57,410
一个人才可以走十几米去邻居家
you walk the 15 feet to your neighbor's house

643
00:20:57,410 --> 00:20:59,360
问问她是否收到过自己的一封情书
and ask her did she get your damn love letter.

644
00:20:59,360 --> 00:21:00,030
某些人说了
For someone that says

645
00:21:00,030 --> 00:21:01,310
不想谈论电影
that they don't want to talk about the movie,

646
00:21:01,310 --> 00:21:02,910
但你刚刚谈的不是电影是什么
that's all you seem to be talking about.

647
00:21:02,910 --> 00:21:03,480
至少那电影
I think it's better

648
00:21:03,490 --> 00:21:04,890
要比把这坨黄黄的糊塞进嘴里强
than putting this yellow mush in my mouth.

649
00:21:04,890 --> 00:21:06,780
如果你能摒弃成见
Yeah, maybe if you opened up your mind,

650
00:21:06,780 --> 00:21:10,040
你会发现其实这些很美味
you would see that this is actually delicious.

651
00:21:12,510 --> 00:21:13,940
其实难吃极了
It was disgusting,

652
00:21:13,940 --> 00:21:16,780
但我不能让杰知道他是对的
But I can never let Jay know that he is right.

653
00:21:16,780 --> 00:21:18,910
食物难吃极了  但老实说
The food is terrible and if I'm being honest,

654
00:21:18,910 --> 00:21:20,670
电影我还挺喜欢的
the movie sort of stays with me.

