[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由Srt2Ass生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.com
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0.00,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.80,0:02:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fe134\an5\i0\u0\s0\fscy100\fsp0\fr0\4c&H00000&\b1\fn方正黑体_GBK}{\3c&HFFFFFF&\fscx700\fs80\alpha&H9F&\c&H000000&\bord1\shad0\pos(192,243)\fad(500,500)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.80,0:02:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fe134\an5\i0\u0\s0\fscx100\fscy100\fsp0\fr0\4c&H00000&}{\fs18\fn方正准圆简体\b1\bord0\shad0\pos(240,242)\fad(500,500)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译\N禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.30,0:02:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,0)\fs16\c&HECB000&\fn方正准圆_GBK\move(-500,258,192,258,0,500)\bord0}翻译：{\fs18\c&HFFFFFF&}小饭  四方虾  王大可  冰蓝  丁小七
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.30,0:02:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,0)\fs16\c&HECB000&\fn方正准圆_GBK\bord0\move(-500,258,192,258,0,500)}时间轴：{\fs18\c&HFFFFFF&}浓子   {\fs16\c&HECB000&}校对：{\fs18\c&HFFFFFF&}olivia_xuxu   {\fs16\c&HECB000&}后期&总监：{\fs18\c&HFFFFFF&}瓜瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.30,0:02:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,74)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48}{\fad(400,400)}摩  登
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.30,0:02:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(183,240)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs48\c&H0497F2&}{\fad(400,400)}家  庭
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.30,0:02:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\pos(304,242)\fn书体坊赵九江钢笔行书\c&HFF00FF&\fs22}第五季 第十五集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.68,0:00:03.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是我们家重要的一天
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.00,0:00:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  好激动
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.86,0:00:06.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都比不上开始一个新工作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.28,0:00:09.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是终于能在已有的工作中充分施展才能
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.16,0:00:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新事物带来的美好承诺
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.24,0:00:12.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回报终于...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.58,0:00:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相反的事情却一样地美好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.74,0:00:16.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-干杯  -干杯
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.16,0:00:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚接受了一份在CFJ的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.67,0:00:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是司法中心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.33,0:00:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那其实是一个
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.40,0:00:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级英雄们的秘密总部
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.48,0:00:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有啦  算是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.35,0:00:26.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我在法学院的一个朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.60,0:00:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,建立的一所司法救援团体
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.75,0:00:31.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我将成为人民的律师
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.27,0:00:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为无法发言的人发言
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.48,0:00:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一样重要的是
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.00,0:00:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.79,0:00:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚  我将主持"春季叮当嘉年华"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.65,0:00:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,筹款  舞会
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.25,0:00:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我的带领下
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.48,0:00:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经打破了学校记录
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.60,0:00:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还加了"叮当"
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.54,0:00:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前一般就叫春季嘉年华
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.70,0:00:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该先说我的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.53,0:00:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.04,0:00:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今晚开场穿这身  说实话
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.67,0:01:00.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看出来我在下面穿了别的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.09,0:01:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚就是SCARB之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.13,0:01:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,南加州房地产经纪人年会
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.68,0:01:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是南加州房地产经纪人的盛会
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.55,0:01:09.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  唯一的盛会
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.97,0:01:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这家伙主持了两次
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.44,0:01:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三次
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.02,0:01:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三次宴会  史上唯一一人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.96,0:01:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不幸的是  我今年无法参加了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.04,0:01:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样也好
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.83,0:01:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在这种场合总是被无视
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.15,0:01:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嫁给大明星就是这么不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.08,0:01:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幸运的是  我另找了一个伴侣
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.42,0:01:26.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老爸  你还没睡
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.84,0:01:28.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  还在想宴会上要讲的段子
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.98,0:01:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟我一起去怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.38,0:01:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然好了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.23,0:01:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会答应我毫不意外
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.42,0:01:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那丫头天生懂房产
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.78,0:01:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她小时候常常跟着我
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.91,0:01:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去带客户看房
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.39,0:01:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们甚至还谈过
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.32,0:01:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父女档一起合作呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.56,0:01:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  她最近有些偏离正轨
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.01,0:01:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但让她感受一下
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.98,0:01:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,地区房地产经纪人的魅力之夜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.48,0:01:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许能重新燃起她的激情
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.47,0:01:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难以置信我居然得去参加这种宴会
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.47,0:01:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我有什么选择呢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.98,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当然愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.83,0:01:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不会吃饼干不配牛奶吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.32,0:01:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对噢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.50,0:01:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不给力啊  菲尔
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.36,0:02:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息区
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.29,0:02:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,复印机
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.30,0:02:21.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小臭狗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.14,0:02:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.01,0:02:25.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚刚吐了一地
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.51,0:02:26.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天呐
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.83,0:02:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你和米歇尔·奥巴马
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.02,0:02:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我姨
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.23,0:02:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.55,0:02:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我为什么会以为
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.24,0:02:32.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,淡定  别有什么白人内疚感
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.55,0:02:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是米歇尔·奥巴马
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.64,0:02:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.87,0:02:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  这15年你成就了很多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.08,0:02:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在事业上是的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.63,0:02:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经六个月没有约会了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.22,0:02:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候周日我会开车去看看我的冷冻卵子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.70,0:02:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是从好的一面来说
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.08,0:02:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟我妈妈非常亲密
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.98,0:02:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那照片  我都看出相似之处了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.61,0:02:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是马娅·安杰卢
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.44,0:02:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.24,0:02:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面有签名  米奇
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.49,0:02:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.39,0:02:53.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们合作会很有意思的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.45,0:02:54.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.33,0:02:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我真的非常期待  -你
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.99,0:02:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚那身衣服算怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.40,0:02:58.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可是商务晚宴
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.56,0:03:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.08,0:03:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温迪  我尽力了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.94,0:03:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就更努力一点啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.96,0:03:05.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的办公室
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.01,0:03:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.11,0:03:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.54,0:03:09.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  丹尼斯以前也很喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.79,0:03:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来就不喜欢了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.21,0:03:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过会儿再来找你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.94,0:03:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.64,0:03:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.94,0:03:19.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[快跑]
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.79,0:03:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新来的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.44,0:03:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你好  我叫米奇尔·普里契特
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.02,0:03:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是丹
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.08,0:03:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你周日晚上没有安排
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.76,0:03:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹  你怎么还在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.97,0:03:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.75,0:03:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.96,0:03:30.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.88,0:03:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那边
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.11,0:03:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.94,0:03:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[离开  否则你会死的]
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.12,0:03:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢皮革的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.26,0:03:47.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就试着喜欢丝绸的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.72,0:03:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿皮革出去太热了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.00,0:03:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说这辆车
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.93,0:03:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便说一句
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.57,0:03:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天去经销商那里  我来讲价
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.86,0:03:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.59,0:03:56.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我是生意人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.59,0:03:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟人打交道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.75,0:03:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道该怎么从他们那里得到我想要的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.31,0:04:01.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这块表
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.10,0:04:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙最后是半价卖给我的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.26,0:04:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这鞋  三分之一
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.06,0:04:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些  是免费的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.41,0:04:13.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说谁更会说服人  生意人先生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.53,0:04:14.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们方法不同
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.92,0:04:16.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们都很厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.02,0:04:20.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  米奇
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.66,0:04:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.70,0:04:23.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来像是要站起来走路啊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.01,0:04:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大器晚成  好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.03,0:04:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁在乎别人家的小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.07,0:04:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫你"慢吞吞的乔"呢
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.13,0:04:30.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就是这样叫你的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.06,0:04:32.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜拜
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.99,0:04:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得下次再去买车了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.24,0:04:36.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米奇得去工作
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.51,0:04:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小卡得去跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.52,0:04:39.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得照看莉莉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.94,0:04:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么了  -没啥
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.36,0:04:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是...换做我的话就能推掉这件事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.30,0:04:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住手
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.49,0:04:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-吃掉  -从我身上下去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.20,0:04:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃草吧  牛儿
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.64,0:04:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-朗达  -您好  邓菲太太
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.24,0:04:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.06,0:04:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  舞会就快开始了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.88,0:04:54.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该进屋去换衣服吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.08,0:04:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经换了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.94,0:04:55.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在来的路上
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.66,0:04:56.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从这里骑车去
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.84,0:04:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢  朗达
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.96,0:04:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要进屋去把自己弄干净吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.07,0:05:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我没事  -是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.27,0:05:01.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你脸上还有泥巴呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.71,0:05:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克  你在这等着
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.09,0:05:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你朋友们骑车去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.02,0:05:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带朗达去  来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.21,0:05:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进屋之前像狗那样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.93,0:05:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好抖抖身上的泥巴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.90,0:05:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.59,0:05:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸有三处纹身
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.89,0:05:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为啥啊  你都是当爹的人了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.24,0:05:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,父母想要跟上潮流真是太可悲了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.78,0:05:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妈又在耳朵上打了耳洞
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.20,0:05:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说  拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.60,0:05:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您都50了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.54,0:05:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这把年纪还打耳洞简直老到掉渣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.11,0:05:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩决定去舞会了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.10,0:05:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  但不是认真地去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.07,0:05:29.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但我们要去  -什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.34,0:05:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要带着讽刺态度过去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.11,0:05:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘲笑所有把这事看得很重的孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.04,0:05:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讽刺个屁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.82,0:05:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾丽克斯喜欢德鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.34,0:05:37.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只是在打安全牌
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.99,0:05:40.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有那种鲁莽讨厌的妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.02,0:05:41.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢卷入其中
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.17,0:05:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为他们撮合撮合
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.01,0:05:45.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是好意
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.52,0:05:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,衬衫不错啊  塔克教练
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.13,0:05:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  你知道我喜欢说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.87,0:05:54.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能是教练[二等舱]
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.49,0:05:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我坐头等舱
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.78,0:05:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想不想
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.97,0:06:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在今晚的舞会上致开幕词啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.83,0:06:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艺术委员会从来没有取得这么大的成就
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.23,0:06:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这全都是因为你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.42,0:06:07.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  我六个月前来到这所学校时
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.44,0:06:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从没想到你们会敞开怀抱接纳我
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.89,0:06:12.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  这里是化学实验室吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.07,0:06:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我在期待"大反应"
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.10,0:06:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就有了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.38,0:06:16.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.20,0:06:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这位是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.42,0:06:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休假过得怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.24,0:06:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒极了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.59,0:06:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备好...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.14,0:06:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,度另一个假了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.00,0:06:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么称呼啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.96,0:06:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡普兰先生  传奇的西班牙语老师
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.58,0:06:33.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点同情他
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.99,0:06:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他离开时还是大家的最爱
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.81,0:06:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢肯定关于我的消息传出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.22,0:06:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不想让他觉得被取代了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.33,0:06:44.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  让一让  大个儿
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.40,0:06:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都有礼物哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.22,0:06:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安吉拉  这是刚从阿奴拉达普勒带来的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.04,0:06:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凯伦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.13,0:06:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个要和印度薄饼搭配吃哦
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.59,0:06:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是给...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.01,0:06:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-她叫玛西亚  -玛西亚
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.02,0:06:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然啦  我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.47,0:06:58.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚才满脑子肯定都是西班牙语
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.92,0:07:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,某人总是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.17,0:07:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是谁干的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.51,0:07:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.18,0:07:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人把我的包摔到地上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.32,0:07:06.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摔坏了我的手机
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.60,0:07:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  你知道是怎么回事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.58,0:07:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他干的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.07,0:07:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.99,0:07:12.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我要去玩了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.57,0:07:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她撒谎了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.59,0:07:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔怎么会把包从桌子上推下去
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.43,0:07:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都不会走路
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.33,0:07:18.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去和她谈谈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.31,0:07:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么是你
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.27,0:07:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你是个知道怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.03,0:07:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和别人谈话的生意人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.42,0:07:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  我跟她谈完之后
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.04,0:07:26.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不但会承认错误
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.50,0:07:28.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还可能卖给她一个橱柜
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.13,0:07:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得有次
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.06,0:07:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小伙伴们和我在玩石头大战
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.20,0:07:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是个游戏
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.82,0:07:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把石头丢到对方的脑袋上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.45,0:07:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能出什么事啊  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.14,0:07:41.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把一块石头砸到了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.95,0:07:43.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸漫步者车的窗户上
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.44,0:07:47.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得是我的小弟弟干的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.02,0:07:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无法接受
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.74,0:07:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉他是我干的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.26,0:07:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坦白的感觉棒极了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.95,0:07:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸很为我感到骄傲
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.70,0:07:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至都没被他责罚
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.71,0:07:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.38,0:08:01.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是乔干的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.33,0:08:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.29,0:08:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看看  学着点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.08,0:08:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得她不吃你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.26,0:08:09.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露乳沟这一套吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.19,0:08:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我又不是只会这一招
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.41,0:08:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  莉莉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.80,0:08:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外公去哪儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.87,0:08:15.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心杰
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.33,0:08:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在这里只有我和你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.97,0:08:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.75,0:08:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最喜欢哪个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.77,0:08:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.31,0:08:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.89,0:08:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们都会消失
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.77,0:08:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或早或晚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.95,0:08:31.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会找到你最爱的那个
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.65,0:08:33.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士们先生们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.63,0:08:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是中介之王
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.98,0:08:38.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他太棒了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.37,0:08:40.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家鼓掌欢迎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.59,0:08:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔·邓菲
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.91,0:08:47.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢这么好的司仪
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.48,0:08:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也就是我
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.60,0:08:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像前几年
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.63,0:08:54.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会再站在这
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.09,0:08:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直冲你们叽哩呱啦
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.34,0:08:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  女士们先生们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.34,0:08:59.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该给你们点好东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.00,0:09:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今年
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.54,0:09:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把词都唱出来
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.64,0:09:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我要卖*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.12,0:09:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*周六挂出一间房子开卖*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.84,0:09:18.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*经纪人们的聚会*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.19,0:09:21.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*出现在大篷车*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.28,0:09:27.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我刚刚离婚*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.46,0:09:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我现在需要间房子*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.34,0:09:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*可以让我养猫*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.21,0:09:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们说伟大的艺术家
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.97,0:09:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝不会让任何事情影响表演
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.86,0:09:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许这些伟人没有女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.38,0:09:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你计划好的五次实时台上换装中的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.98,0:09:44.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第三次时走神
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.73,0:09:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不得不说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.16,0:09:47.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这让我丧失了信心
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.28,0:09:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*在板子上*
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.22,0:09:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是表演的一部分吗
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.32,0:09:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.24,0:09:57.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是表演的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.53,0:10:04.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在法学院
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.22,0:10:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温迪·柯克就有点容易情绪激动
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.76,0:10:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直希望她会越来越温柔  可是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.65,0:10:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人会向相反方向发展
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.60,0:10:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地方是个噩梦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.12,0:10:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,情况很糟糕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.39,0:10:16.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都不应该
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.46,0:10:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每天遭受这样的虐待
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.32,0:10:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么暴君像这样完全不尊重人命啊
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.57,0:10:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我干不下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.71,0:10:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须干下去
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.36,0:10:27.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温迪需要听到
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.04,0:10:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  可我紧张  要是她
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.89,0:10:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-米奇尔  -是  你好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.24,0:10:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚想到一个好主意
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.12,0:10:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你最适合培训雷克斯了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.12,0:10:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Groom有清洗和培训两个意思]
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.65,0:10:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.54,0:10:36.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得他真的会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.93,0:10:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和你这样的人产生共鸣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.23,0:10:39.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不介意吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.52,0:10:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  怎么会
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.41,0:10:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.27,0:10:43.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦你过去自我介绍一下吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.52,0:10:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自我介  好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.46,0:10:46.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.41,0:10:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  我是米奇尔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.87,0:10:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然这现在是我的工作了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.26,0:10:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐  你真臭
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.18,0:10:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都在看我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.45,0:11:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你让我把你打扮得很漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.39,0:11:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别瞎说  我漂亮吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.32,0:11:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很美
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.01,0:11:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩得开心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.68,0:11:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.73,0:11:11.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德鲁  你好  德鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.32,0:11:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩得开心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.36,0:11:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开心  还好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.11,0:11:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德鲁  德鲁  听我说
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.32,0:11:18.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和菲尔今晚会很晚才回家
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.89,0:11:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你开车带艾丽克斯回去时
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.17,0:11:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里没有大人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.57,0:11:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道我什么意思吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.47,0:11:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  别担心
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.99,0:11:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会开车送她回去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.31,0:11:27.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会进屋的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.25,0:11:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大房子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.41,0:11:31.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  可爱的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.29,0:11:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不反对你送她进门
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.54,0:11:34.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们回家前陪着她
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.90,0:11:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚说了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.75,0:11:38.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们很晚才回家
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.09,0:11:39.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听明白了  邓菲太太
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.91,0:11:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.75,0:11:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不得不相信你啊  因为我们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.99,0:11:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法知道你会干些什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.74,0:11:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样  要是你的车挡在车道上
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.36,0:11:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就鸣两次笛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.88,0:11:48.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后等你出来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.75,0:11:50.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -很好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.95,0:11:52.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找她吧  小伙子  快去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.88,0:11:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干得好  塔克
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.30,0:11:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做了很多
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.31,0:11:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不可能做出的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.61,0:12:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但大部分效果不错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.08,0:12:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.99,0:12:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是看你策划的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.12,0:12:04.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多很多舞会视频
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.23,0:12:06.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后就想出了这么一个主意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.50,0:12:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.68,0:12:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小甜心们
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.39,0:12:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对朗达做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.03,0:12:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把她整干净了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.92,0:12:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你毁了她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.22,0:12:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢这样的她
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.49,0:12:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她美极了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.72,0:12:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.52,0:12:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把她变回去  这样很伤脑筋
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.53,0:12:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卢克啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.16,0:12:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"家里没人"
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.99,0:12:27.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在给我拉皮条
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.61,0:12:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩显然喜欢对方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.40,0:12:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时需要有人推你们一把
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.70,0:12:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可是行为监督人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.03,0:12:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快消失吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.33,0:12:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这舞会不是你该来的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.57,0:12:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真走运  居然是水
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.46,0:12:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.05,0:12:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她已经生了一个小时的闷气了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.71,0:12:51.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不如锁上门
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.19,0:12:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉了电闸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.37,0:12:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她意识到我们态度有多严肃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.20,0:12:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们先采取温和点的手段吧  监狱长
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.20,0:12:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Gitmo: 古巴臭名昭著的关塔那摩湾监狱]
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.78,0:13:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们仔细思考了一下你的供词
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.58,0:13:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不怎么有说服力
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.84,0:13:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放包的地方对乔来说太高了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.25,0:13:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已经能够着这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.45,0:13:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为了拿到我的小动物们
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.09,0:13:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把婴儿爽身粉碰倒了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.75,0:13:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不信
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.85,0:13:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  这还有他走过的脚印呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.65,0:13:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.34,0:13:21.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  莉莉  莉莉
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.17,0:13:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔还不会走路呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.67,0:13:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在我面前走了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.15,0:13:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你有办法让他走路吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.42,0:13:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莉莉  就承认是你做的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.76,0:13:31.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来  乔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.73,0:13:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像你之前做的那样
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.37,0:13:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝  你在自找难堪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.35,0:13:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-过来  乔  -他不会走路
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.82,0:13:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他居然会走了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.37,0:13:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前点的那些蜡烛起作用了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.50,0:13:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看他的步子迈得多大
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.68,0:13:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他走得跟山羊一样稳健
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.65,0:13:48.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就说嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.71,0:13:51.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真对不起我们怀疑你了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.14,0:13:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢相信我居然这么幸运
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.58,0:14:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他学会说话之前
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.37,0:14:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他都会是我的替罪羊
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.28,0:14:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个男人跳着华尔兹自以为是舞池之王
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.30,0:14:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说什么帮助不发达地区建学校
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.88,0:14:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不知道他在斯里兰卡干了什么勾当
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.85,0:14:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都不知道他想干嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.98,0:14:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对那个男人是不是有点太苛刻了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.32,0:14:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我把他的二流舞会办成了年度盛事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.76,0:14:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  小混混和书呆子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.37,0:14:20.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能这么和谐共处
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.20,0:14:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的功劳
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.42,0:14:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很遗憾  小卡
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.58,0:14:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别替我遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.72,0:14:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,马上就是教职员工舞蹈环节
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.22,0:14:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡普兰不会跳舞
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.21,0:14:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都传到Tumblr上了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.21,0:14:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[Tumblr: 微视频社交网站]
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.20,0:14:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他的一大耻辱
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.69,0:14:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.63,0:14:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他抢不走我的风头
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.27,0:14:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  到了教职员工起舞的时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.17,0:14:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老师们  上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.86,0:14:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.29,0:14:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停  现在是小卡秀场
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.58,0:14:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不介意我也来跳吧  教练
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.98,0:15:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休假期间
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.97,0:15:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在斯里兰卡跟质多斯那学了点舞蹈
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.97,0:15:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}[质多斯那: 斯里兰卡舞蹈之父]
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.38,0:15:09.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道他是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.01,0:15:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你说话的态度很讨人厌
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.47,0:15:12.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像谁都应该知道他似的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.48,0:15:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来那个可悲的孔雀男
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.10,0:15:17.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要跟我一战到底
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.98,0:15:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须做出选择
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.33,0:15:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么跳得比他好  要么比他大度
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.74,0:15:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我离开了舞台
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.12,0:15:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了最正确的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.45,0:15:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想吸引大家的注意力吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.88,0:15:28.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去邀请一位孤独的母亲共舞吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.99,0:15:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没有想到我这一招
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.29,0:15:31.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也一样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.47,0:15:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  老兄
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.02,0:15:44.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,学着点吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.49,0:15:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我尝试看向事物更积极的一面
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.29,0:15:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是那种即使要给臭狗洗澡
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.35,0:15:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也依然乐观的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.18,0:15:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我应该醒悟了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.01,0:15:56.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的老板是个禽兽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.03,0:15:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来这里工作是为了替弱势群体说话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.66,0:16:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可没想到弱势群体居然就是我的同事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.94,0:16:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们迫切地需要屠龙的英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.21,0:16:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  不好意思我来晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.73,0:16:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷克斯  你跟米奇尔处得怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.85,0:16:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新来的那个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.47,0:16:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没见过他呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.60,0:16:14.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪  我让他来自我介绍了啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.35,0:16:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人看到我的狗了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.98,0:16:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,皮克希
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.70,0:16:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她来了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.18,0:16:22.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温迪  不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.21,0:16:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有话想跟你说
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.32,0:16:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些在座诸位都不敢说的话
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.66,0:16:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你现在做的都是好事
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.60,0:16:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是这也不能成为你如此对待别人的借口
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.14,0:16:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这倒有可能导致
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.83,0:16:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有亲密爱人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.00,0:16:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毕竟谁也不想回家面对
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.21,0:16:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个冷血无情的恶棍
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.57,0:16:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  你都在说什么啊
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.16,0:16:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是一名经验丰富值得尊重的律师
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.42,0:16:42.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是上班第一天
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.63,0:16:44.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你居然让我去给雷克斯洗澡
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.65,0:16:45.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有点无法忍受
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.88,0:16:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也无法忍受
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.37,0:16:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我还是做了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.47,0:16:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那是皮克希
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.35,0:16:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是雷克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.39,0:16:53.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让你培训的实习生
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.54,0:16:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.99,0:16:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我负全责
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.95,0:16:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可即使那样
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.52,0:16:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也没有理由因为他
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.74,0:17:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天的穿着对他大吼大叫
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.20,0:17:02.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时是为了他给我挑的衣服生气
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.06,0:17:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显  我招了世界上唯一一个
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.20,0:17:06.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有时尚嗅觉的男同性恋实习生
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.02,0:17:07.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不了解当时的背景情况
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.57,0:17:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是我  我不是一个人  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.56,0:17:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这屋里肯定还有别人觉得你是
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.87,0:17:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该怎么说呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.06,0:17:16.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个毫不尊重他人的暴君
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.54,0:17:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来像我那个恶房东案子的总结陈词
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.14,0:17:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你写完了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.12,0:17:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写得超棒
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.09,0:17:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是他不好意思给你看
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.51,0:17:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么对自己那么苛刻呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.35,0:17:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那  那么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.00,0:17:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你强迫我们周日工作又怎么说
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.96,0:17:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在说  周日晚去我家烧烤吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.29,0:17:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.00,0:17:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么还在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.12,0:17:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是你的结婚纪念日  快回家
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.03,0:17:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  告诉我这不是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.64,0:17:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  她很疯狂
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.75,0:17:36.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到她攻击自动售货机
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.38,0:17:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从丹尼斯把它弄坏以后就只能那样用了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.69,0:17:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹尼斯就是之前用我那间办公室的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.36,0:17:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  他曾是那个机器最好的客户
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.47,0:17:43.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到他开始跑步
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.50,0:17:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一天他说  他一定要离开  否则
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.38,0:17:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就会死  好吧  好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.79,0:17:47.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,温迪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.88,0:17:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也许应该向你道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.75,0:17:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.00,0:17:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很明显  这里每个人都很爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.83,0:17:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前把一切都搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.52,0:17:55.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  对不起
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.54,0:17:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  你也不是全搞错了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.95,0:18:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我虽然拿这事开玩笑  但你是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.16,0:18:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我孤单一人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.84,0:18:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也不是第一次有人说我冷漠
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.21,0:18:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的那些卵子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.78,0:18:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些卵子取出来就是冷冻的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.32,0:18:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我还这么高
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.65,0:18:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使我能找到一个人来爱我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.49,0:18:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们也够不着啊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.51,0:18:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.73,0:18:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个很了不起的女性
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.14,0:18:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是个了不起的女性
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.98,0:18:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且  你是个榜样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.34,0:18:19.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是个英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.46,0:18:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是个六尺高的英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.91,0:18:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  别这样
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.92,0:18:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你周围的人都爱你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.55,0:18:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有丹还有雷克斯
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.30,0:18:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有我  过来
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.00,0:18:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有挂在那里的塞缪尔·杰克逊
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.91,0:18:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你妈妈戴着袋鼠牌帽子  是吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.56,0:18:33.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.98,0:18:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定你自己在干什么吗  塔德
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.74,0:18:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你来自抵押医生[机构]  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.98,0:18:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人问  这里有医生吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.77,0:18:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道我不应该站出来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.17,0:18:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  你需要我帮你脱掉裙子吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.29,0:18:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你想看我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.19,0:18:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一丝不挂只穿着一个新年婴儿纸尿裤
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.07,0:18:45.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你在发短信时
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.66,0:18:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要唱的歌的结尾重头戏
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.25,0:18:49.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就收了一条短信  我看了大部分节目
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.28,0:18:50.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这就走了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.12,0:18:51.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能回桌子上
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.09,0:18:52.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿我的钥匙和包吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.65,0:18:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.34,0:18:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想聊聊吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.13,0:18:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底能假扮几种医生
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.06,0:18:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  到了揭晓今晚大奖的时刻了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.37,0:19:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"年地经"奖[年度地产经纪]
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.32,0:19:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都不知道自己为什么生她的气
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.51,0:19:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许只是因为她整晚都显得很无聊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.14,0:19:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你感觉自己不被她接纳
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.97,0:19:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我自己的错
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.08,0:19:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给了自己一个错误的希望
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.72,0:19:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为她会愿意追随我进入地产业
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.61,0:19:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔·邓菲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.57,0:19:12.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她现在有自己的生活了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.42,0:19:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不知道我们还能在哪里有联系
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.92,0:19:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.66,0:19:16.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.80,0:19:17.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扶我起来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.10,0:19:20.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都知道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.96,0:19:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,菲尔今晚出了点小意外
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.61,0:19:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们很乐意
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.63,0:19:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-替他接受这个奖项  -等等  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.47,0:19:25.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.32,0:19:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.09,0:19:28.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家好  我是
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.85,0:19:30.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是海莉  菲尔的女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.85,0:19:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  你赢得了"年地经"
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.91,0:19:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都知道他是个出色的地产经纪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.18,0:19:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我知道他还是世界上最棒的爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.79,0:19:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据我所知
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.99,0:19:44.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也是年度最佳父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.48,0:19:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"年爸爸"奖得主
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.81,0:19:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚真的很遗憾
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.90,0:19:49.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没有听完他的完整演出
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.80,0:19:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我有听过他排练
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.40,0:19:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们哪位是J.J.·麦卡宾
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.82,0:20:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快速问答  J.J.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.35,0:20:01.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么一个好的抵押就像
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.67,0:20:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老婆的床上表现
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.51,0:20:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个月一次还低利息[兴趣]
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.69,0:20:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑什么  斯基普·伍斯奴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.25,0:20:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从你加入海军后
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.21,0:20:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就没收过佣金了[服役]
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.81,0:20:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她真是棒极了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.82,0:20:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是我闺女
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.62,0:20:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我会在"海军"上加重语气
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.45,0:20:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么  还有什么来着
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.70,0:20:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛格利特·福曼也来了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.84,0:20:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要提醒一下她的男伴
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.46,0:20:24.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她比房利美公司拥有更多资不抵债住房
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.45,0:20:28.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者说  房利一定会美
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.13,0:20:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都希望别人看到自己最好的一面
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.42,0:20:33.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以有时我们会隐藏一些事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.18,0:20:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以保护自己
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.13,0:20:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们不必害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.69,0:20:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为真相永远是一件好事
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.07,0:20:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真相让我们自由
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.18,0:20:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我们更亲近
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.44,0:20:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想不想告诉我们
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.66,0:20:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乔的鞋怎么会穿错脚了呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.20,0:20:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来小家伙学会了自己穿鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.33,0:21:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始吧  伙计  你能行
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.40,0:21:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.31,0:21:08.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然乔会走路了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.38,0:21:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得他应该分担些家务了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.93,0:21:10.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,稳一点  大小伙
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.95,0:21:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家务  什么样的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.63,0:21:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他来了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.56,0:21:14.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.93,0:21:16.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.17,0:21:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啤酒  你疯了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.47,0:21:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪  你想来点吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.89,0:21:20.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也可以给你拿
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.67,0:21:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我简直不敢相信你竟然教他做那种事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.65,0:21:24.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看完第二段再评论吧
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.75,0:21:25.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.71,0:21:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放心吧  是我自己
