1
00:00:11,010 --> 00:00:16,010
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:00:11,010 --> 00:00:16,010
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:00:11,010 --> 00:00:16,010
{\an5}{\pos(145,227)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:00:11,510 --> 00:00:16,010
{\pos(67,223)}m 50 0 l 179 0 b 208 0 229 21 229 50 l 229 179 b 229 208 208 228 179 228 l 50 228 b 21 228 0 208 0 179 l 0 50 b 0 21 21 0 50 0

5
00:00:11,510 --> 00:00:16,010
{\pos(67,223)}m 0 0 b 1 -1 2 -2 4 -1 b 7 1 3 2 5 5 b 6 7 8 7 9 5 l 15 -6 b 18 -7 20 -6 20 -3 b 19 -1 17 2 17 4 b 16 7 20 7 21 6 b 22 4 23 2 25 -1 b 27 -2 29 -1 29 1 b 29 2 28 3 29 5 b 30 7 32 7 33 6 b 34 5 34 4 35 3 b 37 2 39 3 39 5 b 39 6 38 8 37 9 b 34 13 29 13 25 9 b 22 13 17 13 13 9 b 10 13 3 13 0 8 

6
00:00:11,510 --> 00:00:16,010
{\pos(84,223)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

9
00:00:17,010 --> 00:00:47,520
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

10
00:00:16,510 --> 00:00:47,520
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

20
00:00:04,040 --> 00:00:05,990
No one is around. Again.

21
00:00:06,080 --> 00:00:08,800
Is it just me or people have been avoiding us lately?

22
00:00:09,070 --> 00:00:11,680
I get it, twins are a ton of work.

23
00:00:11,680 --> 00:00:14,630
But Haley and Dylan ask us to help out a lot.

24
00:00:14,880 --> 00:00:17,870
Maybe we're both just loopy from sleep deprivation.

25
00:00:17,870 --> 00:00:20,330
I don't even remember making this cup of tea.

26
00:00:20,630 --> 00:00:22,630
It's fine, I'll just jog with them.

27
00:00:22,630 --> 00:00:24,750
Don't push yourself too hard on that run.

28
00:00:24,910 --> 00:00:26,650
Please. You know who you're talking to?

29
00:00:26,860 --> 00:00:29,030
Why does everyone always ask me that?

30
00:00:31,430 --> 00:00:32,320
That was close.

31
00:00:32,330 --> 00:00:33,370
- Are they gone? - Yes.

32
00:00:34,020 --> 00:00:37,530
Okay, who'd like to help me with a magic trick?

33
00:00:38,500 --> 00:00:39,600
Alex. Great.

34
00:00:39,650 --> 00:00:41,490
Now, uh, take this dove --

35
00:00:41,490 --> 00:00:42,290
Try not to rile her up.

36
00:00:42,290 --> 00:00:45,020
She's about to spend the better part of an hour in my pants.

37
00:00:57,920 --> 00:01:01,280
Until now, we haven't had the best of luck with renters.

38
00:01:01,390 --> 00:01:05,140
So, when you said you were a cat person on your application...

39
00:01:06,690 --> 00:01:08,500
Oh, oh, that's -- that's just my watch.

40
00:01:08,510 --> 00:01:11,380
But then Brad and Paul moved in, and it was like

41
00:01:11,390 --> 00:01:14,030
the perfect friend couple showed up at our front door.

42
00:01:14,030 --> 00:01:17,830
And you wanted to stop renting completely after the cat lady.

43
00:01:17,830 --> 00:01:21,320
I just -- I couldn't listen to her scream every time she took a bath.

44
00:01:21,660 --> 00:01:23,820
I can't believe how much we have in common.

45
00:01:23,820 --> 00:01:26,420
Daughters the same age, you both played football.

46
00:01:26,420 --> 00:01:29,550
You know, an ex-teammate of mine is a coach for the Chargers.

47
00:01:29,550 --> 00:01:31,140
He can get us right on the field.

48
00:01:31,140 --> 00:01:32,480
You just have to watch where you stand,

49
00:01:32,480 --> 00:01:34,140
'cause you could end up under a wide receiver.

50
00:01:34,140 --> 00:01:35,740
Okay, stop selling! I'm in!

51
00:01:35,740 --> 00:01:37,900
They even pre-paid for six months.

52
00:01:38,140 --> 00:01:39,960
That means they'll be here till Christmas.

53
00:01:40,060 --> 00:01:41,860
We can include them in our Secret Santa!

54
00:01:41,870 --> 00:01:44,360
Oh, it would be nice not to get Lily again.

55
00:01:45,440 --> 00:01:47,530
The Duke...

56
00:01:49,620 --> 00:01:51,970
becomes a uke...

57
00:01:53,560 --> 00:01:56,060
becomes a Luke.

58
00:01:56,280 --> 00:01:57,550
Dad, that was amazing!

59
00:01:58,170 --> 00:02:00,440
Amazing that I think a hacky parlor trick

60
00:02:00,440 --> 00:02:01,970
is gonna cut it at SCARB.

61
00:02:01,970 --> 00:02:04,830
You heard me right, Alex -- SCARB!

62
00:02:04,830 --> 00:02:06,970
The Southern California Area Realtors' Banquet

63
00:02:06,970 --> 00:02:07,940
is the biggest event of the year

64
00:02:07,940 --> 00:02:09,890
for Southern California Area Realtors.

65
00:02:09,890 --> 00:02:11,420
The other events -- SCARL,

66
00:02:11,420 --> 00:02:14,270
SCARD, SCARP, SCARG, SCARF --

67
00:02:14,270 --> 00:02:18,040
t-they're fine, but SCARB, it's -- it's the show.

68
00:02:18,120 --> 00:02:19,550
I performed at last year's SCARB,

69
00:02:19,560 --> 00:02:21,140
and -- and I did well.

70
00:02:23,160 --> 00:02:24,220
Too well.

71
00:02:24,450 --> 00:02:25,730
Thank you.

72
00:02:25,730 --> 00:02:28,540
Wait, was there someone else who wanted to say thank you?

73
00:02:28,780 --> 00:02:29,950
Oh, that's right.

74
00:02:30,110 --> 00:02:32,190
Puff wanted to say thank you.

75
00:02:33,940 --> 00:02:35,720
Thank you so much. Thank you.

76
00:02:35,720 --> 00:02:37,670
Unbelievable!

77
00:02:37,670 --> 00:02:39,420
When you were underwater for nine minutes,

78
00:02:39,420 --> 00:02:41,890
I almost broke the glass myself!

79
00:02:41,950 --> 00:02:44,010
You have got to come back next year.

80
00:02:44,010 --> 00:02:45,960
Well, I guess I could, uh...

81
00:02:47,380 --> 00:02:49,440
...get behind you on that.

82
00:02:51,310 --> 00:02:53,200
I don't know how I did that.

83
00:02:53,710 --> 00:02:54,710
For the last year,

84
00:02:54,710 --> 00:02:57,120
I haven't paid for a drink in any Realtor bar in California.

85
00:02:57,120 --> 00:02:58,700
I've never known that kind of adulation.

86
00:02:58,700 --> 00:03:01,000
If I blow it tonight, it all goes away.

87
00:03:01,000 --> 00:03:03,540
I'm just another bum walking into Brokers

88
00:03:03,540 --> 00:03:05,840
paying for my own Long Escrow Iced Tea!

89
00:03:05,840 --> 00:03:08,130
Dad, I'm on the short list for this NASA job.

90
00:03:08,130 --> 00:03:09,600
I just need to finish these forms,

91
00:03:09,600 --> 00:03:12,700
but I -- I swear to you, it really was great.

92
00:03:12,990 --> 00:03:14,510
I'm sorry.

93
00:03:14,540 --> 00:03:16,330
And I am a tough audience.

94
00:03:16,330 --> 00:03:17,490
I'm a scientist.

95
00:03:17,490 --> 00:03:20,420
It's not like I'm fooled by simple misdirection.

96
00:03:20,420 --> 00:03:22,040
I told Janice I'm 21.

97
00:03:22,040 --> 00:03:23,420
I'm pretty sure she'd break up with me

98
00:03:23,420 --> 00:03:25,320
if she found out I wasn't even legal yet.

99
00:03:25,610 --> 00:03:28,610
Then she asked if I'd buy wine for dinner tonight.

100
00:03:29,040 --> 00:03:30,710
Mind moving your thumb...

101
00:03:30,980 --> 00:03:32,290
Alexandra?

102
00:03:33,390 --> 00:03:34,890
That's what that's short for?

103
00:03:45,490 --> 00:03:47,070
So sweet of you to take them to the park.

104
00:03:47,070 --> 00:03:48,750
Just make sure they're someplace shady.

105
00:03:48,750 --> 00:03:49,650
Will do.

106
00:03:51,340 --> 00:03:53,330
It's amazing how well you've been doing

107
00:03:53,330 --> 00:03:55,770
selling Aunt Miranda's hot sauce.

108
00:03:55,780 --> 00:03:56,590
I don't want to tell you

109
00:03:56,590 --> 00:03:59,630
how much money I have lost trying to sell it over here.

110
00:03:59,630 --> 00:04:01,370
I wouldn't mind having an exact figure --

111
00:04:01,370 --> 00:04:04,610
I can't believe that you guys are already engaged!

112
00:04:04,610 --> 00:04:05,990
Where did you guys meet?

113
00:04:05,990 --> 00:04:07,890
On the street where I sell my artwork.

114
00:04:07,890 --> 00:04:09,710
One day, she let me paint her.

115
00:04:09,870 --> 00:04:11,100
She became my muse.

116
00:04:11,100 --> 00:04:12,660
I am so happy for you, Sonia.

117
00:04:12,660 --> 00:04:15,790
Finally, you found the love that you deserve.

118
00:04:16,460 --> 00:04:19,150
It's great seeing you being supportive of Sonia for --

119
00:04:19,150 --> 00:04:20,120
She's an idiot.

120
00:04:20,120 --> 00:04:21,640
He's obviously a gold digger,

121
00:04:21,640 --> 00:04:23,150
and I'm going to prove it to her.

122
00:04:23,150 --> 00:04:24,680
How do you know he's a gold digger?

123
00:04:24,680 --> 00:04:27,080
He's a starving artist, she has money.

124
00:04:27,080 --> 00:04:29,630
Do you really think that someone young and beautiful like that

125
00:04:29,630 --> 00:04:32,370
is gonna fall in love with a rich, older person?

126
00:04:32,370 --> 00:04:33,710
Never happens.

127
00:04:34,180 --> 00:04:36,520
I hear what I'm saying, and we're fine.

128
00:04:39,270 --> 00:04:41,050
When Sheryl McCray comes in,

129
00:04:41,050 --> 00:04:43,560
pay for her coffee with this.

130
00:04:44,490 --> 00:04:47,760
Sheryl McCray, Powerhouse real-estate developer.

131
00:04:47,760 --> 00:04:50,260
I've been trying to land her closet business for years,

132
00:04:50,260 --> 00:04:52,450
but it's impossible to get a meeting.

133
00:04:52,660 --> 00:04:54,110
This article, though,

134
00:04:54,110 --> 00:04:57,560
says where she buys a latte every Saturday at 10:00.

135
00:04:57,560 --> 00:05:01,010
Today, I'm gonna buy that latte, we'll get to talking,

136
00:05:01,010 --> 00:05:02,240
and before you know it,

137
00:05:02,240 --> 00:05:04,890
she'll be buying a latte closets.

138
00:05:05,370 --> 00:05:06,420
Sheryl McCray?

139
00:05:06,480 --> 00:05:08,450
Matthew Kang, Kang Cabinets.

140
00:05:08,450 --> 00:05:09,770
Would you have just two minutes to, uh, sit dow--

141
00:05:09,770 --> 00:05:10,710
Are you serious?

142
00:05:11,560 --> 00:05:13,190
I'm not gonna do business with someone

143
00:05:13,190 --> 00:05:15,160
who interrupts me in a coffee shop

144
00:05:15,160 --> 00:05:17,330
while I'm trying to enjoy a few precious moments

145
00:05:17,330 --> 00:05:20,260
of alone time with my child. And her nanny.

146
00:05:20,260 --> 00:05:21,520
I think she's wet.

147
00:05:22,170 --> 00:05:24,060
Change of plans, big spender?

148
00:05:26,010 --> 00:05:28,510
Ohh! Really? An emergency?

149
00:05:28,510 --> 00:05:29,380
Well, I guess I could --

150
00:05:29,390 --> 00:05:31,410
Relax. They don't need help with the babies.

151
00:05:31,410 --> 00:05:32,400
Luke has them.

152
00:05:32,400 --> 00:05:33,210
Oh, thank God.

153
00:05:33,210 --> 00:05:35,900
Ugh. Let's get rid of this bad reminder, huh?

154
00:05:35,900 --> 00:05:37,100
Oh, I know that lady.

155
00:05:37,100 --> 00:05:38,080
What? How?

156
00:05:38,080 --> 00:05:39,810
Oh, Mommy and Me class at my yoga place,

157
00:05:39,810 --> 00:05:40,930
she's there every week.

158
00:05:40,930 --> 00:05:43,210
Oh, in fact, it's starting in half an hour.

159
00:05:43,210 --> 00:05:45,680
Think I'm gonna grab the kids and go do my thang.

160
00:05:45,680 --> 00:05:46,990
‭‭You know what?

161
00:05:46,990 --> 00:05:48,800
I haven't spent any time with those little ragamuffins.

162
00:05:48,800 --> 00:05:49,880
Why don't you let me take 'em?

163
00:05:49,880 --> 00:05:52,190
- But I kind of wanted to take-- - Oh, take the help!

164
00:05:52,190 --> 00:05:54,290
Don't be a hero, super mom, huh?

165
00:05:56,980 --> 00:05:58,980
Is it me, or is your mom acting weird?

166
00:05:58,980 --> 00:06:00,860
No. No!

167
00:06:00,860 --> 00:06:02,010
Don't you ev--

168
00:06:02,010 --> 00:06:04,120
Your cue is "Cadabra"!

169
00:06:09,130 --> 00:06:11,230
We made kale smoothies. We wanted to share.

170
00:06:11,230 --> 00:06:12,340
Thank you.

171
00:06:13,110 --> 00:06:14,980
Oh, no! We're intruding.

172
00:06:14,980 --> 00:06:16,830
You're throwing a big pancake brunch.

173
00:06:17,070 --> 00:06:18,090
Where is everyone?

174
00:06:18,090 --> 00:06:20,100
Uh, this is just for us.

175
00:06:21,200 --> 00:06:23,710
- What's this? - Art project for school.

176
00:06:23,710 --> 00:06:25,260
I just grabbed something out of the trash

177
00:06:25,260 --> 00:06:26,850
and threw glitter glue on it.

178
00:06:26,850 --> 00:06:28,050
Got a 70.

179
00:06:28,050 --> 00:06:29,320
She knows that's out of 100, right?

180
00:06:29,320 --> 00:06:31,710
Vera went through a Found Art phase.

181
00:06:31,710 --> 00:06:32,970
This is, um...

182
00:06:33,150 --> 00:06:34,880
This is the Michelangelo's David

183
00:06:34,880 --> 00:06:36,430
that she made out of plastic.

184
00:06:36,430 --> 00:06:37,990
Recycled plastic.

185
00:06:38,060 --> 00:06:41,000
We only get one planet, let's take care of it.

186
00:06:41,600 --> 00:06:43,720
Guess someone's never heard of the moon.

187
00:06:43,770 --> 00:06:46,260
Oh, hey, speaking of art, you're so lucky

188
00:06:46,260 --> 00:06:48,130
to live right around the corner from the museum.

189
00:06:48,130 --> 00:06:50,360
Who was your favorite artist in the postimpressionist show?

190
00:06:51,690 --> 00:06:52,540
I mean, gun to my head?

191
00:06:52,540 --> 00:06:53,560
I would say...

192
00:06:54,030 --> 00:06:55,440
Gauguin, perhaps?

193
00:06:55,440 --> 00:06:57,570
To the exhibit? Yes. In a heartbeat.

194
00:06:57,570 --> 00:06:59,540
Uh, you know, actually, I'm thinking about going today.

195
00:06:59,540 --> 00:07:00,930
Would you guys care to join?

196
00:07:00,930 --> 00:07:02,300
Oh, I'd love to,

197
00:07:02,300 --> 00:07:05,240
but I promised this one we'd go on a canyon hike.

198
00:07:05,240 --> 00:07:06,610
Once an underwear model...

199
00:07:06,610 --> 00:07:08,240
A couple International Male covers

200
00:07:08,240 --> 00:07:09,430
to pay for medical school,

201
00:07:09,430 --> 00:07:11,970
he'll never let me forget it!

202
00:07:11,970 --> 00:07:13,040
Okay, we should go.

203
00:07:13,270 --> 00:07:15,060
Oh! Unless, did you want to join for the hike?

204
00:07:15,060 --> 00:07:18,410
Oh, I'm sorry, I'm -- I'm running the Santa Monica stairs

205
00:07:18,410 --> 00:07:19,620
this afternoon, so...

206
00:07:19,630 --> 00:07:20,200
Oh. ‭It's Saturday.

207
00:07:20,200 --> 00:07:22,170
If they don't see me there, they get worried.

208
00:07:22,530 --> 00:07:23,790
And thank you for the yummies.

209
00:07:24,910 --> 00:07:26,160
They sure are!

210
00:07:26,820 --> 00:07:27,740
Oh, no.

211
00:07:28,120 --> 00:07:31,110
So, um, I didn't know you were a museum lover.

212
00:07:31,110 --> 00:07:33,260
Oh, well, yeah, before you and I started dating,

213
00:07:33,260 --> 00:07:34,700
I used to go to the museum all the time.

214
00:07:34,700 --> 00:07:37,050
I'm not blaming you, of course.

215
00:07:37,050 --> 00:07:38,880
You know that the Hollywood Wax Museum

216
00:07:38,880 --> 00:07:39,860
isn't an actual --

217
00:07:39,860 --> 00:07:40,810
Okay, what about you, Rocky?

218
00:07:40,810 --> 00:07:43,310
You get winded taking towels upstairs.

219
00:07:43,310 --> 00:07:45,940
Well, that's because after we met -- not blaming you --

220
00:07:45,940 --> 00:07:48,370
um, I sort of -- I tapered off a little bit.

221
00:07:48,370 --> 00:07:50,150
To focus on the relationship.

222
00:07:50,210 --> 00:07:52,080
But this is good.

223
00:07:52,080 --> 00:07:54,030
Yeah. ‭Us getting back to our roots.

224
00:07:54,030 --> 00:07:55,210
You know, enjoy the museum.

225
00:07:55,210 --> 00:07:57,160
- Yeah, enjoy your run. - ‭I will.

226
00:07:57,950 --> 00:07:58,880
You haven't, by chance --

227
00:07:58,880 --> 00:07:59,730
They're still in the box.

228
00:07:59,730 --> 00:08:01,240
- Back of the closet? - ‭Uh-huh.

229
00:08:02,910 --> 00:08:04,810
How come you never let me play with that thing?

230
00:08:04,870 --> 00:08:08,110
This "thing" medaled in three different Air Expos, Manny.

231
00:08:08,110 --> 00:08:09,190
It's not a toy.

232
00:08:09,190 --> 00:08:10,750
Hey, look at this.

233
00:08:10,780 --> 00:08:12,370
That's Sonia's fiance, right?

234
00:08:12,500 --> 00:08:14,650
It says he's from one of the richest families in Colombia.

235
00:08:14,650 --> 00:08:16,020
I knew the guy was all right.

236
00:08:16,030 --> 00:08:18,220
Oh, I see. Being rich makes you "all right."

237
00:08:18,220 --> 00:08:19,060
That's not what I meant.

238
00:08:19,060 --> 00:08:20,900
Your mom thought he might be a gold digger.

239
00:08:20,900 --> 00:08:23,700
And by the way, unlike you, I grew up working-class.

240
00:08:23,700 --> 00:08:25,760
Oh, please. The only blue collar in this house

241
00:08:25,770 --> 00:08:28,250
is the bedazzled one on your purebred French bulldog.

242
00:08:28,250 --> 00:08:29,930
She was going through a depressed period.

243
00:08:29,930 --> 00:08:32,840
You're only as happy as your least happy child, Manny.

244
00:08:32,840 --> 00:08:33,970
I'm just saying, I've never seen you

245
00:08:33,970 --> 00:08:35,910
show much interest in someone who didn't have money.

246
00:08:35,910 --> 00:08:36,930
That's ridiculous.

247
00:08:36,930 --> 00:08:38,880
Hey, buddy! Come on, take a load off.

248
00:08:38,880 --> 00:08:41,220
- Have a drink with us. - Oh, thank you, sir.

249
00:08:41,220 --> 00:08:44,000
I know what it's like to put in a hard day's work.

250
00:08:44,010 --> 00:08:45,440
Jay Pritchett, by the way.

251
00:08:45,450 --> 00:08:46,740
‭Yes, we've met many times.

252
00:08:47,070 --> 00:08:49,250
Remember, a couple years ago, I loaned you money for a cab?

253
00:08:49,250 --> 00:08:50,860
Oh, yeah, right.

254
00:08:52,390 --> 00:08:53,300
Ay, Mama.

255
00:08:53,300 --> 00:08:55,220
She's not after our money.

256
00:08:55,630 --> 00:08:56,710
How do I know?

257
00:08:56,760 --> 00:08:58,310
She has money! Lots of it.

258
00:08:58,540 --> 00:08:59,870
And I'm marrying this woman.

259
00:09:00,050 --> 00:09:01,710
I'll see you for the wedding next week.

260
00:09:02,700 --> 00:09:04,420
Ay, next week?

261
00:09:04,500 --> 00:09:05,750
That's very quick.

262
00:09:06,090 --> 00:09:08,320
I don't want to give Sonia a chance to change her mind.

263
00:09:08,320 --> 00:09:09,940
I'm sure you don't.

264
00:09:10,640 --> 00:09:12,800
You can't marry my sister.

265
00:09:12,830 --> 00:09:13,490
Why?

266
00:09:13,490 --> 00:09:14,410
Two words.

267
00:09:14,940 --> 00:09:16,490
Maybe one, with a hyphen.

268
00:09:16,490 --> 00:09:17,720
Gold digger.

269
00:09:17,720 --> 00:09:19,210
I've always hated to see people

270
00:09:19,220 --> 00:09:21,590
take advantage of others in that way.

271
00:09:21,590 --> 00:09:23,340
I can't let that happen here.

272
00:09:23,340 --> 00:09:25,350
But doesn't your sister have a lot of money?

273
00:09:25,350 --> 00:09:28,040
Would you be that quick to marry her if she didn't?

274
00:09:30,540 --> 00:09:32,040
Hey, have you seen Nestor?

275
00:09:32,110 --> 00:09:33,490
I sent him off.

276
00:09:33,490 --> 00:09:36,090
Nobody's taking anyone's money today.

277
00:09:36,090 --> 00:09:37,560
Oh, I didn't need that much from him.

278
00:09:37,560 --> 00:09:39,890
I just need to reshoot the end of my thesis film.

279
00:09:39,890 --> 00:09:42,670
The special effects are weak, and Prague was clearly faked.

280
00:09:42,680 --> 00:09:44,230
What the hell are you talking about?

281
00:09:44,230 --> 00:09:46,320
Nestor. His family's loaded.

282
00:09:46,320 --> 00:09:47,300
I looked him up.

283
00:09:48,550 --> 00:09:50,020
He's a Berellez?

284
00:09:50,400 --> 00:09:52,810
They own a soccer team, 12 hotels,

285
00:09:52,810 --> 00:09:54,330
and five judges!

286
00:09:56,290 --> 00:09:57,090
Oh, really?

287
00:09:57,090 --> 00:10:00,310
Well, I don't care if you want to buy 10,000 closets.

288
00:10:00,310 --> 00:10:01,310
I'm not at work.

289
00:10:01,310 --> 00:10:04,420
I am trying to bond with my child...ren.

290
00:10:04,910 --> 00:10:05,860
Bye.

291
00:10:06,230 --> 00:10:07,100
Hi.

292
00:10:07,270 --> 00:10:09,370
So sorry about that. It's just -- Ugh.

293
00:10:09,370 --> 00:10:11,180
People are constantly trying to sell me,

294
00:10:11,180 --> 00:10:14,490
and it is not always appropriate, you know?

295
00:10:14,770 --> 00:10:15,610
I hear that.

296
00:10:15,610 --> 00:10:17,730
Mommies, mommies.

297
00:10:17,730 --> 00:10:18,700
Gary.

298
00:10:19,380 --> 00:10:21,320
Let's start with a deep hip stretch.

299
00:10:22,890 --> 00:10:25,450
I find this class hard enough. How do you do it with twins?

300
00:10:25,450 --> 00:10:27,660
Well, uh, it's nothing compared to the babies

301
00:10:27,660 --> 00:10:29,490
I got to juggle at the office, huh?

302
00:10:29,700 --> 00:10:30,890
I know that feeling.

303
00:10:30,890 --> 00:10:33,870
Now up and down, a little deeper.

304
00:10:33,900 --> 00:10:36,430
You know, there's a baby-friendly tapas place

305
00:10:36,430 --> 00:10:39,720
Atticus and I go to after, if you ladies are up for it.

306
00:10:40,100 --> 00:10:41,800
I don't think it's time to bond, Gary,

307
00:10:41,800 --> 00:10:43,790
and I'm pretty sure you had to sue to get in here.

308
00:10:43,790 --> 00:10:45,070
He did. And up.

309
00:10:45,070 --> 00:10:46,660
We had to settle. And down.

310
00:10:47,910 --> 00:10:49,450
So, what kind of closets do you make?

311
00:10:49,450 --> 00:10:50,720
Because I actually need --

312
00:10:50,720 --> 00:10:52,840
You know what? Would it be okay if we did this after class?

313
00:10:52,840 --> 00:10:55,460
It's just, I get no time with them.

314
00:10:55,460 --> 00:10:56,970
Of course, of course.

315
00:11:03,470 --> 00:11:04,870
Oh. Hey. How were the steps?

316
00:11:04,870 --> 00:11:07,010
Uh...so -- so great. So tough.

317
00:11:07,010 --> 00:11:08,260
Uh, love the burn.

318
00:11:08,260 --> 00:11:09,830
What's up with the hat? I can barely see your eyes.

319
00:11:09,830 --> 00:11:11,010
Uh, same old eyes.

320
00:11:11,020 --> 00:11:12,420
I'm just gonna go ahead and, um --

321
00:11:13,350 --> 00:11:15,960
Why is there a Wilson logo on your forehead?

322
00:11:15,960 --> 00:11:17,180
I don't know. Must be the hat.

323
00:11:17,260 --> 00:11:18,390
Nobody's buying it.

324
00:11:18,390 --> 00:11:20,300
Just skip to the part where you tell us the truth.

325
00:11:20,300 --> 00:11:23,470
Fine. I-I never made it to the stairs, okay?

326
00:11:23,470 --> 00:11:25,460
I got distracted.

327
00:11:34,680 --> 00:11:36,220
I'm a fraud. Happy?

328
00:11:36,220 --> 00:11:37,990
I never even made it to the stairs.

329
00:11:38,040 --> 00:11:39,370
Don't even know where they are.

330
00:11:39,380 --> 00:11:40,630
You know, I can't say I'm --

331
00:11:40,630 --> 00:11:42,660
I'm not a tad bit disappointed in you, Mitchell.

332
00:11:42,660 --> 00:11:44,200
It's just a little lonely going on this journey

333
00:11:44,200 --> 00:11:45,690
of self-improvement all by my--

334
00:11:45,690 --> 00:11:47,690
- What is that? - Hmm? What?

335
00:11:47,690 --> 00:11:49,970
What -- What part of the museum did you get this from?

336
00:11:50,390 --> 00:11:51,760
Uh, well, apparen--

337
00:11:51,760 --> 00:11:52,860
obviously, you're not...

338
00:11:53,190 --> 00:11:55,610
familiar with Matisse's feather...period.

339
00:11:55,610 --> 00:11:58,500
Did you maybe get this across the street from the museum?

340
00:11:58,530 --> 00:11:59,480
Hmm? ‭No.

341
00:11:59,480 --> 00:12:02,690
'Cause if you had, you'd have a distinctive and sparkly...

342
00:12:02,690 --> 00:12:04,090
hand stamp!

343
00:12:04,540 --> 00:12:05,730
I-I just need one ticket.

344
00:12:05,730 --> 00:12:07,250
Oh, my God, you guys, let's hurry!

345
00:12:07,250 --> 00:12:08,200
Hurrying where?

346
00:12:08,200 --> 00:12:09,980
Uh, there's a retrospective --

347
00:12:09,980 --> 00:12:12,900
"Cher in the '70s: Gypsies, Tramps and Thieves."

348
00:12:13,760 --> 00:12:14,990
You went without me?

349
00:12:14,990 --> 00:12:16,490
What do we always say?

350
00:12:16,620 --> 00:12:19,080
Every Cher experience should be

351
00:12:19,080 --> 00:12:21,320
- a shared experience. - Shared experience.

352
00:12:21,570 --> 00:12:22,860
I'm -- I'm sorry, Mitchell.

353
00:12:23,190 --> 00:12:24,920
If I could turn back time --

354
00:12:26,940 --> 00:12:27,670
Knock knock!

355
00:12:27,670 --> 00:12:28,460
Give -- Give me the feather.

356
00:12:28,470 --> 00:12:29,920
No, put the feather in your cap.

357
00:12:30,060 --> 00:12:31,900
Hey, just checking in. How was the museum?

358
00:12:31,900 --> 00:12:33,550
Oh, so great. Sit down!

359
00:12:33,550 --> 00:12:35,960
Cam was actually about to tell us

360
00:12:36,140 --> 00:12:37,710
what he learned about Picasso.

361
00:12:37,710 --> 00:12:39,610
Oh, I know so little about him.

362
00:12:39,640 --> 00:12:43,840
Well, it -- it turns out he was born, um...

363
00:12:44,150 --> 00:12:47,420
in the wagon of a -- of a traveling...show.

364
00:12:47,420 --> 00:12:48,810
His mother, poor thing,

365
00:12:48,810 --> 00:12:51,520
she was forced to dance for all --

366
00:12:51,520 --> 00:12:52,990
You want me to teach you how to play bridge?

367
00:12:52,990 --> 00:12:55,060
- Sure. - ‭I need a new partner.

368
00:12:55,190 --> 00:12:56,640
I keep beating the computer.

369
00:12:56,850 --> 00:12:58,190
Listen, we want to invite you guys

370
00:12:58,190 --> 00:12:59,590
to a dinner party tonight.

371
00:12:59,590 --> 00:13:01,540
Yeah, you guys are gonna love Xander and Mateo.

372
00:13:01,540 --> 00:13:03,690
They just finished an ultramarathon in Mozambique,

373
00:13:03,690 --> 00:13:04,680
where they're lecturing.

374
00:13:04,680 --> 00:13:05,990
And to build up an appetite,

375
00:13:06,000 --> 00:13:07,520
we play sprinting charades.

376
00:13:07,520 --> 00:13:10,210
Yeah, and, uh, this silly version of Celebrity

377
00:13:10,210 --> 00:13:12,650
using only characters from Dickens.

378
00:13:13,170 --> 00:13:13,950
That sounds so fun.

379
00:13:13,950 --> 00:13:14,980
We'll be-We'll be right back.

380
00:13:14,980 --> 00:13:17,960
We were just fanning out some celery on a platter.

381
00:13:20,150 --> 00:13:21,700
Okay, I want them gone.

382
00:13:21,700 --> 00:13:23,390
Even if you mean kill them, I'm in.

383
00:13:23,400 --> 00:13:24,290
I mean, what are we supposed to do?

384
00:13:24,290 --> 00:13:26,260
Spend the next six months with our drapes closed,

385
00:13:26,260 --> 00:13:28,670
like Pepper after one of his cheek implants fell?

386
00:13:28,670 --> 00:13:30,350
Speaking of Picasso.

387
00:13:30,350 --> 00:13:32,590
How are we supposed to get out of this?

388
00:13:32,610 --> 00:13:33,670
Move out west.

389
00:13:34,010 --> 00:13:36,300
That's what those towns are for -- disappearin'.

390
00:13:36,300 --> 00:13:38,530
We live a mile from the ocean. What town?

391
00:13:38,640 --> 00:13:39,920
What's wrong with me?

392
00:13:39,920 --> 00:13:41,920
I am so stupid!

393
00:13:41,970 --> 00:13:43,530
Sweetie, what is it?

394
00:13:43,530 --> 00:13:46,230
She beat me, and she never even played before!

395
00:13:47,370 --> 00:13:50,160
I'm such a loser!

396
00:13:52,170 --> 00:13:54,170
Is she okay, or...?

397
00:13:54,170 --> 00:13:55,300
Vera has this thing

398
00:13:55,300 --> 00:13:57,540
where she needs to be perfect all the time.

399
00:13:57,540 --> 00:13:59,610
You know, the only reason we moved to this neighborhood

400
00:13:59,610 --> 00:14:00,630
was so we could be closer

401
00:14:00,630 --> 00:14:03,340
to this accelerated school she got into.

402
00:14:03,670 --> 00:14:05,920
Maybe we need to reconsider the move?

403
00:14:06,110 --> 00:14:08,560
Naturally, we'll pay for all six months.

404
00:14:08,560 --> 00:14:09,280
Yes.

405
00:14:09,290 --> 00:14:10,330
We should go talk to her.

406
00:14:10,330 --> 00:14:11,360
I'm sorry, guys.

407
00:14:11,360 --> 00:14:13,460
I was looking forward to that celery.

408
00:14:13,460 --> 00:14:16,260
I could really use a cheat day.

409
00:14:16,550 --> 00:14:17,660
Vera?!

410
00:14:17,950 --> 00:14:19,440
Lily, how --

411
00:14:19,440 --> 00:14:21,740
I set up my mirror so I could see her cards.

412
00:14:21,740 --> 00:14:22,680
I had to!

413
00:14:22,680 --> 00:14:25,410
I couldn't stand her making me feel bad about myself.

414
00:14:25,410 --> 00:14:26,530
No, no, I get it.

415
00:14:26,530 --> 00:14:29,440
I'm not sure they don't enjoy making people feel inferior.

416
00:14:29,440 --> 00:14:31,510
Which is something you guys could never do.

417
00:14:34,130 --> 00:14:35,260
Wait, did she just say

418
00:14:35,260 --> 00:14:37,010
that we could never make people feel inferior

419
00:14:37,010 --> 00:14:39,270
because we're so inferior ourselves?

420
00:14:39,270 --> 00:14:42,150
But cleverly wrapped in a compliment to avoid detection?

421
00:14:42,150 --> 00:14:43,880
In other words, the perfect gay zinger?

422
00:14:43,880 --> 00:14:45,150
Well, she may not finish high school,

423
00:14:45,150 --> 00:14:46,960
but she will hold her own at any Tony party

424
00:14:46,960 --> 00:14:48,810
- the rest of her life. - Yeah, she will. Yeah.

425
00:14:49,250 --> 00:14:50,830
I'm really sorry to hear that,

426
00:14:50,830 --> 00:14:53,010
but honestly, if your wife left you

427
00:14:53,010 --> 00:14:54,680
just because you missed her birthday --

428
00:14:54,680 --> 00:14:55,870
To drive you to the airport.

429
00:14:55,870 --> 00:14:57,310
I heard him, Manny. Thank you.

430
00:14:57,830 --> 00:14:59,690
you're probably better off without her.

431
00:14:59,850 --> 00:15:00,770
You're right.

432
00:15:01,120 --> 00:15:02,500
I only wish I had something nicer to wear

433
00:15:02,510 --> 00:15:04,050
to our son's wedding tonight.

434
00:15:04,050 --> 00:15:06,000
You know, you and I are about the same size.

435
00:15:06,000 --> 00:15:07,440
Why don't you borrow my tux?

436
00:15:08,730 --> 00:15:09,630
Really?

437
00:15:09,630 --> 00:15:10,480
I insist.

438
00:15:10,480 --> 00:15:12,550
In fact, I want to give you something else.

439
00:15:12,920 --> 00:15:13,820
Your plane?

440
00:15:13,820 --> 00:15:15,500
Uh, no, I was reaching for my wallet.

441
00:15:15,500 --> 00:15:18,030
You know, to give you that money I s-still owe you for the cab.

442
00:15:18,030 --> 00:15:19,180
I've admired this plane

443
00:15:19,180 --> 00:15:21,060
ever since I fell off the roof getting it for you.

444
00:15:21,060 --> 00:15:22,520
I'm so touched and honored.

445
00:15:22,520 --> 00:15:23,140
Well, actually --

446
00:15:23,140 --> 00:15:24,520
He fell off the roof.

447
00:15:28,650 --> 00:15:29,560
Fine.

448
00:15:30,250 --> 00:15:31,180
Enjoy.

449
00:15:31,390 --> 00:15:34,070
I will name her Roberta.

450
00:15:34,780 --> 00:15:36,080
It's a boy plane.

451
00:15:40,420 --> 00:15:42,000
I feel like I got the buckles wrong.

452
00:15:42,000 --> 00:15:43,790
Does this straitjacket look right on me?

453
00:15:43,790 --> 00:15:45,140
More and more.

454
00:15:45,140 --> 00:15:45,970
Dad, I love you,

455
00:15:45,970 --> 00:15:48,270
but I don't have time for another magic trick.

456
00:15:48,270 --> 00:15:49,460
I can't find my ID,

457
00:15:49,470 --> 00:15:51,510
and I need a copy of it for this NASA job,

458
00:15:51,510 --> 00:15:53,930
and my application has to be mailed by 5:00.

459
00:15:53,930 --> 00:15:55,640
I'm sorry. Can I help you look?

460
00:15:56,530 --> 00:15:57,540
This is hopeless.

461
00:15:57,640 --> 00:15:59,220
Unless there is some way to jump the line

462
00:15:59,220 --> 00:16:01,730
at both the post office and the DMV,

463
00:16:01,740 --> 00:16:04,290
and the only way to get to either of them at this hour

464
00:16:04,290 --> 00:16:05,780
is to drive in the carpool lane.

465
00:16:05,780 --> 00:16:07,360
We're ba-a-ck!

466
00:16:07,750 --> 00:16:10,270
Oh, my God! I missed you so much!

467
00:16:10,270 --> 00:16:13,410
Oh, I got this. You look so tired.

468
00:16:13,410 --> 00:16:14,650
But I've been napping all day.

469
00:16:14,650 --> 00:16:15,550
You're welcome.

470
00:16:16,860 --> 00:16:18,710
Can I at least smell their heads?!

471
00:16:19,420 --> 00:16:20,040
Nestor?

472
00:16:20,040 --> 00:16:22,110
Hi. It's Gloria Pritchett again.

473
00:16:22,110 --> 00:16:23,810
Please call me back.

474
00:16:23,820 --> 00:16:25,490
I need to explain.

475
00:16:25,490 --> 00:16:27,520
This was all a big mistake.

476
00:16:27,520 --> 00:16:30,000
Nestor, where are you, my love?

477
00:16:30,010 --> 00:16:30,890
Ay, no.

478
00:16:32,740 --> 00:16:33,770
Sonia...

479
00:16:34,280 --> 00:16:36,860
I have very bad news to tell you.

480
00:16:36,860 --> 00:16:38,380
Let me get Nestor. He's my rock.

481
00:16:38,390 --> 00:16:39,350
Nestor!

482
00:16:39,350 --> 00:16:42,180
Ay, what happened to my independent sister

483
00:16:42,180 --> 00:16:44,830
that I admired so much because she needed no man?

484
00:16:44,830 --> 00:16:46,410
Where...is he?

485
00:16:46,420 --> 00:16:48,480
Well, I thought he was a gold digger,

486
00:16:48,480 --> 00:16:50,120
so I chased him out.

487
00:16:50,120 --> 00:16:51,270
You did what?!

488
00:16:51,270 --> 00:16:54,890
But the silver lining is that you still have all your money!

489
00:16:54,890 --> 00:16:57,600
What money? I don't have any money!

490
00:16:57,600 --> 00:16:58,180
What do you mean?

491
00:16:58,180 --> 00:17:01,270
The money from the hot-sauce business that you're doing so well.

492
00:17:01,270 --> 00:17:02,390
No, it was all a lie.

493
00:17:02,390 --> 00:17:04,260
I just didn't want him to be suspicious.

494
00:17:04,260 --> 00:17:06,360
Look, I'm wearing aluminum earrings!

495
00:17:06,360 --> 00:17:08,160
They're turning my ears green!

496
00:17:09,170 --> 00:17:13,220
It took me two years to land that rich, beautiful moron.

497
00:17:13,220 --> 00:17:15,910
Where am I going to get that kind of money?!

498
00:17:18,670 --> 00:17:19,850
Oh, I tripped!

499
00:17:19,850 --> 00:17:21,340
Someone call a lawyer!

500
00:17:21,340 --> 00:17:22,260
You didn't trip.

501
00:17:22,260 --> 00:17:23,600
Yes, I did! Look!

502
00:17:23,600 --> 00:17:25,120
Uh, the floor is all wet.

503
00:17:25,610 --> 00:17:28,830
Sonia, that didn't work at the Princess Cruise ship,

504
00:17:28,830 --> 00:17:30,560
and it's not going to work here.

505
00:17:30,890 --> 00:17:33,010
Every time I try to get my life together,

506
00:17:33,010 --> 00:17:34,620
you always ruin it for me.

507
00:17:34,670 --> 00:17:36,220
You owe me a rich husband.

508
00:17:36,220 --> 00:17:37,390
I'll find you one.

509
00:17:37,390 --> 00:17:40,060
There are plenty of old, rich men around here

510
00:17:40,070 --> 00:17:41,730
that would do anything that you say.

511
00:17:41,730 --> 00:17:43,220
Some of them can still hear.

512
00:17:43,770 --> 00:17:45,500
Oh. Who's this?

513
00:17:45,740 --> 00:17:46,740
He's, um...

514
00:17:48,490 --> 00:17:50,480
He's the best hedge guy in town.

515
00:17:50,480 --> 00:17:53,410
Congratulate him. He just got a new plane.

516
00:17:54,330 --> 00:17:55,640
Ohh. A hedge guy.

517
00:17:55,640 --> 00:17:56,960
Fascinating.

518
00:17:56,960 --> 00:17:59,240
And how did you get started in that business?

519
00:17:59,240 --> 00:18:00,720
I bought the clippers.

520
00:18:02,410 --> 00:18:04,940
And where are you going, dressed so nice?

521
00:18:04,940 --> 00:18:05,800
A wedding.

522
00:18:05,800 --> 00:18:07,300
Ohh, I love weddings.

523
00:18:07,300 --> 00:18:08,340
Would you like to accompany me?

524
00:18:08,340 --> 00:18:10,260
I would love to!

525
00:18:10,260 --> 00:18:11,540
And can we take your plane?

526
00:18:11,540 --> 00:18:12,520
Yeah, sure.

527
00:18:14,770 --> 00:18:17,230
Why is our gardener wearing your tuxedo?

528
00:18:17,230 --> 00:18:19,110
Why is Nestor gone?

529
00:18:19,350 --> 00:18:20,920
Let me lock the door first.

530
00:18:22,010 --> 00:18:24,520
Gloria! You ruined my life again!

531
00:18:26,440 --> 00:18:27,890
Is this your ring?

532
00:18:28,800 --> 00:18:29,720
It is!

533
00:18:32,230 --> 00:18:33,780
Is this your sock?

534
00:18:34,610 --> 00:18:35,550
It is.

535
00:18:38,730 --> 00:18:40,860
Is this...your card?

536
00:18:40,860 --> 00:18:42,320
I don't remember!

537
00:18:42,770 --> 00:18:45,460
Now everything is where it belongs.

538
00:18:45,460 --> 00:18:49,240
Except for this candle, which obviously belongs...

539
00:18:50,810 --> 00:18:52,420
...on the piano!

540
00:18:52,420 --> 00:18:54,050
- Oh, my God! ‭- What?!

541
00:18:54,050 --> 00:18:57,060
You're right. It's like I want to fail!

542
00:18:57,060 --> 00:18:59,540
Dad, stop being crazy. Your act is great!

543
00:18:59,540 --> 00:19:02,210
It's a flat finish, which means it's a flat act.

544
00:19:02,210 --> 00:19:04,190
It's obviously two candles.

545
00:19:04,430 --> 00:19:06,540
I put the second one over there while I was distracting you

546
00:19:06,540 --> 00:19:08,970
by throwing a card into that stupid grape.

547
00:19:10,550 --> 00:19:11,370
We're home!

548
00:19:11,370 --> 00:19:13,140
My babies!

549
00:19:13,150 --> 00:19:16,340
I feel like I haven't seen you all day!

550
00:19:16,340 --> 00:19:18,090
Did you have fun today?

551
00:19:18,100 --> 00:19:19,410
Well, that's easy to find out.

552
00:19:19,410 --> 00:19:21,860
Let me just upload this baby cam footage.

553
00:19:21,910 --> 00:19:23,240
The what -- what was that? ‭Hmm?

554
00:19:23,240 --> 00:19:25,220
Oh, one of their buttons is actually a camera.

555
00:19:25,220 --> 00:19:26,610
It's not the greatest quality, but...

556
00:19:26,610 --> 00:19:29,790
Wait, you took my babies to a liquor store?!

557
00:19:29,790 --> 00:19:30,990
No, it's the --

558
00:19:31,660 --> 00:19:33,150
it's the wine museum.

559
00:19:33,160 --> 00:19:34,580
It's Ace Liquor, Luke.

560
00:19:34,580 --> 00:19:36,400
I've been going there since I was 15...

561
00:19:36,400 --> 00:19:38,460
minutes past my 21st birthday.

562
00:19:38,460 --> 00:19:39,680
Well, I am horrified --

563
00:19:39,680 --> 00:19:41,260
Wait, wait, wait, I just fast-forwarded,

564
00:19:41,260 --> 00:19:44,020
and it's you talking to some lady at a yoga class.

565
00:19:44,020 --> 00:19:45,100
She's from the magazine!

566
00:19:45,100 --> 00:19:47,490
You pimped out my babies for a sales pitch?

567
00:19:47,490 --> 00:19:48,690
Who did it hurt?

568
00:19:50,400 --> 00:19:51,120
Poppy!

569
00:19:51,120 --> 00:19:53,320
Oh, disgusting. Personally, I can't stand --

570
00:19:53,320 --> 00:19:54,940
Some guard at the DMV

571
00:19:54,940 --> 00:19:57,710
giving our five-month-old a bite of his hot dog.

572
00:19:57,710 --> 00:19:59,380
He only watched them for a second.

573
00:20:00,190 --> 00:20:03,380
I was so happy you all wanted time with the babies today,

574
00:20:03,380 --> 00:20:05,300
because lately, it has felt like

575
00:20:05,300 --> 00:20:07,520
you didn't even want to be bothered with them.

576
00:20:07,520 --> 00:20:10,600
Turns out you only want to help when it can help you.

577
00:20:10,600 --> 00:20:13,340
Part of me wonders why we even stay here.

578
00:20:13,340 --> 00:20:15,050
Because you eat and live here for free?

579
00:20:15,060 --> 00:20:16,020
I said "part."

580
00:20:16,020 --> 00:20:18,360
Okay, I'm not saying what they did was great,

581
00:20:18,360 --> 00:20:19,850
but isn't that what families do?

582
00:20:20,260 --> 00:20:21,400
Help each other out?

583
00:20:21,400 --> 00:20:23,350
And are we ever really too young

584
00:20:23,350 --> 00:20:25,810
to come to our family's aid?

585
00:20:26,850 --> 00:20:28,420
You're not seriously trying to get us

586
00:20:28,420 --> 00:20:31,110
to let you use them for your magic trick, are you?

587
00:20:32,710 --> 00:20:34,090
It is my card!

588
00:20:36,620 --> 00:20:38,340
You guys have been great.

589
00:20:38,410 --> 00:20:41,190
But I should be getting my beautiful assistant here

590
00:20:41,190 --> 00:20:46,160
out of this tuxedo and into some warm jammies.

591
00:20:52,720 --> 00:20:53,720
You guys.

592
00:20:54,320 --> 00:20:55,830
It's you that make it work.

593
00:20:59,640 --> 00:21:01,910
So, I'm sorry about earlier. I hope I wasn't rude.

594
00:21:01,940 --> 00:21:03,930
Please. I totally get it. Are you free for a bite now?

595
00:21:04,820 --> 00:21:06,850
Sure. I guess I got a couple minutes.

596
00:21:06,850 --> 00:21:08,130
Perfect!

597
00:21:08,130 --> 00:21:10,240
I'll get us a table at Straight to the Tapas.

598
00:21:10,240 --> 00:21:11,550
Great. Meet you there.

599
00:21:12,200 --> 00:21:13,880
I'm just getting rid of him. We're not going.

600
00:21:13,880 --> 00:21:14,630
Oh, thank God.

601
00:21:14,630 --> 00:21:15,830
When his shirt rose up earlier,

602
00:21:15,830 --> 00:21:17,560
I saw a Dora the Explorer tattoo.

603
00:21:17,560 --> 00:21:19,980
And I do not want to hear the story behind that one.

604
00:21:24,500 --> 00:21:26,040
This stays between us.

