1
00:00:09,990 --> 00:00:14,990
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

2
00:00:09,990 --> 00:00:14,990
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

3
00:00:09,990 --> 00:00:14,990
{\an5}{\pos(145,227)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

4
00:00:10,490 --> 00:00:14,990
{\pos(67,223)}m 50 0 l 179 0 b 208 0 229 21 229 50 l 229 179 b 229 208 208 228 179 228 l 50 228 b 21 228 0 208 0 179 l 0 50 b 0 21 21 0 50 0

5
00:00:10,490 --> 00:00:14,990
{\pos(67,223)}m 0 0 b 1 -1 2 -2 4 -1 b 7 1 3 2 5 5 b 6 7 8 7 9 5 l 15 -6 b 18 -7 20 -6 20 -3 b 19 -1 17 2 17 4 b 16 7 20 7 21 6 b 22 4 23 2 25 -1 b 27 -2 29 -1 29 1 b 29 2 28 3 29 5 b 30 7 32 7 33 6 b 34 5 34 4 35 3 b 37 2 39 3 39 5 b 39 6 38 8 37 9 b 34 13 29 13 25 9 b 22 13 17 13 13 9 b 10 13 3 13 0 8 

6
00:00:10,490 --> 00:00:14,990
{\pos(84,223)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

9
00:00:15,990 --> 00:00:46,500
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

10
00:00:15,490 --> 00:00:46,500
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

20
00:00:05,100 --> 00:00:06,480
Are -- Are you awake?

21
00:00:06,550 --> 00:00:08,830
I slept for six minutes two hours ago.

22
00:00:08,920 --> 00:00:10,460
I'm gonna have to take a sleeping pill,

23
00:00:10,460 --> 00:00:11,910
which means you're gonna have to hide my car keys,

24
00:00:11,910 --> 00:00:14,000
laptop, and Reba McEntire wig.

25
00:00:14,870 --> 00:00:16,390
It's been a crazy couple days.

26
00:00:16,390 --> 00:00:17,900
Uh, yesterday, I found out I didn't get

27
00:00:17,900 --> 00:00:20,660
the college football coaching job that I had been chasing.

28
00:00:20,660 --> 00:00:22,180
I was -- I was devastated.

29
00:00:22,190 --> 00:00:22,990
And moments before that,

30
00:00:22,990 --> 00:00:25,150
we got a phone call from our old adoption agency

31
00:00:25,150 --> 00:00:27,430
with the opportunity for us to adopt a baby boy.

32
00:00:27,430 --> 00:00:29,320
So, a door closes...

33
00:00:29,320 --> 00:00:32,000
A window opens. But do you answer it?

34
00:00:32,000 --> 00:00:33,730
You don't answer windows.

35
00:00:34,110 --> 00:00:36,630
Well, how fun for you. Cam made a little mistake.

36
00:00:37,740 --> 00:00:40,620
I keep making lists of all the pros and cons in my head.

37
00:00:40,620 --> 00:00:42,650
Uh, the -- the way a baby smells is on both.

38
00:00:42,650 --> 00:00:44,830
Okay, alright. Pros, go.

39
00:00:44,830 --> 00:00:47,700
Okay, well, a baby to love. The sound of giggling.

40
00:00:47,700 --> 00:00:49,400
‭You know, a bigger family,

41
00:00:49,400 --> 00:00:52,430
an extra vote on whether to pull the plug on us when we get old.

42
00:00:52,430 --> 00:00:54,340
I'm worried that Lily has an itchy trigger finger.

43
00:00:54,340 --> 00:00:55,890
Yeah, and another child would help us figure out

44
00:00:55,900 --> 00:00:57,570
how much of Lily's personality is our fault

45
00:00:57,570 --> 00:00:58,420
and what's on her.

46
00:00:58,420 --> 00:00:59,650
It would be nice to be vindicated.

47
00:00:59,650 --> 00:01:01,830
Okay, other pros -- Christmases.

48
00:01:02,540 --> 00:01:05,380
Dipping little toes into the ocean for the first time,

49
00:01:05,440 --> 00:01:07,620
the way a toddler run towards the door

50
00:01:07,620 --> 00:01:09,940
in their jammies saying, "Daddy!"

51
00:01:10,040 --> 00:01:11,270
Okay, you'd better hit me with some cons.

52
00:01:11,270 --> 00:01:12,430
I'm practically ovulating.

53
00:01:12,430 --> 00:01:15,800
Okay, no sleep, car seats, diapers,

54
00:01:15,800 --> 00:01:18,780
coughs and colds, all -- all the doctor's appointments,

55
00:01:18,780 --> 00:01:21,090
- plastic toys everywhere. - Everywhere.

56
00:01:21,090 --> 00:01:22,760
Our -- Our place is already too small.

57
00:01:22,830 --> 00:01:24,270
We don't have enough bedrooms.

58
00:01:25,580 --> 00:01:27,080
Oh, God, the clock is ticking.

59
00:01:27,080 --> 00:01:28,770
We have half a day to give them an answer.

60
00:01:28,770 --> 00:01:30,260
Okay, you know what, no thinking.

61
00:01:30,470 --> 00:01:33,420
On the count of three, say yes or no.

62
00:01:34,510 --> 00:01:36,310
One, two, three...

63
00:01:37,610 --> 00:01:39,210
- I don't know. - ‭I can't decide!

64
00:01:53,970 --> 00:01:56,780
Why is there a black Suburban outside with a driver?

65
00:01:56,780 --> 00:01:58,030
My company sent it.

66
00:01:58,310 --> 00:02:00,460
I'm manning the Helo Dynamics booth

67
00:02:00,470 --> 00:02:02,140
for the job recruitment fair at Caltech.

68
00:02:03,130 --> 00:02:06,980
Look at you, being chauffeured in a giant SUV.

69
00:02:07,060 --> 00:02:09,600
When I picture you driving, you're crying in a Prius.

70
00:02:09,600 --> 00:02:11,580
I do cry less when I'm driven.

71
00:02:11,580 --> 00:02:13,790
And that outfit is on point.

72
00:02:13,790 --> 00:02:16,870
Well, I mean, it's -- it's sort of a triumphant return for me.

73
00:02:16,880 --> 00:02:19,800
I spent four years there in sweats, with greasy hair,

74
00:02:19,810 --> 00:02:21,490
caring only about grades.

75
00:02:21,490 --> 00:02:22,790
The only time anyone ever noticed me

76
00:02:22,790 --> 00:02:25,890
was when I pulled out all my eyebrows during finals week.

77
00:02:26,120 --> 00:02:29,440
Now I have a big job, swanky apartment,

78
00:02:29,440 --> 00:02:31,730
shoes that cost more than my first laptop...

79
00:02:31,730 --> 00:02:33,460
Oh, it's like a rom-com --

80
00:02:33,460 --> 00:02:36,240
you left a nerd and returned a hot nerd.

81
00:02:37,050 --> 00:02:38,250
Speaking of hot people,

82
00:02:38,250 --> 00:02:40,350
maybe I should go and recruit for NERP.

83
00:02:40,350 --> 00:02:41,020
For legal reasons,

84
00:02:41,020 --> 00:02:43,560
we need a science-y person to endorse product.

85
00:02:43,560 --> 00:02:45,800
Considering we're all a bunch of people who didn't graduate college,

86
00:02:45,800 --> 00:02:48,070
we sell a lot of products that go inside of you.

87
00:02:48,070 --> 00:02:50,810
Yeah, no, it doesn't really work that way.

88
00:02:50,810 --> 00:02:52,430
A, you have to be invited,

89
00:02:52,430 --> 00:02:54,610
and B, no self-respecting scientist

90
00:02:54,620 --> 00:02:56,960
is going to endorse the nonsense your company is pushing.

91
00:02:56,960 --> 00:02:59,800
Excuse me, but our copper-infused toothpaste

92
00:02:59,800 --> 00:03:03,100
is on the FDA's top ten items to watch, so...

93
00:03:05,040 --> 00:03:06,930
Phil! Phil, can you come in here?

94
00:03:07,060 --> 00:03:10,510
I've worked up a little presentation for my Skype interview,

95
00:03:10,510 --> 00:03:12,130
and I would love to get your feedback.

96
00:03:12,130 --> 00:03:13,410
Yes, please!

97
00:03:13,420 --> 00:03:15,900
You've been such a cheerleader for me with all my magic shows

98
00:03:15,900 --> 00:03:18,210
and SCARB dinners, I'd love to be yours.

99
00:03:18,210 --> 00:03:19,000
Hit it.

100
00:03:19,490 --> 00:03:21,060
I'm gonna stop you right there.

101
00:03:22,220 --> 00:03:23,870
I've been out of work for a few months,

102
00:03:23,870 --> 00:03:25,580
and I've gotten kinda antsy.

103
00:03:25,580 --> 00:03:29,260
To channel my anxiety, I have cleaned, I have organized.

104
00:03:29,260 --> 00:03:31,180
Perhaps a bit obsessively.

105
00:03:31,180 --> 00:03:32,330
Doctors were consulted.

106
00:03:32,330 --> 00:03:34,800
One -- a therapist, so not even a real doctor.

107
00:03:34,800 --> 00:03:36,680
But meds were quickly dismissed.

108
00:03:36,680 --> 00:03:39,030
We didn't want the sexual side effects.

109
00:03:39,040 --> 00:03:40,220
Anyway...

110
00:03:40,220 --> 00:03:43,660
I am going to channel my anxiety into a career.

111
00:03:43,660 --> 00:03:45,980
I am interviewing for my dream job --

112
00:03:45,990 --> 00:03:51,750
Senior VP of my favorite organizing chain store, organize 'Em!

113
00:03:51,750 --> 00:03:53,410
I'm so excited, I could have an organaz--

114
00:03:53,410 --> 00:03:54,640
You're better than that.

115
00:03:56,800 --> 00:03:57,760
So, throughout the call,

116
00:03:57,760 --> 00:04:00,250
I'm gonna be referring to this organizational system

117
00:04:00,250 --> 00:04:03,520
that I created using the Organize 'Em products.

118
00:04:03,520 --> 00:04:05,480
- Smart. - ‭Yeah. Watch.

119
00:04:06,030 --> 00:04:08,380
Oh, Ms. Beckman, what an interesting point.

120
00:04:08,380 --> 00:04:11,130
I should jot that down.

121
00:04:18,410 --> 00:04:19,650
What the hell is that?

122
00:04:21,740 --> 00:04:23,240
Oh, my God. What?

123
00:04:23,240 --> 00:04:25,910
Oh, yeah, I forgot to tell you, your dad came over to help me.

124
00:04:25,910 --> 00:04:27,100
I gotta fix that step.

125
00:04:27,100 --> 00:04:28,120
It splintered.

126
00:04:28,120 --> 00:04:30,430
I wiped out this morning and landed on my head.

127
00:04:30,430 --> 00:04:31,280
Yeah, but my call.

128
00:04:31,280 --> 00:04:34,030
We gotta take care of that before someone gets hurt.

129
00:04:34,030 --> 00:04:34,880
Someone did.

130
00:04:34,880 --> 00:04:36,560
I mean, what if it was Haley with the babies? Or Dylan?

131
00:04:36,560 --> 00:04:38,380
- Or...? - ‭Or me. I threw up.

132
00:04:38,380 --> 00:04:41,440
Holy Moses. Gloria was here yesterday in heels.

133
00:04:41,440 --> 00:04:42,750
That could've been ugly.

134
00:04:42,750 --> 00:04:43,960
I'm sleepy.

135
00:04:43,990 --> 00:04:46,240
Buddy, you gotta move. Someone's gonna trip over you.

136
00:04:46,240 --> 00:04:48,280
Hey, guys, we can't do this right now, okay?

137
00:04:48,280 --> 00:04:50,880
I've got -- I've got an interview at 1:23.

138
00:04:50,880 --> 00:04:51,950
Well, that's specific.

139
00:04:51,950 --> 00:04:53,620
No, not for Audrey Beckman.

140
00:04:53,620 --> 00:04:56,060
Her whole life is scheduled down to the second.

141
00:04:56,060 --> 00:04:57,850
She's a god to OCD people.

142
00:04:57,860 --> 00:04:59,120
Why do you think I've got that bumper sticker

143
00:04:59,120 --> 00:05:01,860
that says "Straighten It Like Beckman"?

144
00:05:01,860 --> 00:05:03,350
Can I come down now?

145
00:05:03,350 --> 00:05:05,370
If I don't have the babies' bottles when they wake up,

146
00:05:05,370 --> 00:05:06,270
they're mean.

147
00:05:06,270 --> 00:05:08,430
You're not even in the terrible twos yet.

148
00:05:08,430 --> 00:05:09,970
Oh, when do those start?

149
00:05:09,970 --> 00:05:11,560
Okay, look, it's almost time.

150
00:05:11,570 --> 00:05:13,590
Just please, nobody make any noise,

151
00:05:13,590 --> 00:05:14,750
nobody go in that office.

152
00:05:14,750 --> 00:05:16,570
I have all my ducks in a row.

153
00:05:16,570 --> 00:05:18,240
I'm just gonna run upstairs and change my shirt.

154
00:05:18,240 --> 00:05:19,490
Oh, okay, but be careful.

155
00:05:19,490 --> 00:05:21,390
I know what I'm doing, I have got this.

156
00:05:22,370 --> 00:05:23,620
Oh, boy! Oh, God!

157
00:05:23,620 --> 00:05:25,000
My leg is stuck!

158
00:05:25,000 --> 00:05:26,270
Somebody do something!

159
00:05:26,480 --> 00:05:28,050
I'm really good at getting rings off.

160
00:05:28,060 --> 00:05:29,920
Do you want me to butter your thighs?

161
00:05:30,110 --> 00:05:32,100
Hey, Dylan, sometimes I like to play things out

162
00:05:32,100 --> 00:05:34,310
in my head first, if that's helpful.

163
00:05:36,270 --> 00:05:39,590
Hey, honey, uh, we need to talk to you about something.

164
00:05:39,590 --> 00:05:40,890
Sweetie, this is something pretty big,

165
00:05:40,890 --> 00:05:42,670
and I -- I want you to brace yourself.

166
00:05:44,470 --> 00:05:46,070
The adoption agency called --

167
00:05:46,080 --> 00:05:47,200
I'm not going back!

168
00:05:47,200 --> 00:05:50,270
Do you know what happens to soft, entitled kids in Da Nang?

169
00:05:50,270 --> 00:05:52,130
No, no, no, no, no, no! No, no.

170
00:05:52,130 --> 00:05:53,390
N-No. No.

171
00:05:54,420 --> 00:05:55,730
There's a baby boy --

172
00:05:57,400 --> 00:05:58,630
I think you should do it.

173
00:05:58,670 --> 00:06:00,190
- Really? Just -- Just like that? - ‭What?

174
00:06:00,190 --> 00:06:02,620
Whatever stops you dropping by my sleepovers.

175
00:06:02,620 --> 00:06:04,330
You guys are way too focused on me.

176
00:06:04,330 --> 00:06:06,260
Plus, I think it'd be fun to have a baby brother.

177
00:06:06,260 --> 00:06:07,540
‭Although...

178
00:06:08,170 --> 00:06:09,240
Although what?

179
00:06:09,240 --> 00:06:11,940
Aren't you guys kind of old to be having a baby?

180
00:06:11,940 --> 00:06:14,140
I'm getting into the juicy part of my teen years.

181
00:06:14,140 --> 00:06:15,930
I don't want to have to take over for you.

182
00:06:15,930 --> 00:06:18,180
Okay, we are not that old.

183
00:06:18,180 --> 00:06:19,390
You're like 50.

184
00:06:19,410 --> 00:06:21,330
Oh, my God! No!

185
00:06:21,580 --> 00:06:23,640
Daddy's 44, and I'm 48.

186
00:06:23,640 --> 00:06:26,450
You do realize when the baby's a senior in high school,

187
00:06:26,450 --> 00:06:28,070
you guys will be senior citizens?

188
00:06:28,070 --> 00:06:29,830
We will not be senior c--

189
00:06:29,830 --> 00:06:31,820
- Cam. - ‭Sixty-six.

190
00:06:31,820 --> 00:06:32,900
I'll be sixty-six.

191
00:06:32,900 --> 00:06:33,850
And I'll be sixty-one.

192
00:06:33,850 --> 00:06:34,650
Well, sixty-two.

193
00:06:34,660 --> 00:06:35,920
Not until June!

194
00:06:39,130 --> 00:06:42,190
It's not working! My leg is really stuck in there!

195
00:06:42,190 --> 00:06:44,280
It might be time to return to my idea.

196
00:06:44,290 --> 00:06:45,630
I'm not cutting my leg off.

197
00:06:45,630 --> 00:06:48,000
Think about how fast you would run with a robot leg.

198
00:06:48,000 --> 00:06:50,640
Luke, your mom's not getting a robot leg!

199
00:06:50,760 --> 00:06:52,970
She'd need two, or she'd just run in circles.

200
00:06:52,970 --> 00:06:54,180
Come on, let's check under the stairs.

201
00:06:54,180 --> 00:06:55,870
Yes, please, and hurry!

202
00:06:56,150 --> 00:06:57,860
What the hell's the matter with this house?

203
00:06:58,430 --> 00:07:00,430
How could two steps be broken?

204
00:07:03,340 --> 00:07:06,470
My God, the humidity. My hair's gonna frizz out.

205
00:07:06,470 --> 00:07:08,510
That's why I never show any pictures from 'Nam.

206
00:07:08,510 --> 00:07:10,780
Oh, no, I totally forgot about the humidifier

207
00:07:10,780 --> 00:07:12,300
for my mushroom log.

208
00:07:13,190 --> 00:07:14,830
It needed darkness and moisture.

209
00:07:14,830 --> 00:07:16,360
It must have rotted the wood.

210
00:07:18,630 --> 00:07:21,640
Wow, honey, you're really wedged in here tight.

211
00:07:21,640 --> 00:07:22,700
Yeah, no kidding.

212
00:07:22,980 --> 00:07:25,270
Why can't you buy your mushrooms at a store,

213
00:07:25,270 --> 00:07:26,870
like a normal person?

214
00:07:26,870 --> 00:07:28,120
Store-bought mushrooms?

215
00:07:28,140 --> 00:07:30,440
You really don't get my generation, Boomer.

216
00:07:30,670 --> 00:07:32,250
Maybe this'll enlighten you.

217
00:07:32,620 --> 00:07:33,410
Open up.

218
00:07:33,410 --> 00:07:34,320
Get your hand away from my --

219
00:07:34,320 --> 00:07:35,570
Open up!

220
00:07:39,580 --> 00:07:40,630
That's damn good.

221
00:07:41,130 --> 00:07:43,310
Why do I always default to "No"?

222
00:07:43,310 --> 00:07:46,920
Is Gloria right? Should I try slim-cut jeans?

223
00:07:47,570 --> 00:07:49,640
Guys! What's going on down there?!

224
00:07:49,640 --> 00:07:51,890
Your foot's stuck between two copper pipes.

225
00:07:51,890 --> 00:07:52,860
We're gonna have to cut it.

226
00:07:52,860 --> 00:07:54,850
It might take a while.

227
00:07:54,860 --> 00:07:56,370
I don't have a while!

228
00:07:56,550 --> 00:07:58,970
I can't believe this. I'm going to miss my interview.

229
00:07:58,970 --> 00:08:01,020
And this was my dream job!

230
00:08:01,020 --> 00:08:03,070
I was gonna get to organize the whole world.

231
00:08:03,070 --> 00:08:05,620
And now everything is gonna stay so messy.

232
00:08:05,620 --> 00:08:06,820
Can't you just reschedule it?

233
00:08:06,820 --> 00:08:09,330
No! Phil, I'd look like a flake!

234
00:08:09,330 --> 00:08:10,860
This is an organizational company,

235
00:08:10,860 --> 00:08:12,960
not the loosey-goosey world of real estate,

236
00:08:12,960 --> 00:08:15,030
where everything's "See you noon to three,

237
00:08:15,030 --> 00:08:16,400
and I'll bring the cookies"!

238
00:08:16,790 --> 00:08:18,190
Sorry. I'm lashing out.

239
00:08:18,190 --> 00:08:19,580
No, it's okay. The lion doesn't lose sleep

240
00:08:19,580 --> 00:08:21,000
over the opinions of sheep.

241
00:08:21,010 --> 00:08:23,290
Honey, just take the call from there.

242
00:08:23,290 --> 00:08:26,490
How ridiculous would I look taking a call on stairs?

243
00:08:26,490 --> 00:08:28,780
Plus, I need my shelves, 'cause I had this whole thing

244
00:08:28,780 --> 00:08:30,510
worked out with the products and --

245
00:08:30,510 --> 00:08:31,820
You don't need gimmicks!

246
00:08:32,000 --> 00:08:35,150
You were the C.E.O. for Pritchett's freakin' Closets.

247
00:08:35,150 --> 00:08:36,850
You know how many people can say that?

248
00:08:36,980 --> 00:08:37,970
Me and you!

249
00:08:38,150 --> 00:08:39,850
And Margaret every five years,

250
00:08:39,850 --> 00:08:41,820
when I went under for my colonoscopy.

251
00:08:42,360 --> 00:08:44,350
Fine. Give me my phone.

252
00:08:44,350 --> 00:08:46,950
I'll bomb the interview from right here.

253
00:08:48,670 --> 00:08:51,140
She's lost her confidence. She needs those shelves.

254
00:08:51,140 --> 00:08:52,830
You know what, if she can't get to the office,

255
00:08:52,830 --> 00:08:54,650
we can bring the office to her.

256
00:08:56,740 --> 00:08:57,800
You're staring.

257
00:08:58,190 --> 00:08:59,740
I'm frizzing, aren't I?

258
00:09:01,570 --> 00:09:04,650
I've got to admit, walking onto that campus...

259
00:09:04,780 --> 00:09:07,420
All those eyes on me, the adoration...

260
00:09:07,420 --> 00:09:09,270
It felt good. It felt right.

261
00:09:09,340 --> 00:09:12,530
Like I had earned everything that was coming my way.

262
00:09:12,890 --> 00:09:14,050
You suck!

263
00:09:15,320 --> 00:09:17,100
No! You!

264
00:09:17,410 --> 00:09:17,980
What?

265
00:09:17,980 --> 00:09:20,390
Helo Dynamics is evil!

266
00:09:20,390 --> 00:09:22,320
Excuse me? We help people.

267
00:09:22,320 --> 00:09:25,710
Yeah! People like fascists, dictators, oligarchs.

268
00:09:25,710 --> 00:09:27,150
What are you talking about?

269
00:09:27,150 --> 00:09:28,720
We make things like facial scanners

270
00:09:28,720 --> 00:09:31,350
that detect predisposition to genetic diseases.

271
00:09:31,360 --> 00:09:32,710
Which oppressive governments use

272
00:09:32,710 --> 00:09:35,040
to identify political dissidents.

273
00:09:35,610 --> 00:09:39,030
Well, I mean, it's also used on video chats

274
00:09:39,030 --> 00:09:40,550
to turn yourself into a unicorn.

275
00:09:40,550 --> 00:09:41,910
Name one thing more fun!

276
00:09:41,910 --> 00:09:45,120
Why don't you walk your fancy shoes outta here, you sellout?!

277
00:09:45,120 --> 00:09:46,900
Why is someone wearing socks and sandals

278
00:09:46,900 --> 00:09:48,370
yelling at your fabulous shoes?

279
00:09:48,380 --> 00:09:49,600
- Sellout! - I don't know!

280
00:09:49,820 --> 00:09:51,010
And what are you doing here?

281
00:09:51,010 --> 00:09:52,390
Well, I'm recruiting for NERP.

282
00:09:52,390 --> 00:09:54,230
I told you I need a science-y person.

283
00:09:54,230 --> 00:09:56,890
You can't just saunter in here. You have to be approved.

284
00:09:56,900 --> 00:09:59,370
Oh. Hey, kid. You don't care what you look lik. You must be smart.

285
00:09:59,380 --> 00:10:00,930
Want to work at a place that has a lot of hot girls?

286
00:10:00,930 --> 00:10:01,740
Stop it!

287
00:10:01,740 --> 00:10:04,250
Could you make this horrible situation any worse?

288
00:10:04,250 --> 00:10:07,930
Hell no, Helo! It's time you go!

289
00:10:07,930 --> 00:10:11,290
- I didn't do that. - Hell no, Helo, it's time you go!

290
00:10:11,650 --> 00:10:13,370
I've never seen nerds swarm like this before!

291
00:10:13,370 --> 00:10:15,640
We're not typically a clustering people.

292
00:10:15,640 --> 00:10:16,820
Oh, my God. It's Arvin.

293
00:10:16,920 --> 00:10:18,810
Oh, no. I emailed him I'd be here.

294
00:10:18,810 --> 00:10:20,990
Oh, this is gonna be so awkward for me!

295
00:10:20,990 --> 00:10:23,240
The last time I saw him, I broke his heart.

296
00:10:23,240 --> 00:10:24,300
Awkward for you?

297
00:10:24,300 --> 00:10:27,180
These people hate me so much, they're making eye contact!

298
00:10:27,820 --> 00:10:29,250
Alex? Hi!

299
00:10:29,600 --> 00:10:30,750
What's all the com--

300
00:10:30,960 --> 00:10:31,960
Haley.

301
00:10:32,320 --> 00:10:34,160
Arvin. Hi.

302
00:10:34,160 --> 00:10:35,410
I didn't know you'd be here.

303
00:10:35,410 --> 00:10:37,380
This isn't going to be easy to say.

304
00:10:37,550 --> 00:10:39,400
I got married, and I have twins.

305
00:10:39,400 --> 00:10:40,490
I know. Yes.

306
00:10:40,500 --> 00:10:43,430
It was the lead story in Dylan's holiday newsletter.

307
00:10:43,430 --> 00:10:45,660
You sure you haven't been stalking a little?

308
00:10:45,660 --> 00:10:47,290
No. No, that's why.

309
00:10:49,270 --> 00:10:51,080
Alex, is this directed at you?

310
00:10:51,170 --> 00:10:52,930
Yes. Yes, it is.

311
00:10:52,930 --> 00:10:55,270
And they are so mean!

312
00:10:55,270 --> 00:10:56,510
Hell no, Helo!

313
00:10:56,510 --> 00:10:57,420
Uh, excuse me.

314
00:10:57,470 --> 00:11:01,180
Uh, you-you all know I'm a cool guy, right?

315
00:11:01,180 --> 00:11:03,210
I'm chill with you calling me Arvin.

316
00:11:03,210 --> 00:11:07,130
We had class outside that one time.

317
00:11:07,130 --> 00:11:08,700
Will you just give us a minute?

318
00:11:08,700 --> 00:11:12,430
I assure you, she will feel the full effects of my rage.

319
00:11:14,130 --> 00:11:15,610
- So, how have you been? - Not so great.

320
00:11:15,610 --> 00:11:17,370
They're not fans of your employer?

321
00:11:17,370 --> 00:11:19,540
Which is so unfair!

322
00:11:19,810 --> 00:11:21,360
I'm doing very advanced research

323
00:11:21,360 --> 00:11:23,040
that could have far-reaching implications.

324
00:11:23,040 --> 00:11:24,400
Yeah. Of course you are.

325
00:11:24,400 --> 00:11:25,060
One sec.

326
00:11:25,060 --> 00:11:27,430
How do you sleep at night?!

327
00:11:27,490 --> 00:11:28,990
Okay, so, you, too?

328
00:11:28,990 --> 00:11:29,950
No, of course not.

329
00:11:29,950 --> 00:11:32,720
I am not here to judge you or your boss --

330
00:11:32,720 --> 00:11:33,810
Satan!

331
00:11:36,180 --> 00:11:38,550
Anyway, I just thoht I'd drop by and say a quick hello.

332
00:11:38,550 --> 00:11:39,780
Haley, lovely to see you.

333
00:11:39,780 --> 00:11:41,140
You have to move on.

334
00:11:41,140 --> 00:11:44,250
Alex, I wish you nothing but the best. Okay.

335
00:11:44,290 --> 00:11:46,990
Right, guys. Now with feeling.

336
00:11:47,330 --> 00:11:50,730
Hell no, Helo! It's time you go!

337
00:11:50,730 --> 00:11:53,940
Hell no, Helo! It's time you go!

338
00:11:53,940 --> 00:11:55,310
What Lily said really got to us.

339
00:11:55,310 --> 00:11:57,910
Maybe we are too old to have a new baby.

340
00:11:57,910 --> 00:11:59,940
Yesterday, I found hairs on my ears

341
00:11:59,940 --> 00:12:01,520
and I yelled at the local news.

342
00:12:01,520 --> 00:12:04,240
And I called Seinfeld "Steinfeld."

343
00:12:05,080 --> 00:12:06,090
You know, but on the other hand,

344
00:12:06,090 --> 00:12:08,590
there are a lot of men our age having babies.

345
00:12:08,590 --> 00:12:11,570
Yes, but-but they have second wives and nannies --

346
00:12:11,570 --> 00:12:13,070
who are often the same person.

347
00:12:13,070 --> 00:12:15,280
We just needed to talk to a-a parent

348
00:12:15,280 --> 00:12:17,320
that had a baby when they were old.

349
00:12:17,560 --> 00:12:20,560
You must be mistaken, because I had Joe when I was 35.

350
00:12:20,570 --> 00:12:22,500
No, I remember. You had just turned --

351
00:12:22,500 --> 00:12:23,550
She's not gonna budge.

352
00:12:23,550 --> 00:12:26,190
Okay, j-just tell us, how hard is it?

353
00:12:26,190 --> 00:12:28,780
Well, are there nights where you don't sleep

354
00:12:28,780 --> 00:12:30,500
and you want to kill yourself?

355
00:12:30,500 --> 00:12:31,410
Of course.

356
00:12:31,410 --> 00:12:33,560
Are there shooting pains in your back

357
00:12:33,560 --> 00:12:37,010
from picking the baby and putting him down?

358
00:12:37,280 --> 00:12:38,560
Constantly.

359
00:12:38,560 --> 00:12:40,130
Okay, well, is there a but?

360
00:12:40,250 --> 00:12:42,460
It's hanging in there, but it's not the same.

361
00:12:42,460 --> 00:12:45,350
Look, I know that you guys worry that you're too old

362
00:12:45,350 --> 00:12:49,370
or too slow to have a baby at this age.

363
00:12:49,370 --> 00:12:51,490
But guess what.

364
00:12:51,580 --> 00:12:52,850
You can!

365
00:12:53,570 --> 00:12:55,750
- What the hell was that? - A doll.

366
00:12:55,750 --> 00:12:59,570
It was supposed to prove that you guys were ready to have a baby,

367
00:12:59,820 --> 00:13:02,760
but if this was a real one, you would have killed it.

368
00:13:02,770 --> 00:13:05,190
Well, wouldn't it be your fault for throwing it?

369
00:13:05,200 --> 00:13:07,530
Give me a break. I was trying something.

370
00:13:07,530 --> 00:13:09,640
I'm in the middle of selling a house.

371
00:13:09,640 --> 00:13:11,030
Oh, yeah, it's very cute, by the way.

372
00:13:11,030 --> 00:13:12,210
How many bedrooms is it?

373
00:13:12,220 --> 00:13:13,320
Three and a den.

374
00:13:13,320 --> 00:13:14,520
Oh, that's one more than we have.

375
00:13:14,520 --> 00:13:15,870
Mitchell, this house, huh?

376
00:13:15,870 --> 00:13:17,820
Cam, I can't even begin to think about a house

377
00:13:17,820 --> 00:13:19,940
when we haven't even made a decision about whether or not

378
00:13:19,950 --> 00:13:21,650
- we're going to -- - But maybe it's a sign.

379
00:13:21,650 --> 00:13:23,720
You know, the new job goes away, a baby comes along,

380
00:13:23,720 --> 00:13:25,020
and all of a sudden, we're standing in a charming

381
00:13:25,020 --> 00:13:27,110
- three-bedroom -- - Three and a half bath.

382
00:13:27,110 --> 00:13:29,370
Which, holy cow, we could afford if we just switch back

383
00:13:29,370 --> 00:13:30,840
- to grocery store face cream. - ‭No.

384
00:13:30,850 --> 00:13:33,210
And it's in a great school district.

385
00:13:33,210 --> 00:13:34,670
You know what? She's right about that.

386
00:13:34,670 --> 00:13:35,690
They have a full-time nurse.

387
00:13:35,700 --> 00:13:37,980
We have a Band-Aid jar and a can of ginger ale.

388
00:13:37,990 --> 00:13:39,520
Okay, we already have too much on our plate.

389
00:13:39,520 --> 00:13:41,100
We're not buying this house!

390
00:13:41,110 --> 00:13:43,790
Oh, and in the basement, they have a karaoke room

391
00:13:43,790 --> 00:13:45,990
for people that want to impersonate divas

392
00:13:45,990 --> 00:13:48,500
without their fathers seeing them.

393
00:13:49,470 --> 00:13:51,130
Well, I guess it wouldn't hurt to look.

394
00:13:54,630 --> 00:13:57,460
I don't know, guys. Does it really look like I'm in my office?

395
00:13:57,460 --> 00:13:58,780
Jaws wasn't a real shark,

396
00:13:58,780 --> 00:14:01,260
but I still wouldn't sit on a toilet seat for months.

397
00:14:01,470 --> 00:14:02,670
‭How's this angle, Mom?

398
00:14:03,200 --> 00:14:05,080
Um, uh, fine, I guess.

399
00:14:05,080 --> 00:14:07,870
My cheek is itching! Is there something on my face?

400
00:14:07,870 --> 00:14:10,870
Admiral Ackbar, what the hell happened to you?

401
00:14:10,870 --> 00:14:12,690
I'll bet it was your stupid mushrooms!

402
00:14:12,720 --> 00:14:14,130
Why do I try new things?

403
00:14:14,130 --> 00:14:16,310
I'm sticking to my Brett Favre jeans!

404
00:14:16,900 --> 00:14:18,280
Oh, God! That's her! That's her!

405
00:14:18,280 --> 00:14:19,400
Everybody quiet!

406
00:14:19,400 --> 00:14:20,580
Wait, I have to get up there with the babies --

407
00:14:20,580 --> 00:14:21,430
Sit!

408
00:14:23,340 --> 00:14:24,670
Hi, Ms. Beckman.

409
00:14:24,670 --> 00:14:26,470
Thank you so much for this --

410
00:14:27,050 --> 00:14:29,900
...opportunity.

411
00:14:29,930 --> 00:14:31,470
You're welcome.

412
00:14:32,640 --> 00:14:33,910
I-I wasn't mocking you.

413
00:14:33,910 --> 00:14:35,600
It's just that whenever I hear someone sneeze,

414
00:14:35,600 --> 00:14:38,230
I have to sneeze, too, so that it's an even number.

415
00:14:38,240 --> 00:14:39,730
It's-it's perfectly normal.

416
00:14:39,740 --> 00:14:41,710
Oh, no, I completely understand.

417
00:14:41,710 --> 00:14:44,660
A few years ago, I forgot to tap the towel rod twice

418
00:14:44,660 --> 00:14:45,760
when I got out of the shower,

419
00:14:45,760 --> 00:14:48,390
and we lost George Michael that day, so...

420
00:14:48,390 --> 00:14:49,940
That was you?

421
00:14:50,060 --> 00:14:52,440
Let me tell you a little bit about our company.

422
00:14:52,440 --> 00:14:54,140
I'd love that.

423
00:14:54,140 --> 00:14:56,130
But first, I'd like to take some notes.

424
00:14:58,110 --> 00:14:59,150
Tilt up!

425
00:14:59,150 --> 00:15:01,280
That's what I love about this industry --

426
00:15:01,280 --> 00:15:03,410
never a "Dull" Moment.

427
00:15:03,410 --> 00:15:04,880
It's not plugged in.

428
00:15:09,300 --> 00:15:11,210
We like to think of "Organize 'Em"

429
00:15:11,210 --> 00:15:13,450
as a wellness company --

430
00:15:14,840 --> 00:15:16,540
A mindfulness company.

431
00:15:18,030 --> 00:15:19,290
Are your shelv shaking?

432
00:15:19,960 --> 00:15:21,600
Uh...yeah.

433
00:15:21,860 --> 00:15:23,770
Yeah, I think we're having a little earthquake.

434
00:15:24,000 --> 00:15:25,120
You know what? Why don't I tell you

435
00:15:25,120 --> 00:15:27,290
a little something about myself?

436
00:15:28,790 --> 00:15:30,750
I like to think I'm the kind of person

437
00:15:30,750 --> 00:15:34,370
who can see where the consumer trends are leaning,

438
00:15:34,930 --> 00:15:36,560
adjust quickly,

439
00:15:36,650 --> 00:15:39,200
and lean back the other direction.

440
00:15:41,110 --> 00:15:42,230
Oh, my God!

441
00:15:43,780 --> 00:15:45,590
Do I love organizing!

442
00:15:45,590 --> 00:15:47,720
Baby, do I love it!

443
00:15:47,720 --> 00:15:50,200
M-Ms. Dunphy, have you been drinking?

444
00:15:50,580 --> 00:15:52,610
Just lie. She can't smell your breath.

445
00:15:52,610 --> 00:15:54,180
No, Poppy, no!

446
00:16:00,320 --> 00:16:01,900
What the hell is happening?!

447
00:16:01,900 --> 00:16:03,040
I'm calling it.

448
00:16:03,440 --> 00:16:06,290
I'm sorry, Ms. Beckman. This was a terrible idea.

449
00:16:06,300 --> 00:16:07,770
I -- Okay.

450
00:16:08,400 --> 00:16:11,340
I fell through a step, and my leg is stuck.

451
00:16:11,340 --> 00:16:14,910
And listen, there's no company I would rather work for.

452
00:16:14,910 --> 00:16:17,670
I didn't want to cancel on you, so I asked my family

453
00:16:17,670 --> 00:16:21,840
to make it look like this was my office.

454
00:16:21,860 --> 00:16:24,660
Jay Pritchett, closeteer, but you probably know that.

455
00:16:26,140 --> 00:16:29,270
Could you just please get him out of my ear shot?

456
00:16:29,600 --> 00:16:30,990
Yeah, yeah, sure.

457
00:16:31,220 --> 00:16:34,110
Listen, I wanted you to think that I was a person

458
00:16:34,110 --> 00:16:35,910
who had it all together, but I'm not.

459
00:16:36,020 --> 00:16:38,700
The reality is I live in chaos!

460
00:16:38,700 --> 00:16:40,500
But that's why I love your products.

461
00:16:40,660 --> 00:16:42,320
When -- When my kids are fighting

462
00:16:42,320 --> 00:16:43,820
or -- or the grandkids are crying

463
00:16:43,830 --> 00:16:47,650
or my husband is making pancakes on a pogo stick,

464
00:16:47,800 --> 00:16:50,390
I know that I can go into my office

465
00:16:50,390 --> 00:16:53,570
and file bills in a color-coded divider

466
00:16:53,570 --> 00:16:56,280
and experience one moment of peace.

467
00:16:57,490 --> 00:16:59,890
I know I'm what your company needs,

468
00:17:00,060 --> 00:17:02,520
because I know how much I need your company.

469
00:17:06,970 --> 00:17:08,690
I got the job!

470
00:17:08,690 --> 00:17:10,090
I'm so proud of her!

471
00:17:10,090 --> 00:17:11,830
I guess it's our lucky step.

472
00:17:14,730 --> 00:17:16,360
Don't worry. It's just me.

473
00:17:16,360 --> 00:17:17,540
Oh. ‭See?!

474
00:17:22,180 --> 00:17:24,040
You know what? You could have defended me!

475
00:17:24,190 --> 00:17:25,630
Mm. Should I have?

476
00:17:25,960 --> 00:17:27,480
Are you saying you agree with them?

477
00:17:27,480 --> 00:17:29,600
I found their chant rather simplistic.

478
00:17:29,600 --> 00:17:31,860
You know, I would have probably gone with something like...

479
00:17:31,860 --> 00:17:34,520
"Helo Dynamics is a multinational corporation

480
00:17:34,520 --> 00:17:37,530
that prioritizes profits over ethics."

481
00:17:37,530 --> 00:17:39,880
I knew it. You are judging me.

482
00:17:39,880 --> 00:17:42,150
Do you judge all of your students like this?

483
00:17:42,150 --> 00:17:42,960
Alex...

484
00:17:43,650 --> 00:17:46,910
all my students don't have the potential you do!

485
00:17:47,050 --> 00:17:48,430
You were extraordinary!

486
00:17:48,430 --> 00:17:50,250
You were meant to change the world!

487
00:17:52,080 --> 00:17:53,790
And it's not just me that thinks it.

488
00:17:54,090 --> 00:17:56,130
Dylan said so in his newsletter.

489
00:17:56,130 --> 00:17:57,180
Oh, spare me.

490
00:17:57,200 --> 00:17:59,880
The sanctimonious academic, looking down on the star pupil

491
00:17:59,880 --> 00:18:02,330
because of her thousand-dollar shoes!

492
00:18:02,330 --> 00:18:04,050
Those shoes were a thousand dollars?

493
00:18:04,050 --> 00:18:06,540
Damn it. Do they come with medicine for a village?

494
00:18:06,540 --> 00:18:08,230
You know what? I hate to say it,

495
00:18:08,230 --> 00:18:11,260
but I don't need your approval, because I love what I do.

496
00:18:11,260 --> 00:18:13,720
Ah. Well, I am sorry to hear that.

497
00:18:13,720 --> 00:18:16,930
- Don't be. - ‭I'm sorry because I am assembling a research team

498
00:18:16,930 --> 00:18:19,310
to create A.I. capable of everything

499
00:18:19,320 --> 00:18:21,850
from discovering exoplanets in deep space

500
00:18:21,850 --> 00:18:24,240
to biomarkers of disease in humans.

501
00:18:24,240 --> 00:18:28,680
And you would've been a superb addition

502
00:18:28,750 --> 00:18:30,340
to an exceptional team.

503
00:18:30,340 --> 00:18:31,390
But pbht!

504
00:18:31,390 --> 00:18:33,710
Well, Professor...

505
00:18:33,810 --> 00:18:35,730
you can take that job...

506
00:18:36,420 --> 00:18:37,920
and give it to me.

507
00:18:38,280 --> 00:18:40,180
But I'm going to need you to match my salary!

508
00:18:40,180 --> 00:18:41,530
I'm not sure we have that kind of money.

509
00:18:41,530 --> 00:18:42,360
Deal.

510
00:18:44,300 --> 00:18:46,440
I'm gonna go see if I can still return these.

511
00:18:48,090 --> 00:18:51,010
And finally, back to the beautiful family room.

512
00:18:51,010 --> 00:18:52,080
It's great.

513
00:18:52,080 --> 00:18:53,300
I mean, it is beautiful.

514
00:18:53,300 --> 00:18:54,190
I can see you both

515
00:18:54,190 --> 00:18:57,450
having a delightful misunderstanding here.

516
00:18:57,450 --> 00:18:59,300
Okay, now, Mitchell. ‭Hmm?

517
00:18:59,300 --> 00:19:01,670
You know I'm not usually impulsive --

518
00:19:01,670 --> 00:19:03,610
Please. You never go to the grocery store alone

519
00:19:03,610 --> 00:19:04,930
and not come home with a balloon.

520
00:19:04,930 --> 00:19:07,020
But that bathroom upstairs is amazing.

521
00:19:07,020 --> 00:19:10,170
Yeah, and I -- I do love the idea of me having my own sink.

522
00:19:10,180 --> 00:19:12,520
Our housekeeper would finally realize who the real villain is.

523
00:19:12,520 --> 00:19:14,000
Okay, so we should -- we should do it!

524
00:19:14,000 --> 00:19:14,880
Let's do it!

525
00:19:15,270 --> 00:19:16,720
- Buy this house? - ‭Yeah.

526
00:19:16,930 --> 00:19:19,220
We haven't even made a decision about the baby yet.

527
00:19:19,230 --> 00:19:22,650
Oh. Another broker just sent me a text.

528
00:19:22,650 --> 00:19:25,030
An offer is coming at six o'clock.

529
00:19:25,030 --> 00:19:26,860
Great. Another ticking clock.

530
00:19:26,860 --> 00:19:28,510
Let's also disarm a time bomb

531
00:19:28,510 --> 00:19:30,990
while buying Beyonce tickets online with an expired credit card.

532
00:19:30,990 --> 00:19:33,030
Okay, that one got to me. I'm having hard time breathing.

533
00:19:33,030 --> 00:19:34,300
I feel like I'm gonna have a heart attack!

534
00:19:34,300 --> 00:19:37,140
And this big family room with the cozy fireplace

535
00:19:37,140 --> 00:19:39,470
is the perfect place to have that.

536
00:19:39,470 --> 00:19:40,570
Okay, you know what, Gloria? Stop.

537
00:19:40,570 --> 00:19:42,680
We -- We -- We need to think.

538
00:19:42,680 --> 00:19:44,060
No, no, no, we do not need to think.

539
00:19:44,060 --> 00:19:45,520
We need to stop this.

540
00:19:45,910 --> 00:19:47,410
Okay, within the span of eighteen hours,

541
00:19:47,410 --> 00:19:50,260
we're supposed to completely and utterly change our lives?

542
00:19:50,260 --> 00:19:53,770
No -- No big, life-altering decision should be made that way.

543
00:19:55,060 --> 00:19:58,830
You're right. Here, let's -- Then let's not.

544
00:19:58,840 --> 00:20:00,560
- Okay. ‭- It's just way too much.

545
00:20:00,560 --> 00:20:01,510
When things are right,

546
00:20:01,510 --> 00:20:04,120
i-it shouldn't be a struggle like this.

547
00:20:04,120 --> 00:20:05,120
You just know it.

548
00:20:05,120 --> 00:20:06,360
Yeah. I know.

549
00:20:06,360 --> 00:20:08,560
That little boy, he's gonna find an amazing family, right?

550
00:20:08,570 --> 00:20:11,310
- Of course he is. - ‭Yeah. Yeah.

551
00:20:11,460 --> 00:20:13,020
You -- You know what? I already --

552
00:20:13,100 --> 00:20:14,800
I already feel a little lighter.

553
00:20:14,800 --> 00:20:16,200
And we don't need the stress of moving.

554
00:20:16,200 --> 00:20:17,290
- No. - ‭Because you know what?

555
00:20:17,490 --> 00:20:18,930
- I love our house. - ‭I do, too.

556
00:20:18,930 --> 00:20:21,140
- It is not perfect. But neitare we. - ‭No. We aren't.

557
00:20:21,140 --> 00:20:22,460
And neither is your car.

558
00:20:22,470 --> 00:20:25,040
Can you please remove that thing from the driveway?

559
00:20:25,040 --> 00:20:27,340
I'm trying to sell a life style here.

560
00:20:28,220 --> 00:20:30,420
Is that the adoption ancy?

561
00:20:30,420 --> 00:20:31,370
Yep.

562
00:20:33,010 --> 00:20:33,850
I'll -- I'll tell them.

563
00:20:34,910 --> 00:20:35,800
Hello.

564
00:20:41,400 --> 00:20:43,880
Uh, yes, my husband and I would love to adopt him.

565
00:20:44,700 --> 00:20:45,990
Let's write up an offer.

566
00:20:55,100 --> 00:20:57,290
- Dad. Wake up. - Oh, what -- what -- what --

567
00:20:57,290 --> 00:21:00,910
- I think Daddy took a sleeping pill again. - Is he...

568
00:21:00,910 --> 00:21:01,930
- Yep. - ‭Okay.

569
00:21:02,010 --> 00:21:04,090
♪ He taught me to love him ♪

571
00:21:04,090 --> 00:21:06,240
♪ And promised to love ♪

572
00:21:06,240 --> 00:21:09,830
♪ And cherish me over all others above ♪

573
00:21:09,840 --> 00:21:12,160
Come on, sing it with me, Tucson! ‭

574
00:21:12,660 --> 00:21:16,180
♪ My poor heart is wonderin', no misery can tell -- ♪

575
00:21:16,180 --> 00:21:19,080
Hey, Mitchell. I have a dozen wings for Reba.

576
00:21:19,090 --> 00:21:20,880
Yup. Okay, thank you so much.

577
00:21:20,880 --> 00:21:22,130
We'll see you next time.

578
00:21:22,130 --> 00:21:24,540
Tony, I'm getting a little feedback in my ear here.

579
00:21:24,840 --> 00:21:27,060
Tony Hammond, ladies and gentlemen.

