(HARVEY READING)
But it's not Woodall
coming after us.
It's Sean Cahill.
Welcome to the new SEC.
We target law firms.
- Mr. Forstman.
- No.
You'll miss the opportunity
to get back at Harvey Specter.
You've got my 230 mil.
Once the deal closes,
you cut Sidwell out.
What happened to
"You think I'm staying if you leave?"
Yeah, that was before I knew you were
gonna screw over Sidwell.
Forstman doesn't throw money around
without getting something in return.
I have no other choice!
So, we're just going to go
back and forth, trading favors?
Are you my lawyer or not?
Seriously, Rachel, I couldn't
have done it without you.
(WHISPERING)
Logan, I should go.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
- I'm right here.
- Did you turn off my alarm?
- I did.
- It's after 9:00.
- I've been sleeping for...
- Almost six hours.
I know. And the truth is,
you need more.
- Why would you do that?
- Rachel, you've been running
back and forth between school
and the firm like a maniac.
I don't even remember the last
time you got a good night's sleep.
That doesn't give you the right to do
that. Plus, Harvey's going to kill me.
- He'll get over it.
- And I've got three briefs to write,
plus a paper for torts, and a...
And a contracts exam tomorrow.
- I don't have the luxury to sleep in.
- Then you need to ask Harvey
for a day off this week.
Did he ever give you time off
because you were overworked?
No, he didn't.
Exactly. I don't want
to be any different.
Mr. Jamieson, you are hereby remanded
to the federal penitentiary
in Danbury, Connecticut.
(GAVEL BANGING)
You might want to call me
about an appeal.
The prosecutor has a reputation
for bending the rules.
You must be the infamous
Harvey Specter.
And you must be the chump Eric
Woodall ordered to come after me.
Chump is my name on my mother's side.
I do prefer Cahill.
And I prefer you manufacturing bullshit
to get my clients to turn on me.
I'm sorry. I'm not in the
manufacturing business.
I'm just a humble civil servant. And
if you're as clean as you say you are,
your clients won't have
anything to give us.
Unless you bully them
into making things up.
Oh, see, now,
I think you've got us confused.
Because that sounds like
something that you might do.
The point is, Sean,
you had a secret little plan
and I've taken away
your element of surprise.
Have you?
You may know that I'm coming,
but do you know where?
Or when?
You see, while you're
battening down the hatches
at B4, I might be at D12 or H3.
And before you know it,
I have sunk your battleship.
That's a cute game.
I was more of a
Rock 'em Sock 'em Robots guy.
So you think you can knock
my block off, Harvey?
I know I can.
Because I had Eric Woodall fired.
So, stay the hell away from my clients
or I'll pave the same career path for you.
Okay, your hands
weren't full with Eric.
They will be full with me.
Harv.
- You want to talk about it?
- Talk about what?
That 10,000-pound weight
on your shoulders.
Mike, if you feel this way now,
what are you gonna feel like
when you cut Sidwell out?
If I cut him out.
- What are you talking about?
- I've been thinking about it.
I haven't actually taken
Forstman's money yet.
If I can get Harvey to back off before I do,
then I might not even need it.
You want to use the idea
of Forstman's money to cut a deal.
But Mike, they have money, too.
Yeah, which they can't spend
until their TRO expires.
Yeah. But that's next week
and it's not like
there's some huge block
of shares available now.
Wexlefs merging two of their funds.
So what?
So, their investment
parameters don't allow
for more than 4% of their holdings
in any one industry.
They have to sell a block of something.
But how do you know it's gonna
be Gillie Industries?
Because I did the math.
That's what I would do.
- You think Harvey will go for it?
- There's only one way to find out.
Hey, I don't have any cash on me,
but if you want to bring my luggage up,
I'll get you on the way back.
Yeah, you know what?
That's okay.
I don't need a tip now that I have enough
money to buy your whole building.
Yeah. What are you doing here, Mike?
Well, you came to give me
some friendly advice.
I thought I would return the favor.
- (SCOFFS) I don't remember asking.
- Mmm, yeah.
Neither did I.
Walk away, Harvey.
Excuse me?
- You're gonna lose.
- If you think
you getting a little loan
is gonna stop me,
I didn't teach you much.
It's not a "little" loan.
I've got one of the most powerful players
in the world behind me.
Which is exactly where he needs to be
to stab you in the back.
Well, wherever he's standing,
this is what I'm prepared to offer
Logan Sanders to go away.
I know I don't need to remind you
that you're legally required
to run that by your client.
I just ran it by him.
No deal.
Harvey, what are you...
You haven't taken
Forstman's money yet.
He's got some kind of gun to your head
and you're just trying to use
his promise of cash
as leverage against me.
This isn't a bluff, Harvey.
- I came here to give you a way out.
- Bullshit.
You came here to give
yourself a way out.
But I wasn't born yesterday
and I'm not giving it to you.
See the money wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back,
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
Did you go to see Sean Cahill
in court this morning?
I'm not in the mood
for a lectu re.
I'm not lecturing.
I'm asking you a question.
Yes, I did.
And before you tell me
this is what we brought Malone in for.
- I'm not going to tell you that.
- Good, because...
- Now, Cahill's coming directly after you.
- Exactly.
And you're on your way to tell Malone
to concoct some bullshit
to legally get us that Wexler block.
Look who's been reading the papers.
I'm not the only one who can
read the papers, Harvey.
So can you. So can Mike Ross.
He's gonna go after those shares.
- He is now.
- What are you talking about?
- He tried to buy us off.
- And you turned him down?
Yes, which is why
I'm going to see Malone.
- No, you're not.
- Jessica, we have to...
I'm not saying we don't.
I'm saying I'm going
to be the one to do it.
You know he's not gonna like it.
He doesn't have to like it.
He has to do it.
DONNA: Therefore,
prepare thee to cut off the flesh.
Shed thou no blood, nor cut thou less,
nor more but just a pound of flesh.
If... Louis.
How long have
you been standing there?
- Long enough to become part of you.
- Okay.
You know what?
I don't have time
for you to be creepy.
So, does this mean
you're doing theater again?
Yes, I am playing Portia
in Merchant of Venice.
Now, can you please
just let me get back to...
Holy shit, Donna.
That is a meaty part.
Yeah, it's 588 lines,
which I have yet to memorize.
EEK!
- So, you're not off book?
- Louis,
if I were off book, would I be pacing
around the copy room
with a script in my hand?
All right. Just calm down.
No need to panic.
- When do you open?
- Tonight.
Tonight? And you're not off book?
What the hell's wrong with you, Donna?
- I mean, only...
- This isn't helping.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to be...
- I knew it.
I bit off more than I could chew.
No, no, no, no, no. Just relax.
Okay? I don't care if it takes all day,
we are gonna memorize
these lines together.
- Thank you, Louis.
- No need.
For one canst choke on the joy of life
without thy mouth full.
- Is that the Bard?
- No, it's the Litt.
And roughly translated, it means
when we're done,
you are gonna kick Shakespeare's ass.
M'lady.
- I take it, it didn't go well.
- What gave it away?
Because I know you,
and you don't have your usual
"I'm super cool Mike Ross" face.
If you knew me that well,
you'd know I'm not in the mood.
Mike, I'm not your enemy and
I don't appreciate being treated like I am.
I know. I'm sorry.
So, what did Harvey say?
It's not what he said.
It's what he did.
He knew what I was trying to do
and he called my bluff right there.
He didn't even share
the offer with Logan?
- No, he didn't.
- But you said he had to.
You want me to sue him for that?
- So, what are you gonna do?
- You know what I'm gonna do.
- Mike...
- I don't want to hear it.
I wasn't disapproving.
I just want to make sure
you've exhausted
- all your options.
- I have.
Then, maybe you...
Amy, the second I bid
on that block of shares,
I've already taken
Forstman's money.
(PHONE RINGING)
Mike Ross' office.
I'll tell him.
- Sidwell?
- He wants to see you.
You look good.
- This isn't a social call.
- All right, I take it back.
Wexler is divesting
a huge block of Gillie Industries,
and I need you to find a creative way
to buy them for Logan Sanders.
If I'm not mistaken,
Logan Sanders has a TRO
that actually prohibits him
from buying any additional shares.
Which is why you're going to set up
a trust for us to buy it for him.
- That's called parking, Jessica.
- I know what it's called.
- Then, maybe you also know it's illegal.
- I know it can be illegal.
And I need you to figure out
a way to make it questionable.
And here I thought you came in here
to tell me how much fun last night was.
Well, speaking of last night,
you said you blamed yourself
for helping Cahill drop those cases.
So here's your chance to make up for it.
Remind me never to have a moment
of self-reflection around you.
I'm not using this as ammunition,
I'm using it as motivation.
So, figure out a way
to set up the trust,
and do it quickly because
we're running out of time.
You wanted to see me?
Come here.
I want to show you something.
Lionsdale Electronics.
Three million shares
bought out by management.
My first IBO.
I was right out of school. All I wanted
was to get that first tombstone.
Because it meant...
- Your first deal.
- Broke my cherry.
Must have been nice.
It was.
You know what the difference
between you and me is?
I was just an analyst.
I mean, sure I did all the work,
but I didn't do any of the work.
Know what I mean?
- Jonathan...
- Don't be modest.
I know I've been on your case.
But the truth is,
you made this all happen.
- I haven't made anything happen yet.
- No. You haven't.
And there's a rule against giving out
tombstones too early.
Not supposed to jinx it.
But there's no rule against this.
We can fill it in later.
- Thank you, Jonathan.
- You're welcome.
Now, go bring this bad boy home.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
LOGAN: Rachel, they loved it.
We are gonna go after Piedmont
in a week.
We 're gonna have a lot of work to do.
Give me a call when you get in.
(SIGHS)
Harvey. Can I help you with something?
Yes, you can help by telling me
how much longer it's gonna take
for you to find me a way
to bid on that stock.
- It's gonna take as long as it takes.
- Well, it better not
be more than a day
or I won't need it at all.
It's so good to hear this
from the horse's mouth.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means the next time you want me
to break the law, at least have the balls
to ask me yourself.
The balls?
First off, Jessica
insisted on asking you herself.
And I agreed with her because
we're on the same page.
And nobody's asking you
to break the law.
We're telling you to sidestep it.
That's not the job I signed on for.
The job you signed on for is
the job we tell you you signed on for.
That's a bullshit justification
and you know it.
What I know is
there's a reason we make
the kind of money we do.
It's because we figure out a way
to get things like this done.
So, stop questioning my integrity
and start doing your job.
- Harvey, do you have a second?
- That's about all I have.
All right.
I was, um, wondering if
- maybe I could possibly just...
- Time's up.
- Could I get a day or two off?
- A day? Or two?
- A day. I just need one day away.
- Are you sure that's all you need?
- I'm sure.
- Would you also like me
- to make your bed?
- What?
Maybe I can triple your salary
while we're at it.
No, that's not...
No, really. What can I do
to make your life easier?
That is not fair.
I have been juggling work and school
for months now, and I...
I haven't asked for any
special treatment.
You're asking now.
I'm not asking for time off
to go to the Hamptons.
This is law school I'm talking about.
You said a day away. You didn't
say anything about law school.
- Well, it's for law school.
- Well, this is your law school.
This. Right here. And by the way,
we're paying you for it.
- I know. And I'm grateful.
- If you're grateful,
then you'll stop complaining
about how much work you have to do
and you'll figure out
how to best manage your time.
But as far as getting time off,
that's not gonna happen if you still plan
on working for me.
Now, you still need a day or two off?
No. I can manage.
Thou shalt have nothing
but the forfeiture,
to be so taken at thy peril, Jew.
Why, then that the devil
give him good of it.
I'll stay no longer question.
Come on, let's go.
This "be-eth" awesome.
Where's your script?
I don't need a script.
I'm off book.
How can you be off book?
You're not even in the play.
Because I know all of
Willy's work by heart.
- All 37 plays.
- Mmm-hmm.
Troilus and Cressida?
For to be wise and love
exceeds man's might.
- Titus Andronicus.
- Vengeance is in my heart,
death in my hand, blood and revenge
are hammering in my head.
What? What's the matter?
(LOUDLY)
Are you kidding me?
You have every word this man's
ever written memorized,
and I'm on in an hour and a half,
and I'm gonna make a fool of myself.
Donna, forget about my extraordinary
gift and focus on yourself.
We have done this whole play.
You know your part. It will be fine.
It's not gonna be fine.
- Donna!
- I haven't been on the stage in years.
So, you're nervous.
All great performers get nervous.
It brings out the genius.
What if I'm not genius?
What if I'm not even good?
I was pretty damn good, Louis.
I was.
But I knew the odds of somebody
making it were close to zero,
no matter how good they were.
My father lost our money
when I was 13, and I...
I found out what it was
like to struggle. So...
Instead of pursuing my dream,
I chose this.
And that let me pretend that maybe
I was good enough to make it.
But what if I wasn't?
Mmm. All right, look.
I'm gonna tell you something
about myself that I never told anyone.
I have stage fright.
I got it when I was in third grade.
I let it get the best of me.
I never got over it.
And I cannot let you
make the same mistake.
- But I...
- Look at me.
Donna Victoria Paulsen.
You have never been more beautiful
and talented,
and perfect than you are
at this very moment.
Your time is now.
And you're gonna kill it.
Thank you, Louis.
No.
Thank you.
My middle name is Roberta.
I'm so sorry for that.
. HEY-
- Are you working late?
- You really have to ask?
I thought maybe it would be nice
for us to lie down a little bit.
Together.
I would love that.
But if I lie down,
I probably won't get back up.
I know you don't want to hear this,
but I was thinking about it, and...
Harvey did kind of give me
special treatment.
- Mike...
- He let me skip law school.
(SCOFFS) Yeah.
Hey. Maybe if you just find
the right time to ask him...
I did. And he bit my head off.
So please, just let it go.
- Okay?
- Okay.
I just wish all this Harvey and Logan
bullshit would be over.
Yeah. Me too.
Maybe when it is, we can get
out of town for a weekend.
I would love that.
I'm worried about Cahill, Harvey.
I've checked with everyone I know.
He hasn't done a thing.
Me too.
Which is exactly why I'm worried.
Jessica, I don't know what to say.
If I have to look over my shoulder
every 15 seconds,
I might as well give up right now.
Okay, but it doesn't mean
you stop looking altogether.
- Hey. Do you have a minute?
- Did you set up that trust?
- No.
- In that case, we don't.
- I did something better.
- We're listening.
One of the biggest red flags
at the SEC is a stock purchased
with money kept in trusts for clients.
- We've gone over this.
- Let him finish.
On the other hand,
there's nothing unusual about a retainer.
A retainer.
From what I gather, this takeover
is a massive undertaking, right?
Now, I don't know how you've
structured Logan's payments,
but I think it's time he pay this firm
a hefty fee up front.
And something
on the order of $20 million.
And we use $20 million of our own
money to buy that stock.
There's nothing that prohibits us
from investing as a firm.
And when the bulk
of our legal work is done,
it turns out
he has money coming back.
We may just end up giving him the
shares instead of his unused retainer.
Which we cannot plan or even discuss
with Logan Sanders in advance.
And that makes it legal?
No. It makes it questionable.
Because they still might figure out
what we did and make a case.
"We"?
You tell me, Harvey.
Am I on the team now?
Sounds like you're being a little bit of
a dickhead about this whole thing,
so I'd say yes.
Louis. Do you have a minute?
Oh, no.
It could not have been that bad.
Oh, it wasn't.
It was amazing.
I mean, it was like riding a bike.
I got two standing 0's,
and I've got you to thank for it.
Well, that's great.
What's wrong?
Shylock got drunk at the after party,
fell down a flight of stairs
and broke his ankle.
Which means the show won't go on.
Oh, no, no, no.
The show must go on.
Well, the show...can go on.
No.
Louis. Come on.
- You're the only one who can do it.
- No, I can't.
I wanted to be a molar.
But that teacher's pet,
Dorothy McHale, got the part.
So I was forced to be plaque.
I had to wear this ridiculous
flesh-colored unitard
and drape myself over
my classmates.
And every parent
in the audience laughed at me.
Louis...
And then, the next year,
I got a bigger part.
I walked right out on stage. Tommy
Gallup screams out, "Plaque man!"
Once again, everyone laughs at me.
So, right then and there,
in the middle of the stage.
IIII
I Peed my pants.
So I ran right off the stage,
never went back,
and I am not going back again.
Louis.
A part like this
doesn't come around very often.
You gave me a gift,
and I killed it because of you.
- Donna, please.
- I'm not a lawyer, Louis.
This is my chance to shine.
But I'm about to lose
two more glorious nights.
I've never asked anyone for anything
like this, but there's no other choice.
Please do this for me.
Please.
You want me to sell directly to you?
- I don't want you to. You're going to.
- Why would I do that?
Because I'm the only one who's gonna
buy your block at a premium
instead of you flooding the market with
shares and ending up getting a discount.
That's funny.
That's exactly what someone
else just told me an hour ago.
- What?
- And now I'll tell you what I told him.
I'll shut everyone else out,
but you two are going
to have to go head-to-head.
You're talking about
a dark pool bidding war.
That's no different than
what you were talking about.
You just wanted to be
the only one bidding.
Thanks for the scampi, Mr. Ross.
It was delicious.
I'll be in touch with the details.
Who's the other entity?
(SNICKERS)
If you can't figure
that out for yourself,
I don't think you're likely to come out
on top of this whole thing.
What the hell
do you think you're doing?
I think I'm washing my hands,
which I'd like to do without you
bothering me about whatever
bullshit you're here for.
Flaw
We'll see if the SEC thinks it's bullshit
that you're buying stock illegally.
You're throwing some pretty big
accusations around for such a little guy.
You think I didn't do my homework?
The registered bidder traces back
to a shell corporation
we used six times last year.
We're allowed to play the stock market
as much as the next fellow.
You think because you're using
firm money, that makes it legal?
You're damn right I do.
Because we have no plan to do anything
other than keep those shares ourselves.
- Now who's talking bullshit?
- What are you gonna do, Mike?
- You gonna run to the SEC?
- You think I won't?
These aren't your daddy's tapes, Harvey.
These are the rules of the game.
Then let me dial their number for you.
Because if you report us,
they'll put a freeze on this sale.
And by the time we get it all
straightened out, my TRO will be expired
and we'll be right back to
where we're headed this afternoon.
(SCOFFS)
You're a sore goddamn loser.
I would be, if I ever lost.
See you at 6:00.
Guess what piece of shit lawyerjust got
himself a seat in the Wexler pool?
Mike, what are you doing here?
What do you mean?
The sale's not till 6:00.
- Didn't you check your messages?
- No, why?
Columbia University called.
Rachel was taken to the hospital.
- Rachel Zane.
- Sorry?
You have a patient here. Rachel Zane.
What room is she in?
- Uh, Miss Zane is resting and can...
- What room is she in?
As I was saying,
she can't have any visitors.
Look at me. I'm gonna ask you
one more time. What room...
[RUE
- She's in 1024.
- You've seen her?
- It's locked.
- I don't care.
What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna break the door down?
- Yeah, if I have to.
- I spoke to her doctors.
They said she fainted
at school. She's fine.
If she fainted, she's not fine.
They said she's run down
and a little dehydrated. It's okay.
Okay, so then, why won't
they let us see her?
Because she's sleeping
and she needs it.
Mike. She's fine.
She's gonna be fine.
What are you even doing here?
I'm one of her emergency contacts.
They called me.
Yeah, I know, but...
What's a heartless shithead
like me doing in a place like this?
Yeah, something like that.
I would have come for you if you ever
worked hard enough to pass out,
but you never did.
(SCOFFS)
Look. There's a steakhouse
across the street.
Why don't you and I
go get something to eat?
What, are you gonna break
the door down and wake her up?
No, I'm gonna wait outside of it
and be there when she does.
Yeah, which won't happen for another
eight hours because they sedated her
to make sure she got some sleep.
Now, come on. Let's go get some food.
Don't you need to be at an auction?
Right now, I don't want to be
at that sale any more than you do.
You're saying you're
willing to postpone it?
I'm saying I already did. Come on.
No, I'm telling you, Dr. Lipschitz,
this is like the whole plaque
incident all over again.
Yeah. Yes, I have told you
about the plaque incident.
What... At least twice. I...
No, you know what? That's... Forget it.
That's not the point.
The point is, is that I'm supposed to be
leaving for the theater in 10 minutes
and I am a complete wreck.
I have the worst case
of cotton mouth in the history of...
What? No, you can talk
with cotton mouth.
That's friggin' lockjaw. You...
You know something, Doc?
Sometimes I just think
that I've wasted every single
Monday, Wednesday, and Friday
for the last 14 years.
You know, this is the first time
we've ever had a steak dinner.
I didn't know you were keeping a tally.
It's pretty easy to do
when the grand total is zero.
I know.
I said I wanted to take you out the night
you told me you were leaving.
We never got around to it.
I never got around to it.
What's the real reason
you were at the hospital tonight?
The truth?
Rachel asked me for some time off
and I all but spit in her face.
- So, you felt guilty.
- Pretty much.
Plus, I knew you needed something
to take your mind off her,
but I can see this dinner
with me isn't working. So...
Here.
Holy shit. What is this?
Louis is in a play.
You wanted to cheer me up
and you didn't start the night with this?
Come on.
I wanted to save something
for dessert.
Oh, my God. That's got
to be a codpiece, right?
What are asking me for?
I don't want to know
- if Louis is packing that kind of heat.
- What, you think I do?
You're the one who went
mudding with him.
It was covered in mud.
- How much mud?
- Stop.
Why would I ask that?
Aw, man.
I shouldn't be laughing at him.
He still hasn't forgiven me
for using Sheila against him.
Mike, you did what you had to do.
You don't think that was crossing a line.
It was way over the line.
But I got to tell you, it was brilliant.
It was harsh, but it was brilliant.
You know, Harvey, I, um.
I never told you.
What you did with Gillie.
I know you had to do it.
Like I said before.
We do what we need to do.
Louis, you're almost up.
Oh, Christ, you're sweating
more than Nixon.
I've gone through four
Elizabethan collars and a codpiece.
Okay, just breathe.
You're gonna be fine.
No, I can't do it.
Louis, we are in
the middle of the play.
You'll have to ad lib.
Make something up.
Say Shylock went away.
Say that he went to Israel.
Oh, my God.
Wow. I don't even know what to...
You know what?
I never thought you'd be so weak.
Okay, why do you got to say
something hurtful right now?
Screw hurt.
Turn that into rage.
Why would I do...
You always turn hurt into rage,
you idiotic piece of shit!
- It is what you do.
- Okay, now, I'm mad at you.
Good! Now, imagine you're in court.
How? It's too hard with the curtains.
- Just do it, dipshit.
- Okay, fine. I'm in court.
- Goddamn it. You happy now?
- No, I'm not happy, you idiot.
Now, you're in court
and you're enraged
and you are fit to kill.
Now, do you see
that audience out there?
- That's your jury.
- They're a bunch of morons.
Yeah. They're beneath
you, aren't they?
- They're beneath everybody.
- What else?
They're a bunch of civil servants
who can't keep up with what I'm saying.
You have absolute and total
contempt for them, don't you?
I want to rip out their stupid brains
from their stupid heads.
Exactly.
Now, get out there
and make your case.
Unless, of course, you're a pussy
and you were only meant
to play plaque your whole life.
3,000 ducats...
I'm gonna head back.
Hey.
Tell Rachel she should take
the day off tomorrow.
Thanks for this, Harvey.
Excuse me. Which one of you is Franklin
and which one of you is Bash?
Did you boys have a nice date?
Couldn't be better. He even paid.
Oh, I guess he's flush with cash
ever since he left you
- and went into investment banking.
- I'm sorry. Do I know you?
No, but I know you, Mike Ross.
Sean here's with the SEC,
and he's using his position
to harass my clients
on behalf of Eric Woodall.
Actually, not anymore, Harvey.
I decided to take your advice
and focus on you.
- Are you following me?
- Oh, I've got guys who do that.
Then, you also better also
have authorization
- from the Justice Department.
- Getting authorization was easy.
Because I told them you two
are on opposite sides
of a takeover battle
and that your girlfriend
is your associate.
Are you trying to say
that we're colluding?
Oh, you went right there,
didn't you?
Because you led him there.
Well, in six hours that I've been there,
this is what I've learned.
Your girlfriend,
who I just mentioned works for you,
faints at law school for five minutes.
You guys meet at the hospital.
Then you have dinner for two hours,
where you cancel a private stock sale
that you both arranged.
And one hour ago,
that stock mysteriously
gets bought
by some shell corporation
set up last year.
Wait. What?
- Bullshit.
- Here's my favorite part,
where you feign outrage
and you feign ignorance
to help sell the whole story.
Anyway, I just wanted to give
you a little heads-up.
Smile for the cameras. Harvey.
You gave me your word.
- And I kept it.
- Oh, yeah?
Then what about that stock?
- Jessica must have done it.
- Bullshit!
No, it's not bullshit.
When were you planning on telling me
this guy was up your ass for collusion?
I didn't know about this
until five seconds ago.
There are only so many things
that I can buy, Harvey.
Listen to me. We can deal
with this guy's bullshit later.
Right now, let me deal with
the stock situation. I'll make it right.
- You can't make it right.
- Mike,
you used to trust me.
I need you to trust me right now.
(WHISPERS)
Rachel, wake up.
Hey. Where were you so late?
I was out.
- Thinking.
- Thinking what?
I don't want to be a fraud.
- What?
- I love you.
I'm married to her.
But I don't want to do that anymore.
I want to be married to you.
- Logan...
- Rachel,
will you marry me?
I can't.
Why not?
Because you'll always be a fraud.
How can you say that to me?
(GASPS)
Hey.
You okay?
Come on, go back to sleep.
I'll be here when you wake up.
- Who told you to buy that stock?
- Excuse me?
Let me start again.
Hello, Jessica.
I just found out we bought
the Wexler block.
Would you by any chance know
how that came to happen?
It came to happen when I found out
the dark pool had been canceled
and I couldn't reach you.
So, you took it upon yourself
to make a preemptive bid.
Of course I did.
If I hadn't, Forstman would have.
So, why are you here?
I gave Mike my word
we'd postpone the sale.
Well, I didn't give Mike anything.
- Do you even want to know why?
- Not particularly.
It was because Rachel
passed out at school
and was in the hospital.
- Is she all right?
- Do you care?
Don't you make me out to be
the villain in this, Harvey.
I am sorry Rachel fainted,
but our obligation is to our client,
and I'm not undoing that sale.
We can't tonight, anyway.
Why not?
'Cause Cahill came out of nowhere.
He's been having me followed.
He thinks Mike and I are
colluding on Gillie.
And if we undo that sale,
it will just fuel the fire.
I told you I was
still worried about him.
What did you want me to do?
Have myself tailed to pick up
a possible tail?
What did you come in here
to tell me, Harvey?
Now that Sean Cahill is involved,
we also can't ever transfer
those shares to Logan.
Which conveniently helps fix
your deal with Mike Ross.
- Jessica...
- You know what?
It doesn't matter.
We don't need to transfer them.
We'll just vote Logan's way
when the time comes.
Jessica, I gave Mike my word.
Harvey, I don't care
if you took a blood oath.
Our duty is to our client,
not a handshake with Mike Ross.
And this discussion's over.
I checked you out. You're free
to go on your own recognizance.
How much was bail?
Oh, it's okay. I took care of it.
How are you feeling?
You know, I'm actually feeling...
I'm feeling pretty good.
In fact, I think that I'm going to...
Rachel, no.
You can't do any work today.
I'm just gonna stop by the office and put
away just three files, send four emails.
That's it. I...
I have to do this just
for my own peace of mind.
No more?
No more. I won't even tell
anybody that I'm there.
I won't.
Louis, can I talk to you for a minute?
Of course.
First of all, you were
remarkable last night.
Who said?
Everyone in the cast.
The Flushing Chronicle?
Um, you know,
I don't actually read the local...
You should.
Because they said I was
a shock to the senses.
I bought six copies
this morning.
I'm gonna send five to Esther
because she thinks she's a great singer.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay. Louis, what I came
in here to say...
- Donna, I'm retiring.
- You're what?
You helped me get over a fear
that I never thought I'd get over.
But I don't want to see
the audience as the jury.
L...don't want to have
disdain for them.
I am the audience.
And I want to love them.
- Louis...
- Donna, I'm sorry.
Because I know I'm taking away
your last glorious night from you.
But I...
Can't go on again. I, um...
I can't do it.
It's okay, Louis.
It's okay.
It turns out that the other Shylock
only sprained his ankle.
Looks like he's gonna be able
to go on tonight after all.
Wait a minute.
He never hurt his ankle at all, did he?
You know, I just knew that you
had a lot of things going on lately
with Harvey and Malone and...
Sometimes, the best way to deal
with disappointment in one arena
is to accomplish something else.
Thank you.
You're welcome, Louis.
Hey. Remember when you said
that you're not a lawyer?
You could be.
I got Donna's message.
What's going on?
How's Rachel?
She's good. Resting.
- Mike...
- Goddamn it, I knew it.
- I knew you wouldn't fix it.
- I tried.
You tried. You're a name partner.
And she's the managing partner,
and you know it.
That wouldn't have made a difference
if you were fighting for you.
I fought Jessica for you
and won more than once,
but this isn't one of those times.
Mike, believe me,
this isn't what I wanted.
My mistake was believing you
when you gave me your word.
No.
I made the mistake
by not believing in you the second
you brought me your takeover plan.
Look.
I don't have a lot of regrets.
It's just not who I am.
But...this is one of them.
If I could go back and change it, I would.
But...
I can't.
Is that supposed to stop me?
No, I just wanted you to know it.
Do what you have to do.
Mr. Ross.
What I can help you with?
Actually, nothing.
Nothing?
What do you mean, nothing?
I mean I made a mistake.
I'm gonna find another way
to win this thing.
I'm, I'm grateful, but...
I'm not gonna need
your money anymore.
You may not need my money, but...
You've got it.
What are you talking about?
You think I didn't know
what you were up to?
You tried not to fund the money
so you could leverage Specter
out of the deal and get out of our deal.
- How...
- Did I know?
I've done the same thing
a hundred times.
I'm actually glad you did it, because now
I know the kind of person I'm in bed with.
A sneaky little shit like me.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, but you know the difference
between you and me?
I'm not taking the money
because I don't want
to screw over my partner.
And if I were you,
I wouldn't want to screw him over either.
That man has nothing
but wonderful things to say about you.
You had him take the money,
didn't you?
He couldn't believe
it hadn't happened already.
He told me he's having
a little tombstone made up for you.
[RUE
We are partners on this,
whether you like it or not.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to deliver these.
Who are those for?
Who do you think they're for?
- For you, for your dressing room.
- Thank you.
Let's go.
You're coming?
You think I'm gonna miss
your closing night?
I didn't know you were
a Shakespeare fan.
I'm a Donna fan.
You know, Harvey,
you don't have to do this.
I know you've got a lot
going on with Mike.
The only thing I've got
going on tonight is you.
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English