(HARVEY READING)
Professor Gerard,
I came to ask for a favor.
- The answer is no.
- Which is why I brought this.
- You know.
- And you talk a big game,
but you're just as human
as everyone else,
you smug son of a bitch.
- Louis. What are you doing here?
- Leaving.
That way, I don't have to
look at either one of you two liars.
(DOOR SLAMS)
- Oh, my God, he knows.
- He doesn't just know.
He's a name partner.
She came to me and lied to my face.
She did it to protect me.
I'm going to keep hammering on her
until you break.
With a new name
comes a new beginning.
Here's to our newest
name partner, Louis Litt.
Louis has something on you.
Daniel Hardman embezzled money
from the firm and I covered it up.
Why couldn't you
trust me with this before?
Because I didn't know
how you'd react.
Jessica,
your secret is safe with me.
I thought we were done
with rooftop conversations.
- Some things require privacy.
- I haven't heard you say that
since the midnight coup
of Schmidt, Gordon, and Van Dyke.
- Are you done?
- It wasn't a joke.
Neither is this. I told Jeff Malone
I helped cover up
Daniel Hardman's embezzlement.
Why the hell would you
open that time capsule?
Because he knew the explanation
we gave the partners about Louis
was bullshit and I had
to tell him something.
You could have told him
it was none of his business.
Harvey, I didn't bring you here
to get relationship advice.
I brought you here to tell you what I did
in case it ever came up.
No, you didn't.
You brought me here
because now you have
to get Louis to back you,
and you knew you'd be mad at me when I
told you what you didn't want to hear.
You're right.
I don't want to hear it.
How do you think it's going to go
when I tell Louis he holds the fate
- of my relationship in his hands?
- How do you think it's going to go
the first time Malone
brings up Louis' blackmail?
- I don't care.
- Well, I'll tell you how it's going to go.
Louis is going to look back
with his beady little eyes and say,
"Embezzlement? That's not
how I got my name on the wall."
And the shit's going
to hit the fan anyway.
You know what?
You can be a real son of a bitch.
Yeah. But instead of being pissed at me,
why don't you take a look in the mirror?
Because we held out an olive branch.
And after Louis hears this,
he's going to take that branch
and beat the shit out of us with it.
Louis.
Professor Gerard?
What are you doing here?
I've got a small
legal matter to attend to.
Well, is it anything
I can help you with?
Actually, I'm here
to speak with Harvey.
Ah. Ah. I understand.
You're looking for a name partner.
Well, you can't quite see it from here,
but if you walk back about 10 feet,
take a gander to your left,
you'll see I've gotten a little
- recognition.
- I appreciate that.
But as I said,
I'm here to speak with Harvey.
MIKE: So are we going to talk
about that little welcome speech
that Jessica made for Louis?
We don't have to talk about it,
because Louis isn't going to accept it.
Why not?
Because it will be
a cold day in hell
when he can accept
being Maverick to my Iceman.
Don't... Don't you mean Iceman
to your Maverick?
No, I don't.
You actually
want to be Iceman over Maverick?
- Who got the trophy?
- Who's the better pilot?
- The one who got the trophy.
- Wrong.
Because in the end,
Maverick saved Iceman.
And if he hadn't,
Trophy Boy would be sitting
on the bottom of the Indian Ocean
right now.
- Where he'd still be the man.
- According to you.
According to me
is the only according to that matters.
- There we go.
- Maybe.
But according to me,
Viper was the real hero of that film.
What, you think
I'm too old to know Top Gun?
What I think is, you have no business
being in my office.
Are we going to do this
in front of your associate?
We don't have to do anything
in front of anybody.
You just have to go.
Harvey.
I need a lawyer.
Louis' office is down the hall.
I don't want Louis.
I want you.
That's funny.
The last time you saw me,
you told me I wasn't fit to practice law
in your ivory tower.
What I told you was,
is that you'll sacrifice ethics for wins.
And right now, I'm not in my ivory tower
and I need a win.
I knew it. You're just like everybody else.
The ends don't justify the means
until it's your ass on the line.
Do you think I like
asking you for help?
I think this Liberty Rail
thing must have you by the balls.
- So you know.
- I know after their train derailed,
you were appointed to assess
the victims' compensation formula.
And I know after you did,
some of those victims
hired a lawyer
and opened an investigation.
Then you also know they found nothing.
Then the question is, why are you here?
The TSA found $25,000 in my luggage
the day I announced
I was changing the formula.
So now you're being accused
of accepting a bribe.
Which I did not do.
Well, good luck proving that, Professor,
because it won't be with my help.
I was wrong about you, Mr. Specter.
I never thought
that you wouldn't represent somebody
just because didn't like them.
Well, you're wrong again.
I don't like you.
But I'm not representing you,
because you did something shady,
and I'm not screwing over
crash victims for the likes of you.
You know I didn't do this.
What I know is you showed yourself in,
you can show yourself out.
(SINGING) See the money,
wanna stay for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody want to know
how it feel
Everybody want to see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
Okay, I didn't want to
say it in front of Gerard,
but has it occurred to
you that you're an idiot
if you don't take this case?
Last year, you were shitting yourself he'd
find out about you.
And now you think we
should work with him?
No, I wasn't worried he'd find out.
I was worried about Louis.
Gerard didn't bat an eye at me
back then and he didn't just now.
But we get him out of this,
and he ever does find out about me,
he's going to owe us.
Mike, that man is never
going to compromise his ethics
just because we got him out of a jam.
Never going to compromise his ethics?
You just said he took a bribe.
So what does that have
to do with anything?
It has everything to do with everything,
because you don't think he did it.
(SCOFFS)
- So what?
That means you're not turning him down
because you think he's shady.
You're turning him down
because you have
a Henry Gerard-sized
chip on your shoulder.
- I do not have a chip on my shoulder.
- You sure sound like you do.
Which makes you worse than an idiot,
it makes you a jackass.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
You know that he divided that money
fairly, which means that you're...
I don't care what it means.
And I don't need a lecture from you.
Apparently, you do.
Because you're about to screw over
a bunch of innocent people
just to stick it to some guy
who hurt your feelings.
And that's not something
I ever thought I'd be saying to you.
Oh, look who it is.
The woman who put me in my place.
What now?
You want me to sign a piece of paper
admitting that I was the man
on the grassy knoll?
I meant what I said
at that ceremony, Louis.
You mean the ceremony
that you only had in order to trick me?
I had it because you demanded it.
But I'm not here to talk about that.
I'm here to talk about Jeff Malone.
- What about him?
- You may be aware that he and I are...
Fifty Shades of Grey?
I'm aware.
I'm going to let that go.
Because you may also not be aware
that I had to lie to him.
He doesn't know about Mike, does he?
No. But he does know
you committed a crime
and that you resigned
and now your name is up on the wall.
- What did you tell him?
- I told him you found out
that I covered up
Daniel Hardman's embezzlement
and that you used it to strong-ann me.
And now, you want me to protect
another one of your secrets.
It's the same secret, Louis.
And you have just
as much invested in it as I do.
No, I don't. Because I don't care if your
relationship with Jeff survives or not.
What do you want, Louis?
I want something
for continuing to cover your ass.
You got something.
You got your name on the wall.
Now I want the respect
that comes with it.
- Meaning?
- I want one of Harvey's clients.
Which one?
That's between me and Harvey.
(SINGING)
You wasted all your time
You didn't mean it
You stole what was mine
I didn't need it
Okay. I agreed to meet.
I hope it's not just so you can tell me
more about what a horrible person I am.
I came here to tell you
that I changed my mind.
So, you admitted to yourself
that I didn't do this?
I've admitted to myself
that you came to me
because this case needs rule-bending.
And you're going to tell me why.
Right now.
- The money.
- Yes, the money.
If you weren't bribed, where the hell
did you get that $25,000 from?
You know where it came from.
It's the same thing you tried to use
to blackmail me last year.
Let me get this straight.
You have an explanation for the money
that would get you out
of this whole thing.
But I can't use it.
- Where are you going?
- To get you out of this.
Welcome to the real world,
Professor.
I need you to find out everything you can
on Garrett Brady.
Absolutely.
Who's Garrett Brady?
The guy on the other side
of Gerard's suit.
Wait a second.
Does this mean you took his case?
You know that means I took his case,
and I don't want to hear any gloating.
Gloating? No. No, no, no.
I'm not... I'm not gloating.
I'm merely recognizing
the fact that you
completely changed your mind
based entirely on what I said.
- Which is gloating.
- Potato, po-tah-to.
But as long as you're going
to think of it that way,
I might as well point out
that since you listened to my lecture,
maybe you should start
calling me Professor.
I'm going to start
calling you unemployed
if you don't figure out
a way around using Gerard's alibi.
Wait. We can't say where
the money came from?
No, we can't.
Because he was playing
back room poker.
And if that comes out,
Harvard fires him.
Are you kidding me? He's an ethics
professor and he's breaking the law?
Where the hell do you
think my chip comes from?
Well, if we can't use his alibi,
how are we supposed
to get him out of this?
I don't know, Professor.
But you're the one
who wanted us to take this case,
so why don't you use that big brain
of yours and find a solution?
- You're giving me Henry Gerard.
- What?
I saw him, I want him,
you've got him, he's mine.
That's not how the way
it works, Louis.
I'm afraid you'll have
to find yourself another boyfriend.
Oh, this is exactly how it works.
You talked to Jessica, didn't you?
I sure did, and she used me
to cover her ass.
So, I get one of your clients
in return.
You want one of my clients,
we can talk about that.
But Gerard's staying with me.
Oh, please. Don't pretend
like you actually care about him.
He can't even stand you.
Louis, I just offered to consider
giving you one of my clients.
So I suggest you let Gerard go.
No, I'm not letting anything go,
because it doesn't make any sense.
Not only can't he stand you,
he doesn't respect you.
- Because he's got things...
- What did you just say to me?
I said he doesn't respect you.
Well, you know what?
He definitely doesn't respect you.
Because when he told
me he needed a lawyer,
I tried to send him your way.
And his exact words were,
"I don't want Louis. I want you."
Fine. Then I'll just take another one
of your clients.
- You're not taking a thing.
- You just said that I...
I don't give a shit
what I just said, okay?
My clients are my clients.
And you don't get out of my office
in the next three seconds,
something is going to happen
between you and me.
And I guarantee it won't end with you
keeping all of your teeth.
No. Just turn around
and walk right back out that door.
- Harvey.
- Did you hear what I said?
I did. But apparently,
you didn't hear what Jessica said
about wiping the slate clean.
And apparently you
didn't hear what I said,
because I just told Louis
he could have one of my clients.
And three seconds later,
you told him he couldn't.
Yeah, because I realized
that I'm paying for Jessica's mistake.
No, Harvey. You were willing
to pay for her mistake
right up until Louis
said Gerard doesn't respect you.
- Oh, that has nothing to do with it.
- You can lie to yourself all you want,
- but I'm not going to let you bullshit me.
- What the hell are you talking about?
Henry Gerard is the one person you
respect who never respected you.
And Louis touched that nerve.
And I told you,
that has nothing to do with it.
- You really think that?
- I don't think it, I know it.
Then you know what, Harvey?
You're no different than Louis.
Because you have
a chance to help us all move on,
and you are blowing it off
out of pettiness,
which is exactly
what Louis would do.
- What do you want from me, Donna?
- I want you to be a grown-up
and do what you said you'd do
in the first place.
You got something?
Yeah, we've been
overlooking the obvious.
Yeah, I'm not in the mood
for 20 questions. Give it to me.
Unless you're traveling
internationally and don't report it,
carrying cash on board
a plane isn't a crime.
Great, except for the fact that
Gerard's not being charged
with smuggling, he's being sued.
Right. But my point is, how did
Garrett Brady even find that out?
He found out because
Gerard was detained by the TSA.
Who talked to him for five minutes
and then sent him on his way.
Those searches aren't
a matter of public record.
- Exactly.
- Holy shit.
Brady bribed the TSA.
Which isn't only illegal,
it makes that report totally inadmissible.
You figured this out on your own?
I would have done it faster,
but I had to order some sushi.
Would have done it faster.
That's what you said
your first week here.
- Except it was pizza instead of sushi.
- Yeah, I'm growing.
You mean Rachel
taught you how to eat.
Like I said, I'm growing.
Donna, I'm a little
busy at the moment.
Too busy to take on this?
What's that?
Just the first client that Jessica gave
Harvey when he made name partner.
Harvey said he wouldn't let me
have any of his clients.
No, he said he would.
But then, instead of taking him up on it,
you went ahead and shit on his feelings.
Please.
Harvey doesn't have feelings.
That's not true and you know it.
And you of all people
should know that a person
can overreact when they're hurt.
If you're referring to me,
I do not overreact when...
Okay. Whatever you say,
Fatty-Baldy.
Okay, get the hell
out of my office and...
Fine, you have a small
legitimate point.
- I really hurt his feelings?
- Yeah, you really did.
But then he realized
he was overreacting
and that this was a chance for us all
to get back to where we were.
You swear that is the first client
that Jessica gave him
after he made name partner?
I swear.
Leave me the file.
You two go ahead.
I haven't decided yet.
Actually, we're not here for the falafel.
We're here to introduce ourselves.
Mike Ross.
Harvey Specter.
We represent Henry Gerard.
Oh. (CHUCKLES) Well, in that case,
let me buy you two lunch.
Because I'm about to come
into an unexpected windfall.
Well, I guess that's your thing,
paying people off.
I hope the TSA
got more than some shitty falafel.
What the hell are you talking about?
I'm talking about this.
- Bribery?
- HARVEY: Ironic, isn't it?
You suing Professor Gerard
for accepting a bribe
when you're the one paying off
federal employees?
Allegedly paying, Counselor.
Tsk-tsk.
- You don't want to slander me.
- So you admit it?
I don't admit a thing.
Your client sold out
victims of a train derailment.
He's going to pay.
You may not be
willing to admit anything here,
but you'll have to
in front of the judge.
Because I've drafted subpoenas
for every TSA employee
- on duty that night.
- Drop the case, Mr. Brady.
- Are you threatening me?
- We're informing you.
Well, let me inform you.
In case you forgot, the TSA falls under
the Department of Homeland Security.
Which makes this a
national security issue.
This has nothing to do with national
security and you know it.
All I know is, the government found
a large sum of cash on a passenger.
How they came to know that,
how they proceeded to investigate that,
and what they did with that information
is the government's business.
- And that's what you're going with?
- That's not what I'm going with.
That's what they're going to go with.
So you can call up
as many TSA agents as you like,
but they're not going
to be saying a thing.
And you can buy
your own damn falafel.
(SNAPS FINGERS)
I need Cutie Pie Cosmetics.
You want to try that again?
I have a meeting with Joan Walsh tonight
and I need her files.
- Joan is Harvey's client.
- Not anymore.
Since when?
Since it doesn't matter,
because I'm name partner.
Which means when I say
I need something,
your response should either be
"How high?" or "Can I have another?"
Fine. There are a few things
that you should know...
You see, what I know is,
your boss seems to think
all it takes to impress Joan Walsh
is getting Donna to make
a fancy dinner reservation.
But I'm going to impress her
with so much legal domination
that by the end of the night,
all she's going to be able to say is,
"Harvey Specter who?"
- Okay, that's a mistake, and I...
- A mistake? Oh, I get it.
You're trying to impress me
with your legal domination
to prove that you're not just a paralegal,
but an associate.
No, Louis, I'm not...
See, I don't care
what you call yourself.
So unless you did such a shitty job
the files are un-readable,
hand them over to me right now.
That's more like it.
What's this?
I know you have to work tonight.
But you also need to eat.
I wouldn't call this just eating.
Well, you deserve
better than paper plates.
- I don't mind paper plates.
- Oh, I know you don't.
- I just said you deserve better.
- Is that ropa vieja?
Mmm-hmm. I made it myself.
Which means you got it
at the Cuban place
- that I love on 40th and Lex.
- By myself.
What did I do to deserve this?
I don't know.
I'm just... Feeling closer.
Because I confided in you.
Because the walls
are coming down and I can feel it.
What did I do to deserve you?
Mmm. Well, we can talk about that
over this delicious meal
that I made all by myself.
(SIGHS)
(KISSES)
To us.
(GLASSES CLINK)
(mum-nus)
And then I said,
"Helen, that's no Pomeranian.
"That's a Pomimo.
You've been had."
(LAUGHS)
That is hilarious.
Really. Dogs. They are...
They are so fascinating.
- Do you have many dogs, Louis?
- Hell, no.
Building regulations,
it's a cluster...
I've been fighting them for years.
- Oh, that's horrible.
- Yes.
As is what's going on with your stock.
Oh, Louis, we're having dinner.
Put that away.
No, no. But I just thought you'll
be interested to know
that we could skyrocket
the share price...
Right now, what I'm interested in
is having another Manhattan
and hearing what's
on the dessert list.
We don't need a list.
Get the creme brfilée.
- Now, this stock issue? I have...
- Fax the papers to my office,
and I'll review them
when I get home.
When you get home? What the...
What the hell did we come
to dinner for then?
- For this.
- What this?
This.
Okay, I don't know how Harvey handled
these quarterly reviews, but...
Oh, Harvey was magnificent.
(SIGHS) Truth be told,
I was a little disappointed
when I heard that you'd be
handling this instead of him.
But I haven't seen your Cha-Cha yet,
so the jury's still out.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
- That was a lawyer joke.
- Yep, got it.
Yep. Listen. Joan.
I think you're going to be really glad
that it was me here tonight, because
I already sent a letter to your board.
- You did what?
- I notified them of this.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
Why the hell would you do
something so patently stupid?
Stupid? Hey. I didn't become
name partner being stupid.
Didn't you? Two members of my board
are about to reach their term limits.
At least one of them is being circled
by Glamour Cosmetics.
You have just notified
that person of a product
that I've had in R 8; D for years.
And now, they can trade information
for a seat on the board
of my biggest competitor.
- Joan, I didn't know.
- Tell me, Mr. Litt.
Did you actually graduate
from law school
or did you just buy your
way onto the letterhead?
Yeah, you better put that bag down.
Because we're staying all night.
It didn't go well with Joan, did it?
No, it didn't,
because you sandbagged me.
I didn't sandbag you.
Well then, what do you call
not telling me
that Glamour was circling
her board members?
I tried to tell you, but you couldn't
hear me through all of your rage.
What I'm not hearing is the sound of you
putting your bag down.
Because the board members
are meeting tomorrow afternoon,
and I only have until then to fix this.
And you want me to help you?
You're the associate on this case,
aren't you?
So now I'm an associate?
Okay, you know what?
Now is not the time to get into it.
No, now is exactly
the time to get into it.
Because you have taken
every opportunity possible
to make me feel like I am nothing.
And now, even though
you want something,
you're still treating me
like I'm nothing.
I'm treating you like
every other associate.
That is bullshit. And you know,
even if it were true,
you didn't used
to treat me that way.
I didn't used to know
you lied to me on a daily basis.
Louis, it would serve you right
if I take my bag and leave you here
and go home to the man that I love.
- So you're not going to help?
- No, I'm going to help you.
But not because you deserve it.
I'll do it because I am an associate
and I am a professional,
which means I am capable
of putting the personal aside
in order to do my job.
- And one of those, please.
- Just what I was in the mood for.
Well, if you're getting a bagel,
that means you kicked ass.
Which I did.
You called up the TSA and busted up
their national security defense?
No, I used their defense.
Gerard's going to testify under seal
because it's a matter of national security.
And the judge bought that.
What's not to buy?
The TSA made the argument for us.
- What did Brady say?
- That's the best part about it.
He doesn't even know it.
- It's a matter of national security.
- We testify under seal,
the judge realizes that Gerard
is a degenerate gambler.
But a fair mediator.
The case gets dismissed,
and Garrett Brady
and Harvard Law
never know what happened.
You thought of all
of that on your own?
You think you're the only one
who can come up
with an intelligent solution?
You are 1 for 400 in the time
we've worked together.
Okay, smart guy,
since I did your job for you,
- you're going to do my job for me.
- You want me to prep Gerard
because you don't want to sit in a room
and listen to him talk for two hours.
I didn't want to 15 years ago,
and I don't want to now.
We only get one shot at this,
and his testimony better be rock solid.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Thanks.
Oh, yeah. Sure. Help yourself.
Dick.
I see you haven't slept.
I have a lot of work
that needs attending to.
I bet you do, considering the phone call
I got from Joan Walsh this morning.
Oh. She called you?
She wanted to know what the other
name partners were going to do
- about the one that screwed the pooch.
- Oh, come on. That is not fair.
I didn't have all of the information and...
You had enough information
to make a deal to get her from Harvey.
And part of that deal
was you backing me with Jeff.
Oh, so that's why you're here.
- You don't trust I'm still going to do it.
- Because you haven't done it yet,
and you have a history
of making poor decisions
when things aren't going your way.
The only poor decision I made
is agreeing to cover
for you in the first place.
You didn't think that was such a bad idea
when you were using it
to get what you wanted.
And now, you're threatening
to take that thing away.
Louis, you want
to keep Joan, that's on you.
But I held up my end of the bargain.
You better hold up yours.
MIKE: I just want to go over it
one more time, Professor.
- How much money was in that pot?
- I'm tired of going over it.
Why do we have to keep replaying
every moment of this game?
Because your entire case depends on it.
My case depends on the fact
that I won that money gambling,
not whether I won it with a flush.
Your case depends
on the judge believing you.
And if he finds any holes
in your testimony, then we...
I gave you the names
of everyone I knew at that game.
But none of those men were there
when you won that money.
I can't help it if I didn't get the name
of the guy I beat.
Which is why your story
needs to be rock solid.
Okay. Go ahead.
So, I ask you again, Professor,
how much money
was in the final pot?
- Roughly $12,000.
- And you won that hand?
As I said before,
I won and then I cashed out.
And what did you have again?
I had a queen-high flush.
- And who did you beat?
- I told you, I didn't get his name.
- Okay. So, what did he have?
- Two pair, queens over sixes.
Wait a second. You said before
that the man next to you
folded with two queens up.
And now this guy had two queens
and you had a queen-high flush?
I said that the man next to me
folded with two kings.
- No, you didn't.
- You heard me wrong.
No, I didn't.
Is this part of prepping me
or are you accusing me of something?
- I'm trying to get your story to line up.
- My story does line up.
- Not to me, it doesn't.
- Look, young man,
if you're going to
sit over there and call me a liar...
I'm not calling you a liar. But if you say
tomorrow what you said today,
we're going to be in a lot of trouble.
Because where I come from,
there are only four queens in a deck.
I said two kings.
And I'm going to
say that again tomorrow.
So you do your job
and I'm going to do mine.
- MIKE: He's lying.
- What are you talking about?
Gerard's story about winning all
that money playing poker is bullshit.
All right, slow down.
What the hell happened?
I did the math
and the hands don't add up.
What do you mean,
you did the math?
I mean, first, he said
that he drew a queen on fourth street.
And then, when I pressed
him about it, he told...
Wait a second.
This conclusion is based
on him recalling hands
under cross-examination?
Harvey, I got kicked out
of Atlantic City for counting cards.
- I know this shit.
- That doesn't mean he's lying.
I've got a little
experience with that, too.
And I'm telling you he was.
- Or maybe he's tired.
- Or maybe I'm right.
Or maybe you don't know
what the hell you're talking about.
- Why are you defending him?
- Because you asked me to.
Look.
Harvey. I'm not saying
that he took a bribe.
I'm just saying that he didn't get
that money playing poker.
Well, unless he admitted that,
he's testifying tomorrow.
Since when do you stick
your head in the sand?
- Did he admit it?
- No, he didn't.
But he screwed up the details.
And he shouldn't have,
because people who
are telling the truth get it right.
And you know it.
- What's that?
- Jacks full of fours.
- I can see that. But why...
- Why is it staring you in the face?
It's what I threw down
the last time I won a huge hand.
It was six weeks ago,
and I can remember every hand
that every player at that table had.
Now, if you won money
the other night, you'd remember it, too.
I do remember.
- And as I explained to your associate...
- Yeah, stop bullshitting me.
Where the hell did that money
really come from?
Because if you don't tell me the truth,
I'm canceling that hearing right now.
It came from a student of mine.
- For what?
- In exchange for changing his grade.
- Jesus Christ. For $25,000?
- He was going to fail my class.
And that would have stopped him
from getting an offer from...
You goddamn hypocrite.
You preach about ethics
and you do this?
This is about ethics.
And you don't have
any idea why I did it.
I don't care why you did it.
I care about what you're making me do.
Because I'm not suborning pel'jury.
Well, you tell me
that you've never done anything worse.
I knew it.
You would do it for someone else,
but not for me.
You know what, Professor?
There's a small part of me
that actually thought
that you came to me
because you thought I'm the best.
But you just think I'll do
whatever it takes to win.
Isn't that what
makes you the best?
Get someone else to do your dirty work,
because I'm not suborning pel'jury.
(GRUNTING)
What are you doing?
Getting my blood flowing.
I've been sitting here all night
and restless leg syndrome
kills 14 people every hour.
I don't think that's accurate.
I don't care what you think.
What do you have?
I found a way to
fix things with Joan.
Okay. You're arguing
anything in R & D
is the intellectual property of the person
who suggested the product?
Until such time
that the results become public.
Which they did the second I sent
the board that letter.
Except board members are subject
to the non-disclosure agreement.
Well, the board members haven't signed
a non-disclosure agreement.
Yet.
- What's to stop them from refusing?
- Nothing.
But if they do,
then the non-compete kicks in.
Preventing them from revealing
the contents of my letter
- under threat of prosecution.
- Specifically corporate espionage.
Oh, my God!
You got this idea from...
- Our bylaws.
- My bylaws.
Rachel, holy shit, this is...
Acceptable.
I think the word you're
looking for is "awesome."
Well, the word
I'm saying is get out.
Because I have
a meeting to prepare for.
You know what, Louis?
I have been working all night
and this gets your ass
out of a major sling.
So instead of dismissing me,
you should be asking me
to come with you.
Excuse me, Miss Professional.
You wanted me to treat you
like every other associate. Now I am.
By acting as if I did nothing?
No, by acknowledging
you did acceptable work.
Letting you come with me is something
that I would only do for you
if we were friends.
Which we are not.
You canceled the hearing.
You were right.
He was lying.
I'm sorry.
You know, I knew he was a hypocrite
after I found out about the gambling.
But I never thought
he'd sell out Harvard.
What are you talking about?
He did take the bribe, but it had nothing
to do with the accident victims.
He did it to change someone's grade.
- Why would he do that?
- What difference does it make?
Either way, he was going
to let me suborn perjury.
It makes a difference
because we still have to win this case.
Oh, I don't give a shit
about winning this case. (SCOFFS)
I've never heard
you say anything like that before.
You... You care about
winning every case.
Every game.
Every argument.
Did you hear me?
He was going to let me subom perjury.
So would every client you have
if they thought they'd get away with it.
He's not every client.
No, he's one you hated in the first place.
- I didn't hate him.
- Harvey, what is going on here?
I thought he was better than us.
I sat in that class
and I listened to him talk
about what kind
of lawyers we should be.
And I always let him down,
because I knew
that wasn't the kind of lawyer that wins.
And I wanted to win. So I'd argue
with him and he looked down on me.
And now,
instead of you letting him down,
he let you down.
He turned out to be
no better than any of us.
So then, let's make him better than us.
- Ms. Walsh.
- You are not on my schedule today.
Ms. Walsh, please,
take a look at this.
What is it?
- It's a chance to make things right.
- Huh.
You cannot call board
members employees
based on them having access
to an expense account.
Not just an expense account.
They have corporate cards
and standing offices.
Which, as defined by Section 14.2
of the Internal Revenue Code,
makes them employees.
Well, Mr. Lift,
it seems I won't be demanding
a new point person after all.
- I'm glad to hear that.
- Huh. Are you?
Of course I am.
You're my first client as name partner.
You're very important to me.
Well, I suppose
we'll find out the truth
when someone else
makes name partner.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm not an idiot.
I know that no one in your firm
wants to deal with me.
That's not true.
In fact, I fought for you.
You may have thought
you were fighting for me,
but I know that
Jessica dumped me on Harvey.
And it seems that
the second you made name partner,
Harvey did the same thing to you.
Oh, you didn't know that, did you?
Then maybe we were
meant for each other,
since we're both left out of the club.
You betrayed me.
You make this big speech
about repairing our friendship
- and all it was was more words.
- What are you talking about?
You convince me to take Joan,
while conveniently leaving out the fact
you're doing Harvey a favor?
That's not why I did it, Louis.
Well, just tell me right now.
Can he stand her?
No. But he was going to
keep her, because you...
Hurt his precious feelings?
I know. I felt so awful about that.
You know what, Louis?
You should.
And while you're at it,
you should feel pretty awful
about being a dick to me right now.
- You lied to me again.
- No, Louis, I fought for you. Again.
No. You made Joan
sound important.
The first client that Jessica gave Harvey
when he made name partner.
She is important, Louis.
But you can't see that
because you didn't
want a client.
You just wanted to take something away
from Harvey.
What I want is respect.
Then get out of your own way
and get on the goddamn team.
You mean the team
that kept Mike's secret from me?
No, Louis! I mean the team
that protected its own.
Because that's what teams do.
And you know,
I shouldn't even be telling you this
because she wasn't going to.
But if you need a little bit more evidence
of what we do for each other,
then take a look at Rachel,
because she got Katrina a job.
- What?
- That's right. Your former associate.
And you've been
treating Rachel like shit.
So if you're done yelling at me,
then I suggest
you go fix one of the thousand things
that you have screwed up lately.
Because the rest of us?
We are done fighting for you.
Mr. Ross.
You must be Ian.
And please, don't call me Mr. Ross.
- Mike is fine.
- Oh, sure.
Hey, thanks for your call, Mike.
Pearson Specter is a great firm.
Yeah, well, you're a great candidate.
I'm a little curious
why you're still interviewing.
I heard you had
a solid offer at Skadden.
I do, but Skadden Arps
is no Pearson Specter.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
Are you sure it's not
because you're worried
they'll find out that you failed
Professor Gerard's legal ethics class?
- What?
- Oh, shit. You don't know.
He hasn't changed your grade.
But he still has your $25,000.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm exactly who I said I was.
The only thing I left out is that
Professor Gerard is my client.
Come on. He can't be
in trouble for this. I'd know.
He's not. He's being
accused of accepting a bribe
while conducting
a federal mediation because of this.
- That's not my problem.
- It's your problem now.
Which is why you're going to sign this.
What is that?
It's a sworn affidavit stating the money
that you paid Gerard is a loan.
- What happens to my grade?
- It stays the same.
Because Henry Gerard
doesn't take money to change grades.
That's bullshit. We had a deal.
Yeah, well, consider this your first
lesson in the real world.
Deals change.
I don't care what world it is.
I'm not signing anything.
That's too bad.
Because the truth will come out.
And this way, you're failing a class
instead of getting thrown out of school
for bribing a professor.
It's up to you, Ian.
You want an F? Or do you want
to not have a legal career at all?
GERARD: So I sign this
and the bribery allegations are gone?
And no one ever knows a thing.
But I still have to pay
Ian back the money.
- That's the way loans work.
- You say that like I am a monster.
I say it like it's true.
You know,
you never let me tell you
what the money was for.
You didn't listen to
me when I told you I don't care.
Who's the monster now?
I don't care because you always said
the circumstances don't matter.
Well, do you care that
after Mike grilled me,
I was so impressed with him that
I wondered why I had forgotten him.
So I looked through my old records,
just to see how he did.
But I couldn't find any record of him
ever being in my class.
Just like they're not
going to find any record
of you accepting
a bribe from a student.
Hmm.
- Are you saying we're even?
- I'm saying you got a two-for-one.
Because they're also not going to find
any record of you gambling last year.
That's why you came to see me
back then, isn't it?
You didn't want
anyone to find out about him.
I'm not going to tell you why I came
to see you last year, Henry.
Because the circumstances
don't matter.
(CHUCKLES)
You really did pay
attention in my class.
A lot more than you think.
I'm sorry I let you down, Mr. Specter.
Professor...
Don't worry about
paying back that loan.
I got it.
(SINGING)
Where do we go from here?
Where do we go?
And is it real
Or just something
we think we know?
And where are
we going now?
Mmm, where do we go?
Louis. What can I do for you?
The question isn't
what you can do for me, Jeff.
But it's a matter
of what you're going to do.
Which is cut
the bullshit right now.
- What?
- You heard me.
I know Jessica told
you about Hardman.
Yes, she did tell me.
And I have refrained
from coming to see you
about blackmailing her out of courtesy.
Courtesy? You haven't so much
as wished me a congratulations.
You want me to kiss the ring,
Louis, after what you did?
You're damn right I do.
Because I don't care how it got up there.
My name is on that wall.
And if I had a crowbar handy,
- I would pry it off.
- Well, Jeff, you don't.
So, the question you've
got to ask yourself is,
do you want to
stick with the team?
Because my name is up there to stay,
whether you like it or not.
Who can we trust
from here?
Who can we trust?
From cradle to grave
From ashes to ashes
From dust to dust
Hey.
Thanks for meeting me.
What's going on?
I wanted to thank you
for making me take Gerard.
What happened?
What makes you think
something happened?
Because I know you.
And I know you don't have
moments of self-reflection,
let alone have
a drink with someone
to tell them about it
unless something happened.
You know what?
Something did happen.
I dealt with some shit
and I'm trying to thank you for it,
because it turned out
to be a good thing.
I think the word
you're looking for is closure.
That's your word.
The word I'm looking for is,
"You're welcome, Harvey.
That's nice of you to say."
Thanks, Harvey.
Good. Now, listen to me.
For a minute there, I thought you were
going to tell me that he knows.
- What?
- Maybe I'm crazy.
But when I was prepping him,
for a second he looked at me
and I thought...
He's suspicious.
And then, you called, and after
everything that's happened already...
It's fine, Mike.
He doesn't know.
How do we move around
with all these eyes on us?
And all on us
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English