(HARVEY READING)
MIKE: Walter, I can't
guarantee you we'll win,
but I can guarantee you that
I will never sell you out.
You told me that
Mike Ross wasn't a threat,
and then he handcuffed us with a TRO.
I want proof that he's giving up his bid.
And if I don't get it by the morning,
I'm going to call my private investigators
and I'm going to finish what I started.
What did Harvey tell you?
WALTER: Looks like he told me the truth.
We're done.
I want you to stop
the personal attacks on Mike.
You told me this wasn't going
to be a problem.
You don't have to stop this
because you're some changed man.
You have to stop this
because you owe me.
Mr. Ross. Eric Woodall.
I'm the U.S. Attorney...
For the Southern district of New York.
Yeah, I know who you are.
Since when does the SEC
go around intimidating law firms
by going after their clients?
They don't, but they will when Eric
Woodall starts there next week.
Seven clients, seven subpoenas.
All coming tomorrow.
Back to sin again
must be fate
The wait was all day
Uh, excuse me.
You don't have an appointment.
I don't need an appointment.
Sit down, shut up, and listen.
Harvey might forgive you because you
returned those recordings, but I don't.
- Donna.
- Not done.
What Harvey did with Gillie,
it was harsh,
but using what I told you
in a private conversation?
That crosses a line
that even Harvey never would.
- Donna.
- Still not done.
When you left our firm,
you left me too.
But I honestly thought
that we'd always be friends.
Now, I'm not so sure.
Amy, did you send
Donna the package?
Guilt gift. Didn't open it.
It was a Balenciaga Classic Town bag.
- Ivory?
- Anthracite with an outside pocket.
His idea or yours?
Don't answer that.
It was yours.
I'm sorry, Donna.
You and Harvey want to knock each
other out, you go right ahead.
But don't ever betray me again.
Nice shoes.
She's even better than I imagined.
And nothing ever lasts
that hesitates
HARVEY: Looking for this?
Harvey Specter.
What brings you to Montclair
at 7:00 in the morning?
Oh, you know what
brings me here.
I woke up to find these
on my welcome mat.
As much as I'd love to have
been responsible
for subpoenaing
seven of your firm's top clients,
I didn't even
know about this until just now.
You didn't even have
the balls to come at me directly.
- Get off my property.
- What's the matter, Eric?
- You're afraid I'll get you fired again?
- (CHUCKLES) I get it.
You want to hear me say
I'm using my new position
to destroy your business,
because you're the piece of garbage
that got me fired.
Isn't that what you want
to hear me say?
Oh, I know you'll never say that.
But I do want you
to admit that you sent
- an Agent Brian Harris after my firm.
- Sorry.
I don't even have jurisdiction
over that department.
That department's run
by a man named Sean Cahill.
So, all on his own,
Sean Cahill just happened
to target my firm.
Well, he is a killer attorney
with a nose for sleazy lawyers.
And I should know. We came up together
at the Justice Department.
You know, that little governmental
agency that protects their own?
Well, Eric, your big brother couldn't
protect you from getting fired before,
and I don't see how this is gonna
be any different.
By the way, that's yesterday's paper.
- You wanted to see me?
- Sure did.
Have a seat.
I was going over our trade sheets.
I couldn't help but notice
you bought another
100,000 shares of Gillie Industries.
- It's gonna be fine...
- Do I look like an asshole to you?
- Where the hell did you get the money?
- You know where I got the money.
I bought the shares on margin.
- And leveraged my company.
- The bylaws said I can do it.
I don't care what the bylaws say.
You did this without asking.
- Look, I know you're pissed...
- Oh, I'm not pissed.
I've been waiting for you
to have the balls
to do something like this
since you got here.
You raised my risk, but you also raised
my reward, and on top of it,
you did it like an investment banker...
Without permission.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, thank you, Jonathan.
Go get 'em.
- One more thing.
- Yeah.
You have a week
to deleverage my company.
If you don't, you're out of a job.
You wanna explain to me why you went
to Eric Woodall's house this morning?
I understand you're bent out of shape
because I stepped on your territory.
You think I give a shit
about my territory?
(SCOFFS) Then what the hell
are you doing in here?
Listen, I really don't care
if you work this thing or I do.
- But whoever it is has to not be an idiot.
- And how exactly am I an idiot?
- You poked the bear.
- Eric Woodall isn't the bear.
No, I am.
And whatever you were about to say,
don't say it.
Harvey, this is his case.
It's why we brought him in,
- and I don't want you involved.
- Me?
I'm the one who found out
it's not Woodall coming after us. It's...
Sean Cahill.
You think I didn't know that?
HARVEY: These are my clients,
and when they call in a panic,
I need to be the voice
on the other end of the line.
Then be the voice
on the other end of the line,
but you're not handling the SEC.
I'm the reason they're coming after us.
Which is why you wanted to hire Jeff
in the first place.
JEFF: That was before
all this became real.
Now that it's happening,
he doesn't want to sit on the sidelines.
- Damn right, I don't.
- JESSICA: Well, then, find yourself
a comfortable spot on the bench.
Because like it or not, Jeff's in charge.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
So, did it go
just like you said it would?
Exactly. Except for the part
where if I don't find a new investor
in a week, I'm out of a job.
Well, I'm surprised he gave you a week.
(SIGHS) Amy, it's not funny.
I know it isn't. I was just trying
to make the best of the situation.
Well, if you want to make
the best of the situation,
get me a meeting
with Tony Gianopolous.
Because if I can't get in there...
(SIGHING) I'm in trouble.
We're in trouble.
You really mean that?
You think I'm staying
here if you leave?
- Thank you, Amy.
- I'm just kidding.
Epstein's been trying to peach me
since the day I got here. Mmm.
Yeah, you think those
flowers bought themselves?
You...
Wow.
Can I talk to you a second?
If you want an update on the takeover,
you should talk to Harvey.
That's not why I'm here.
- Look, Logan, I... I know that you...
- I have five companies here
that I'm looking at for my next deal,
and I need someone to evaluate them
from a legal standpoint.
- Your next deal.
- Yeah, my next deal.
Harvey told me not to hurt my future
by going below the belt with Mike.
So, instead of not hurting my future,
I thought I'd start planning for it.
So, then, maybe Harvey is who
you should be planning it with.
Well, Harvey's got stuff to do.
And he's not the one who convinced me
to back off Mike.
(CHUCKLING) Are you
saying that I owe you?
No. I'm not saying that,
but that is what you said to me.
So, we're just gonna
go back and forth, trading favors?
Rachel, this isn't a favor.
I have a board meeting on Friday.
I need to be prepared.
So, are you my lawyer or not?
- I will get right on it.
- Thank you.
Louis, I need your help.
- We're gonna need to...
- Don't speak.
You may speak.
What were you doing?
Just thanking the Lord God Almighty.
We taking down Jessica?
We firing Malone?
I am tingling. What, Harvey?
Just tell me what.
Mike Ross just bought another 2%
of Gillie Industries.
He must be leveraged up
to his scrawny little neck.
Exactly. And he's gonna be
scrambling for funding.
You want me to get
your TRO removed.
How do you know that?
Because you pissed off Judge Ramos,
and now she can't stand you.
How do you know that?
Oh, because I keep a list of
your enemies. You want to see it?
- Just get it done.
- Oh, I'm gonna get it done.
It's like taking candy from a baby.
Louis, we're splitting Mike's focus.
That doesn't mean he won't be prepared.
Oh, he can prepare all he wants, but
the student is about to meet the master.
Because Ralph Macchio doesn't stand
a chance against Mr. Miyagi.
You know The Karate Kid?
(CHUCKLES)
That's not cool, Harvey.
Oh, let me see
if I can guess why you're here.
You came to tell me the way I handled
Harvey this morning was sexy.
Oh, you mean when I told him
to leave you alone.
And the way that I allowed you
to do that was very sexy.
- Uh-huh.
- And this is...
The Griffen Cosmetics subpoena.
I looked them all over.
This is the weakest one.
- The weakest one.
- Exactly.
Once this one goes down,
the others fall like dominos.
First of all, if I were going
to take that strategy,
I would go for the hardest one.
Second of all,
why don't you walk yourself
back to your office
and let me do my job?
Excuse me?
You told Harvey you brought me in
to handle this.
(SIGHS)
Your job isn't to worry
about what I told Harvey.
Your job is to worry
about what I'm telling you.
Mmm-hmm.
And what I'm telling you
is that I'm not walking into an SEC
negotiation with a babysitter.
- Negotiation? This is going to be a war.
- I know that.
And I'm gonna win it with one shot.
Then I suggest
you warm up to this.
You're not walking into the SEC
with a babysitter.
You're walking in there with a bazooka.
(EXHALES)
- Hey, Mike, you need to see something.
- No, I don't have time.
I'm working on
the Gianopolous proposal.
Yeah, that proposal
isn't gonna matter if they win this.
Goddamn it.
- Harvey's trying to roll back the TRO?
- No, it's not Harvey. Check the docket.
It's some woman named Lois Litt.
(CHUCKLES)
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
I know how to handle her.
Um, here.
This is 90% done.
Check it over.
Make sure there's not
one comma out of place.
Uh, Mike, come on.
You know I can do more than...
I don't have time, Amy.
Just do it.
Okay-
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACKING)
How long did you work
in this shithole?
Sorry, I'm late.
Been up to my neck in work.
Just filed seven huge subpoenas.
- Yeah, we know what you filed.
- Oh.
I see you brought the missus.
JEFF: Jessica, whatever
you're about to say, don't say it.
- How about I say it with this?
- Ooh, a subpoena?
- (SNIFFING) Smells fresh.
- It is.
And you'll be answering it
in court tomorrow.
Oh. Well, then, I better see what flavor
bullshit you're sewing up.
(READING INDISTINCTLY)
Ah. Ah, now, this is a good one.
"Malicious prosecution
of Pearson Specter clients."
- And how exactly are we doing that?
- JESSICA: I'll tell you how.
You come at our clients, our clients leave
us, you drop their cases.
Well, I certainly wouldn't tell them
that's how to avoid SEC scrutiny.
But it's not my fault if dropping
Pearson Specter starts catching on.
JESSICA: Enough bullshit.
You're targeting my clients on behalf
of Eric Woodall, and you know it.
That is a lovely theory,
but if you had any proof,
you wouldn't be
standing here right now.
I have proof, Sean.
I have proof you filed seven cases
in one day against our clients,
which we both know has never
happened in the history of the SEC.
It has now.
We've filed nine cases
against clients of Weil Gotshal,
eight against Skadden
and six against Cravath.
Welcome to the new SEC.
We target law firms.
And as long as we're not
only targeting yours,
the only way to shut this down
is to shut us down.
You and I both know
what's really going on here, Sean.
- And I'm gonna prove it.
- Well, good luck.
But how do you think Judge Hopkins
is gonna respond to your allegations
when I tell him they're coming
from a man who was about to be fired?
(CHUCKLES) Oh, you didn't tell her?
(INHALES DEEPLY)
(WHISPERS) That's awkward.
I'll see you in court.
- JEFF: Jessica.
- I don't wanna hear it.
- JEFF: Well, you need to hear it.
- What? That you lied to me?
- You know, I didn't actually lie to you.
- Oh, no, no. No.
You tell me that you didn't lie
because we never directly
asked you the question,
and I will knock your head off.
All right, fine. I lied.
I lied because it doesn't matter.
I wanna fight for you
and I'm the best man to do it.
Well, the new part of the equation
is that you just made me look like a fool.
- Jess.
- Don't pull that "Jess" shit with me.
I wanna know what it says in your file.
- I don't know what it says.
- How the hell do you not know?
Because whatever it is, is bullshit.
Because the reason
they were gonna fire me
is that I refused to go after you.
Then why didn't you tell me that
when you came at us demanding a job?
Because good lawyers negotiate from
a position of strength, not weakness.
Well, the position you just put us in
is pretty goddamn weak.
Ah, well, if it isn't the Boy Wonder.
- Louis. Hey.
- Don't "Louis" me.
You left without even the courtesy
of a "How's your father."
What does that mean?
It means that I'm not here
to exchange pleasantries.
- I'm here to get that TRO lifted.
- I'm sorry you feel that way.
I'm also sorry to hear about Sheila.
Bullshit, you're sorry to hear about
Sheila... What are you talking about?
Come on, you have to have heard.
- Heard what?
- She's engaged.
It's all over Harvard's Facebook page.
Oh, my God.
How could she do this?
She said she could never be attracted
to a handsome man.
Yeah, and that picture
doesn't even do him justice,
but this one, however...
- A thong?
- Yeah.
- Uh...
- What the...
Yeah, it's a whole, like, beach thing,
I guess.
Long weekend.
You're a son of a bitch, Mike.
You're not even sorry at all.
- You're using this to get into my head.
- Louis.
Come on. I can't believe you.
You think I would use
Sheila's engagement
- just to get you off your game?
- Never gonna work.
That I would stick it in your face
that she's all up in this guy's business
in a way that you've never seen before?
Water off a duck's back.
That right now,
she's probably scrapbooking
the first day of their relationship,
which apparently happened
just weeks after you broke her heart?
- You're the devil.
- BAILIFF: Next up on the docket,
Sidwell Investment Group
v. Sanders International.
Looks like that's us.
I'll see you in there.
HARVEY: Louis, I can't believe it.
I give you one goddamn job to do,
and you... What are you doing up there?
Harvey, please. I can explain.
Explain why you stood
in front of the judge like a moron?
- What possible explanation...
- Sheila got engaged.
What? When?
This morning.
Louis, I'm sorry.
I was so sure that she would
just come around
about having children,
you know?
That's why I've been
turning down all those JDate requests.
We'll get Mike another way.
Oh, you're goddamn right
we're gonna get him.
I'm going to get that son of a bitch
if it's the last thing I do.
What are you talking about?
He used the Sheila news
to get into my head, Harvey.
Used the news,
or gave you the news?
Oh, please.
What difference does it make?
It makes all the difference.
Like, on the one hand,
I feel for you,
and on the other,
you're the world's biggest idiot.
Look at my computer. I've been staring
at it for three hours. It's real.
I don't believe it.
Yeah, that Adonis on that yacht
is Sheila's fiancé.
That Adonis is a photoshopped picture
of Lorenzo Lamas from 1998!
- Who the hell is Lorenzo Lamas?
- Well, I can tell you who he isn't.
He isn't Sheila's fiancé!
(CHUCKLING)
Oh, thank God.
Are you even listening?
It was bad enough that Nigel rattled you
with your unread cat letters.
Now, you're letting Mike do this?
- Harvey, please.
- Shut the hell up!
Look, I tried to warn you.
And you stood there
with your stupid leg up in the air
telling me that the student
was no match for the master.
And all it took was one doctored picture
for you to shit the bed!
- I didn't mean to.
- Shut the hell up!
(SOFTLY) God!
- Well, fancy meeting you here.
- Rachel, get out of here.
I was just coming
to make some copies.
(WHISPERS) Louis, what's wrong?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Nothing is wrong.
- Well, obviously, something's wrong.
- Well,
if you're so curious, why don't you just
go ask the man of your dreams?
I'm sure the two of you will have
a big laugh about it later.
Okay, I don't...
I don't know what you're talking about.
But seeing you like this, there is
no way that I would laugh at you.
What is it?
Mike convinced me
that Sheila was engaged
to throw me off my game.
- I'm so sorry, Louis.
- Yeah, well, he sure wasn't.
He stuck a knife in me and twisted it
with the thought of her and another man.
It felt like a... drill in my skull all day,
and then to top it all off, it cost me
the respect of my best friend.
- Maybe...
- Oh, don't you even try to defend him.
No, I wasn't going to.
I was going to say,
maybe this is what you needed
to decide to reconnect with Sheila.
What about Harvey?
How do I, uh, repair that?
I'm really sorry for what happened,
Louis. I am.
(PHOTOCOPIER BEEPING)
(WHIRRING)
. HEY-
Did you eat?
Are you asking because
you're concerned about me
or because you wanna know
if I left you any food?
(SIGHS)
Whoa.
- Tough day?
- I'm sorry.
I've just been working 16-hour days
and I'm really...
Stressed.
- Yeah, I know the feeling.
- Really?
Because I heard that you had
a pretty big win today.
- You talked to Harvey.
- I talked to Louis.
Mike, I know you wanna win, but do you
have any idea what your lie did to him?
It wasn't a lie.
It was a strategy.
It was both.
- And it ended up with him near tears.
- Come on, Rachel.
It just seems like all that matters to you
is winning and you don't
care about what
it does to your friends.
You know what?
I'm sorry that I hurt Louis.
But he was going to that courtroom
so they could put their tender offer
to a vote.
I know.
And you also know, because
we've had this discussion before,
that if he got his way,
they would rip that company to shreds.
So, instead of coming down on me
for what I did to Louis,
why don't you start
worrying about all the lives
that Logan Sanders
is gonna destroy if that happens?
You know, it's funny. You told me
you didn't care who's in charge.
You just wanted whoever it was
to not be an idiot.
- Are you saying that I was an idiot?
- I'm saying we both were.
I shouldn't have gone to Woodall,
and you shouldn't have lied to us.
You don't seem pissed.
I've had enough
happen already today.
Besides, lying to me was wrong,
but lying to the woman you're in a
relationship with is a whole other level.
When do you think
she's gonna get past it?
From personal experience,
that could take a while.
That's not my problem.
That's yours.
Then what are you doing here, Harvey?
I'm here to tell you
what you're gonna do about it.
No. No way.
I'm not taking the stand.
Then what are you doing here?
Because Woodall telling you
to go after our clients
is how you got this job in the first place
and happens to make our case.
He didn't outright tell me to do it
and you know it.
- You had to find out somehow.
- I found out from Brian Harris.
He told me he had this funny feeling
that the day after Woodall arrived
that I was gonna start issuing
subpoenas to Pearson Specter clients.
When I asked him why,
he said, "You know why."
Then you're going to get up on the stand
and tell them that.
I can't. I have no proof.
It was vague,
and it's a third party conversation.
Which makes it hearsay,
and I don't give a shit.
Well, I do, because it opens me up
to slander at best
- and pel'jury charges at worst.
- Well, Jeff,
you used that story
to get your ass in here.
Now use it to get the job done.
Amy!
I thought I asked you to leave the
Gianopolous proposal on my desk.
And I did.
Twenty minutes ago.
What? Okay.
- Did you proof it?
- No.
I thought you'd have a better chance
if the document was riddled with typos.
- This is important.
- I know it is.
Which is why I read it
backwards and forwards.
Okay. Did you add the part about
the leveraged recap, like I asked?
I did. But your figures on
the non-voting stock didn't add up,
so I proposed a staggered board
to make up for the imbalance.
- Staggered board?
- Yeah, don't act so surprised.
I'm sorry, I just thought that you...
You just thought that
I didn't know anything
about what goes on here?
(CHUCKLES)
Listen up, T. Boone Pickens.
I actually know a lot
about this business.
- Okay, I said I'm sorry.
- And I know more than enough
to know that that looks like every other
proposal that's come across my desk.
Well, that gives me a shitload of
confidence going into this meeting.
I'm not trying to destroy
your confidence.
That's the one thing
you have going for you.
- Then, what are you trying to do?
- Mike,
you're not here because you crunched
Sidwell some numbers.
You're here because you solved
a problem for him.
- All right. Get rid of this.
- And bring you everything I can find
on Tony Gianopolous. On it.
Amy.
- Why aren't you...
- Why am I an assistant
and not an investment banker?
I'm getting my PhD in Psychology.
Money bores me.
I don't know why you needed
to talk to me in chambers, Mr. Malone.
I was clear on my ruling.
Well, with all due respect, Your Honor,
your ruling didn't cover the fact
that the SEC has a vendetta
against Pearson Specter.
- That's a serious accusation.
- And if it were the truth,
he would have said it out there,
not in here.
I'm doing it in private, Sean,
because I don't want to slander
an entire department
- based on the actions of two men.
- SEAN: Translation.
He doesn't want to be charged
with perjury,
because he's lying, and this is a joke.
It wasn't a joke when I was asked
to do the exact same thing
that he's doing right now.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Before I left the SEC,
I was told to target
Pearson Specter clients.
- And who exactly told you?
- Brian Harris.
Then, go after him,
'cause all you've got on me is hearsay.
And might I point out,
this is the accusation
of a man who was about to be fired,
which I'd say should be taken
with a cubic meter of salt.
Well, that cubic meter of salt
might actually get a little bit smaller
if Sean here
would, say, open up his files
and show us his paper trail.
Our work product is covered under
federal regulation and he knows that.
I also know you're hiding behind your
office and using his court to do it.
All right, all right. That's enough.
Mr. Malone, I don't appreciate
you using my chambers to testify.
And he may not have proof.
But if one client leaves his firm
and their charges
miraculously disappear,
you're looking
at more than sanctions.
You're looking at jail time.
Thank you.
Rachel.
It's only been a day. You already have
a suggestion for my new deal?
I do.
Good. Then which of those five
companies should I go after?
None of them.
So, you've brought me nothing.
No, I brought you five better options.
- What was wrong with the options?
- Just take a look.
These companies
have no disposable assets.
No, they don't.
They have under-performing assets
that can be turned around
and built into something.
Did you even look into the companies
I gave you?
- Yes, I did. But I...
- But what?
Sounds like someone's been drinking
her boyfriend's Kool-Aid.
Well, maybe if more people did,
there just might be...
Oh, goddamn it, Rachel.
I'm not in business to save the world.
I asked for a professional opinion.
And I gave you a professional opinion.
You just don't like it.
No, I don't.
And now we're gonna have to work
all day tomorrow
to do what I asked you to do
in the first place.
You mean spend all day together.
- If that's what it takes.
- Mmm-hmm.
Did you call this board meeting
just so we could spend
more time together?
Did you bring me deals you knew
I'd reject just to avoid it?
Look,
like I said, I have a meeting on Friday
and I need to be prepared for it.
So maybe you should go back
to your office, get cracking and...
Just give me a call when
you have something.
Okay-
TONY: You're kidding me.
- So this is all mine?
- Yep.
In 20 days, the public access
will be gone,
and you will have yourself
a quarter mile of private beach.
What about the Southampton
City Council?
What about them?
They're a bunch of public
access-loving assholes.
Like I said... What about them?
How did you do this, Mike?
The question isn't "how" I did it,
it's "why" I did it.
Oh. You want something from me.
Just your consideration.
Well, you've earned it. Go ahead.
Not interested.
- You didn't even look at it.
- Oh, I don't have to.
You just said that I earned
your consideration.
Mmm-hmm, and you just got it.
Look, Gillie Industries
is ripe for a turnaround.
- And I already own 7%.
- Well, congratulations.
Now, go beg someone else for money,
'cause you're not getting mine.
- I don't understand.
- You don't have to.
Now get the hell out of my office.
- Mr. Gianopolous...
- I said get the hell out.
Hey, Mike. How's it going?
Fancy meeting you here.
- It was you.
- What was me?
I'm just here to thank you
for the advice you once gave me.
You know,
back when we were friends.
- Louis...
- No, no, no.
No, no, no. You once told me that
my actions have consequences.
Remember? Your actions yesterday
have consequences, too.
- What did you say to Gianopolous?
- Not much.
Just that you were
the person responsible
for his number two leaving him.
I was responsible? He agreed to it.
Well, what he didn't know was that
it was his own lawyer
who came up with the idea.
- Now, he does.
- And what does that...
Have to do with it?
He may have agreed to it,
but it was a betrayal by you.
And here's a little something
you obviously do not know
about investment banking.
The only thing more satisfying
to these guys than money,
is sticking it to someone
who stuck it to them.
Louis.
I'm sorry for hurting you with Sheila.
Don't you ever mention
her name to me again.
Okay-
But it was a move...
Like you just did. So...
- Can we move on?
- Move on?
You used the woman I love
to extend your goddamn TRO.
You knew how I felt about her
and you did it anyway.
I will never, ever forget it
until the day I die.
Good luck beating Harvey
without money.
I have good news.
James Dolan died
and left me the Knicks?
Louis stopped Mike
from getting Gianopolous.
- He blocked his funding.
- Good.
You went to Louis with a problem,
he fixed it,
and all you're gonna say is "good"?
Donna, I'm glad
he fixed the problem,
but it was a problem he created.
He created it because when it comes
to people he cares about,
Louis has a blind spot.
Yeah, for people and cats
and who knows what else.
I'll tell you what else.
He cares about you.
(SIGHS) What do you want
from me, Donna?
I want you to tell him
he did a good job.
I'll tell him when we come out on top.
Okay, Harvey.
You do what you're gonna do.
But just remember,
when Louis asked Sheila to marry him,
you were the one
he picked to be his best man.
And you said, "yes."
I'm sorry, but we're not hiring today.
I'd think you'd be looking for a job,
given the beat down
you took in chambers.
I'm not sure what Jeff disgruntled
employee here told you,
but I'm still standing.
Well, what I told her is that you lost.
- Then why are you here?
- We're here to make you an offer.
You drop all seven cases,
we drop the malicious
prosecution claim.
No deal.
Judge Hopkins is going to be waiting
for you to take action.
Now, too much time goes by,
he's gonna think you're full of shit.
But if you fold right now, he's only
gonna sanction you for the exact claim
that we're willing to drop.
JESSICA: Which is why
we'll tell the judge
that in exchange
for those cases being dropped,
we'll give the SEC unprecedented access
to our clients' books.
Which, of course,
you won't be doing.
No, we won't.
So, what exactly am I getting out of this?
- You get to save face.
- I do like my face.
However, I also like my ass,
which will be on the line
if I take this deal.
Then you have 24 hours to decide
which one you like more.
- Mr. Forstman, Mike Ross.
- No.
- Sir, I think that if you hear me out...
- How the hell did you find me here?
The article in Forbes said you can't go
more than three hours
without one of Rosa's Cafe Cubanos.
That article in Forbes
was six years ago.
It also said you never change.
Did you also read where I have
every Bud Fox wannabe
dumped in a local landfill?
If you do that,
you'll miss the opportunity
to get back at Harvey Specter.
And what does a little shit like you
know about Harvey Specter?
I know that he bought that '63
Aston Martin out from under you,
and you've hated him ever since.
You know he keeps it in a garage?
Doesn't even drive it.
What do you want?
- Gillie Industries.
- Gillie Industries
is a black hole of distressed debt.
- I want nothing to do with it.
- No, it isn't.
It's a '63 Aston Martin.
Who do you work for?
Who says I work for anyone?
Because a young kid like you
with enough clout to go after Gillie?
I'd know you.
- I work for Jonathan Sidwell.
- Okay. You've got my 230 mil.
I only need 80.
You don't know what you need.
What happens to the company is my call.
Done.
Oh, one more thing,
when you get those papers.
I have a feeling there will be a provision
buried in there that says that once
the deal closes, you cut Sidwell out.
- I'm... I'm sorry. What?
- I don't know him.
And I don't want him
sucking a chunk out of a deal
that can't happen without me.
- Well?
- He went for it.
- That is great.
- It's not all great.
He'll only give me the money
if I agree to cut out Sidwell.
What? What...
(CHUCKLES)
What does "cut him out" even mean?
It means make sure Sidwell
doesn't get a penny from this deal.
(WHISPERS) Mike.
The second he finds that out,
you're gone.
He's not gonna find out
until the deal closes.
And if I don't find the money,
I'm out of a job anyway.
Oh. I... (CHUCKLES)
I get it. At least, this way,
you get to leave on the winning side.
- We leave on the winning side.
- Who says I'm gonna do that?
What happened to
"You think I'm staying if you leave?"
Yeah, that was before I knew
you were gonna screw over Sidwell.
- Amy, I...
- No. He may be a dick sometimes,
- but he's the reason you're here.
- You think I want this?
I have to make a choice between
the promise I made to Walter Gillie
and what I owe Jonathan.
Mike, Walter Gillie doesn't give a shit
about that promise anymore.
Yeah, but I do.
And so do all the people
that work for him.
So you're gonna do it.
(SIGHS)
(WHISPERS) I don't know.
But I do know that I keep having
to do shitty things just to win this thing,
but I'm gonna go make up
for one of them right now.
I'm sorry I didn't do
what you asked me to do.
- I should have evaluated your ideas.
- You should have.
But I should have remembered
that you don't always do
what people expect of you.
You mean what people tell me to do.
- I chose the nicer version.
- Well, I, um...
I've finished what I should have done
in the first place.
- And?
- And let's go through them.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Oh, what are you doing here?
Waiting for you. I figured if I tried
to go upstairs, you'd have me killed.
Oh, is that a joke?
Because I'm not laughing.
Louis, I didn't say it right the first time.
I want to say it again. I'm sorry.
You think "I'm sorry" makes up
for what you did?
No, but... I'm hoping that we can move
past it and be friends again.
Well, the only problem with that is,
is that you and I both know
that you're only here because
I took away your sugar daddy,
and now you want me to
take it easy on you.
Louis, if you don't wanna
accept my apology, that's fine.
But I'm not here
from a position of weakness.
I'm here from a position of strength.
Bullshit. Where did you get money?
You don't have any friends out there.
No, but Harvey has enemies.
What's that supposed to mean?
You told me these guys hold grudges.
I just found a guy
with one against Harvey.
You son of a bitch.
You didn't come here to apologize.
You came to rub it in my face.
Oh, and I bet you just
can't wait to tell Harvey
that I'm the one
who gave you the idea.
Louis, I wasn't even gonna tell you
how I got the idea at all.
- I'm still not gonna tell Harvey.
- Because you want me to owe you?
Because I'm not as much of an asshole
as you think I am.
What about a buyout?
Never going to happen.
He's got a golden parachute.
Well, then I've got two people
on the board. I can force a vote.
You do that, it triggers a stock split,
his shares double in voting power,
yours don't.
I mean, that's all five.
None of them work.
No, they don't.
So, when you told me you should have
evaluated my ideas first,
you weren't saying
that they were good.
I was saying I wasn't doing my job.
Which was to let me figure out for myself
that my ideas weren't good.
I chose the nicer version.
Logan, there are plenty
of other companies out there.
(SIGHS) None that
we're gonna find in time
for my board meeting tomorrow.
- So, push it.
- I can't. I didn't call it.
- And I thought...
- Yeah, I know.
That I only even arranged it
to spend time with you?
- You really didn't.
- No.
And now they're gonna ask me tomorrow
how Gillie is going,
and I'm gonna have to tell them
we might lose.
And then they're gonna ask me
what else I have,
and I'm gonna have
to tell them, "Nothing."
Well, maybe you won't.
I told you I'm not in that business.
Then convince the board
that you should be.
Okay. Go back to your office,
get your files.
Like you said...
I don't always do
what people expect me to do.
(KEYBOARD KEYS CLACKING)
(SIGHS)
Louis, can I talk to you for a minute?
Of course.
I heard about what
you did with Gianopolous.
Good job.
I appreciate that, Harvey. I do.
Um, but it doesn't matter.
(STUTTERING)
You know, he went...
Somewhere else.
I know. He went to Forstman.
I just wanted to tell you
you did a good job anyway.
You see, that's the, uh, thing.
I didn't.
What are you talking about?
Mike got the idea from me.
What? How?
When I cut him off with Gianopolous,
I stuck it in his face
and I told him that people
hold grudges and I...
He must have known
your history with Forstman,
and that's why he went to him, so...
- I'm sorry.
- Goddamn it, Louis.
I don't wanna keep being mad at you,
but you keep doing the same shit.
But you see,
this wasn't me being duped.
No. It was you
letting your emotions
lead you into doing
something stupid...
Again.
You just had to stick it in his face.
You know what?
I'm done.
It's not fair, you know.
I'm emotional. You're cold.
You're loved. And I'm hated.
Louis...
If I was so cold,
I wouldn't have come here
in the first place.
- What are you doing?
- Pouring us a drink.
Cahill took the deal.
All seven cases are officially dead.
Jessica, I'm sorry that I didn't
come clean with you before.
- Me, too.
- Lying to you was a...
...business decision, and it was wrong.
But I want you to know that I would
never lie to you man to woman.
I appreciate that.
We have a problem.
I just got off the phone
with Richard Coleman.
Last week, Sean Cahill asked him
if I'd ever crossed any lines
in his presence.
Son of a bitch. He doesn't want
our clients to leave us.
He wants them to cough up dirt on me.
At least none of them did
or we'd be in trouble right now.
- How do you wanna handle it?
- Let's talk about it tomorrow.
Right now, I've got
something else to do.
Shit.
They wouldn't turn on Harvey.
Cahill wanted us
to drop those cases anyway,
and I just did him a big favor.
You couldn't have known that.
It was my job to know that.
- AMY: Hey, Mike?
- Yeah.
Harvey Specter's here to...
Harvey, what can I do for you?
(SIGHS)
I wanted to thank you
for the recordings.
Is that why you came
all the way down here?
I came to tell you
I think you're making a big mistake
- getting into bed with Forstman.
- I knew it.
Mike, you don't know this guy.
You could have thanked me
for those recordings days ago,
but instead, you picked the exact day
that I find a new investor
to show up with your thank you
and your friendly advice.
- This isn't some move.
- You only make moves.
- Mike...
- Okay, tell me right now
that you wouldn't do the same thing
if you were in my position.
I was.
And I did.
What? You think our grudge
is about some car?
What the hell
are you talking about?
When I was younger,
I made a shady deal with him
and I paid for it.
(SIGHS)
- Who says that I'm making...
- If you haven't, you will,
because Forstman
doesn't throw money around
without getting something in return.
- He's gonna get money in return.
- Money is third on his list.
The first two are getting back at people
and getting control of people.
Maybe you should
have thought of that
before you had Louis cut me off
from Gianopolous,
because now, I have no other choice.
You always have a choice.
Here's to turning around
Piedmont Avionics.
- What?
- Nothing.
What time is it?
Too late for you
to change your mind.
- Logan, the board is going to be wowed.
- Well, I wish I had your confidence.
You are not short
in the confidence department.
Oh, you don't have
to pay me compliments.
I meant it as an insult.
(CHUCKLES)
You know, if this law thing
doesn't work out...
Then, I could have a career
in venture capital?
No, I was gonna say
you could be my assistant.
Hilarious.
Seriously, Rachel, I...
(STAMMERING)
I couldn't have done it without you.
Yes, you could have.
It just wouldn't have been as good.
Humility. Another thing I love about you.
(WHISPERING)
Logan, I should go.
(SOFTLY)
Rachel, I... Um...
Good luck tomorrow.
Your eyes,
they did flutter again
When you told me
every little thing's
Going to be all right
But we were younger then
And now we're not
And if there was a plan made
Then we forgot about it
And if there was time
Well, I could figure it out now
But life is short
And I don't care for most of it
Because you're all that
All that I want
Well, I know
I'm hard to take
And my bones are
calling out your name
While I beat your cold windows
Break the locks on the gate
While I try to forget
I used to be something great
Because you're all that
All that I want
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English SDH