(HARVEY READING)
It's not Woodall coming after us.
It's...
Sean Cahill.
Your hands weren't full with Eric.
They will be full with me.
What happened to
"You think I'm staying if you leave?"
Yeah, that was before I knew you were
going to screw over Sidwell.
HARVEY: Forstman
doesn't throw money around
- without getting something in return.
- I have no other choice.
You two are on opposite sides
of a takeover battle
and your girlfriend is your associate.
Are you trying to say
that we're colluding?
Oh, you went right there, didn't you?
So, we're just gonna
go back and forth, trading favors?
Are you my lawyer or not?
Seriously, Rachel,
I couldn't have done it without you.
(WHISPERING)
Logan, I should go.
Damn right, you get one, Hunley.
Eisenheim, you silly son of a bitch.
You think I'd leave you out of the fun?
Bryceman, after you killed
the Singer depo? (CHUCKLES)
Out of my way, Johnson. Coffee is
for closers. You don't get a mug.
Am I to assume I'm getting
my own personal Litt Up mug?
Absolutely not.
Those are mere mugs.
This, milady,
is a chalice.
Okay. (WHISPERING)
It looks like all the other ones.
No, Donna. What makes
this a chalice is not the mug.
It's what's inside.
- Wait a second. Is that...
- Mmm-hmm.
An exact replica of the one
Dame Judy Dench wore as Ophelia.
Louis, this must have cost a fortune.
Donna, please. You helped me
overcome my stage fright.
You can't put a price on that.
- I don't know what to say.
- That's all you have to say.
I got one for Harvey, too.
- You know, Louis, I don't think that...
- I know.
He is still upset with me
for leading Mike to Forstman.
But I just thought maybe if he...
Give it to me. I will take care of it.
Thank you, Donna.
Hey, Mike, Sidwell wants to see you.
- Shit.
- What?
He took Forstman's money last night.
You think he knows you're going
to cut him out of the deal?
There's only one way to find out.
- You wanted to see me?
- Damn right I did.
Something you want to tell me?
Jonathan, I don't know what to say.
Well, you better think of something.
'Cause I just got off the phone
with some asshole from the SEC
who accused you of colluding
with Harvey Specter.
(CHUCKLES) That's bullshit.
Then, why the hell were the two of you
sharing a porterhouse
when you were supposed to be buying
stock for me two nights ago?
- It's not what you think.
- What I think
is you better start telling me
what's going on around here.
There's nothing going on.
Look, I know that guy.
He's full of shit.
Well, I don't know him
from a hole in the ground,
but I know that
you're keeping stuff from me.
Jonathan, I...
First, you don't transfer
Forstman's money.
Then, you blow a straight-up
stock purchase
that any first-year trader
could do in his sleep.
It wasn't straight-up.
I had to set up an auction
which happened to get postponed.
Yeah, 'cause you were sipping wine
with Harvey Specter behind my back.
It got postponed because my girlfriend
was in the hospital.
What?
Rachel passed out at school.
Harvey and I went to the hospital,
so we pushed the sale.
- Then, you should have told me.
- You're right. I should have. I'm sorry.
But that's what happened.
- That's it?
- That's it.
Fine.
But if there is anything else
that you're not telling me,
now's the time.
There isn't.
WOMAN: (SINGING)
I remember when
I remember; I remember
when I lost my mind
There was something
so pleasant
- Well?
- Allison is at dinner with some friends,
but she'll be home soon.
I have to go.
Come on. We're working.
(LAUGHS)
We're not working.
I am sneaking around
pretending to work,
so that I can
spend time with you.
Sneaking around?
That's what I'd call it, wouldn't you?
I don't know. I just don't really want
to think of it like that.
I have to go.
Well, she's with her friends.
Aren't you allowed
to be with your friends?
Is that what we are?
We're... We're friends?
I was actually
hoping that we're more than that.
Mmm, we shouldn't be
having this conversation.
You wouldn't be here
if you didn't want to be
having this conversation.
LOGAN: Rachel.
We have had chemistry
from the second we met.
You know it.
And I know it.
WOMAN: (SINGING)
Bless your soul
Really think
you're in control
I think you're crazy
Just like me
- Rachel. Hey.
- Hi.
- What are you doing here?
- I am here because I wanted
to talk to you before you came in
to see Harvey this morning.
- Do you want some coffee?
- No.
I won't be here long enough for that.
Are you sure?
- Look, Logan...
- I know why you're here.
If you knew why I was here,
then I wouldn't need to be here.
I think you're here to tell me
that what's happening
isn't really happening.
But it is.
(LAUGHS)
I have a boyfriend that I love.
So, I need you to stop pursuing me.
No more flowers, no more looks,
no more attempted kisses.
No more anything, okay?
Look, you said that if
I knew why you were here,
you wouldn't need to be here.
I think you do need to be here.
And we both know why.
You're wrong.
I don't think I am.
You once told me that we had chemistry
the second that we met.
(SOFTLY) Logan, please.
Tell me to stop and I'll stop.
- I can't.
- Rachel. Rachel!
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
- Harvey, I need to...
- What the hell is this?
It's from Louis.
He wanted you to have it.
What do you mean,
he wanted me to have it?
(SIGHS)
You haven't talked to him
since Mike landed Forstman.
It's a gesture.
Now, can I please get back to what...
Oh! Why didn't you say
it was a gesture?
Mike has access to Forstman
and his four billion dollars.
Logan's on his way over
to discuss our next move,
which we can't make for two more weeks
because Louis thought
Sheila was marrying Lorenzo Lamas.
But I just got a mug
with something stupid printed on it,
so now, everything's okay.
Great. Are you done being a dick?
Because everything's not okay.
- What did Louis do now?
- Nothing.
And Logan Sanders isn't
on his way here
because he just got
brought down to the SEC.
What the hell do you think you're doing
talking to my client without me present?
Oh, he hasn't said a word yet.
We're waiting for you
to get the party started.
And what gives you the right
to bring him here in the first place?
The United States government
gives me the right.
So, if you don't mind,
I have a few questions
I would like to ask him.
You've got questions for him,
you ask me.
Okay. Here's one.
What makes you think you can get away
with collusion on my watch?
I already told you,
we're not colluding.
And you harassing my client
won't change that.
Will me telling him about
your date the other night
- with Mike Ross change that?
- What?
See, I think he and
Mike Ross are colluding
to allow you to purchase
Gillie Industries stock
- at a cut-rate price.
- That's bullshit.
Then, why would you set up
a private auction
while neither one of you
ended up bidding
and Logan here, mysteriously
bought the stock
without any competition?
That's it. We're done.
You didn't bring us in
here to ask him questions.
You brought us in here
to ask me questions in front of him.
Am I smart enough to do that?
You're dumb enough to try.
And we're leaving.
I have not dismissed you yet.
- Then, arrest us on the way out.
- (CHUCKLES) Gentlemen.
DONNA: Hey. What's going on?
You look upset.
No, it's nothing. Um, I just found out
I have to go to Columbia.
So, could you just tell Harvey
that I won't be able
to make the Logan meeting?
Rachel, there is no meeting.
Logan got hauled down to the SEC.
What? I just saw him this morning.
- That doesn't make any...
- Well, it must have been before...
Wait a second.
They picked him up at his condo.
Why were you at Logan's condo?
Donna, please don't
do your thing on me.
Rachel. What is going on?
The other night, I was working
with Logan and things got intense.
- And...
- And?
And he tried to kiss me.
Okay. So, what did you do?
Nothing. I didn't do anything.
Then, why were you
at his condo this morning?
I went to tell him that I didn't want him
to get the wrong idea.
Rachel, if you went to his place,
you were giving him the wrong idea.
(SIGHS)
Something happened, didn't it?
I kissed him.
- How long?
- Too long.
Oh, God, I feel horrible.
I'm a horrible person.
No, you're not.
You are a great person
who had a not-so-great moment.
Donna, please.
You can't say a word to anyone.
Of course not.
But, Rachel, you can't
say a word to anyone either.
Go ahead. Say what you're going to say.
You know what I'm going to say.
ls what he said true?
Logan, I'm not colluding
with Mike Ross.
Well, if I thought that,
I wouldn't even be standing here.
I'm talking about
you buying that stock.
- Look, I can't talk about that.
- Why not?
Because telling you about it
would make it parking.
But that doesn't matter anymore
because now that
that guy hauled you in,
we can't do a thing
with those shares, anyway.
Well, what can we do?
You and Mike Ross can get
in a room together
and put this thing
to bed once and for all.
No, that's a bad idea.
Logan, if we don't finish this now,
you're going to have the SEC
crawling up your ass day and night.
Look, you can try to scare me all
you want, but I did nothing wrong.
And the last guy I'm getting in a room
with is Mike goddamn Ross.
Don't you ever knock?
Logan Sanders got taken
downtown this morning.
- Sean Cahill.
- Son of a bitch
is throwing shit at the wall
to see what sticks.
And what stuck?
Wexler. Logan found out
we bought that stock.
Did you tell him why
we kept it from him?
- He didn't seem to care.
- All right. Well, it doesn't matter,
because you're going
to end this takeover battle now.
What do you think I've been
doing for the past month?
Harvey, I don't think you
understand what I'm saying.
This guy's already
looking at us for collusion.
The longer this thing drags on,
the more likely he is to come after us
for buying that stock.
- In other words, end this thing.
- Not in other words.
In those exact words.
So, I guess Jonathan didn't know
you sold him out.
- How'd you know that?
- Uh, because if he knew,
he'd have come by your office
and ripped it to pieces.
Instead, you're out here
enjoying a bagel
without the courtesy of coming
by to tell me that he didn't know.
My bad.
- So, now, what are we going to do?
- We're going to kick some ass.
Wait... What...
What are you talking about?
If the SEC called Sidwell,
then I guarantee you
they also called Logan Sanders.
Which means Harvey can't use those
shares and I'm in the driver's seat.
Well, that explains it.
- Explains what?
- Harvey just called.
He wants to have a meeting.
- Jeff.
- Hey.
Did you hear what
Sean Cahill did this morning?
I did, yeah.
(SIGHS) Then, you know he's poking
around the Wexler purchase.
Ah, let him.
- You don't seem very concerned.
- I'm not concerned
because I did a damn good job
protecting this firm from any liability.
Yeah, well, the question is,
did you protect us from all liability?
Is there something that
you want to ask me, Jessica?
I want you to go back over your work
with a fine tooth comb
and make sure it's airtight.
Jessica, you're the one
who asked me to buy that stock,
and I made it questionable,
like you asked.
But if Sean Cahill comes at us
for attempting to park it,
that is on you, not my work.
Jeff, just go back over everything,
like I said.
There's nothing to go back over.
We're as protected as we can be.
Hey, maybe you didn't hear me.
Every partner at this firm
goes over their work if I say so.
And you know what, Jessica?
I'm not every goddamn partner.
So, either you trust me or you don't.
Hey, look what the cat dragged in.
Such a serious expression.
It's because we need to have
a serious conversation.
Well, let's get to it.
I want you to come up with a number
that we can pay you to end this thing.
And why would I do that?
Because Sean Cahill hauled
Logan into the SEC.
Well, all that means is that
you can't vote the shares
that you stole from me.
And that is a 'you' problem.
Mike, it takes two people
to make a case for collusion.
So, if he's coming at us,
he's coming at you.
Which means it's a 'we' problem.
Yeah, you can try
and spin it any way you want.
But I'm happy right where I am.
I guess you agreed to this meeting
just to waste my time, huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Who said I don't want to deal?
- Don't play me.
- Here's the new deal.
You don't buy me out.
- I buy you out.
- What?
We tried it Logan's way.
Now, we're going to try it mine.
Mike...
Because the only way I get
in a room with that guy
is if you guarantee
that I leave with Gillie Industries.
- He's not going to agree to that.
- And that's another 'you' problem.
Rachel, I need to know what's
going on with Logan Sanders.
What?
You spent an extra
20 hours with him last week,
it wasn't billed to the takeover,
and I need to know what it's about.
We were looking at future deals.
- We?
- Yes, we.
He asked me if I could help him
- put together some ideas and...
- Why?
What are you getting at?
I don't know if you've been
paying attention around here,
but we need to wrap this thing up.
So, I need to know if whatever
you and Logan were up to
can force him to end this thing with Mike
once and for all.
- It can.
- How?
Logan is under pressure from his board.
And if he doesn't close this deal soon,
he might lose control of his company.
LOUIS: Jessica, I must say,
an impromptu lunch in the middle of the
day is exactly what the doctor ordered.
Thank you, Louis.
Now, I must admit
that I brought you here because
I have something that I didn't want
to discuss at the office.
If you're firing Harvey,
I can't be in on it.
I just bought him an amazing mug and
we're in a really good place right now.
And I'm happy for you.
But this isn't about Harvey.
It's about the firm.
We recently purchased
a large block of stock
without realizing that we represent
a client with the same interests.
You're worried about the appearance
of parking the stock.
Exactly. And I just want to make sure
that we are as protected as possible.
Sure, I can do it.
- You seem upset.
- No, I'm not upset.
I mean, why would I be upset, Jessica?
You take me to an amazing restaurant.
Then, you feed me some bullshit story
about a stock purchase
with a fabricated company
when it's clear as day
this is Gillie Industries.
- Louis...
- The very same stock purchase
that you went to Malone to structure.
And now, you want me
to double check his work
because you don't trust him?
The question is, can I trust you?
- What?
- This lunch isn't about him.
It's about you.
You knew I'd figure this out.
Just like I know you'll figure out
whether or not we have exposure.
Now, the question is, can you
do it without telling Jeff Malone?
I can.
And I Will.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGING)
If you're going to discuss
what happened, you can just forget it.
Because I...
I am not here to talk about that
and you know it.
- What?
- You told Harvey
about my problems with the board.
I told your attorney about a situation
you discussed with your other attorney.
And now, he's using it to strong-ann me
into caving to Mike.
No, now, he's using it to give you the
opportunity to impress your board.
Did you bring Harvey that information
to get rid of me?
Logan, I didn't bring Harvey that
information. He asked me for it.
And I don't need to get rid of you
because what happened this morning
is never going to happen again.
Okay, Rachel,
you got what you wanted.
I'm going to get in a room with Mike
and come to an agreement.
What do you mean,
you're going to get in a room with him?
Well, how else did you
see this happening?
Did you think I was going to let Harvey
take care of it?
Logan, please.
You can't tell him what happened.
Rachel, I would never do that.
- Thank you.
- But just to be clear, it's not for him.
It's for me.
Because you say what happened this
morning will never happen again,
and I'm still hoping that it will.
And I don't want it to happen
because you two are fighting.
I want it to happen
because you want it to.
- MIKE: Hey.
- Hey.
You want me to heat
some of this up for you?
Mike, I need to talk to you.
Are you upset about something?
No. I...
I heard you might be making a deal.
And you're worried because
you're on the losing side.
No, I'm actually happy
that this thing will be over.
Iii]
I think that you should have Jonathan
Sidwell put this to bed for you.
Rachel...
You and Harvey have
so much bad blood.
Yeah, and this is our
chance to patch it up.
- And what about Logan?
- What about him?
I'm not going to let him get to me.
That's what you said
the last time you two
- got in a room together.
- This is different.
- Mike...
- Rachel, stop it.
Look, we're at the finish line.
I'm not going to pass
the baton to somebody else.
And I'm not going to blow it.
Because this time,
I've got all the leverage.
Well, if you have all the leverage,
then maybe you should ask
for one more thing.
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGING)
- You're a half hour late.
- I got stuck in traffic.
I was starting to think you
didn't want this company.
Harvey, I wouldn't be getting in a room
with that guy if I didn't.
Good. So, we're not going
to have trouble in there?
Not from me.
Then, let's get this thing over with
and get back to normal.
Keep that in mind.
Logan. Sorry I'm late.
Let's get to it.
(MIKE CLEARS THROAT)
HARVEY: All right.
Just so we're clear...
We're agreeing to have you buy us out.
Good. I think you'll find this
more than generous.
It is.
You going to try and spread this
over 1,000 payments?
All up front.
Then, all that's left is
for you to pull out your checkbook.
Well, actually, there is one more thing.
You said it, Harvey.
- Let's get things back to normal.
- What are you talking about?
Once this deal is done,
you go back to being
my lawyer. And he's out.
What?
You sign that, I'm Harvey's client,
and you're looking
for new representation.
(LAUGHS) This...
This is bullshit.
It's not bullshit.
Apple and Dell don't have the same
attorneys and neither will you and I.
Mike, you two aren't those two,
and I can represent you both.
LOGAN: Yeah, but it doesn't matter.
Because it's not about
who you represent.
It's about who Rachel represents.
All right, enough.
We agreed to a number.
We can work this out another time.
No, we're going to work it out right now.
- No, we're not.
- Then, you don't have a deal.
HARVEY: Goddamn it, Mike.
- This isn't the time to do this.
- This is exactly the time to do it
because this is the last time I'm ever
going to be in a room with him.
Well, finally, something we can agree on.
Then, let's agree to something else.
We let Harvey choose which one of us
he wants to represent after today.
- Mike, do not put me in that...
- Done.
And now that we've agreed
to let Harvey decide,
I'm going to let you in on a little secret.
The way he got me into this room
in the first place
was he knows that
I've got 10 deals lined up after this.
- Logan.
- Decide.
I'm going with Mike.
- LOGAN: What?
- Mike's my guy. You knew that going in.
LOGAN: I don't give a shit!
And I don't think Jessica Pearson
is going to let you pick him over me.
Jessica has nothing to do with this.
You just agreed to those terms.
Those were bullshit terms.
- So, you're going back on your word?
- What does it look like?
It looks like there's no deal on Gillie.
Mike, you didn't have to
blow up the deal like that.
- Your client blew up the deal.
- Because you blindsided him.
Fine. Then, once he's had
time to think about it,
you go back and you convince him.
Convince him?
You should have come to me first
instead of looking to rub it in his face.
I wasn't rubbing anything
in anyone's face.
Oh, bullshit. You had leverage
and you were going to
make sure he knew it.
And when he had leverage,
he made sure I knew it.
And I didn't agree to a deal
and then break my word
10 seconds later.
And I'm giving you my word.
Close this deal, and as soon
as it's wrapped up, he's out.
And what about Jessica?
Is she going to agree to it?
- Let me deal with Jessica.
- Oh, just like you did on Wexler.
That was a different thing
and you know it.
Do I?
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGING)
Get him to agree up front
or we don't have a deal.
Louis. I don't usually
get summoned to people.
They get summoned to me.
But you wanted discretion,
and your office is within
earshot of Jeff Malone.
And you don't want him
to hear what you're about to tell me.
So. First off, I went through this
backwards and forwards.
And Jeff did a better job
than 99% of all attorneys.
Fortunately for you, I'm the one.
You found a mistake.
I found a blessing in disguise.
What are you talking about?
Jessica, we're not vulnerable
to allegations of parking
because we never
bought those shares.
- We can't sell them back.
- I'm not talking about selling them back.
This mistake makes
the entire sale invalid.
And we don't have exposure
because the sale never happened.
You just give me the word and I'll
David Blaine this whole thing away.
Louis, this is great work.
But I don't want you to do anything
until you talk to Harvey.
- Are you sure? Because I can just...
- Louis.
I bought these shares
without telling him.
I'm not getting rid of them
without telling him. Are we clear?
As a bell.
- Well, someone saved the day.
- Do tell.
Jeff Malone just dropped
a giant deuce on Jessica's desk.
Please tell me you're
being metaphorical.
Nope. He made a huge mess
of the Wexler purchase.
- And you cleaned it up?
- Even better.
Because of his blunder,
I'm going to make it as though
his shitty deal never even happened.
- What did Jessica say?
- Oh, she loved it.
- And what about Malone?
- That's the best part.
That asshole doesn't
even know about it.
What do you need me to do
to make this unwind happen?
Nothing.
Jessica just wanted me
to run it by Harvey first.
- But I haven't been able to reach him.
- Able to reach him?
Louis, what do you think
is going to happen
if Malone gets wind of this
before you talk to Harvey?
Oh, shit. He's going
to try to fix it himself.
And once again,
he'll be taking what's rightfully yours.
And I'll be left holding a big bag
of Jeff Malone's giant deuce.
- Where are you going?
- To do what needs to be done.
Rachel. What the hell did you do?
What are you talking about?
Mike demanded that Harvey
dump Logan as a client
and it blew up the whole deal.
And based on what I know
and Harvey doesn't,
it wasn't Mike behind that demand,
it was you.
- I'm so sorry.
- Sorry? What good does sorry do?
Donna, I thought it was the best thing
for everyone involved.
You thought it was
the best way to get Logan
out of the picture
and not deal with what happened.
No. I tried to deal
with what happened
without telling anyone,
which is what you told me to do.
I did not tell you to let your personal life
affect Harvey's business.
I was just trying to get Mike and Harvey
back on the same team.
I want you to understand
that the way to do that isn't to pull
strings behind their backs.
I do.
Okay, well, there's got
to be some way to fix it.
That's not the point.
It's being fixed.
What are you talking about?
Harvey's going over Mike's head.
He went to see Charles Forstman
20 minutes ago.
HARVEY: Whoever said size
doesn't matter never saw this table.
Is that an insult or a compliment?
Knowing you, Charles,
you'll take it as both.
How did you get in here, Harvey?
You crawled in through the vents?
I told your secretary I was
George Clooney's brother.
She said it was obvious
who got the looks in the family.
(LAUGHS) Great.
Do me a favor.
Tell her she's fired on the way out.
Can do.
But first, I wanted to show you these.
You want to give me the Aston Martin?
Give is a strong word.
(LAUGHS)
- You want me to buy you out.
- You're going to buy me out.
So, why come to me
instead of Mike Ross?
Because I put him and Logan Sanders
in a room together,
and those two assholes let their personal
shit get in the way of business.
So, what makes you think these two
assholes are going to do any better?
Because as much
as you hate my guts,
you want this deal
and that car as much as I do.
Harvey, taking your car
is tempting, but...
I don't think buying
you out makes sense anymore.
Why not?
Because you're standing
there asking me to do it.
Now, walk your sorry ass
out of my office.
Okay, Charles.
But I'm afraid you're forcing me
to use my leverage on you.
You don't have shit on me, pal.
Who do you think bought that
Wexler block three days ago?
I don't give a shit who
bought it three days ago
because it just went back
on the market 30 minutes ago
and you're looking
at the man who owns it now.
Jonathan, what are you doing here?
Forstman bought the Wexler shares.
What?
They went back on the market
and he snatched 'em right up.
- Holy shit.
- We win.
- We do?
- Mmm-hmm.
You do.
(LAUGHS)
It's not over yet.
I want you to draw up
a tender offer right away.
- Jonathan.
- What?
- I've been thinking about Forstman.
- And?
You know we wouldn't have been able
to do this without him, right?
No shit.
So, think about what else
we can do with him.
You want to team up with him?
Well, you don't need to convince me,
but how the hell are you
going to convince him?
- By giving him a discount on this deal.
- How much of a discount?
Thinking somewhere
in the neighborhood of 100%.
HARVEY: Goddamn it, Louis!
What the hell did you do?
- What are you talking about?
- I just came from a meeting
with Charles Forstman.
And when I reached
for my bargaining chips,
he told me I didn't
own them anymore.
Because you unwound
the Wexler sale.
I was trying to save
the firm from exposure.
- And who the hell told you to do that?
- Jessica did.
She told you to goddamn
wait and you know it.
Check your phone. I tried calling you.
I left three messages.
I don't care if you left me
a million messages.
You were told to wait
for my approval
and you didn't listen
because you never goddamn do.
You know what, Harvey?
I always listen.
I always play the good soldier.
And what do I get for it? Nothing.
I may not be a name partner,
but I am a senior partner. You get it?
(YELLING) I couldn't reach you,
and I made a goddamn judgment call.
You want to know why you're
not a name partner, Louis?
Because every judgment call
you make turns to shit.
Well, then, what do you want, Harvey?
I'll do anything to make up for it.
You want to do something, Louis?
Instead of using Donna to give me
some stupid goddamn mug...
(MUG CLANKING)
...stay the hell out of my business.
You mind grabbing me
a couple of packs of sugar there?
I don't work here.
I'm with Pearson Specter.
I don't give a shit who you're with.
If you're not here to give me something...
I'm here to give you Harvey Specter
on a silver platter.
I already have Harvey Specter
Not like you will
if you let me buy you out.
Listen, asshole.
Harvey came by last night
and tried to make a deal.
I told him to shove it up his ass.
You don't think I know good cop,
bad cop when I see it?
Good cop, bad cop doesn't work
when one of them hates the other one.
And what the hell is this?
Your niece's diary?
It's a time capsule of my rage.
"April 22nd, 2009.
"Harvey told me to file a motion
"to dismiss the odor
emanating from my armpits."
- This is a joke.
- Once again, he picked my biggest fear
and put it on display
for the entire world to see.
Oh, yeah. I can go on.
He hates you that bad, huh?
No. He doesn't give a shit about me
at all. I hate him that bad.
You know, you don't have
the authority to buy me out.
I went to Harvey's client
behind his back and I got it.
Oh, I see. I agree to this,
you steal his client.
And he'll have lost to me,
which is far more humiliating
than losing to you.
You'd go to all this trouble
to stick it to Harvey.
Read May 9th, 2012.
I'd go to the ends
of the goddamn Earth.
What was so important
you couldn't tell me over the phone?
I want to offer you something.
It's my lucky day.
Everyone's bearing gifts.
You want me to buy a controlling interest
in Sidwell Investment Group.
I want you to buy it
at an $80 million discount.
The exact amount I was going
to cut him out of.
Was?
Did you change your mind?
You're not going to cut him out of Gillie?
Guess you haven't heard.
I'm done with Gillie.
I sold my interest to Logan Sanders.
What the hell are you talking about?
That... That wasn't our deal.
What can I tell you?
When you're the biggest
bully in the yard,
people give you their lunch money
without you even asking for it.
Oh, my God.
You son of a bitch.
You promised me
that I would control what
happened to that company.
I promised you if we won.
We didn't.
- You did.
- Yes, I did.
Then, our other deal is off the table.
And you're going to give
Jonathan Sidwell his goddamn cut.
How about I give you
something even better?
- What the hell is this?
- A job offer.
(LAUGHS)
You've got to be kidding me.
What, you think I was going
to hang you out to dry?
I could use a smart son of a bitch
like you working for me.
You're the last person in the world
I'd want to work for.
I'm the only person in the world
you want to work for.
- And why is that?
- Because you're a nobody.
You're a fonner lawyer who's been
an investment banker all of 10 minutes,
and is about to blow the biggest deal
that ever came his way
unless you come over to me.
Go to hell.
Harvey, we need to have a little talk.
I said everything
I needed to say last night.
- Now, get the hell...
- I made a deal with Forstman.
What? You stuck your nose
in my goddamn business
after I told you
to never do that again?
No. I saved your goddamn business
after you told me to never do it again.
- You got him to sign this?
- Damn right.
And who authorized it?
Nobody. I lied and told Forstman
I had Logan's approval.
Can we get Logan's approval?
You're goddamn right we can.
Louis.
This has got to be
the most genius thing you have ever
done in your entire wonderful,
miserable life.
So, you're not mad at me?
Mad at you?
I could kiss you.
And I can let you.
Then go grab a couple of your mugs.
I'll crack open the scotch
and let's see where this thing goes.
Can do.
Hey, Louis.
How the hell did you get him to go for it?
We found common ground.
One more thing.
Charles Forstman got Litt the hell up.
Hey, Mike. Mike.
Sidwell wants to see you.
- Don't tell me...
- He knows.
Shit.
- You little piece of shit.
- Jonathan, let me explain.
There's nothing to explain.
You sold me out the second
you connected with Forstman.
No, I...
I... I thought I could get
out of it, all right?
But then, you took
Forstman's money and I...
Oh, you're... You're going to
put that on me?
I took his money because
I thought we were partners.
I didn't know you were going to
stab me in the goddamn back.
Stab you in the back?
If I didn't make this deal happen,
you said you were going to fire me.
I don't give a shit what I said.
I took a chance on you.
You spat in my face.
- Jonathan...
- You stood right there
selling me on Forstman to stop me
from finding out you betrayed me.
No, I did that to stop me
from having to betray you.
Jonathan, he still
owes us money, all right?
We can still go after it.
There isn't enough money in the world
for me to ever trust you again.
- Listen to me.
- No, you listen to me!
There is no goddamn "we".
You're fired.
Jonathan, we...
We can still talk to Forstman.
- All right?
- You think I didn't try that?
Who the hell do you think
told me that you sold me
out in the first place?
Here.
Put this on your mantle.
Remember me every time
you goddamn look at it.
There is the man of the hour.
Why didn't you tell me
what you were going to do?
If it didn't work, I didn't want you
to take any of the blame.
Well, why didn't you
tell me afterwards?
- It's all anyone can talk about.
- I don't care.
Louis.
Forstman's insisting
that I run the money
through Switzerland and the Caymans
before it comes out on the other side.
What?
He's trying to avoid taxes.
- You're obligated to report it.
- I didn't.
And I'm not going to.
Louis, that's illegal.
You didn't see the look on Harvey's face
when he found out that I was the one
who saved the day.
And I am
not going to be the one
to see the look on his face
when he finds out that I didn't.
Louis.
Leave me alone.
DONNA: Hey. Did you hear
the good news?
There is no good news.
(WHISPERING) Logan won,
which means he's not going anywhere.
(SIGHS) You want to tell Mike
what happened, don't you?
I am going to tell Mike
what happened.
No, you're not.
Harvey said he would drop Logan
when this is over, and he will.
And there's no way
that he's dropping Logan
- if Mike can't even be a client.
- What are you talking about?
I just got a text from Amy.
Donna, Mike got fired.
Now, you really can't tell him.
You said I shouldn't go behind his back.
But not telling him
is going behind his back.
Even if you were going to tell him,
this is the absolute worst time.
If not now, then when?
I mean, just wait till he recovers,
and then smack him down again?
How about not smacking him
down at all?
That would be great.
But I already did
when I betrayed him. And I...
Rachel,
if you do this, I am telling you,
it will bore a hole in his brain.
And you will be risking
your whole life with Mike.
I am risking it if I don't.
- Rachel...
- Donna,
Mike kept a secret from me
that almost ripped us apart
before we even got started.
And he found the courage
to trust me with it.
So, I need to find the courage
to trust him with this.
MAN: (SINGING) One day,
you'll come back here
For my help
Someday,
you'll ask to leave me
Couldn't it be easy
Silent screams, honey
Just ask for my help
Well, I'm drowning
in my clothing
And I'm hoping
you aren't going
If you need my help
Take a hold
Or a part of me
And ask for my help
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English