(HARVEY READING)
I just wanted to tell you that I appreciate
you patching things up with him.
I would do anything
for the woman that I love.
They are gonna come at us
any way they can,
and when they do,
it's not gonna
be about heat sensors.
It's gonna be about you.
I know I'm not the only
guy in that company
that knows
those sensors are faulty.
I'm sorry.
What is it you need again?
All the maintenance work orders
from the past six months.
I can't let you have that
without authorization.
Have you heard of the National
Transportation Safety Board?
That's your secretary
unlawfully gathering evidence,
which means there will be
no settlement of any kind.
And tomorrow, I'm sending this
to the district attorney.
Your whole story
about how Louis got his name
on the door is bullshit!
No, Jeff...
It's over, Jessica.
We're done.
I can't believe
you actually got them
to admit what they did.
You better believe it
because it's happening,
and it wouldn't be
happening without you.
You mean without
me being greedy.
Joe, that's not what
I was going to say.
No, no. (STAMMERING)
I know you don't think
I care about these
people, but I do.
But I'm also a working stiff.
I go paycheck to paycheck
for my whole life,
and then a thing like this...
Could turn your
whole life around.
Guy like you might not be
able to understand that.
I understand.
So, it's a done deal.
Might take a few days
to finalize, but yeah.
It's happening.
You have my word.
You're all right,
Mr. Ross.
Harvey, you know, the only times
you've been here at night
were the God-awful dinner party...
And the other time.
Well, this isn't that.
I want to know why Liberty Rail
has a video of you
in their file room.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about the fact that our
smoking gun just became inadmissible.
Harvey. How did you
get those documents?
Are you asking if I did something illegal?
Because I didn't.
Well, they went to
the DA, which means
they think you did. So, I'm
going to ask you one more time.
How did you get
in their file room?
By walking through the
door they buzzed open.
And why would they do that?
Because I'm me.
What the hell does that mean?
It means that I led the woman
to believe that I was an
official from Washington.
Led them to believe it
or flat out told them?
Because one kills our case
and the other puts
you in a world of shit!
Harvey, I'm not an idiot and I don't
appreciate being treated like one.
I told you I didn't do
anything illegal and I didn't.
Not an idiot?
What the hell were you doing
there in the first place?
Harvey... It was Mike's
idea, wasn't it?
No, he didn't even
know about it.
Where are you going?
To see Mike. I told you,
he didn't even know
I was going to do it.
I don't care
because he sure
as hell knew after.
Let's go.
I am so proud of you.
I've done that before.
I'm not talking about that.
I'm talking about your case. Ah.
You believed in it
and you fought for it.
And I... I love
that about you.
And I love that you
love that about me.
When a person gives you a
compliment like that... Oh?
You're supposed
to give one back.
Uh, I just did. I said that I
love that you love that about me.
And what if I said I love that you
love that I love that about you?
How would that make you feel?
So tired.
(CHUCKLES) Well, we both
know why you're so tired.
Yeah. Because
I'm so good.
Don't you love that about me?
Mmm.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
You knew Donna bullshitted
her way into that company
and you let us use those work orders?
How did you find out?
It doesn't matter how I found out.
Answer my question.
Yes, I knew. But what
difference does it make?
We won.
We didn't win
because Evan Smith has video
of Donna in their offices.
What? She know about this, too?
Harvey, she's just trying
to strong-arm us...
Are you listening to me?
They have the opposing
counsel's secretary
poking around in their
goddamn file room.
If I were the DA, I'd sure
as hell look into it.
The DA?
Yeah, the DA.
Harvey, they let her in.
According to you, but they're
going to claim fraud
or theft or any
number of things.
What are you going to do?
I'm making a deal
to drop this case, that's
what I'm going to do.
And you're going to file the
paperwork as soon as I do.
So, you're just going to let this
woman blackmail you without a fight?
You're damn right I am. Harvey,
we can still win this case
and clear her name...
There is no case. And I wouldn't
give a shit about it if there was.
I care about Donna.
And you think I don't?
If you care so much for her,
then draw up those papers. Because
I'm letting Evan know it's over.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
Ripped By mstoll
What are you doing here?
We have a situation.
Is the fate of the firm
hanging in the balance?
No, it's... Then, I
don't give a shit.
You told Malone, didn't you?
I didn't get a chance
to tell him.
Because he had
already figured out
that I'd been to lying
to him this whole time.
I'm sorry.
Oh. You're sorry.
This morning, I thought
I was going away with him
for two weeks. Now,
I don't know if I'm
ever going to see him again.
He quit?
He didn't get around to
giving me his career plans.
Do you want me to
talk to him for you?
No. This is my mess.
And I will take
care of it myself.
You can take care of it tomorrow.
Right now, I'm making you a drink.
"Zip-a-dee-doo-dah"
or "Grab My Sack"?
What? Messenger service.
Which one do we use?
Uh...
You know what?
Use whoever you want,
just take care of it.
Louis, don't you have
your own secretary?
Oh. You mean Norma,
who I can't find anywhere?
Who's probably taking
the day off again?
I mean, last year, she tried
to get Arbor Day off
and I told her to blow a goddamn
tree and get her ass in here.
You know what, Louis?
Norma's taken four days
off in the last 36 years.
Why don't you back
the hell off of her?
What the hell is the
matter with you?
You usually jump on
the Norma-bashing train
like a hobo in a
1940s action movie.
I'm sorry. I just...
What?
I bullshitted my way into Liberty
Rail to get some documents.
They caught me on video and now
they're threatening to press charges.
You're not saying anything.
It's nothing.
It's fine.
Then, why did you
look so concerned?
Well, I was concerned,
but they're threatening charges,
which means they want
something. And I know Harvey,
and whatever it is they want,
he'll find a way
to give it to them.
Okay. Thanks, Louis.
I'll take care of your stuff.
No, no.
You have enough on your mind.
I'll take care of it myself.
Mr. Specter.
Don't tell me, you're here
to talk about Ms. Paulsen.
I'm here to tell you
you've made your point.
And what point is that?
If you drop any charges
against Donna,
we'll drop the
lawsuit against you.
Well, that's not
a very even trade.
I'm giving your client a chance
to get away with murder.
Last I checked, my client wasn't
being charged with murder.
And I don't need
you to drop your suit
because you have no case.
No case? Your client put a
faulty train on those tracks,
people died, and they knew it
could happen the whole time.
And you have no proof.
And where I come from,
you cut a deal with me to
make sure I stop looking.
Then, I guess we come
from different places
because I didn't give that
video to the district attorney
to leverage you into a deal.
I did it to blow you
out of the water.
This is a person's life.
Maybe you should
have thought of that
before you sent her
to rob my client.
Evan, I care about this woman.
Look, I understand.
She's probably worked
for you for a long time.
Maybe you sleep
together once in a while.
But my job is to
defend my client
to the best of my abilities.
And that's exactly
what I'm going to do.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
Holy shit.
You can't possibly
have a check already.
I don't have a check, Joe.
We have to drop the case.
What the hell are you talking about?
We had drinks last night.
Yeah. We also had proof last
night and now we don't.
Why not?
It's complicated.
You know, it's a lot
of legal rigmarole.
Hey, don't talk down to me.
I'm not talking down to you,
but I'm also not going to stand
here and explain civil procedure.
Maybe I don't understand
civil procedure,
but I know enough to understand
when something doesn't add up.
We got the evidence
the wrong way.
Well, get it the right way.
Subpoena it or something.
I... I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
That money was going
to change my life.
And if you want to go to a
different law firm, I understand.
You know as well as I do, nobody
else is going to take this case.
You told me you cared
about these people.
You gave me your word.
Yeah, and I wish
I could keep it!
I want those bastards as
much as you want this money,
but I've got no proof and
you're not a credible witness.
Oh, that bullshit again?
That's not bullshit.
If you had been straight
with me from day one,
we wouldn't even
be in this mess.
How much did they give
you to dump the case?
It had to be something.
Otherwise, you
wouldn't sell me out.
I'm sorry, Joe.
It's over.
You're sorry?
Jessica.
Do you need something?
I came by earlier,
and you weren't in.
I had a meeting.
And I really didn't think you wanted
to be looped in on my schedule.
I don't. And I'm not
checking up on you,
I just didn't know
if you were coming in.
You mean you weren't sure if
I was ever coming in again.
You wouldn't be the first person to
leave a job for personal reasons.
It sounds to me like
you have an agenda.
I don't.
Well, that's a first.
Are you saying that I came
here to push you out?
I'm saying that I've never known
you not to know what you want.
What I want is to talk about us,
but you don't seem
to want do that.
So, I'm focusing on this.
I'm not resigning
my senior partnership
the day after what
happened, happened,
if that's what you're asking.
I'm asking if you plan
to resign it at all.
And I can't tell you that right
now because I don't know.
Well, when will you know?
Look, Jessica, you're
the Managing Partner.
So, if you want to push
me out, push me out.
But if you're asking me
what I want to do,
I'm telling you that
I haven't decided.
How did it go?
Never mind how it went.
Where's Mike?
Did he file those papers?
(STUTTERING) I don't know.
He's not even in yet.
Well, you tell him
not to file anything.
And you tell him to
do whatever he has to,
to stick it to that woman.
Why?
Because it didn't work.
What didn't work?
I tried to make a deal with
Evan to trade the case.
You mean you offered to drop
the case in exchange for me.
Yes.
And now, what are
we going to do?
You're not going to do anything.
I'm going to do
whatever I have to,
to get Terrence Wolf to back off.
Harvey,
there's no way the DA handles
a case like this himself
just because I work for you.
Whether he handles it himself
or not doesn't matter
because this case won't
even exist in another hour.
How did it go?
I just told a man everything
I promised him was bullshit.
How do you think it went?
Mike, I'm sorry.
(SIGHS) You should
have seen his face.
(SCOFFS) That money was
going to change his life.
And I dangled it in front
of him and ripped it away.
Yeah, but it's not your fault.
You did everything you could.
He accused me of selling out.
You know you didn't do that.
Didn't I?
We gave up because...
Of me?
That's not what I was
going to say.
Yeah, it was.
No, I was going to say
because of Harvey.
What are you talking about?
Harvey never wanted
to take this case,
so he put a clock on it
to get me to drop it.
That's why we're
where we are right now.
Listen to me. Harvey
is out there right now
busting his ass to fix everything.
No, Donna.
He doesn't give a shit about
this case and he never did.
Then, why did he
send me here to tell you
to do everything you can
to stick it to Evan Smith?
She didn't take
the deal, did she?
No, she didn't.
Donna, I'm sorry. I didn't
realize that you were still...
On the hot seat?
Like I said,
Harvey's busting
his ass to fix it.
Which means he's
going to fix it.
Now, finish what we started, and
figure out a way to win this case.
(SIGHS)
Harvey Specter.
I was wondering
when you'd show up.
Funny, I was wondering why you
never sent me a Christmas card.
(LAUGHS)
You don't seem
the least bit worried
about the pending charges
against your secretary.
I'm not because
she did nothing wrong.
Well, you know what I think?
I think you wouldn't be here
if she did nothing wrong.
Listen to me. She
didn't steal anything.
She got those documents by
convincing them to let her in
and that is not a crime.
And the last time you were
in my office, you told me
you hadn't committed a
crime to get the job done.
After I told you, you
had an innocent man
and all you cared
about was procedure.
All I cared about was the law.
Well, if you're so concerned
with people breaking the law,
why don't you take a
look at those documents?
Because they prove Liberty Rail
actually committed a crime.
Unlike Donna, whose only
crime is working for me.
I'm not investigating her
for working for you,
I'm investigating her
for felony fraud.
What the hell are
you talking about?
The woman that let her in
swears your secretary told her
she was with the National
Transportation Safety Board.
That's a federal agency.
Which makes what
she did not a trick.
It makes it felony fraud.
My office now.
Close the door.
Harvey, what happened? What
happened is you lied to me.
What are you talking about?
You told their secretary
you were with the NTSB?
That's not what I said.
Bullshit!
I know when I've been lied to.
Come clean right now.
Uh...
Right the hell now!
I never said I was with them.
I said, "Have you ever heard of
"the National Transportation
Safety Board?"
How is that any different?
I'm sorry. I...
You're sorry?
Harvey, I swear, I didn't know
that, that made it a crime.
You knew when I point
blank asked you,
and you lied to me about it.
Well, I thought that you
would take care of it. I...
How can I take care of it if you
don't tell me the goddamn truth?
Do you think that I didn't
want to tell you the truth?
Then, why didn't you?
Because I was ashamed!
I know that it sounds stupid.
But you and Mike and everyone
pull these rabbits out
of your hats all the time.
And I just sit outside
and I answer the phones.
And then, I got those documents
and people said I saved the day.
And the next thing I knew,
you were on my doorstep
coming at me like I was
some sort of criminal.
And I panicked, and I lied.
Donna.
I'm sorry, Harvey.
I know you are,
but this just got
1000 times harder
for me to get out of.
You mean for you
to get me out of.
Donna, you of all people should
understand by now that to me,
they're the same thing.
What are you doing here?
I went to see you at work.
They said you called in sick.
I said what are you doing here?
I wanted to tell you
the good news.
We're not dropping
your case after all.
Good for you.
Hey, Joe, I know you've
been jerked around,
but things are going to change.
Going to
change? Really?
I thought you said you got the
evidence in the wrong way.
Well... And you said we should
get it in the right way,
so that's exactly what
we're going to do.
Like I said, good for you.
But you're not going
to do it with me.
Joe, I can't subpoena those records
without a legitimate client.
I have no basis and no standing
to move forward if I did.
But now you have time to explain
"procedure" to me, right?
(SIGHS) Okay. Fine.
I deserved that.
But, Joe, this case cannot
move forward without you.
You should have thought of
that before you cut me loose.
They got to you, didn't they?
They gave you a few
dollars to shut you up.
And then, they sealed the agreement
with no admission of guilt.
You know what?
I can't comment on
that and you know why.
But let's get one
thing straight.
They didn't shut me up, you did.
And if I took anything,
it was because
I had no other choice.
Joe, listen to me. If the
check hasn't cleared,
we can still get out of it.
Don't come by here anymore.
So much for really caring
about those people.
Go to hell.
I thought nobody puts
Baby in the corner.
Since when am I Baby?
Since you're sitting
in the corner.
You're usually a
power table kind of girl.
Well, I'm not tonight.
Jessica, what's going on?
It's over between me and Jeff.
What? What happened?
It's not important.
One day, the man's calling me
about taking you to Paris,
and the next it's over, and the
reason for all that isn't important?
No, it isn't.
Because right now, I have to decide
whether he should stay at the firm.
Well, then, I'd say the reason
that you broke up is important.
And I don't want to
get into it right now
because it's not going to change.
Wow.
Heard that before.
Leah, I'm not like Dad
and I'm tired of hearing it.
I know you always say
you're not like him.
But here you are,
scrubbing up for
the next surgery
instead of fighting for
the man that you love.
You know what?
Most sisters would say
"I'm sorry, Jessica,"
then give me a hug.
Jessica, I am sorry
that you're hurting.
And if you want something
sugar-coated, I'll order you dessert.
But that is not how
we show support.
You're right.
We show it by telling
each other what we think.
So...
And what I think is,
two days ago,
this man loved you.
So, unless you cheated on him, stole
from him, or killed somebody,
it seems to me the two of you
should be able to get past
whatever it is you did do.
Joe Henderson backed out.
Harvey.
Did you hear me?
They paid him off.
We have no case anymore.
And right now, I have a bigger problem.
Donna lied.
What do you mean, she lied?
I mean, she didn't just bullshit
her way into that file room,
she used the words "National
Transportation Safety Board."
In what context?
In the context of committing
a crime to help you.
Are you accusing me of
knowing that she did that?
If you didn't know, it's because
you didn't want to know.
Harvey, she told me she
didn't steal those things.
I believed her the
same way you did.
And you lied
just like she did...
I did not lie.
Then how come when I asked you
where those documents came from,
you didn't say one
word about Donna?
Because you wouldn't have
listened to another word I said
after that, and I was
trying to get the job done.
Well, you got the job
done by risking her.
And how is that different than
all the times you risked me?
Because she's different.
Harvey. I swear
I didn't know.
Well, like I said, right now,
I've got a bigger problem.
Donna's going to be charged with
felony fraud and she's guilty.
Five elements.
What?
Proving fraud consists
of five elements.
Yeah, I'm aware of that.
And they have all of them.
What about injury?
How did Donna
injure Liberty Rail?
You know how. I know.
And you know.
But Evan Smith isn't going
to sit in front of a jury
and explain why those
documents have value
without exposing her
client to criminal charges.
And without damages, what
Donna did is trespassing
at the worst.
What do you want me to do?
I want you to stay
on the civil case.
Harvey, the lawsuit's dead.
We don't have a plaintiff.
Then get another one. Because
I'm not letting this woman
get away with a goddamn thing.
All right. I'm paying you
the courtesy of a meeting.
What's on your mind?
Well, based on his
reputation, I would say that
he's going to try to weasel
his way out of this.
What I'm going to do
is save Mr. Wolf
from being embarrassed
in open court.
And I'm sure there's no side
benefit to you in the process.
You do know you're going to have to put Ms.
Smith on the stand, right?
So do you. That's why you
had her come down here.
And did she tell you what
Donna actually took?
You told me what Donna took.
And I also told you
that it proves they
committed a crime.
But she can't say
that, which means
all Donna stole was a
meaningless stack of papers.
And without actual damages...
I know the law. Then, you know
you've got a shitty witness.
Well?
I can't get into the details
of those documents,
but that doesn't mean
that they don't have value.
Of course they have value,
they save your ass.
They're confidential.
They have trade secrets.
The only secret that is in there
is that your trains kill people.
All right, enough.
Ms. Smith,
if you can't show
damages, I have no case.
You don't need damages.
You have intent.
And if you really
knew my reputation,
you'd also know
that I used to work here.
And I can tell you
they've never gone
after anyone for intent
in the history
of the DA's office.
And they're not
going to start now.
It was good doing
business with you, Evan.
Hey.
How are things?
You mean the things that you said
that Harvey would take care of?
Yes, those are exactly
the things I mean.
Well, those are
exactly the things
that Harvey just took care of.
He did?
He did.
Louis? What's wrong?
Nothing is wrong.
It's just, I know it
wasn't going to happen.
But when you first told me
they might press charges,
the thought of you
behind bars...
Oh, come on.
It just would have been some
cushy white-collar resort.
I could have finally gotten
my yoga certification...
It wouldn't have been.
But it doesn't matter
because I was right.
Harvey did whatever it took.
Thanks, Louis.
God, he doesn't even know how
lucky he is to have you.
Norma's still out, isn't she?
Her goddamn sister tripped
and fell in the tub
and she went to help. It's like she
doesn't even care about me at all.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
I know you don't
work in maintenance,
but you do have access
to accounts payable.
So, if you could...
Look... Nope.
Hey, please, just hear me.
Goddamn it.
Another one wouldn't
take your call?
No. None of them will. I've been
through this entire directory.
As soon as I use the words "crash," "heat,"
or "sensors," they all stop talking.
Mike, people died. Somebody's got
to want to do the right thing.
Well, if somebody does,
I can't find them.
Okay. What about
the victims' families?
Oh, you mean the original plaintiffs?
Mmm-hmm.
Yeah. The problem is, they
already have a settlement.
Go on. Look at it.
They weren't stupid.
It prevents them from ever
going after them again.
Mike, I'm just
trying to help you.
I know you are. I'm sorry.
I'm just frustrated.
If I can't find a new plaintiff,
I can't keep this case alive.
Wait a second.
You said no one at
the company will talk to you.
They won't because they're all
afraid they'll lose their job.
Right. So, what about someone
who has nothing left to lose?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about him.
So, I rescheduled the meeting
that you missed with Latham
for three o'clock tomorrow.
Here are the newest contracts.
Also, Kathy Finn called
about the takeover,
so I sent her the latest specs
and I told her to sit tight.
And I noticed the left
pen on your desk set
was out of ink, so I had
the cartridge replaced.
You could have done all of this
while I was out of the office.
I know. But then, I wouldn't
have had a chance to thank you.
Donna.
(SIGHS) Thank you, Harvey.
You're welcome.
TERRENCE: Ms. Paulsen.
Mr. Specter.
Terrence, you better be here
to give Donna a formal apology
from the DA's Office.
(SCOFFS)
No. I'm here to
give her lawyer this.
Harvey, what is that?
Donna, leave the room.
TERRENCE: You can
tell her to leave.
Don't forget to tell
her, her arraignment's
at 9:00 a.m.
Tomorrow morning.
Arraignment for what?
You son of a bitch. You amended
the charges to intent?
You said it's never been done in
the history of the DA's office.
I decided to make history.
By going after someone
for stealing nothing.
She went in there to
find the Hope Diamond.
Just because she came
out with a piece of glass
doesn't mean it wasn't fraud.
That's exactly what it means.
Every time I run into you,
you tell me whatever shady
thing just went down
was about the greater good
or that it didn't happen,
or this, that, or the other.
But a crime was committed here
and I'm going after her for it.
Bullshit, you're going after me.
Oh, you're telling me you
didn't order her to do it?
No, I didn't.
Well, we'll find out.
When she's about to be convicted
and I offer her a deal.
What happens now?
What happens now is we
go in there tomorrow
and enter a plea of not guilty.
But I am guilty.
Donna, intent to commit
fraud is a bullshit charge
and he's just using it
to try to scare you.
Well, it's working.
I'm scared.
Donna.
What's the punishment?
It doesn't matter, because I'm
going to get you out of it.
Harvey, what's the punishment?
Three-to-five years.
Oh, my God.
LOUIS: Three-to-five years for what?
Not now, Louis.
I just saw Terrence Wolf
at the elevator.
Three-to-five years
for what?
He's charging her with
intent to commit fraud.
Holy shit.
Louis, I don't want to hear it.
Well, you're going to because you
were supposed to get her out of this.
This isn't helping. What the hell
do you think I've been doing?
I don't know. But whatever
it is, it didn't do a thing.
You have no idea what
you're talking about.
I told her that you were never
going to let her get in trouble.
It's not so simple. What
the hell isn't so simple?
She's guilty!
Wolf's trying to
use her to turn on me
because he thinks
I put her up to it.
Did you?
Harvey didn't
even know I did it.
You know what? It doesn't even matter.
Because I'm taking over.
No, you're not. He's trying
to get her to turn on you.
You cannot be her lawyer.
She's not going to, so what
difference does it make?
The difference is, if you're out
of the picture, Wolf backs down.
From where he's standing,
I'm in the picture
and he's never
going to back down.
You don't know that and
this is Donna's life.
And I'm not putting
it in your hands.
And it's not your
decision to make.
No, it's not.
It's Donna's.
And she's sticking with me.
Louis, please. I, I know that
you want to help, but just go.
(CHUCKLES)
Mr. Jaworski.
Yeah?
My name's Mike Ross. I'm
with Pearson Specter Litt.
This is Rachel Zane.
She's one of our associates.
Sir, we'd like to speak with
you about the accident.
Look, I was already
deposed for that lawsuit.
The victims got paid. I said
everything I had to say. Okay?
We're not here to
come after you.
We want you to sue Liberty Rail.
Oh, yeah? And why
would I sue them?
Because while you might have
been driving the train,
that accident wasn't your fault.
Is this some kind of a joke?
No, sir, it isn't.
They made you the fall guy.
Bullshit. Why would
they do that?
Because they needed
to blame someone,
and not only were
you at the wheel,
you had no memory
of what happened.
No, I...
I don't believe it.
They're a good company.
(STAMMERING) They... They wouldn't do this.
Mr. Jaworski.
Look, I killed those people.
And they still gave me early
retirement and let me keep my pension.
The reason they did that
was to keep you quiet.
I need you to get off
my property. Both of you.
Sir, you know that
we're telling the truth.
Yeah, well, is the truth going
to support the family of a guy
who can't get another job
for the rest of his life?
If we win, you'll
be set up for life.
Oh, take a look at me.
I ain't the guy who wins.
I'm the guy who loses.
And what if I could guarantee
to take care of all of that
no matter what happens?
What would you need me to do?
BAILIFF: All rise.
You okay?
Mmm-hmm.
Am I going to have to talk?
Just be polite and
say "Your Honor."
It will be over
before you know it.
JUDGE:
State v. Donna Paulsen.
Is the defense counsel prepared
to proceed with the arraignment?
We are, Your Honor. Ms.
Paulsen, you have been charged
with felony intent
to commit fraud.
This carries a maximum sentence
of up to five years in prison.
Do you understand the
charges against you today?
Yes, Your Honor.
How do you plead?
Not guilty, Your Honor.
Very well. Mr. Wolf,
is the state ready
to go to the trial?
We are, Your Honor.
Trial is set to begin Monday.
(GAVEL POUNDS)
JUDGE: Next case.
All right, you've
made your point.
Let's plead this down to a misdemeanor
and both go back to our real jobs.
This is my real job.
(VOICES ECHOING) Maybe if you had
more respect for what it stands for,
you wouldn't be standing here.
Listen. I'm going to wipe
that look off your smug face.
Go ahead and try, Harvey.
But I've got all
the evidence I need.
You're going to have to go
find yourself a new secretary.
I see you're back
to not knocking.
I take it that means
you've made up your mind.
I have.
And what I've decided
is that you shut the door
on me the other night.
And it's not fair for you to dictate
what I do and don't get to say.
I told you.
It doesn't matter
what you have to say
because whatever it is,
I won't believe it.
Well, what if I was
here to tell you
that I love you?
Jessica, you lied
to me for months.
Jeff, please, just listen.
I know I hurt you.
But you were the one
who wanted us to work together
and be in a relationship.
And you were the one who
thought it was a mistake.
Because I was scared.
But I changed my mind
because you refused to give up.
And now, I'm
refusing to give up.
I want you to stay here.
I want us to have both.
Jessica... You wanted me
to let my walls down.
Well, they're down.
I don't dare to make a move
Too much at risk,
too much to lose
This love is overtaking me
Donna, why don't you go home?
You know I like to be alone when
I'm getting ready for a trial.
I need to talk to you.
What is it?
I think maybe Louis was right.
You think Louis was
right about what?
Maybe he should be
handling my case.
Okay. Well, if that's
how you feel...
I knew it. I knew you would
take this as an insult.
How exactly would you
like me to take it?
I would like you take it seriously
and talk about it with me.
Okay, Donna.
Why exactly would you prefer
Louis to handle this?
Because I sat in that
arraignment today
and it hit me for the first time
that I might actually
go to prison.
And you were more
concerned with attacking
Terrence Wolf than
you were with me.
So, you think Louis is right.
I piss off the DA too much.
Well, you sure did today.
Because he's coming at us.
And you're pouring
gas on the fire.
Because that's what I do.
And I don't need you coming
in here second guessing
how I do my job.
Harvey,
why are you attacking me?
I'm not the enemy.
You sure as hell are right now.
What? Why am I the...
Because I'm getting
ready for a fight
and you're telling me you
don't think I can win.
I'm not telling you that. I'm
telling you that I'm petrified.
And I understand. But I don't
have time to comfort you.
Well, I need you to make time.
And I can't because...
Harvey, this is my life!
When I told Louis
how you got me
out of this thing,
he told me how scared
he was at the thought
of me going to prison.
And I just need you to...
Donna,
the thought of you
going to prison
makes me want to
drop to my knees.
You want to hear
me say it? There it is.
But that's not going to happen because
I'm not going to let it happen.
But in order to do that,
you need to let me do what I do.
Harvey.
That's enough...
If you want someone to give
you a hug, go to Louis.
You want someone to
get you out of this thing,
you need to leave me alone.
I need to know everything you have
and I need to know right now.
We got the conductor to sign on,
but we have to give him... I don't
care what I have to give him.
What does that give us?
What do you mean?
It gives us standing. Now we
can subpoena those records.
Well, that's not enough.
It's a start.
I don't need a start.
I need a finish,
and I need it now.
They're charging
Donna, aren't they?
She was arraigned this morning.
(SIGHS)
If this thing goes to trial,
I can't guarantee a win.
So, we're back to trading
the case for Donna.
Yeah, and I don't want to
hear your moral objections
about those people
getting away with murder.
I'm not talking
about that, Harvey.
But if Donna was arraigned, it's not
up to them to drop the charges.
It's up to Wolf, and you know
he's never going to do that.
I'm not talking about
dropping the charges.
I'm talking about making this
whole damn thing go away.
Harvey, if you're saying
what I think you're saying,
that's obstruction ofjustice.
The way I see it, it's justice.
You know what I mean. I do
and I don't give a shit.
This is Donna.
All right, I get it. But what
if what I have isn't enough?
Like you said, it's a start.
Have an official complaint
on my desk by the morning.
What are you going to do?
I'm going to get us enough.
JOE: All right. I hear you,
I hear you.
Do you know who I am? No.
Mike Ross works for me.
Hey, I don't give a shit.
I told him not to take your
case in the first place
because I knew you were a
goddamn shakedown artist.
But now, someone I care
about is in trouble
because you took a payout.
Get out of my face.
Listen to me.
If you don't do what
we need you to do,
I will hurt you.
You'd better be
prepared to kill me
because I'm not going
to give that money back.
Well, if this is just
about money, then...
We don't need to fight at all.
Harvey. This is
becoming a habit.
I've seen you more than
my last three boyfriends.
Somehow, that
doesn't surprise me.
(CHUCKLES) You're
funny. I like you.
But I know you're not here
to mock my relationships,
so what's on your mind?
We wanted to give you this.
What's this?
It's the lawsuit we filed on
behalf of Michael Jaworski.
You know, the man you let take
the fall for the accident.
Michael Jaworski can't sue...
HARVEY: What?
Sue you because you were smart
enough to take care of his expenses?
Well, now I'm taking
care of his expenses.
And now, we have standing
and we are going to
subpoena those documents.
Am I supposed to start
quaking in my boots?
HARVEY: Nope. We know
if you can doctor a report,
you can alter those
maintenance records.
I didn't alter anything. Well,
that's not what Joe Henderson said.
He said you came to him,
admitted everything,
and offered him a
settlement to keep quiet.
We didn't admit anything and
that settlement is sealed.
Oh, you mean this settlement?
We had an agreement.
Well, here's the thing about
paying people off, Evan.
Someone can always
pay them more.
(SIGHS)
His word won't hold up
against Richard Mclntyre's.
Oh, he's not saying that Richard
Mclntyre put him up to it.
He's saying you did.
That's bullshit.
And does that really matter?
What do you want?
You made the author
of that report disappear.
You made
Joe Henderson disappear.
Figure out a way
to make the witness
against Donna change her tune.
That's obstruction of justice.
That's not my problem.
You son of a bitch.
It's your call.
Maybe people will believe
Joe, maybe they won't.
But instead of making money,
you're going to be defending yourself
in court for the next five years.
You're so sure we did this,
you're really going to let us get away
with "murder" for your secretary?
You're damn right I am.
And if I had to do it
again, I'd do it 100 times.
What's that?
You know what it is.
Jeff... Jessica, you were right.
We either need to have both
or it's not going to work.
And you don't want both.
Effectively immediately, I'm
tendering my resignation.
Then, I wish you luck.
Good luck, Jessica.
Do you remember? (CHUCKLES) Yes.
Of course I remember,
it happened right there.
Well, it was your fault
because you made me
burst out laughing.
You didn't just burst,
you spat a piece of
shrimp across the room
and into the back
of my mother's hair.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
And she didn't even feel it
because of all the hairspray.
It was stuck in there
like a tick.
Oh, my God. I could
hardly look at her
or that boyfriend for
the next two hours.
What was his name again?
Who cares?
He was such a loser.
Come on.
He was the reason you had
that God-awful party
in the first place.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
Thank you, Harvey.
You don't need to thank me.
You already thanked me.
No. I thanked
you for fixing it.
Now, I'm thanking you for not
bringing it up all night.
I just figured if you wanted it
brought up, you'd bring it up.
And now you have, so, um...
I told you I'd never let
anything happen to you,
and I won't ever.
So, you don't ever have to
feel scared like that again.
I thought you said you
didn't do the comfort thing.
I didn't say I didn't do it.
I said I didn't have time
because I was so busy
saving your ass.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
I'm sorry I snapped at you.
If anyone else ever
loses faith in me,
it doesn't matter.
But with you, it's different.
I see nothing
I should go.
Why?
You know why.
You know I love you, Donna.
Fade into you
Strange you never knew
I think it's strange
you never knew
Ripped By mstoll