(HARVEY READING)
- Jeff...
- Jessica, you were right.
We either need to have both
or it's not going to work.
Effectively immediately,
I'm tendering my resignation.
Forstman doesn't throw money around
without getting something in return.
- He's gonna get money in return.
- Money is third on his list.
The first two are getting back at people
and getting control of people.
Son of a bitch. You didn't bring me here
for you to sign on the arrows.
You brought me here for me
to sign on the arrows.
Yep.
After Woodall lost his job,
Forstman got him installed at the SEC.
- Where's the proof?
- In Eric Woodall's bank accounts.
This is ridiculous.
- I'm your boss.
- Gentlemen, give me a minute.
You're forcing me to turn you in
for what you did twelve years ago.
CHARLES: You're not gonna do that,
because you did it, too, pal.
Anyone else ever loses faith in me,
it doesn't matter.
But with you, it's different.
I should go.
Why?
You knowl love you, Donna.
Sing, sing, won't you
sing for me?
Beast in your belly,
you've got to let it breathe
- MAN: To Harvey.
- CROWD: To Harvey. Cheers.
Beast in your belly, Lord,
you've got to let it breathe
Breathe for me
Mmm, mmm, mmm...
Jay, can I get a Macallan 18?
You know, usually
when someone wins their first trial,
they at least pretend to finish the drink
their fellow ADAs bought them.
- I'm sorry, do we...
- Know each other?
- Not yet. But today's your lucky day.
- And why is that?
Because it's the day
you get to meet Donna.
- And let me guess, you're Donna.
- Oh, you have no idea how Donna I am.
Well, Donna, I'm Harvey...
Harvey Specter.
You really think
I'd be talking to you
if I didn't know who you were?
And how exactly
do you know about me?
I know about everybody.
What I don't know is,
why is this the first case
you ever took to trial?
Because it was a white-collar crime,
not some drug dealer on the comer.
- Which makes it the kind of case...
- That puts your name in the paper.
- You're not just a pretty face, are you?
- No, I'm not.
So, maybe you should buy me a drink
and we can continue this conversation
in the comer.
Jay?
Nothing % better than
blood on blood
I promise, brother,
you are safe with us
Sean, what are you doing in my building
in the middle of the night?
I thought we were done
with you following me.
I'm not following you,
I'm waiting for you.
I need your help.
You need my help
or the SEC needs my help?
We both do.
But at the moment,
I care more about me
than I do about the SEC.
I can't find the money.
What do you mean
you can't find the money?
What the hell have you been doing
for the last three months?
- Looking for the money.
- Then look harder.
Because Woodall isn't
in the charity business.
Forstman buys people
and we handed them
to you on a silver platter.
And I stuck my neck out for you
when I accused my friend
of being on the take.
Now, if I can't follow
through with that,
Eric Woodall walks.
Charles Forstman walks.
Well, what makes you think
I can find the money when you couldn't?
I don't know if you can or not.
But they're going to shut me down
in five days
and I need all the help
I can get.
Okay. Enough about me,
let's talk about you.
Ooh, my favorite subject.
- Well, you know what I think?
- Hmm?
I think your favorite subject
didn't come up to me
just to find out why I went to trial.
- You want something.
- I sure do.
And I think I might be ready
to give it to you.
It's not sex.
Then never mind.
(CHUCKLES)
Wow. You're going to be
that honest about it.
Saves time.
Well, in that case,
I want to move to your desk.
And why is that?
Because it's no secret
that in a few years
you're going back to
Gordon, Schmidt and Van Dyke.
And let me guess,
you want to come with me when I do.
- No, I don't.
- Then why?
Because I'm going to be an actress
and I want somebody
who understands
that there's more to life
than just the DA's office,
and that I can give my all to them,
but still step out
for the occasional audition.
- So, you're stepping out on me already?
- Yes.
But the important thing is
I'm telling you about it in advance.
- Macallan 36.
- I didn't order a Macallan 36.
It's from the gentleman over there.
DONNA: Okay.
I don't know who that is,
but I'm telling you right now,
he is bad news.
You look... different.
I will take that as a compliment.
I meant I wasn't expecting
to see you like that.
I... I know what you meant.
What you really meant was that you
weren't expecting to see me at all.
- Excuse me?
- Come on, Harvey.
Ever since Mike came back to the firm,
I've basically been non-existent to you.
What's going on?
Cahill can't find the money.
What do you mean
he can't find the money?
What's he been doing
this whole time?
- Yeah, that's what I said.
- And what did he say?
He said he's in trouble
and he needs our help.
And I'm going to tell you
what I couldn't tell him.
He can't find the money because
he's been looking in the wrong place.
- So, where's the right place?
- I don't know exactly.
But somewhere, there's a person
Eric Woodall cares about
- and that's where the money went.
- And why can't we tell Cahill that?
Because I don't want him
to know howl know it.
- How do you know it?
- Because I know.
You want a chance to exist?
Figure out a way to get this done.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
(MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING)
Mmm, mmm
Summer rain,
won't you come to me?
Mmm, mmm
This man needs your sympathy
And wash over me
Mmm, mmm
Louis, I got your note
and I know that Norma's still out,
- but I really don't have time to...
- Hanna's dead.
What?
She died this morning
taking care of her sister.
Oh, Louis, I'm so sorry. I...
You don't need to fake it, Donna.
I'm not faking it.
She was a sweet woman.
She was a friggin' battle-axe,
is what she was.
There wasn't a day
that went by when I didn't want to
rip out one of her varicose veins
and strangle her with it.
Okay, I don't think you're in touch with
how you're really feeling right now.
How I'm feeling is that she left me
high and dry just like she always did.
- You expect her to keep working?
- Look at this.
It's her entire estate laid out on paper.
And she couldn't manage my calendar,
but this crap-fest,
she plans within an inch of her life.
And you want me to make sure
these things are bequeathed properly.
You can stuff them
in a giant pifiata for all I care.
I have to go find the perfect urn to throw
her ashes off the top of the building.
She requested that?
No, she wanted them
to be in here with me.
- But like hell I'm going to do that.
- Okay. Louis,
I will take care of this for you,
but you're not throwing her ashes
- anywhere without me.
- Okay, fine.
Do you want me to smooth things over
with Harvey for you?
No. Harvey will be
just fine on his own.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
I know who you are
and I'm not interested.
Just because I've got a bad reputation?
Because I'm not accepting a drink
for putting your rival behind bars.
You've got the wrong idea, pal.
I didn't buy you that
for putting my enemy away.
I bought you that
for how you put my enemy away.
Okay. You got me.
- What are you talking about?
- You.
You've got something special.
And I want people with something
special working for me.
Why exactly would
I want to work for you?
I can think of a million reasons,
because that's the signing bonus
I'm going to give you.
And that's a hell of a lot more money
than you're ever going to make
as a lawyer.
What if I told you
I don't practice law to make money?
Then I'd ask you
what are you practicing for?
- To bend people to my will.
- Then bend people to your will for me.
And make a lot of money
on top of it.
Well, here's the thing, Mr. Forstman.
Not that it's any of your business,
but I'll be making half a million a year
in no time.
Half a million a year is dick.
My gardener makes that.
Then go offer your gardener a job,
because I'm not interested.
Just so you know,
if you change your mind
and come back to me,
it's not going to be
the same conversation.
Thanks for the drink.
Good luck, Mr. Forstman.
- What are you doing?
- What do you think I'm doing?
If Forstman gave the money to someone
Woodall's close to,
we need to start
by compiling a family tree.
I meant, why aren't you
at school today?
Because I'm going
to prove to Harvey that I exist.
Okay. Now that you mention it,
what was that last night?
Ever since you came back,
it's like you and Harvey
speak this secret language,
and I'm not a part of it.
Rachel, come on.
We have a history.
I'm not talking about history.
I'm talking about respect.
Okay. You don't know
what you're talking about
if you think Harvey
doesn't respect you.
Are you going to tell me that last night
he didn't give you a look that said,
"You don't need to tell her the full story
because she doesn't need to know"?
Rachel, he didn't give me that look
because he doesn't respect you.
He gave me that look
because he's ashamed.
What are you talking about?
(SIGHS)
Let's just say that I'm not the only one
that Charles Forstman duped.
- Harvey got taken by Forstman?
- Yes.
And he only told me because he had to
when we were in the middle of
that takeover battle.
That's why Harvey's
so slow to care about anybody.
Forstman used somebody
he cared about.
Holy shit, I never even
thought about that.
- Who do you think it was?
- I don't know.
But I have a pretty good guess.
Well, what do you think?
I think this place is a dump
and I'm busy. So, why don't you
tell me why we're here?
I want to open a restaurant here.
Marcus, there's already
a restaurant here.
And it isn't working.
Which is why they're going
to lose their lease.
Take a look. I've got a chef.
I've got a liquor license.
I've got renovation plans.
I have everything I need.
Except the money.
- I need $150,000.
- Are you crazy?
Come on, Harvey.
This is my dream.
I know I can make this work.
I'm not saying you can't.
But I don't have that kind of money.
What are you talking about?
You're the big time lawyer
who just got his name in the paper.
My name in the paper
doesn't pay me extra money.
I make $50,000 a year.
And you said you were going to be
a corporate lawyer.
Yeah. And when I am,
I can help you.
- But right now...
- I don't give a shit about right now.
I give a shit about when you were
supposed to be my big brother.
- But instead, what did you do?
- I know what I did.
Then you know I can never get a loan
for as long as I live.
Marcus, when are you going
to take responsibility for your own shit?
What the hell does it look like
I'm trying to do?
I came to you first
because I know you'd want me to.
But if you don't come through,
I'm going to go to Mom.
You don't mean Mom,
you mean him.
And you're not taking
a nickel from that man.
Me taking his money isn't going to make
what he did to Dad any worse.
That's bullshit and you know it.
And I'm not going to let you do it.
Hey, Harvey.
How the hell are you
going to stop me?
HARVEY: Am I crazy
or is that the same dress
you were wearing
the last time I saw you?
You must be crazy, because I don't wear
the same dress ever.
Then you must spend
a fortune on wardrobe.
But I have to say
it's worth it.
I suddenly get the feeling
this isn't just a drop by.
- I want to move up our timeline.
- Harvey, we have a deal.
I put myself on the line for you.
And our deal is not going to change.
I could just pay you
the money back and move on.
And if you could do that,
you wouldn't be here
asking to come back.
How much money
did Marcus lose this time?
He didn't lose anything.
He wants to start a restaurant.
He doesn't want to start shit.
He owes somebody something.
You don't know that.
He's turned his life around.
What I know is, he has a problem
and he's looking
to get money from you.
And you're not going to get it from me.
Then I'll get it somewhere else.
- And what's that supposed to mean?
- I got a job offer from Charles Forstman.
Look at me.
I don't care what he's offering you.
Don't take it.
Because he's got a bad reputation?
You think I don't know that?
I think there are a lot of things you think
you know that you don't.
What I know is that you're either going to
help me or Charles Forstman is.
It's up to you.
Harvey, I can't make
you listen to me.
But what I'm not going to do
is let you come here
and leverage me with some bullshit offer
from a shady banker.
So, do what you're going to do.
But don't say I didn't warn you.
You can buy
all the Wonder Bread you want, Eric,
but you can't take it
with you to prison.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm here to remind you
that once they find the money,
it's all going to come tumbling down.
They're not going to find the money.
- Because there is no money.
- Not in your accounts.
But I know what Cahill doesn't.
Forstman gave it to
somebody you care about,
and if I tell him that,
it will be too late.
I know what you're trying to do.
You're trying to bait me into
moving the body.
We both know you're not dumb
enough to do that.
I'm here to get you to cut a deal
and turn Forstman in.
You don't have the authority
to cut a deal.
No, but I can get Cahill to,
after you hire me to represent you.
You mean hire the fox
to watch the henhouse?
- Not a chance.
- Eric, they're closing in.
And when they do,
you're going to want to call me.
So, why don't you take my card?
(SIGHS) This is ridiculous.
Woodall's got 30 people it could be,
or it could be none of them.
- I know that but this is ourjob.
- No.
Our job is to help Harvey get Forstman.
If you're thinking what I think
you're thinking...
- I am and you are, too.
- Rachel, we are never
going to get Harvey to go after Forstman
- for what they did 12 years ago.
- Why?
- Because of his brother?
- Yes, because of his brother
or because he's ashamed.
Either way, he knows it's a possibility.
He doesn't need me to tell him about it.
No. He just doesn't need
me to tell him about it.
- Rachel.
- This is not about that.
Look. I can't tell him
because I'm not supposed to know.
- But you can.
- And I just told you,
he doesn't want to hear it.
And when has that
ever stopped you before?
- This is different.
- Why?
Because he's ashamed.
Then he's not thinking right.
And he needs your help
more than ever.
- Then we're both telling him.
- Mike, I don't need the credit.
No, this isn't about credit.
This is about us.
He can't tell me something
and expect me not to tell you.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes, where have you been all day?
Why, is there something
you want to talk about?
Yeah, where you've been.
Sean Cahill was at my door last night...
Harvey, Norma passed away.
I've been helping Louis.
Norma died?
That's terrible.
I thought you couldn't stand her.
I couldn't, but I assumed
Louis loved her, so...
- Do what you need to do.
- Oh.
Because she was his secretary,
he must have loved her.
- That's not what I meant.
- But it is what you said.
Okay, Donna.
What's wrong?
How about we start with the fact
that I have been wondering
for the last 10 hours
if you're going to acknowledge
what happened last night.
But you're you,
so of course you're not.
I'm not going to acknowledge it
because nothing happened last night.
Why? And don't tell me
I know why.
Because it would have been a mistake
and you know it.
What I know is something happened.
And you ran away,
but not before you told me you love me.
I did that because
I wanted to make you feel better.
- What did you just say to me?
- No, that's not what I meant.
- I didn't say that to...
- Because you pity me?
- Yeah, you did.
- No, I said it because I love you,
- and I wanted you to know it.
- Love me how?
- Why does that have to come...
That's what I thought.
You either can't answer or you won't.
Which is bullshit, because obviously
you don't just look at me this way.
You're capable
of looking at me that way.
But you don't want to
let those worlds collide
because you're afraid
to risk anything.
- Because we have everything.
- No, Harvey, you have everything!
So, you're saying you want everything?
I don't know, Harvey.
But what I do know is,
I don't want your pity.
Oh, the world
is all around us
But have you noticed me?
Yeah, the world has
overshadowed me
What are you doing here?
Nobody finds out where I live.
I do.
CHARLES: Oh, hold on a second.
Let me turn this off.
HARVEY: You've got to be kidding me.
You're watching Wall Street?
- A monthly ritual, to remind myself.
- Of what?
Of what a pussy Gordon Gekko is.
Now...
Want to tell me
what changed your mind?
- I decided I wanted the money.
- And you turned me down.
So... (INHALES SHARPLY)
Now you're going
to tell me why you want the money.
My brother needs
$150,000 for a restaurant.
Now we're getting somewhere.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Let's have it.
Okay, you want it?
Here it is.
It's not just a restaurant,
it's a second chance.
Marcus has a gambling problem.
- And I gave it to him.
- Mmm-hmm.
And you think this is his way out?
- I know it is.
- Hmm.
We're not a good fit.
Because restaurants fail.
And when this one does,
you'll leave.
So, you might as well
leave right now.
Then how about we bet on it?
You're going to gamble on something
to get your brother
out of a gambling problem?
- I didn't say I had a problem.
- I think maybe you do.
When you always win,
it's not a problem.
(LAUGHING)
I think I might like you, pal.
Louis. I got your message.
What's going on?
What's going on is,
they're trying to screw me
- and I need you to be bad cop.
- What?
MORTICIAN: Have you made
a decision, sir?
No, I haven't made a decision,
you shyster dealer of death.
Okay. I think maybe
we're going to need another minute.
No, we don't.
I don't need another minute to see that
this looks like a pot from Home Depot,
this looks like a lamp
from Motel 6,
and this looks like
a goddamn howitzer shell.
You are lucky that I don't take
this mockery of a final resting place
and shove it up your ass.
- Louis, that's enough.
- No, it's not enough!
I've been handling
this bullshit for two days
for a woman who was supposed
to be handling things for me.
Louis, this isn't about the urn.
Oh, please don't give me
that touchy-feely shit.
And why the hell
are you not being bad cop?
Because that's not what's needed.
Oh, bullshit it's not what's needed.
- Louis.
- You don't care about me.
You never cared about me.
All you care about is yourself...
And your stupid sister,
and your Hummel figurines,
- and your Murder, She Wrote reruns.
- Louis, I'm not Norma.
She's gone...
And it's gonna be okay.
She was a battle-axe!
(CRYING)
But she was my battle-axe.
I know.
Oh, God, she didn't
just leave me high and dry,
she left me for good.
(SOBBING)
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
- HARVEY: Both of you?
- We both work for you.
Which is why we're both here to say
maybe it's time we explore other options.
You got to be kidding me.
You spent two days on this,
and you're ready
to throw in the towel?
We've spent two of our five days on it,
and we still don't have a name,
so we think it's time to consider...
- What?
- Going after Forstman
for whatever he did to you
12 years ago.
- You told her?
- Yes, I did.
Because like I said,
we both work for you.
Which means we both want to help.
You think I haven't wondered
how to go after Forstman
- 100 times in the last dozen years?
- And why don't you?
- Because I'm not the only one at risk.
- MIKE: You mean your brother.
Yes, I do. And I'm not gonna
bring him into this,
because he didn't do anything wrong.
- Harvey, I'm not saying...
- Did you hear me?
He doesn't just have
a gun to my head, okay?
He's got one to my brother's.
And how many times
have you told me
that when someone
has a gun to your head,
- you figure a different way out?
- This is Charles Forstman.
- There is no other way out.
- Harvey, there's...
I gave you a job to do.
Now do your goddamn job.
- RACHEL: Well, that was a bust.
- MIKE: We had to try.
Did we? I told you
he'd be pissed off, and he was.
Yeah, and you also told me he needed to
hear things that he didn't want to hear.
Okay, well, now all he heard is,
not only can't he trust me,
he can't trust you either.
That's not what he heard,
and you know it.
What he heard was that you're the
closest person in the world to me,
I am never gonna keep things from you,
and I'm not the only one in his comer.
I'm the closest person
in the world to you.
- Of course you are. How can you even...
- I'm not questioning it.
I'm the closest person
in the world to you
and I wouldn't be
on your family tree.
- You're talking about Woodall.
- Yes, I'm talking about Woodall.
Woodall's married.
We checked his wife. Nothing.
That's the thing.
We're not married.
Okay, I really don't think
this is the time to bring that up.
I'm being serious. We've exhausted
every person that's related to him.
Maybe it's time we found
someone who isn't.
- That's genius.
- Thank you.
Now I really don't understand
why Harvey doesn't respect you.
It's too soon.
It's too soon for that joke.
(SIGHS)
Too soon.
- HARVEY: I can have any one?
- CHARLES: Take your pick.
It doesn't matter,
'cause you're gonna lose.
That's funny.
I look at it like I'm gonna win twice.
I get to drive a badass car,
and I get to kick your ass.
Cocky. I like that.
A guy like you,
I'm surprised you could stand
working for Cameron Dennis
in the first place.
- What do you mean?
- He doesn't like cocky.
Take, for instance,
what's his name, DuPont?
What's he up for? Tax evasion?
- Insider trading.
- Yeah, whatever.
The point is, after what you did
the other day,
why aren't you leading that?
- Because this is Cameron's case.
- If I were him, it'd be yours.
Harvey, you are his star player,
and he's not even
putting you in the game.
And on top of that, he didn't have
the balls to announce
whether he's going
after DuPont or not.
Don't you worry
about Cameron Dennis.
DuPont's gonna get
what's coming to him.
- That's exactly what I wanted to hear.
- What are you talking about?
Well, you're loyal to the guy
you work for. I like that.
So you were just talking shit about him
to see if I'd jump on board?
And you didn't...
Which is why we don't
have to race anymore.
- You're saying I got the job?
- I'm saying welcome to the team.
Well, that's all well and good,
Charles, but we're still racing.
We sure as hell are.
We just have to find
something else to bet on.
- Hey, Sean. Good to see you.
- Don't give me that shit.
Did you confront Eric Woodall
yesterday morning at his supermarket?
I ran into him by accident.
I like the produce there.
I'm not in the mood, Harvey.
Did you approach
the subject of an SEC investigation
with the express purpose
of intimidating him?
I approached him with the express
purpose of hiring me as his lawyer.
Why the hell would you do that?
You're supposed to be helping me.
And if he's willing to admit what he did,
that is helping you.
And instead, he's claiming that
I sent you there to intimidate him.
Then I guess
that's the way it's breaking.
What the hell
are you talking about?
He's either gonna buy what I'm selling
or cover his tracks.
And if he covers his tracks,
you need to be there.
- Are you asking me to follow him?
- No, I'm telling you to follow him.
I can't do that.
I don't have authorization.
Didn't stop you following me.
Enough. He's filing charges
of harassment against me.
We do this, nothing sticks.
Then we might not get him
because I have nothing.
Well, let me give you
a little extra motivation.
Remember,
Woodall knows all about
Louis Litt's little
Forstman transgression.
So if he gets exonerated,
who do you think's gonna be
the first person he goes after?
So, instead of going to Jersey
for your produce,
go get me something
I can use.
You're having a drink by yourself?
What's going on?
What's going on is,
I just finished having them
scrape Jeff's name off his door.
So why don't you tell me
why you're here, Harvey?
Cahill's having trouble getting evidence
against Forstman and Woodall.
I'm aware of that.
Then you should also be aware
that if Woodall keeps his job,
he's likely to go after Louis.
I could've done that math,
and so could you, so...
I might be able to
help them get Forstman...
On something else.
Does this have something to do
with when he offered you
that job 12 years ago?
Yes.
I told you that man was trouble.
And I told you I wouldn't abandon
Marcus and you were wrong about him.
So this has something
to do with Marcus.
Yes, it does.
(SIGHS) Well, if you are
asking me to choose
between your brother and Louis,
you know who I'm choosing.
- I'm not asking you to do that.
- Then what are you asking?
I want your help
to get my mind right.
(SIGHS)
Here's the thing, Harvey.
Jeff's gone, and he's gone because
of the choices I made.
So I'm not sure if I can help you
get your mind right,
because right now...
Mine's not right.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hang on a sec.
. HEY-
You didn't come down here
just to give me my start date.
I came down here to tell you
I think you have something special,
and I'd love nothing more
than to have you on my desk,
but I'm leaving the DA's office.
Does this have something to do
with that Forstman guy
buying you a drink
the other night?
I thought you didn't know who he was.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, I looked him up
because I thought
I was gonna be working for you.
- And I'm telling you, he's shady.
- Because he's got a bad reputation?
Oh, I don't care what his reputation is.
You don't know this about me yet,
but I know people,
usually better than
they know themselves.
And the same way
I know you are a good person,
I can tell you that man
is rotten to the core.
You're just trying to get me to stay
so you can work at my desk.
(SCOFFS) Listen to me.
I don't care whether
I work on your desk or not.
You're making a mistake
if you take a job with that man.
Then I guess I'm making a mistake,
because I already did.
It was nice knowing you, Donna.
(SIGHS)
So you're keeping her here after all.
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah, I couldn't throw her off the roof
after you got me to cry.
I'm glad.
Donna, I can't thank you
enough for what you did.
Oh, you're welcome, Louis.
The truth is,
I needed this more than you know.
Well, I get it.
You needed a distraction after
everything you just went through.
- Uh, yeah. Something like that.
- Truth is,
I could use a distraction myself.
Well, there is one thing
that you still need to do.
You need to start thinking
about a new secretary.
Donna, I know
I've asked you this before,
but we're so much closer now
than we were then, and...
Louis, I work for Harvey.
You know I can't be your secretary.
But we have this bond...
You and I.
Shakespeare, The Gun Club.
We've always spoken the same
language, and you know it.
- Louis, I can't.
- I get it.
We're better as friends.
Hey.
How about I set up
a little farewell for Norma
as my last official act
as your interim secretary?
Thank you, Donna.
Are you sure we've got
the right address?
I'm positive.
Can I help you?
Uh, yes, is there
a Maryanne McGrath here?
- Who can I say is asking?
- We're with Pearson Specter Litt.
We'd like to speak with her
in regards to an ongoing case.
I'm afraid that won't be possible.
You just said she was here.
I don't understand...
Maryanne has advanced Alzheimer's.
- But she's 55.
- It's early onset,
and hers is particularly aggressive.
I'm sorry.
Can I ask how long she's been a patient?
We're not supposed to disclose any...
Please. It's really important.
She was moved here
about a year and a half ago.
- And before that?
- I don't really know,
but I don't think
she was getting the best care.
Thank you.
My mother's 55.
You know, and if she's only here
- because Forstman pays for it...
- I know.
Harvey wants us to find
the person Woodall's close to.
- That's all we can do.
- Well, "All we can do"
is gonna send her back
to some horrible facility.
- We don't exactly know that.
- Yes, we do.
Rachel, it's terrible.
I don't like it any more than you do,
but it's not up to us.
I know. It just sucks.
HARVEY: You goddamn liar.
Oh, don't be mad.
Yeah, Conchita
tells everybody I'm not home.
You know what I'm talking about.
DuPont Investments
dropped through the floor today,
and you sold short based on something
that I told you in confidence.
I don't recall
you telling me anything at all.
You son of a bitch.
You made over
$100 million on that trade.
Yeah, I did. Welcome to
the real world, pal.
My real world doesn't involve
befriending young attorneys
to get inside infonnation.
Maybe you're not the right man
for me, after all.
You think I still
want to work for you after this?
You wanted competition and money.
You got the competition.
Here's your money.
You can shove that
million dollars up your ass,
because I'm not only not taking your job,
I'm gonna prosecute you.
Then you might as well
add your name to the indictment
since you've already
shared in the profits.
- What are you talking about?
- Take a look at this check.
It's not $1 million.
It's $850,000.
Bet you can guess
where the other $150,000 went.
- What did you do?
- You know what I did.
Marcus had nothing
to do with this.
He wouldn't have had you said yes
right away. But you didn't.
- We're giving you the money back.
- You're gonna break his little heart.
He thinks that money
came from you.
And you snatch cash out of an addicted
gamblefs hands, take away his dream,
only one way that story ends.
So you can either pout about it
or you can embrace it
and prove to everyone I was right when
I said I saw something special in you.
Someday the shoe's
gonna be on the other foot, Charles.
Words spoken by
every loser I've ever met.
See you around, pal.
It's Woodall's first wife.
Her name's Maryanne.
They grew up together.
They got married when they were 21
and had it annulled six months later.
- And what's the money for?
- She has Alzheimer's.
Don't tell me.
He moved her to a high-end facility
and pays for round-the-clock care.
And the problem is,
we called the company
that handles the billing, and...
And everything's in cash up front,
probably paid five years in advance.
And Maryanne couldn't tell us
because she doesn't speak.
Which means we don't have any proof.
- Where are you going?
- I'm gonna go get us some proof.
- You did this?
- Mike and I both did.
- Then why isn't he here?
- You know why.
Because it was more you than him.
You did a good job, Rachel.
Shopping, renting videos.
- You must be going stir-crazy.
- That's all right.
My suspension is about to expire.
HARVEY: Yeah, I wouldn't count on it.
We found Maryanne.
I'm told she's doing well
at the new facility,
you know, the one
Forstman's paying for.
You son of a bitch.
I'm not here to exploit your tragedy, Eric.
- I'm here to tell you it's over.
- Well, if this were over,
you'd be with Sean Cahill right now,
which means you're still
looking for me to cut a deal.
I'm looking for you
to turn on Forstman.
You accost me
for the second time in three days
and throw Maryanne's name around
like a bargaining chip,
and you think I'm gonna help you?
Drop dead.
Eric, please.
The reason I knew to look for someone
that you cared about was that
Forstman did the same thing to me.
He finds your weakness
and presses down
until you don't have the will
to stand up to him.
With you, it was an ex-wife
with Alzheimer's.
With me...
It was a little brother
addicted to gambling.
I don't care.
You don't have proof,
and you're not gonna get it
in the next 24 hours.
You're right, I don't.
But here's the thing.
Cahill may have a deadline, but I don't,
and I don't care how long it takes,
because I'm gonna find that proof
if you don't turn on Forstman.
LOUIS: A lot of you don't know this,
but the truth is, I hated Norma.
I hated her clogs,
her mustache,
her stupid seasonal sweaters.
But the thing I hated most about her
was her favorite story
about how Abe Vigoda
asked her to marry him in 1975.
I mean, we get it.
You were hot.
You turned him down, and it was
the biggest regret of your life.
And like everything you ever said,
I couldn't stand it at the time.
But now that you're gone,
I understand what you meant.
Don't let the moment pass.
Don't let the people you love walk by you
without letting them know
how you feel about them,
because life slips by,
and then it's over.
And I'm not gonna let
another minute pass me by
without letting you know
how much you mean to me.
I love you, Norma.
Thank you, Louis.
That was a lovely ceremony.
- That was beautiful, Louis.
- I couldn't have done it without you.
- Oh, that's not true.
- Yeah, it is.
I couldn't even see how I felt
without you showing me.
And the truth is, Donna, you know me
better than I know myself.
Like I said, Harvey
has no idea
how lucky he is to have you.
I'm gonna turn
from the start line
And then we're leaving,
we 're leaving
'Cause you told me
that the stars are mine
You didn't mean,
didn't mean it
Hey, don't color my heart
Blues and grays
Don't tell me
that I'm not okay
Don't color my heart
'Cause I'll make it through
CHARLES: Looking for the money
I supposedly gave Eric Woodall?
You want to save me the trouble
and just admit what you did?
Now, where would be the fun in that?
Fine. Keep playing your games,
but this time, you're gonna lose.
Why, because you think
you convinced Woodall to give me up?
Yeah, he came to see me.
Said you tried to get him
to turn me in.
What I said was,
you're an arrogant bastard
who's spent his life
manipulating people.
And you're the loser who only cares
about competition. (GRUNTS)
- Not my fault you can't beat me.
- I can this time.
Oh, I don't think so, pal, because...
(INHALES SHARPLY)
He turns on me, I turn on you.
If you're talking about 12 years ago,
let me remind you,
- we were both part of that deal.
- Yes, we were.
All three of us were,
you, me, and your brother.
- You leave my brother out of this.
- Not a chance.
And you don't leave
this Woodall thing alone,
by the time I'm done,
all anybody will know
about 12 years ago
is you gave me a tip
and made sure your little brother
profited from it.
I didn't give you shit.
You tricked me into giving you
inside information
and then blackmailed me
by giving Marcus money
he didn't even know was dirty.
That may be the truth, but they're never
gonna hear it from me.
I'm afraid they just did.
SEAN: Hi, Charles.
- Sean Cahill. Nice to meet you.
- Who the hell are you?
I'm the guy from the SEC
that isn't in your pocket.
- I asked Sean to follow Woodall.
- Couldn't. No authorization.
But I had no problem getting
authorization to follow you.
Which is howl knew
when to turn this on.
You're wearing a goddamn wire?
For someone
whose favorite movie is Wall Street,
- that's got to be pretty embarrassing.
- Son of a bitch.
You may have gotten the better of me
12 years ago, Charles,
but this time, you didn't.
So remember what it feels like,
because I know I will.
Harvey, this isn't over.
Words spoken by
every loser I've ever met.
HARVEY: See you around, pal.
Two for two.
He didn't touch my balls.
DONNA: Black, two sugars,
splash of vanilla.
How do you know
that's how I take my coffee?
The same way
I know you're not taking that job.
You know I'm not taking that job
because I came into work today.
No, Mr. Specter.
I knew you weren't taking that job
the second you walked away
from me the other night.
I told you I know people better than
they know themselves.
Well, what did you do with Tina?
Oh, I had Big Bertha reassign her.
- To who?
- Do you really care?
- Not a bit.
- Good.
Here's the deal.
I will take a bullet for you.
And I don't mean that literally.
But what you do for me is,
when I need something,
you give it to me.
It's not just a one-way street.
Will you also do some
actual secretarial work?
Take a look at what I did
with your calendar there, hotshot.
Holy shit.
When'd you get that done?
Hmm. I told you
I'm not like every other secretary.
I'm Donna.
Then let's get to work.
But for the record,
I don't take vanilla with my coffee.
You will after you taste that.
- Oh, my God, this is awesome.
- When will they learn?
(EXHALES)
Perfect timing.
- And what are we celebrating?
- Our win.
"Our win."
- I like the sound of that.
- Me, too. Where were you?
I'll get into that in a minute.
I want to talk to you for a second.
What is it?
Rachel, you know I told you I loved you
from the second I met you.
- Well, you loved my pencil skirt.
- I loved your face.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
You're the most amazing woman
I have ever met,
and you're not just beautiful,
but you're sweet
and caring and kind,
- and brilliant, and tenacious.
- Mike, are...
Are you doing
what I think you're doing?
(CHUCKLES)
I called your father today.
And then I went to get
Grammy's ring cleaned.
Oh, my...
I don't want to go 40 years
wondering why I didn't
do this one day sooner.
(SIGHS)
Rachel Elizabeth Zane,
I love you...
And I always will.
You're my whole life.
(SIGHS)
Will you marry me?
Yes.
- Yes?
- Yes.
(LAUGHS)
Here.
Oh, my God.
It's beautiful.
She wore it every day
for almost 60 years.
(SOFTLY) So will I.
(BEEPS)
(PHONE LINE RINGING)
- MARCUS: What's up, dickhead?
- What's up, loser?
Hey, Harvey. Good to hear from you.
Whatk going on? Everything okay?
Yeah, everything's okay.
I just haven't talked to you in a while
and wanted to see how you were doing.
I'm great. Katie? good.
The kids are good. Everything3 good.
Great. That's exactly
what I wanted to hear.
You sure there's nothing going on?
Nothing. Like I said, I just haven't talked
to you in a while, and I miss you.
I miss you to o, Harvey,
but unless you got
something else, I've got to go.
- The kids are in the bath.
- Nothing else.
Love you, Harvey.
I love you, too.
(BEEPS)
. HEY-
Listen, I was thinking
about what you said,
about me pitying you.
And I don't.
Nothing could be
further from the truth.
I think you're one
of the most amazing women
- I've ever met, and just because I...
- I'm leaving you, Harvey.
What?
This isn't working for me anymore.
Donna, I know how you're feeling,
but you just went
through something huge,
with being on trial, and, uh...
You need to give it time.
You can't just quit.
I'm not quitting.
I'm going to work for Louis.
Donna.
Donna, please.
I love you, Harvey.
Walk this empty
northern hemisphere wide
And the kingdom it came,
well it all fell down
It all fell to dust
Watch it all fly around us
Oh, while you were sleeping...
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English