(HARVEY READING)
I have a Iist here
of the signing bonuses
of the top three associates
who have come into this firm.
An advance, plus my salary,
will cover my tuition.
Those numbers don't add up.
Summer associates work as Iawyers,
and I can do the same.
It's an offer Ietter.
We're investment bankers.
Ourjob blows yours out of the water.
Harvey, Stephanie Liston just called me.
She said they just brought Mike in
for questioning.
You're a dirty Iawyer,
and now you're on my radar.
I'm tired of putting the people
I care about in jeopardy.
I called Jonathan Sidwell
this afternoon.
I took the job.
Mike Ross never went
to Iaw school.
I knew it, and I hired him anyway.
- I still can't stay, Harvey.
- I'm sorry.
Give me permission to go.
- You going to work or school?
- Both.
You think have time
for some of this? (LAUGHS)
Maybe if you loan me your limo.
Hmm.
- I'm sure we can work something out.
- Mmm-hmm.
(CHUCKLING)
- I thought you were getting dressed.
- I did get dressed.
- And then you got undressed.
- I got a little hot.
Yes. You did.
Come to think of it, it is
getting a little warm in here.
Mr. Gillie.
Mike Ross. Nice to meet you.
You should know I'm only doing this
as a courtesy to Jonathan Sidwell,
but I'll tell you right now,
the answer is no.
- Good.
- Why good?
Because a yes is always
so much better when it starts as a no.
You're a confident young man,
but I know what my
distribution centers are worth.
- You know what they're worth to you.
- This is what they're worth to me.
This is bigger than I expected.
- I've heard that before.
- Okay, fun time's over.
I'm not interested in selling
to someone who I don't know
where they're coming from.
Let me tell you
where I'm coming from.
I do my homework.
These centers are a beacon
to every predator out there
that you haven't laid the groundwork
to get out of the DVD business.
Sounds to me like where you're coming
from is trying to scare me.
No. No, I'm not trying to scare you.
I'm trying to help you.
They're circling and you know it.
You don't do this,
you might as well
send out an invitation
asking for a hostile takeover.
- This number can't be real.
- It is.
Then, what the hell are you going to do
with my distribution centers?
I'll be happy to tell you that
five seconds after I buy them.
Walter, I know you want
your people to be okay,
and I give you my word they will be.
But these centers...
Have become a headache.
And you need cash for when
those predators come knocking.
Let them knock.
I'm not answering the door.
No, you're not hearing me.
If you don't raise enough money,
they're coming in whether
you answer that door or not.
That offer's good for another hour.
You are not my hair-gelled
partner in crime.
I haven't used hair gel
since ninth grade.
I was trying to avoid the frizzy look.
Where is he?
Uh, Donna said that he had a morning
meeting outside of the office.
- And where's Donna?
- Right here.
I prefer to appear
at the exact moment I'm needed.
I wish I could say
the same for Harvey.
- Oh. Well, Harvey has a very...
- Save it.
She may have been born yesterday,
but I know that morning meeting
doesn't mean morning meeting.
Everyone knows that.
It's just not my place to say it.
Not mine, either.
He did it yesterday, too.
When he resurfaces,
tell Specter Pearson wants to see him.
I used mousse in high school.
It was the '90s.
- Was it?
- I heard that.
- Did you bring me lunch?
- Chen Dynasty.
- How many egg rolls are in here?
- Two.
- You closed Gillie.
- Oh, I killed Gillie.
Well, I hope you told them
no mushrooms in the lo mein.
- You never told me that.
- I didn't think I had to.
Aren't you supposed to be
the one taking care of me?
Ugh. How am I supposed to do that
when there are mushrooms
in my lo mein?
Why do I keep you around again?
Deal memo on Friedman Technologies,
engagement letter signed by Stillman,
and oh, two front row tickets to Daft
Punk for you and Rachel tonight.
But why do I keep you around?
Mike, Sidwell's in there waiting for you.
Be careful, okay?
He's not in a good mood.
It's okay. You know why?
Because I killed it with Gillie.
- Hey, Amy.
- Yeah?
Eat the mushrooms.
They're good for you.
Screw you.
- Morning.
- Where have you been?
Oh, you know, just getting Walter Gillie
to sell us all of his distribution centers.
Oh.
- What the hell are you doing?
- What does it look like I'm doing?
I'm sending a message.
We're not a convent.
We're in business to make money.
And this deal does that.
You did this deal to retain
those people's jobs.
- And to make us 30 percent.
- We're a hedge fund.
If we don't make 50 percent,
we might as well buy time
shares and hope for the best.
That's bullshit.
This deal is solid.
No, what's bullshit is you've
been here for three months.
All you've done is hit singles
and I need a goddamn home run.
- Jonathan.
- I don't want to hear it.
I want you to get your head
out of your ass.
Stop trying to save people's jobs,
and start making us some real money.
Or go back to being a lawyer.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
- I heard you wanted to see me?
- That was three hours ago.
If you knew what I was
doing three hours ago,
I don't think you would
have wanted to see me.
I know what you were
doing three hours ago.
Well, then, you should
have come on over.
Maybe you should try having
some morning meetings yourself.
Don't you worry
about my mornings.
What you need to worry
about is Logan Sanders.
What? He drive one of his father's
subsidiaries into bankruptcy?
The opposite.
Boy got his shit together.
Max is retiring,
and Logan's taking over.
- Let me guess, he wants a meeting.
- He's got one.
- With you. Tomorrow morning, 10 a.m.
- Great.
Push it a week.
Harvey, this kid considers
himself a young lion.
He's going to want to make his mark.
And the easiest way for him to do that
is to change lawyers.
Maybe. But the last thing a lion wants
is to have his dinner handed
to him on a silver platter.
You're gonna give him a hunt.
Did you think of that all on your own?
I'm extra sharp. I haven't
worked a minute all morning.
See, that's funny because
I was late from all the sex.
Get the hell out of my office.
(IN SING-SONG VOICE)
Bow-chicka-bow-bow.
Look what the cat dragged in.
- And you're wearing a vest.
- Here it comes.
Here what comes? Maze! tov.
Congratulations on your special day.
- That's a good one.
- DONNA: Harvey, leave him alone.
- He looks better than you do.
- Thank you, Donna.
You're welcome.
Oh, and Mr. Peanut called,
and he said he'd be happy
to lend you his top hat.
Are you two finished?
I could go all day.
- I think the vest had enough.
- Yeah.
So, you come all the way down
here just to let me know
that you were right about Walter Gillie?
I came all the way over here to tell you
lam done playing in the kiddie pool.
- I'm listening.
- I'm going after a whale.
- I think I'm in love. Let's go to war.
- That's the thing.
We're not going to war.
Mike, the second whoever it is
finds out that you've got five
percent of their company,
we're going to war
whether you like it or not.
They're not going to find that
out because I don't own five percent.
Do I need to give you
a tutorial on the procedure?
- You start by buying shares.
- I know what the procedure is, Harvey.
- How many shares have you bought?
- None.
This phrase,
"I know what the procedure is"?
I don't think it means
what you think it means.
Well, as inconceivable
as it might be to you, Harvey,
- I'm actually not going in hostile.
- What are you talking about?
I'm talking about approaching someone
to buy their company
in order to keep it alive
instead of selling it for parts.
You're offering someone
hugs and rainbows.
I'm offering someone
the chance to survive
and banking that they'll take that chance
rather than give up.
You don't have the money, do you?
No. I don't. But even if I did,
I wouldn't use it.
Oh, welcome to what every person
who doesn't have money has ever said.
Oh, I get it.
You think this is the meeting
where you make fun of my idea.
No, no, no, no, no:
This is the meeting where you realize
that my idea is happening
whether you like it or not.
- Where's the fun in that meeting?
- Oh, the fun?
It's all right over here
on this side of the table.
Hey, I'll give you a chance
to get acquainted with the new reality.
I'll be in my office.
Get back to me by the end of the day.
Wow. Looks like
our baby boy's all growns up.
Hey, tell me, sweetheart,
you guys validate parking?
Oh, yeah. Sure thing.
I've got it right here.
And how many hours
is that good for?
What's it matter? We're just going
to charge it back to you anyway.
You know my secretary is, like, so much
younger and fitter and funnier than you?
Start running.
Did he say "fitter"?
- What did you find out?
- Woodall's resurfacing.
- Me, too. When?
- Next week.
- Me, too. Where?
- SEC.
- Me, too. Title?
- Supervisor.
- Director.
- Me, too.
I just threw that in to make sure
you weren't yes-maning me.
- Talk to me.
- I found out the name
of the man Woodall's sending after us.
Jeff Malone.
Jeff Malone is a beast.
Well, the only way to beat a beast
is with a bigger beast.
I need to get in there
before everyone else
and let Harvey and Jessica know that
I had the foresight to look for it,
the cunning to find it,
and the balls to stop it.
- Then, you take on Malone.
- Next stop, name partner.
Pearson, Specter, Litt.
Okay, you know what? Just... Let's not
count our chickens before they hatch.
But just for shits and giggles,
say it one more time. Leave out Specter.
Donna, I got Paul Porter's
annual restructuring proposal.
Can you file it under
"I don't give a shit"?
What about Mike?
You want me to have Rachel prepare
a dog and pony show for him?
- That won't be necessary.
- Why not?
Harvey, I need to talk to you right now
about something very important.
Harvey, wouldn't it be necessary?
Because you don't beg
the girl to go out with you.
You wait. She'll call.
- That's not even...
- Excuse me, hold on a second.
- Um, what if they don't call?
- They always call.
Well, what about people
who aren't you?
- You mean you?
- Yeah, of course I do.
If they don't call, then they don't call.
But once they smell your desperation,
they won't respect you
and you'll never get
what you want, anyway.
I'm sorry. Did you want
to talk to me about something?
It can wait.
Come to think of it, tell Rachel
when she's back from school,
she can have the rest
of the day off.
Harvey.
You do that, you might as well send Mike
a telegram that says,
"I'm not putting any thought
into your idea."
Yeah, might as well.
Okay, are you sure that's
how you want to play this?
Didn't I just answer that?
You did. But this isn't about
whether or not Mike calls back.
This is about you not letting
Mike call the shots.
I let him call the shots, all he's going
to do is shoot himself in the foot.
Maybe. But if this was
anybody other than Mike,
- you wouldn't be acting like this.
- Bullshit.
I don't let Tony Gianopolous
push me around.
You think I'm going to let Mike Ross?
No, of course you don't
let Tony push you around.
But I've never seen you
mock one of his ideas.
Yeah, because his ideas
aren't ridiculous.
This is Mike's first big idea.
And I just told you
his first big idea sucks.
And if you use Rachel
to deliver that message,
- this is going to end badly.
- Okay.
Thanks, Mom, but I think I'm going
to keep playing ball in the house.
Okay. Act like a child
who doesn't want to be told what to do.
But Mike's a client and you need
to start treating him like one.
Donna, the next time I need help
figuring out how to treat a client,
- I'll let you know.
- Okay, great.
Harvey, what can I do for you?
There's a Jeff Malone waiting
in the conference room,
wanting to see both of us.
Any idea who he is?
I've run into him before.
He's a hot shot at the SEC.
- What do you think he wants?
- Let's go find out.
Ms. Pearson.
And you must be Harvey Specter.
- I'm Jeff Malone.
- I know who you are.
- My question is "why are you here?"
- You seem hostile.
You investigate publicly traded
companies. We're not publicly traded.
No, but your clients are.
- Hence his question and our hostility.
- Our?
We tend to stick together when an
uninvited guest interrupts our dinner.
Well, I didn't bring any wine.
But, uh, when I go, I hope
you'll be happy that I dropped by.
Yeah, I doubt that.
So, why don't you tell us which client
you're here for and be on your way?
All of them.
Since when does the SEC
go around intimidating law firms
by going after their clients?
They don't, but they will when Eric
Woodall starts there next week.
He comes at our clients
after what he did.
This time, he won't get fired.
He'll end up in jail.
Except it won't be
Woodall who's coming.
- It will be him.
- Exactly.
Listen, I'm going to be getting
a vaguely-worded assignment
with the not-so-vague agenda
of getting up your clients' asses
with the full power of the SEC.
And when they ask why,
and they always ask why,
I'm going to be expected to tell them that
it's because they're clients of your firm.
Why are you telling us this?
Because he doesn't want
to work for Woodall.
He wants to work here.
I've always heard
how good you were.
It's nice to see it's true.
Anyway, here's the thing.
I'm really tired of
being a public servant.
And more importantly, I've always
thought that Eric Woodall was a, um...
Oh, shit, I'll just go ahead
and say it. He's a dick.
Finally, something we can agree on.
Seems to me the only thing
left for us to agree on, Harvey,
is my starting salary.
(LAUGHS)
I'm just kidding. I'm sure all your
new senior partners get paid the same.
Before you start picking out floor
patterns for your new office,
I'd like to discuss this
with my partner first.
I'd expect nothing less.
Oh, uh, just one more thing.
I haven't been formally given this
assignment yet, so I have no conflict.
But in one more week, I will,
which means this offer will be gone.
Is that a threat?
I would never threaten someone that
I want to be in business with, Jessica.
It's just the truth.
I like him.
- How did it go with Harvey?
- It didn't.
What do you mean "it didn't"?
You're the only man here
who can take on Jeff Malone.
- How could he not see that?
- I didn't bring it up.
Louis, winter is coming.
I know. And I'm the Night's Watch.
But right now, we need to be patient.
- Patience is not your strong suit.
- Well, today, it is.
Because if there's one thing
that I've always known
is that you don't call the pretty girl.
You wait for her to call you.
Louis, I'm seeing someone.
I'm happy for you, though I have no idea
why you're saying that right now.
Katrina, trust me. They're going to find
out about Jeff Malone soon enough,
because he's going to come calling.
And when he does, they're going
to come right over to me.
Like him all you want,
I'm not hiring him.
- Why not?
- Why do you think?
Because you don't like making decisions
staring down the barrel of a shotgun.
Jessica Pearson, nice to meet you.
Jessica, the man walked in here
and offered to fight for us.
- If it's not him, who's it going to be?
- The guy in the office next door.
Louis?
Harvey, Louis knows everything
there is to know about the SEC.
He's damn good and you know it.
This guy isn't damn good,
he's a killer.
And he's a prosecutor.
We need a defender.
If I'm in a dark alley,
I'd take the killer over the defender
seven days a week.
And Eric Woodall's going
to put us in a dark alley.
Louis is a known quantity.
And right now, Jeff Malone's
biggest selling point
- is telling us that Woodall is coming.
- Louis sure as hell didn't.
Which means he either didn't know
or he wasn't man enough to come
in here and take the job for himself.
Harvey, do you know why I don't like
being strong-armed into decisions?
Because I'll never be able to trust
the person who did it.
Then, figure out a way
to get someone as good
or hire this guy
and come to terms with it.
Because if it's Louis against
Malone in a street fight,
I'm picking that dude.
Oh. Thank you.
Hey, how'd your meeting go with
the mysterious Harvey Specter?
Being a dick doesn't
make you mysterious.
Well, then, I guess
you're an open book.
You know, I was going to give you
those Daft Punk tickets.
But now, after that,
I think I'll give them to Edna.
Okay. First of all, Edna was 63
when Daft Punk was born.
Really? With that skin?
You know what?
I worked hard to get you those things.
- Why aren't you going?
- I dropped the hammer on Harvey,
which means Rachel's going
to be working all night.
Hey. What are you doing here?
Donna texted me
when I was at Columbia.
Mmm-hmm.
And told me that Harvey
gave me the rest of the day off
because I'm kicking ass.
- He's giving you the rest of the day off?
- Mmm-hmm.
So, I figured we could celebrate
over dinner before the concert.
What? Are you jealous 'cause
he never did that for you?
- Um. No, that's great. You pick a place.
- Mmm.
I'll meet you there. I've got to, uh, just
set up some meetings for tomorrow first.
What about The Little Owl?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Mike, what are you doing here?
You delivered a message,
so, now I'm delivering one.
Pearson Specter
is formally in review.
What did you just say to me?
You want my business?
You're going to have to earn it.
- I have earned it.
- By shitting on my plan?
You don't have a plan.
You're running into a wall
and it's not my job
to crash into it with you.
Crash into it? You didn't even ask me
who I'm going after.
I didn't have to because it doesn't
matter. But go ahead. Who is it?
Gillie Industries.
That's not a whale.
That's a monster.
A man like Walter Gillie
isn't going to listen to a guy like you
offering to save him
with sunshine and rainbows.
That's exactly what you said to me
before I got him to sell me
his distribution centers.
Congratulations,
you got to walk his dog.
That doesn't mean he's going
to let you marry his daughter.
Listen to me.
You want to be my guy?
You stop telling me why I can't do this
and you start figuring out how I can.
I already told you how you can.
You get some money,
start buying some shares,
and you walk in there with a club
and the balls to use it if you have to.
Harvey, when I told you
my plan's happening
whether you like it or not,
I meant it.
I'm interviewing
law firms tomorrow.
You show up with a better attitude and
another move or you just lost a client.
RACHEL: So, you want to talk about it?
Talk about what?
About whatevefs going on
with you and Harvey.
(SIGHS)
Why does everybody think
that I was born yesterday?
I tell you he that he gives me
the rest of the day off work,
you vanish until dinner, and then you're
pissed off for the rest of the night.
- So, it doesn't take a rocket scientist.
- Clearly.
- I meant I love you.
- Mmm-hmm. Nice recovery.
It doesn't get you out
of answering my question.
You really want to know?
I'll tell you.
Harvey was Michael Jordan.
And now it's Lebron's time
and he can't take it.
That's a pretty big accusation to make.
Well, there's more to the story
than you know.
What?
Rachel, come on. I said I didn't want
to get between you two.
What?
Let's just say that you
kicking ass for him
isn't the reason
you got the day off.
- I thought you had law school today.
- I do right after this.
- He told you.
- Did you think he wouldn't?
Look, if you want to send a message
to Mike, go right ahead.
If you want me to send a message
to Mike, tell me when and where.
But please don't ever
use me like that again.
You're right.
I'm what now?
- I shouldn't have done that. I'm sorry.
- Is it April Fool's Day?
No, but don't ever let it be said
that I can't admit when I'm wrong.
Then I will stop saying that.
- Didn't you say you have class today?
- I'm on my way.
What was that all about?
- Just some administrative stuff.
- Administrative stuff.
- You and Rachel.
- I don't want to talk about it.
You mean about how everything
I said would happen happened,
and now you realize
I was right the whole time?
No one likes a gloater, Donna.
Well, then, I guess the Harvey
Specter University of Gloating
is gonna have to shut down.
I can still give lectures
on the weekend.
Do you want to hear it?
You were right.
(SIGHS)
Call Ray. I'm going to go let
Mike know I'm his lawyer.
You're going to push
a meeting with me?
Harvey, Logan Sanders
is here to see you.
HARVEY: First of all, I don't
appreciate you stomping
into my office with an attitude.
Yeah, well, I don't
appreciate being put off,
especially when I know that you never
pushed a meeting with my father.
Your father never went to Jessica
to set a meeting with me.
Then, I assume that next
time I call you directly,
- you'll pick up the phone.
- Logan,
let me give you the ABCs of me.
I don't take meetings. I set them.
And my respect isn't
demanded, it's earned.
That's only two things.
What's "C"?
"C" is for people who show me
they know "A" and "B".
Well, since we're
quoting Jerry Maguire,
all I want is for you
to show me the money.
You just took step number one
towards earning my respect.
- And I dig that about you.
- Great.
Would it be too much trouble for me
to discuss my business now?
Well, I was going to move on
to Crimson Tide, but, yeah, go ahead.
Knock yourself out.
Did you ever hear of a family
called the Winwards?
No. Should I?
In 1950, they were worth
the equivalent of $1 billion.
By 1988, one of them owned
a couple of dry cleaners.
And it didn't happen because
they squandered it.
It happened because
they stayed a dinosaur.
And you don't want
to become a dinosaur.
No. I like to think of
myself as a shark.
- Keep moving forward or die.
- You're talking hostile takeover.
You think I'd be here if I wasn't?
You just took step number two
towards earning my respect.
What's the company?
Gillie Industries.
And I already own 4.9 percent.
Logan, we have to end
this conversation right now.
What are you talking about?
I thought I just earned your respect.
You did, but we have a conflict.
- What do you mean you have a conflict?
- I mean, we have a conflict.
And what are you going
to do about it?
I'm going to go and resolve it.
Well, you'd better do it fast
because I am in on this.
And that means you're either
with me or against me.
And that includes all
$1 billion of my business.
Hey. Prunie?
What is that?
It's a prune smoothie.
I invented it myself.
Rain check.
Louis,
guess who stopped by yesterday
for an impromptu meeting
with Jessica and Harvey.
Please tell me it was Dick Cheney.
Why would you want it
to be Dick Cheney?
Why wouldn't I want
it to be Iron Dick?
Holy shit, I think I know
who you were talking about.
- I think you do, too.
- Is it a certain SEC beast
whose name happens to rhyme
with Schmeff Schmalone?
- Schmess it is and schmess it does.
- Well, schmuck me.
Louis, we have a problem.
What's the problem?
As if I didn't know. (CHUCKLES)
I just got out of a meeting
with Logan Sanders.
Logan Sanders?
- This isn't about...
- About what?
(STUTTERING) Never mind.
What's the problem?
He wants to go after the same company
that Mike pitched me first.
So, what's the problem?
Mike brought it to you first.
- You're obligated to stick with him.
- The problem is,
Mike formally put us in review.
Holy shit. That's why
you're coming to me.
You're going to lose Mike and you want
to know if there's any way around it?
- Is there?
- No. Harvey.
I'm sorry, but you're going
to have to drop Mike.
- What happened with Harvey?
- Nothing.
He had an emergency with Mike.
Fine, but don't you think now
is the time to act for yourself?
No, we have a good plan
and we're sticking to it.
They're stewing on Malone.
And the more they stew,
- the...
- The more leverage we have.
BOTH: Name partner.
And as I've said,
all we need to do is be patient.
Well, patience may be
one of your virtues,
but it is not one of mine.
- I didn't want to jinx it.
- You didn't.
Katrina, this is one of the sweetest
things anyone's ever done for me.
I want to make sure you don't waste
your opportunity to get this.
I promise I won't.
Ah.
What are you doing here?
We shouldn't be seen together.
Well, you had no problem
walking into my place of business.
Why should I have a problem
walking into yours?
Because unless you're here to tell me
that I have the job,
then you're putting
my position here in jeopardy.
How do you think I felt when I found
the man that I'm sleeping with
standing in my
conference room?
Jessica, will you please
lower your voice?
Not only that, but you stood there
with a shit-eating grin on your face
and tried to strong-ann me
into giving you a job.
Are you as turned on
as I am right now? (LAUGHS)
- You're not funny.
- Oh.
Why didn't you come to me
first with this?
Because if I had come
to you with this first,
you would have thought I was
trading on our relationship.
- Aren't you?
- No.
And if we weren't together, I would have
gone to both of you. All right?
So, I went to both of you.
Now, it may not
have been perfect,
but there was no perfect way of doing it
unless I hadn't done it.
Now, that sounds pretty perfect to me.
- What are you so afraid of?
- Do I have to draw you a picture?
I'm not the one that made up the saying
"you don't shit where you eat".
Am I the shit or the food
in this little painting of yours?
Because if we're just a fling,
then what difference does it make
whether I work with you or not?
I didn't say we're just a fling.
Then, if there really is a chance for us,
then why not go for both?
Because I've seen what happens when
things go south between partners.
And I'm not willing to put
my business in jeopardy.
- Your business.
- Yes, my business.
The one that I have fought tooth and nail
to keep together.
The same business that you
strolled into with a shotgun
and said, "Marry me
or I'll start shooting."
Jess, if you want me to apologize
for the way that I asked, then I will.
But I don't ask for things
that I don't want.
And what I want is to work at Pearson
Specter and to keep seeing you.
Those two things are not
both going to happen.
Then, I guess you have to decide
what's more important to you.
What we have
or what you have.
Hey, Mike, there's another
prospect here to see you.
But he's late and his tie is too fat.
Should I let him in?
- You tell her to say all that garbage?
- He didn't need to, Johnnie Fat Tie.
Yeah, I guess I have time
for one more meeting.
Mike, I need to talk to you...
Oh, I'm sorry, sir.
You've missed the pastries.
- I can call you some up.
- Listen to me.
I came down here
because I wanted to tell you if you want
to run through this wall,
I'm ready to run through it with you.
- Good.
- But I can't.
- What?
- What I can do is tell you
I'm ready to run through another one.
- What the hell are you talking about?
- We have a conflict.
Bullshit. Who is it?
- It's not bullshit.
- Then who is it?
- You know I can't tell you that.
- No, what I know is that
it's very convenient that
you suddenly have a conflict
the day after you tell me that my idea
isn't good enough.
I don't find it convenient at all.
But you put us in review, and now,
I have to go with the other client.
I put you in review because
you refused to get on board.
And I just told you I want
to run through another wall with you.
And we still can if you drop this.
And why should I be the one to drop it?
Because they're not going to
and I have to stick with them.
And I'm telling you,
you're going to lose.
Why, because you're
on the other side?
Because their plan is better.
Says the professional bullshitter
who has a brand new vested interest
in me bowing out.
I'm going to let that go.
But if you don't let this go,
I can't represent you
on anything until it's over.
Then I guess we're done here.
You cook?
You come home to this in your kitchen
and that's what you're going to ask me?
Well, I was going to ask you
how the hell you got into my apartment,
but I knew you weren't
going to tell me.
Do you remember when you told me
I should think about taking
some morning meetings?
I can't say that it's
never crossed my mind,
- but you really think it's a good idea.
- Jeff Malone.
Well, he's not my type.
You've got to be kidding me.
Why didn't you tell me yesterday?
Because I wasn't going
to hire him yesterday,
so it was none of your business.
But today, I might.
So, now, it is.
And you want
to know how I feel about it.
You're my partner.
Well, I already told you
how I feel about hiring him.
- This doesn't change that.
- Good to know.
Seems like something else
is on your mind.
He doesn't just want
to work together.
He wants us to keep seeing each other.
And you don't want to risk
the one to have the other.
No, I don't.
- I've been there.
- I know.
Then, you need to figure out
which is more important.
I guess I do.
So, you two have, uh...
Yes.
So, he's seen you naked?
That's usually how
these things work.
Are you picturing me
naked right now?
Maybe.
- Yes.
- Go wash your hands.
And don't spend too much time
in that bathroom.
JONATHAN: Let me get this straight.
You come to me with a killer idea,
and all of a sudden you don't want to do
it anymore because you lost your BFF?
I don't want to do it
because it's not a killer idea anymore.
- Why the hell not?
- Because Harvey has a conflict,
which means somebody already
has a dog in the fight.
- Who gives a shit?
- I do.
Because whoever it is
is already buying shares.
You didn't come in here to give up,
you came in here to get my money.
You're damn right I did.
I give you my money
and now I have downside.
Jonathan, look.
You said you wanted a home run.
You've got to pull out your checkbook
because I can't compete without it.
- You could yesterday.
- Now, it's today.
And you're still going in there,
another banker in a suit,
hoping he'll trust you
based on nothing.
I've got more than nothing.
What the hell are you talking about?
Trust me. I did my homework.
Batter up.
What are you doing here?
I said I'd tell you what we were going
to do with your centers
five seconds after we closed.
- When did we close?
- About three seconds ago.
I guess we better hurry.
All right. What's going
to happen to my employees?
We're going to sell your distribution
centers to a pharmaceutical company.
As distribution centers.
They use your workers. They hit
the ground running. Win-win.
You're a man of your word.
But that's not
why you're here.
No, it isn't.
I'm not interested in selling my business.
I know that.
Because I know why you've thrown
your whole life into this company
and why you chose
the movie business in the first place.
What's your point?
Phillip.
Yburson.
You loved watching movies together.
That's why you started this company
and why you won't let go of what
it's become for any amount of money.
How do you know that?
I told you. I do my homework.
You lost him,
and you needed an outlet.
And that's what this
company is to you now.
- Your family.
- I told you, I'm not selling.
And I told you, they're coming after you
whether you like it or not.
And the difference between me and them
is they want to tear your company apart,
and I want to keep it together.
You don't have the resources to do that.
Yes, I do.
As of an hour ago, I started investing.
So, by this time next week,
I will own 4.9 percent.
I didn't have to tell you that.
And that's supposed
to make me trust you?
I lost both of my parents
when I was 11 years old.
So, I know a little something
about needing family.
Walter.
I can't guarantee you we'll win.
But I can guarantee you that
I will never sell you out.
All right, I'm in.
Listen, Zane, I want that goddamn filing
on my desk nine seconds ago
or you can forget
you ever worked here.
Now, excuse me. I've got to go
be a dick to someone.
Sit down.
(SIGHS)
Is this about you and Mike?
Listen to me. This is
going to be a street fight,
and there's only going to be one man
standing when it's over.
- So, I'm only going to ask you this once.
- You don't need to.
I don't want out. I want in.
And when I said, "You want me to send
a message to Mike?", I meant it.
I was just going to ask
if you were comfortable
getting me coffee in the mornings.
I'm serious. I didn't back down
from a fight with my dad,
and I'm not going to back
down from one with Mike.
Good.
Now, I actually am
going to get coffee.
Great. One sugar, splash of cream,
and don't skimp on the hazelnut.
Too soon.
Instead of failing to be channing,
why don't you do something useful
and get moving on drawing up
a tender offer for Logan Sanders?
Logan? Don't you mean Max Sanders?
No, I keep forgetting that you're
in law school half the time.
Max is retired. It's Logan's show now.
LOGAN: You wanted to see me?
- We need to move up our timeline.
- Well, I'm buying shares as fast as I can.
I'm talking about a tender offer.
The plan is shock and awe.
If we rush a tender offer,
we won't have enough leverage
to force people to vote with us.
It's fine to have shock and awe
when you're the only one in the game.
But Walter Gillie knows we're coming
and he got himself an ally.
How do you know that?
Because I do.
- Your conflict. Who is it?
- I can't talk about it.
- Well, when the hell can you?
- In another hour.
(SIGHS)
You have it for me?
Harvey, you know you can
still get out of this if you want to.
Mike's not going to sign that thing
if you tell him not to.
- It's too late for that.
- (SIGHING) Oh, my God.
Hey. Just the woman
I wanted to see.
Donna, would you happen to have the
measurements to Hardman's old office?
Louis, get out of my way.
- Whoa. What's going on, Donna?
- What's going on?
That bullshit Harvey told you
about waiting for the girl to call?
It's bullshit.
He waited and now it's too late.
Change of plans. Cancel anything
you have. We're staying here all night.
- What for?
- The SEC is coming,
and Jessica's hiring
one person to fight 'em,
and first thing tomorrow we need
to convince her that person's me.
Hey.
- I see you have the movies.
- Mmm-hmm.
I guess that means you've decided which
relationship you want us to have.
I have.
But it's not what you might think.
If you still want the job,
it starts tomorrow.
I do.
Then, tonight is our last night.
We'll see if you still think
that in four hours.
Oh, you want to go three times?
No, I was including one of the movies.
- No.
You finally got yourself an office.
Maybe you forgot but I had an office
before. I just gave it back.
I remember, as a show of loyalty.
Yeah, well, that was then.
This is now.
What you got there, Harvey?
You think you could meet with
Walter Gillie and I wouldn't find out?
No, I knew you'd find out.
I just didn't care.
Then, maybe you won't mind
signing this.
Let me guess.
You want me to waive
the conflict that you still have
after hearing my plan first.
I sure didn't come here
to see your shitty office.
Aren't you supposed to be nice
to the person you need something from?
They're still coming
whether you sign it or not.
But if I don't sign it,
they won't be coming with you.
True.
Of course, if you don't sign it,
it may cause some people to say
you're afraid of me.
And by some people, I mean me.
Of course, if I sign it
just because you said that,
then it might cause some
people to say you baited me.
But I knew you were coming
the second I went
to see Walter Gillie, so...
I went ahead and signed one for you.
- I guess it's on.
- I guess it is.
You think we need
to lay out some ground rules?
Rules? In a knife fight?
I guess somebody ought to yell,
"One, two, three, go."
One, two, three, go.
You know, usually when
someone gets a new office,
you're supposed to
bring them something, right?
Like, an orchid or something?
No? Nothing?
(DOOR CLOSES)
- You signed the waiver, didn't you?
- You know I did.
- I couldn't back down from Harvey.
- Hmm.
And I suppose you
got Gillie on board with your plan?
I wouldn't have needed to sign
the waiver if I didn't.
Hey.
Hey, it's going to be okay.
This thing between me and Harvey,
it doesn't have to affect us.
We won't let it.
I didn't know that Logan Sanders took
over his father's company until today.
What does that have
to do with anything?
- He's Harvey's client.
- Yeah? So?
Do you remember when
I told you that I...
That I once had an affair
with a married man?
It was him.
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English SDH