(HARVEY READING)
Mike Ross never
went to law school.
I knew it, and I hired him anyway.
I still can't stay, Harvey.
I know. I just want to stop
lying to the people I love.
This makes it look
like Forstman's payment
never went to any offshore accounts.
That's forgery.
Which is less of a crime
than what you did.
I had no choice!
HARVEY: Bullshit,
you had no choice!
You could've said no at any
goddamn point along the way.
One thing is for sure.
When all this is over,
I'm gonna fire
the shit out of you.
I went to Robert Zane
and I asked him to give Louis a job.
You want to see if I can break
my partnership agreement.
If you can't do that,
what the hell good are you?
Louis won't be going to Zane.
And neither will you.
I'm here to ask you
to take Louis anyway.
- And why would I do that?
- If you do, I'll owe you one.
Mike Ross doesn't forget anything.
See, the reason
he didn't recognize this
was because
he didn't go to Harvard.
You've been lying to me since
the day Mike Ross arrived.
- I am your friend, Louis.
- No, you're not.
And don't you ever
say that to me again.
You might as well spit it out.
You asked me what I wanted
once before and I told you.
And then, you told me
that I couldn't have it.
Pearson...
Specter...
Lift.
The whole world s
sitting on a ticking bomb
So, keep your calm
and carry on
The whole world s
sitting on a ticking bomb
The silent war has begun
We 're staring down
a loaded gun
No refuge found
on solid ground
The whole world s
sitting on a ticking bomb
Want to tell me what was so important
I had to get back here?
He knows.
I know what you're thinking.
Why didn't Donna tell you?
I'll tell you why.
Because as my first official act
as name partner,
I told her not to.
- What?
- You heard me.
You can look at her as long as you want.
She can't help you.
Because my name is going up there
first thing tomorrow.
- No, it isn't.
- Yes, it is.
But it won't be tomorrow.
I'm not waiting just so
you can have your own...
Louis, I have to sell this
to the senior partners.
I can't just slap your name up there
one morning.
You did it for him.
- I didn't resign the week before.
- I don't care.
Louis, that's enough.
This is going to take time.
And while it does,
you're going to keep this to yourself.
Bullshit. You're just trying to buy time
so you can get out of this.
I'm not trying to buy anything.
We have an agreement.
And this is for your own good.
Well, for your own good,
you better remember
what I'll do if this takes too long.
- Please tell me you had no other choice.
- You know damn well I didn't.
- No, I don't.
- That's because you didn't see him.
All he's ever thought about since
the day he was born was getting this.
So, if I have to choose between giving it
to him and going to jail...
He really threatened that?
He didn't just threaten it.
He was going to do it.
- And what are we going to do?
- We are going to take it.
We give him this,
it is never gonna end.
Harvey, before you say
another word to me,
I want you to think about the fact
that I just ate a big bowl of shit
because you brought that kid
into my house, and I had to take it.
So, you're going to take it.
- Harvey.
- You don't need to say it.
Yeah, I do.
Louis came looking for you
and I didn't know what to do.
He was going to call Sheila
and tell her everything.
- I'd never seen him like that before.
- Donna, this is not on you.
Yes, it is.
He pressed me and I broke.
It doesn't matter,
because he already knew.
- How can you know that?
- Because I know Louis and I know you.
And he couldn't have broken you,
unless he knew the truth already.
So, this is not your fault, and I never
want to hear you say that again.
I should have at least
warned you before you got here.
All that would have done
was antagonize him even more,
because he would have
known you did it.
You did everything
you could have done.
Okay-
We have to tell Mike.
- No, we don't. Not now.
- Harvey.
I'll tell him in the morning.
We just had a huge win and I am not
in the mood to ruin his night.
Louis.
What are you doing here?
- They didn't tell you.
- Tell me what?
Jessica made me name partner.
- But, uh...
- But... But... But what?
I resigned in shame?
Well, that's all changed.
And it's all because of you.
Remember this?
No, you don't.
Because you can't remember
something you never knew.
Cool to the end.
Well, it doesn't matter,
because Donna told me.
And Harvey.
And Jessica.
When I told them that I knew
that you were a fraud,
did they run from you
like you were the plague.
What do you want?
I already got what I want from you.
Name partner.
You must want something else.
Otherwise, you wouldn't be here.
See, that's what
I love about you, Mike.
Almost always a step ahead.
What I want from you is to know
that you're dead at my law firm.
You can't fire me.
Why would I fire you,
when I can break you?
You see, I'm going to bury you
under a mountain of shit so big,
you're going to be
begging me to take it off.
And all you'll have to do
is say two simple words.
The same two words that you let me say
to Harvey and Jessica.
"I resign."
(DOOR OPENS)
Louis.
- What are you doing here?
- Leaving.
That way, I don't have to look at
either one of you two liars.
(DOOR SLAMS)
- Oh, my God, he knows.
- He doesn't just know.
He's a name partner.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
You know.
Yeah, I know. And a little
heads up would have been nice.
I wanted to give you the night.
Well, the night kind of got blown up
when Louis showed up at my apartment
and said he was going to break me.
What do you want from me, Mike?
I want to know how you let him
become name partner.
Would you rather we let
him go to the police?
Come on. I don't believe that Louis
would actually go to the police.
He would.
Because Jessica said he would.
So, if you're here to say that
we can figure some way out of it,
that's not going to happen.
(SIGHS)
He knows.
And it's done.
Did you hear what I said?
Louis came to my apartment
filled with rage,
and he told me he was making it
his personal mission to break me.
Then, you make it your
mission not to let him.
Harvey, he's name partner.
Did I ever tell you
the story about the gym?
I'm really not in the mood
for a story right now.
Well, you're going to hear it anyway.
When I was a kid,
my father put me in boxing camp.
Middle of summer, 90 degrees.
Every day after sparring in that,
they'd make you do
100 laps and 50 pull ups.
They'd push you until you either
threw up or passed out or both.
Anyone could leave at any point,
all you had to do was quit.
- And let me guess, you didn't quit.
- I quit every goddamn day.
I just never said it out loud.
Because no way was I going to give
them the satisfaction of breaking me.
So, I guess it's time for me to drop down
and give Louis 20.
I think it's going to be a little
more than 20, buddy.
I see you noticed I scraped
your little associate title away.
You scraped it away.
Yeah. Just like I'm going
to scrape you away.
- Starting with these.
- Well, Louis, go ahead.
Give me all of the shittiest cases
that you can find.
But I'm telling you,
it's not going to break me.
You overestimate yourself.
Did you think when I said
I was going to bury you in shit,
I meant legal work?
No, no, no.
You're not a lawyer,
which means you must be a paralegal.
And that's exactly the kind of work
you're going to be doing.
Louis, you can't do this.
Everyone out there
thinks of me as a lawyer.
And two days ago, they thought of me
as someone who used to work here.
Look at us now.
Oh, and if you're thinking of crying to
Harvey, that would be a major mistake.
Because this is
between you and me.
What are you doing here?
I'm here because I know you're angry
and you're feeling betrayed,
but I am not going
to let you throw our friendship away.
I can't throw away something
that never existed in the first place.
- Louis...
- Donna, we're not friends.
We never were friends,
because it was all based on a lie.
So you think my giving you this,
and every other nice thing
that I ever did for you,
was just to keep you
from finding out about Mike?
No, I don't.
But I do think, if you had the chance
to take back all those nice things you did
in exchange for me never finding out
about your little secret,
you'd do it in a heartbeat.
You want a chance
to tell me the truth?
Go ahead.
Tell me the truth right now.
And that answers my question.
You know what, Louis?
It was a bullshit question
designed to do nothing
but make me feel like shit.
Mission accomplished.
And now, I'm going to tell you
what I told Mike. You're dead to me.
Okay. You want to hate me? Hate me.
You want to hate Mike? Hate Mike.
But everybody at this firm
can't be dead to you
because sooner or later,
you're going to need someone.
Thank you, Donna.
But that someone isn't going to be you.
Donna said you wanted to see me.
No, I didn't want to see you,
I needed to see you.
I know you're under a lot of stress,
but that was a one-time thing.
(EXHALES)
I don't need you to do that to me.
Louis has already done it.
- What are you talking about?
- Look at this.
He's buried me in paralegal work.
Okay, that's bullshit.
He can't treat you like that.
Rachel, I don't care how he treats me.
All right?
I can take it until he gets over this.
But look at these deadlines.
There's no way I can get all of this work
done on time without your help.
I will do whatever you need.
But, Mike, he is not going to get over it
- unless you make him get over it.
- Rachel, please.
[RUE
The day after what happened
in here happened, I shut you out.
But then, a week later,
you came to my door
and you said you weren't going
to let me go without a fight.
That is not the same.
I wanted you to fall in love with me.
I was already in love with you
and you knew it.
Yeah, well, Louis is a lot of things,
but he's not in love with me.
He used to be.
You just have to
make him remember that.
Okay. The first thing we need to do
is finish all of this work.
Unless, of course, that offer still stands.
I don't recall making an offer.
- You did say, "Whatever I need."
- That's not what I meant.
And then you said,
"Never take no for an answer", so...
- Okay.
- Lock the doors.
- Are you serious?
- Take yes for an answer.
I'm locking the door.
Louis, you sounded urgent
on the phone. What's going on?
I'll tell you what's going on.
I'm back at Pearson Specter.
- What? I don't understand.
- Let me explain it to you.
I just became name partner.
Louis...
(LAUGHS)
This is amazing.
I'm so happy for you.
Okay. Well, you can keep
being happy for me
but you better start being happy for you
because I'm bringing you back.
What? I don't... Oh!
Katrina Amanda Bennett,
will you be my associate?
Louis Marlowe Litt,
I will be your associate. Again.
You've just made me
the happiest attorney on Earth.
When do we consummate
our new pre-existing relationship?
As soon as my new
position is official.
- Wait, why isn't it official?
- I can't tell you that.
Louis, I think I've more
than proven you can trust me.
No, are you kidding me?
You're the only one I can trust.
It's not that. It's just...
Okay, Louis,
you don't need to tell me. But...
...if you won't tell me,
and they won't tell the world,
- something's wrong.
- Katrina, I know what I'm doing.
And Jessica knows what she's doing,
which is playing you for a fool.
Harvey, I was just gonna call you.
I'll save you the trouble. We're bringing
Louis Litt back to the firm.
That doesn't matter.
Because that call was to tell you
I'm hiring him and you owe me.
Flaw
- You calling me a liar?
- I'm not calling you anything,
but you are calling
Sylvia out there a liar.
Oh, no, no.
Sylvia wouldn't tell you shit.
Wrong. One compliment
about her hair
and she told me you gave Louis
the bad news an hour ago.
See you around, Robert.
Harvey, uh, one more thing.
- You do still owe me that favor.
- What kind of math are you doing?
The kind of math that says Jessica
Pearson hiring Louis Litt back
- adds up to shady.
- If that's all you've got,
you can collect your favor when
the clock strikes kiss my ass,
because partners leave firms
and come back all the time.
Maybe, but they don't come back
with their name on the wall.
Oh. I'm guessing he wasn't
supposed to tell me that.
But he did. And Louis Litt
is not name partner material,
which means he must
have something on you.
So, unless you want
me going around town
flapping my big mouth that something
isn't right in your kitchen,
you're going to make
good on that favor.
Sylvia didn't slip up at all, did she?
No, she didn't.
You have your girl Friday, I have mine.
But you can still tell her how nice
her hair looks on the way out.
I'll be in touch.
Oh, you tapping out already?
I thought you'd have a lot
more backbone than that.
I'm not tapping out.
I finished all of the work.
Which I expected
to be done an hour ago.
Come on, Louis, you didn't
expect it to be done at all.
- Just like you didn't expect this.
- What the hell's that?
It's a gift certificate.
What, are you trying
to bribe me now?
It's not a bribe, it's a reminder.
Look, the gift certificate
is for Peter's Steak House.
The place that you and I saved.
Together.
And after we saved it, you told me
that we had something in common.
- Yeah, I don't give a shit.
- Yes, you do.
Because what we had in common
was a love of the law.
You told me that when you asked me
to be your associate, Louis,
and I am still the same person.
And if I found out a woman
that I had something in common with
was actually a man,
I wouldn't keep seeing her.
Okay. What I did is not at all
the same thing.
No, it's worse.
You say you love the law so much,
but every single case you've ever
touched is tainted.
So, you get exposed,
Peter's gets bulldozed.
It wouldn't even be there
to get bulldozed
if you and I hadn't worked together.
All right, genius.
You want to work together?
You love the law so much?
You're going to memorize every case
that I've ever done.
- (STAMMERING) Louis.
- No, get to work
and use that magnificent
memory of yours
for something more than bullshitting
your way through life.
- We have a problem.
- Unless it's urgent, I don't have the time.
Louis is telling people.
- What people?
- For starters, Robert Zane.
Why the hell is Louis even
talking to Robert Zane?
I asked him to hire Louis
after we took back VersaLife.
And you didn't think to tell me that
after last night?
I was handling it.
From what I can tell,
you handled it like shit.
- So, this is my fault?
- Well, it sure as hell isn't mine.
You know what, Jessica?
I'm not the one who wanted to fire Louis,
and I'm not the one
who wanted to deny him clients.
I did that because of
his performance as an attorney.
You antagonized him for years
for your own pleasure.
Tell yourself whatever you want.
You handed out your share of abuse.
You're the one who hired a fraud
and gave Louis leverage.
And I told you Louis would get worse
and you said I had to take it.
Well, I don't care whose fault it is.
He is getting worse
and I'm not going to take it.
Oh, yes, you are.
You're going to take it and you're going
to do it with a smile on your face
until I say otherwise.
And what the hell
are you going to do?
I'm going to clean up this mess,
once and for all.
What do you mean you don't have
diamond encrusted business cards?
Fine. What about
the embossed ivory?
Okay, great. Well, how much would
10,000 of those run me?
Money is no object.
What, are you crazy?
I'm not paying that much.
Unless it comes with a reach around.
Which, by the way,
I'm still not paying that much.
Elite Printing, my ass.
I gave you one simple instruction
to keep your mouth shut,
and you couldn't even do that.
Um, okay. Did you make
an appointment with Norma?
- What?
- To see me.
Did you check
with my secretary, Norma?
Cut the shit, Louis.
I'm not in the mood.
Well, get in the mood.
Because I hold all the cards.
And those cards are getting you
your name on the wall,
but you need to keep this to yourself.
Why? So you can figure
out a way to screw me?
I gave you my word.
Well, no disrespect, Jessica,
but your word means shit.
So, if you want me
to stop telling people,
you better start telling
people yourself.
I told you, in good time.
And I just told you I don't give a shit.
So, I suggest you call a meeting
with the senior partners.
- Those meetings are on Thursdays.
- Well, consider today Thursday.
I told you, I have yet
to figure out how to sell it.
You want to sell it?
I'll tell you how to sell it.
You and Harvey do it together,
you do it like you mean it,
and you do it now.
Got it? Good.
JESSICA: I'm sure
you've all heard rumors
about why we called this meeting.
But that's because it's hard
to keep good news quiet.
We'll be making this
official later this week,
but we are here to announce
our newest name partner,
Louis Litt.
(APPLAUDING)
Thank you, Jessica.
Harvey.
Some of you may be wondering
how this happened.
There's a simple explanation,
and all it requires
is for me to admit something.
I made a mistake.
I never should have
accepted Louis' resignation.
Because not only is he a billing machine
and a damn good attorney,
he has personally gotten me
out of more than one jam.
And there's no one I'd rather have my
name next to than my friend, Louis Litt.
Thank you, Harvey.
Um, even though it's not official,
I already feel like my name's been up
there as long as yours. (CHUCKLES)
And I, um, definitely feel like it's going
to be up there for a long, long time.
HARVEY: A lot of good that did.
Leave it to Louis to take
his big moment like a dick.
- Harvey, calm down.
- Calm down?
I just did exactly what he wanted
and he acted like a dick
and he's not going to stop.
He's not going to stop
because you didn't do what he wanted.
What? Jessica,
I just got up there and kissed his ass
in front of the entire partnership
and pretended to like it.
Exactly. Pretended.
Oh. You want me to actually like it?
- I want you to make him feel accepted.
- Jessica...
Harvey, what Louis wants
is to be accepted.
And like it or not, the person he wants
that from the most is you.
So, you are going to go to him,
you're gonna make nice
and that is how we're going
to put all of this to bed.
You want to tell me
what the hell that was?
Okay. If you'll excuse me, I'm going
to let Jessica handle this conversation.
I have to go kill myself.
- Jeff, I can't do this right now.
- Should I make an appointment?
Because the partners may have bought
that fairy tale about
Louis' triumphant return,
- but they don't know what I know.
- What exactly is that?
That Louis committed a crime,
and then he resigned five seconds
before you were about to fire him.
And now, he's not only back,
he's name partner.
I reconsidered.
Which, as managing partner,
I am entitled to do.
And as someone with a brain,
I'm entitled to come to the conclusion
that Louis has something on you.
Jeff, you said you didn't
want me to lie to you anymore.
And I'm trying like hell not to.
And that's the same thing as lying to me.
- No, it's not.
- Oh, you are one hell of a lawyer.
So are you.
Which is why you're here.
So, I'll come clean.
I can't tell you
the truth about this,
and that's as honest
as I can be with you right now.
Can you handle that?
I can handle it for now.
But I won't handle it forever.
Louis, what are you doing here?
I noticed you haven't
congratulated me yet.
So, I wanted to give you
a chance to make up for it.
Right. Congratulations, we're all so
happy for you. Is that what you wanted?
- Seemed a little disingenuous.
- Then, let me be clear.
I don't mean a word of it.
You really want to talk that
way to the new name partner?
I'm talking to you that way
because you threatened
to throw the man that I love in jail
to become that name partner.
So, you know what, Louis?
I'm sorry that I didn't bake you a cake.
That's too bad.
You didn't do anything for me,
but I got something for you.
Doc review.
Filings to be done in triplicate.
Paralegal work,
since you like doing it so much.
You know I don't like
doing it at all.
You helped your boyfriend
with his work.
You didn't think I'd figure that out?
You know what? I don't care.
You have no authority over me.
I'm Harvey's associate.
Yeah, but I run the associates.
Therefore, I run you.
- I know what you're doing.
- But do you know what you're doing?
Not only do you live with a fraud,
you're just like him.
Pretending to be a lawyer
when you're not.
I'm not pretending to be anything.
I am in law school.
Are you really going to make it through?
You could barely handle the LSATs.
You couldn't get into Harvard.
As a matter of fact,
your boyfriend may be a fraud,
but he's a better lawyer
than you'll ever be.
You have no idea what kind
of lawyer I'm going to be.
Don't I?
You learn from the best
liars around, Rachel.
Harvey.
[RUE
Your father.
Yeah. I know exactly the kind of lawyer
you're going to be.
But until that day,
this kind of work is all you're good for.
(LAUGHING) So, you like
marinated meat, right?
(LAUGHS) Oh, yum.
Okay, wait.
But which one do you make?
- Kansas City or Memphis style?
- Oh, hell. When it comes to ribs,
- I make them every which way I can.
- I am now officially starving.
- Harvey.
- Please, have a seat.
Don't let my law firm
get in the way of your coffee klatch.
Oh, now, now,
don't blame Donna here.
I told her you and I had
some unfinished business.
Already. What, did you pick something
out of your generic favor file?
I've never done anything
generic in my life.
This favor is tailor-made for you.
It's very specific and very personal.
We're in a little dispute
with another firm.
I need you to get them
to back off of it.
Why can't you do it yourself?
Because I don't know the lawyer
on the other side. You do.
Good luck.
- What the hell is he talking about?
- It's Scottie.
- Oh, shit.
- I know.
Scottie doesn't do favors like this
and I don't have any leverage on her.
Yeah, you do.
You're just not going
to like using it.
Hey, there you are. Look, I just finished
memorizing all of Louis' cases.
I had an idea I want to run by...
- Rachel, what happened?
- Nothing happened.
What did Louis do?
It's nothing.
Um, he found out that I helped you
and now he's giving me
paralegal work and I was
a little upset, but now I'm okay.
You weren't just a little upset.
You were crying.
And a little paralegal work
wouldn't do that.
It is not important. And you know what?
I had it coming.
You had it coming?
What are you talking... Rachel...
Mike, I was the one that told you
to make up with him.
- I helped you with the work. And you...
- What did he do?
And you know what, like I lied to him
just as much as you.
What did he do?
It's not what he did,
it's what he said.
What did he say?
Mike, I'm a big girl.
And I can take care of Louis.
This isn't about you.
This is about me and him.
And I'm going to make
him remember that.
You piece of shit. You said
this was between me and you.
It is between me and you.
No, it stopped being between me
and you the second you went to Rachel.
You put her between us the second
you went to her to help you.
God, are you insane? Rachel has never
been anything but kind to you.
I can't even count the amount of times
that she defended you.
And now she tries
to help me just a little bit,
and you rip her to pieces.
No. That's not the help
I'm talking about, fraud.
Then what the hell
are you talking about?
You went to her to help you
lie to me about who you are.
And like the good little lackey that she is,
she came to me and lied to my face.
She did it to protect me, Louis.
Well, good for you.
But when I found out about it,
I felt like shit for the 180th time.
So, I just went to her
and did the same thing. (SIGHS)
You know, Louis, I've just been
memorizing all of your old arguments.
I was actually going to
try and come in here
and use one of them to change
your mind about me.
- Well, it won't work.
- Oh, I know.
Because while I am the same person
that I was before,
you're not.
You're right.
I'm not the same person.
I used to be a man of my word,
but you people taught me that
doesn't mean a thing. So...
When I told you it was
between me and you, I lied.
I found your weak spot.
And you know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to keep hammering on her
until you break.
Jessica.
Please, if it can wait, I've had a long day
and I need to go home.
Too bad. You're staying here
and drafting Louis Litt's
new partnership agreement.
- So, you're piling on, too, now.
- I'm not piling on.
I am giving you
this because it's non-billable work.
And the only reason
it exists is because of you.
This again. Ha.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
I've seen this movie before.
And the reason it keeps rerunning
is because every time
I think I'm done with you,
you and your dirty little secret
rear your ugly heads.
You know what, Jessica?
I have had it up to here with you saying
that this is my dirty little secret.
You could have fired me
when you found out, and you didn't.
No, you decided
to keep me around
because you were more concerned
with beating Daniel Hardman
and keeping your power.
And then, you kept me around
because you didn't want to lose Harvey.
And then, you wanted to use
my secret to beat Harvey
and then again
and again and again.
So, please, Jessica,
why don't you tell me
when the hell does this become
your dirty little secret?
This seat taken?
Hi.
Hey.
Since your message was so cryptic,
I'm assuming this is about business?
I need a favor.
Hey, Scottie.
How are you?
How have you been since you left?
I heard that you took some time off.
Where did you land?
I need you to settle your case
against Robert Zane.
- And why would I do that?
- Because I owe him one.
Harvey, I'm just getting back
on my feet at a new firm.
This case is winnable.
The firm knows that it is
because I told them it is.
I settle, I look like shit.
I know that. But you came to me once
to take it easy on you
with Folsom Foods.
Because you said if I was
ever in trouble personally...
I am in trouble personally.
What the hell is personal
about Robert Zane?
You don't do this for me,
Zane's going to put it
together about Mike Ross.
You selfish son of a bitch.
You said you told me that
because you didn't want to keep lying
to the people you love.
- I didn't want to...
- And now you come to me
trading on the fact that I know
how to get you out of a jam
for doing something stupid and selfish
that drove a wedge between us
before we ever even had a chance.
- I told you the truth.
- After it was too late.
- Scottie...
- I loved you!
I loved you.
And you let some stupid secret
that I would never tell anyone
come between us because
you couldn't trust me with it.
You're right, Scottie.
I don't have a leg to stand on.
But if you don't do this for me,
I am in trouble.
I'm going to recommend
we settle with Robert Zane.
- Thank you.
- But to be clear,
you get to ask me this once.
And I never want to hear
the name Mike Ross again.
- Scottie...
- Once.
You wanted it to be official.
There it is, Louis. It's official.
So, that's it.
People are just going to walk in here
tomorrow morning
like it's any other day
and see it or maybe not see it?
What were you expecting?
A ceremony and a brass band?
We don't do that.
Well, I'm name partner,
and I say we do now.
- Excuse me?
- You heard me.
I want pomp and circumstance
in the fonn of an unveiling.
I'm going home, Louis.
I'm not spending the rest of the night
emailing invitations to an unveiling.
You're going home.
Well, then, I'll send them out myself.
Because tomorrow,
this is happening. 4:00 p.m. sharp.
- I have a meeting at 4:00.
- Then reschedule it.
You don't want me to reschedule.
What you want is to know
that you've earned that.
I have earned it.
But I want you to know it.
Okay, here it is.
You got your name up there
by finding leverage
and using it to strong-ann me
into doing something
that I never would have done.
- See? I knew...
- Let me finish.
It was a stone cold move.
And it's exactly what
Harvey would have done.
Now, if that doesn't tell you that you've
earned it, then I don't know what will.
You still want me to reschedule
my meeting?
Yes, I do.
Fine. I'll be there.
You and Harvey.
Of course, Louis.
We're your partners.
Jesus, you look like shit.
What's going on?
Between drafting Louis' partnership
agreement for Jessica
and Louis' never-ending onslaught,
I didn't get any sleep.
Well, splash some water on your face,
'cause we have to go
to his debutante ball
- and look like we give a shit.
- No. I'm not going.
What do you mean, you're not going?
Now is not the time to poke the bear.
It's too late. The bear is an asshole
and he's not just
taking it out on me anymore.
- He's taking it out on Rachel.
- What?
Yeah, he made it clear that he found
the weak spot that's going to get to me.
And he's going to keep pressing it and
pressing it until I can't take it anymore.
Mike, you are not ringing that bell.
You're damn right
I'm not ringing that bell.
But if I have to go raise a glass
to that son of a bitch,
I'm going to end up
smashing it over his head.
Come with me.
- What are you going to do?
- Enough is enough.
Harvey. You're just in time.
Jessica's on her way down
with the partnership agreement.
Are you here to be my witness?
He's here to keep me
from ripping your face off.
Oh, I see. Now that big brother's here,
you're just going to...
HARVEY: Okay, that's enough.
Louis, you got everything you wanted
and you are done taking it out on him.
Because no matter what you do,
I'm not letting him quit.
Then, I'll just fire him.
- You can't.
- I can and I will.
Because Jessica would rather he be fired
than you all go to jail.
- No one's going to jail.
- See? She knows what's what.
I sign the agreement, he's done,
and then I hire Katrina
back as my associate.
- And that's not going to happen.
- What are you talking about?
Louis, I'm afraid you've made your last
dictate to me as name partner.
I'm not going to let you
take this away from me.
I'm not taking anything
away from you.
You are still name partner,
right after you sign this.
I added a little something extra
after you finished drafting it.
This says I'm co-conspirator
to hiring a fraud.
JESSICA: You are.
You became one the second you used
him to get your name on the door.
I know I'm not a real lawyer,
but that sounds like he is to me.
I am a real lawyer. He is.
- I'm not signing it.
- JESSICA: Louis, here's the thing.
I told you not to tell anybody about this.
And then you went and
you shouted it to Robert Zane.
And then, you made me
tell the partners.
And the capper is
there are about 100 people
waiting to greet you after
the unveiling you arranged,
which won't happen
if you don't sign that.
I can still go to the police.
Yeah, you could, but you won't.
Because you used that little secret
to get where you are right now.
It was the only bullet in your chamber,
and I am taking your gun away.
- You set me up.
- You set yourself up.
Just like you did
with Charles Forstman.
And what I learned from him, was once
you get something that you want,
you will do whatever
it takes to keep it.
So, why don't you go ahead and sign
so that we can get out
to your goddamn party?
JESSICA: You know what's funny?
We've never had a ceremony
when we've changed names before.
But Louis Litt had the audacity
to convene us all here today.
And as it turns out,
his first decision
as name partner is brilliant.
Because a ceremony like this
gives us the chance to reevaluate where
we've been and where we're going.
Perhaps you had
a disagreement with a colleague
or there's some other issue
that's been on your mind.
The point is, with a new name
comes a new beginning.
For me, I'm hoping we can see this
as a chance to wipe the slate clean.
With that said,
here's to our newest name partner,
Louis Litt.
(APPLAUDING)
- Nice speech.
- Let's hope it takes.
It's got a better chance of taking now
that you made him sign the agreement.
That it does.
Speaking of which, when exactly did you
know you were going to do that?
Oh, um... About 15 seconds
after Donna told me he knew.
And you didn't feel the need
to bring me in on that plan?
- I felt the exact opposite.
- What are you talking about?
Harvey, Louis wanted to see you suffer.
If I had told you,
you would have had to fake it.
- And you're a shitty actor.
- Excuse me, but I can act.
No, everybody thinks they can act.
The fact of the matter is,
you're just a pretty face.
Oh? You think I'm pretty?
Pretty stupid.
(INDISTINCT)
I can't believe
it's actually up there.
This firm has changed
names more than Prince.
Who?
You're kidding, right?
Purple Rain.
Raspberry Beret.
I'm kidding.
(LAUGHS)
I almost had to re-evaluate
our entire relationship.
Mmm-hmm. After you were going to go
and beat Louis up for me?
I doubt that.
Mike. Thank you.
Hey, it just seemed right.
- After all, you stood up to Louis for me.
- Mmm-hmm.
And I almost got pummeled for it.
That took guts.
And that's why I love you.
I love you, too.
I wanted to tell you that you were right.
I started this whole thing by hiring Mike.
It's my fault.
Thank you.
But I've been on board long enough.
And it's time I accepted the fact
that it's my secret, too.
So, where do we go from here?
We fight like hell to protect it.
No cake.
What are you doing here, Jessica?
I know you're tired of
waiting for an explanation.
So, I'm here to give you one.
You've given me explanations before.
I want the truth.
Are you ready for the truth?
Because it's not pretty.
There's only one way to find out.
It seems like forever ago,
but it wasn't that long ago at all.
Daniel Hardman embezzled money
from the firm and I covered it up.
Now, make no mistake,
I found out about it,
I confronted him,
and I eventually
made him pay it all back.
But I did cover it up
from the partners,
from the police, from everyone.
I even adjusted
our books to hide the crime.
And being a bloodhound about
these things, Louis found out
and used it as
leverage to come back.
As name partner?
As name partner.
Why couldn't you
trust me with this before?
Because I didn't know
how you'd react.
And I didn't want
to risk losing
everything I had.
(SIGHS)
Jessica,
your secret is safe with me.
- You're late.
- But I come bearing gifts.
Uh-huh. That doesn't look like cannoli.
It's better than cannoli, Dad.
It's the resume of your new associate.
If this is Harvey's way of trying to
make up for the fact
that I didn't hire Louis...
This isn't from Harvey.
It's from me.
And you're going to do this for me.
And I am not going to owe you a thing.
This is what
they're teaching you at Columbia?
- Because that's not how favors work.
- I know how favors work.
You do this and then you want
something from me someday.
But by then, you're going
to understand that right now,
I'm the one doing you a favor.
Because Katrina Bennett
is an amazing lawyer.
I was wrong about you.
You're not like your mother.
You're like your father.
(IN RASPY VOICE)
Come on.
- Oh, that's good.
- That was a good one. (LAUGHING)
That was a good one.
Sounds just like me, baby girl.
I had you fooled, huh?
You did. I can't stand...
Now, let me show you
how a lawyer cooks.
- LOUIS: What do you want?
- I just thought you'd want this.
The associates saved it for you.
No, they didn't.
You saved it for me.
Because you want to pretend
to be my friend again.
Louis, didn't you hear
Jessica's speech?
This is our chance
to wipe the slate clean.
I did hear her speech.
And I know that she sent
you here to say that to me.
No one sent me here.
I'm here because I want to be here.
You see? That's sweet.
But how can I ever
believe a word you say?
I want to know if
you ever thought once
to tell me the truth about Mike.
No, I didn't.
Of course you didn't.
Because we're not friends.
You're wrong. We are friends,
but my professional loyalty
to Harvey comes above that.
Which is why I never told anyone.
Jessica, Rachel, anyone.
So, put yourself in my position
and ask yourself,
"What would you have done?"
I want you to tell me
something else.
(SCOFFS) Yes. Anything.
- Did you ever sleep with Harvey?
- Wait. What?
It's not a professional question.
It's a personal question.
Can you put our so-called
"friendship" high enough
to answer that one honestly?
Louis...
Because it's the only thing I can think of
to know if I can even
begin to trust you again.
Once.
That's my way of wiping
the slate clean.
You can accept it or not.
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English