(HARVEY READING)
You got your name on the wall.
Now, I want the respect
that comes with it.
- Meaning?
- I want one of Harvey's clients.
My clients are my clients.
And you don't get out of my office
in the next three seconds,
something is going
to happen between you and me.
And I guarantee it won't end with you
keeping all of your teeth.
Avery McKemon was the first client
I ever brought into the firm.
They win. Like me.
They know Trevor isn't in the class.
So, they know he couldn't
have been the one to steal the test.
- I'm not going to expel your friend.
- Thank you, sir.
There's just one thing.
I'm going to call Harvard.
Believe me when I tell you,
you're never going there.
Remember this?
No, you don't.
Because you can't remember
something you never knew.
You can't fire me.
Why would I fire you
when I can break you?
You see, I'm going to bury you
under a mountain of shit so big,
you're going to be
begging me to take it off.
DONNA: First of all,
give me that Manhattan
and go get yourself a drink
a man would order.
Come back here in fifteen minutes
and if I still remember who you are,
I'll be shocked.
Okay. So, why are we really here?
I mean, you didn't just bring me out
to talk about Khaleesi.
I did. Paul Porter
says I look like her translator.
- He's a Throner?
- No.
He says I'm a less attractive version
of her translator.
Okay. You're just trying to get me to say
that you're hotter than her.
- Am I?
- You're way hotter.
She has that accent.
- Fair point.
- You know, look.
The reason that I brought you here
is to tell you that I know that
you told Louis that I got Katrina a job.
- Look, I...
- Relax, I'm not mad at you.
But I do remember you being
the person who told me
not to force things
that weren't meant to be.
Rachel. Just because a person
gives advice, doesn't mean
that they have to follow
that same advice.
That's one of the core principles
outlined in The Book of Donna.
Seriously, though, I didn't mean
to tell Louis. it just came out. I'm sorry.
Like I said, it's fine.
He actually ended up asking
if we could be friends again.
- And?
- And I told him that
things would never be the same
between us unless he forgave Mike.
And what'd he say?
He said he couldn't do it.
JESSICA: That's easy,
the jumper over Ehlo.
Wrong, the switch-hand lay-up
over Perkins and Green.
I'm surprised at you, Harvey.
The Ehlo jumper was a game winner.
The lay-up was a statement. "I can do
whatever I want. I own this league."
Are you talking about Jordan
or yourself now?
Is there a difference?
A big difference.
Which brings me to why I'm here.
You can't do whatever
you want, Harvey.
You want me to make things
right with Louis.
He made things right
between Jeff and me.
So, I'm supposed to kiss his ass forever
because of that?
- No, you're supposed to make peace.
- Jessica, I'm willing to make peace.
- But that's never going to happen.
- Why not?
Because Louis is never going
to forgive Mike.
Then figure out a way
to make him forgive Mike.
Donna, how many times have I told you?
I want you out front.
I'm the only associate
with a secretary.
It'd be nice if people
could see my secretary.
Well, then, maybe your next secretary
can figure out where to put this
without coming into your office.
- You're kidding.
- Not kidding.
You didn't forge this?
I am a lot of things,
but I am not a monster.
I would do that to
neither Michael nor you.
Oh, so, he's Michael now.
Well, I'm Donna to him,
he's Michael to me.
Which is what I told
His Aimess when he called.
Wait a second.
You're not kidding.
He signed with me?
Well, technically, he signed with me.
Holy shit, Donna,
we have to celebrate tonight.
Oh, I'm gonna celebrate.
You, on the other hand,
are having drinks with Louis.
What? We've been over this.
Whenever Louis asks to have drinks
with me, the answer's always no.
Listen to the words that I'm saying.
You're getting drinks
with Louis tonight.
- Fairchild's retiring.
- Fairchild's dead.
That's almost as good
as the Jordan news.
- Huh. Not to Fairchild.
- Who gives a shit about Fairchild?
The real tragedy is I have
to get drinks with Louis.
Which is why I got you a secluded
restaurant with a table in the back
where no one will see you.
And you'll call a half an hour in
and say there's an emergency.
Already in place.
And if I can't get through,
then I'll just have the waiter
spill drinks all over Louis.
- You can have that done?
- Oh, please.
I could have Louis held captive
in a Tibetan monastery if I wanted to.
Yeah, I don't think you could really...
Now, get the hell out of your office.
I got work to do.
Hmm.
Excuse me. Can you tell me
where Jim O'Donnell's office is?
That depends. What do you know
about immigration law?
What, are we talking visas, or are you
trying to process a labor certification?
- You know about immigration law?
- Doesn't everybody?
Okay, tough guy. What do you think
about my strategy on this?
Hmm.
- I think it's a winner.
- Why is that?
Because everyone knows
Gonzalez v. State of Maryland
was a kick-ass precedent,
but your case is better.
It was a kick-ass precedent,
but I'm not sure
that my case is better.
- Oh, it is.
- Well, what about Viteri v...
Trust me, it's better. Viteri needed magic
dust and a sympathetic judge to win.
- Have we met?
- No. But I'm Mike, by the way.
Claire.
Are you sure?
Because you look very familiar.
Oh, that's probably because I've been
delivering packages to your office
for the last two months but
you haven't given me the time of day
because you didn't think
I was smart enough for you.
- It's 9:15.
- Wait, that worked?
It's working so far,
but I'm going to need to know
your full story if it's going
to keep working.
I'll tell you the full story once
you give me your phone number.
I'll give you my phone number
when I know the full story.
How about this? I'll tell you
everything you want to know
at dinner tomorrow night.
In that case, I'll show you
where Jim O'Donnell's office is.
Jim O'Donnell's office?
Where do you think I just came from?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
I need you do something for me.
- Okay. What is it?
- Never mind what it is.
Unless you want to go back to whatever
you were doing before I hired you,
you'll be here at 9 a.m.
- This is the address for your car club.
- Oh, yeah, your memory.
I'd remember this even
if I had your memory.
It was right before
our first case together.
You're right. McKemon Motors.
So, this time, be on time
and put your seat belt on.
Because we're about
to take a trip down memory lane.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
HARVEY: Morning, sunshine.
- What are you...
- I think you call it a "prunie"?
Congratulations. Donna
told you my favorite breakfast drink.
But what does that have
to do with the price of tea in Antarctica?
Donna also told me
that you were pissed because
you found out I gave you
a client I didn't want in the first place.
Hmm. And you think this
is going to make up for that?
No, but I think giving you
50% of McKemon Motors will.
What's the catch?
The catch is you and I are
about to take a road trip
to their corporate
headquarters right now.
- You serious?
- I don't joke about McKemon Motors,
and you know that as well as I do.
- To Fairchild.
- To Fairchild. God rest his soul.
Screw his soul. You know how they say
heaven just got another angel?
They ain't saying it now. (LAUGHING)
Why do you keep checking your phone?
- No reason, I just...
- Please, I'm not an idiot.
We've been here 28 minutes and in two
minutes, Donna's going to call
with some preplanned emergency.
- Louis, that's not...
- Harvey, look.
Why do you think I used
Fairchild's retirement
to get you to have drinks with me?
Because you knew I thought
it would never happen.
Because he doesn't have
an heir apparent.
Louis, if you're thinking
what I think you're thinking,
Hardman's not going
to make one of us senior partner.
I'm not talking about one of us.
I'm talking about the both of us
convincing Hardman that
two kick-ass junior partners
are worth as much
as one new senior partner.
Louis, that is the best idea
you've had since I've known you.
Yeah. Here's another one.
When did you come up
with this one?
When you were in the bathroom
wasting seven minutes of our half hour.
(CHUCKLES)
(PHONE VIBRATING)
You have to get that?
No, I don't.
Let's drink to this.
Asshole.
That was Donna, wasn't it?
- Yeah, Trevor, this is so stupid.
- It's not stupid, dickhead.
I want you to see it for the first time
from the middle of the room.
It's your apartment, ass-face.
And don't even think
about giving me a wet willie.
You suck the fun out
of everything.
- Go ahead. Open your eyes, dick-foot.
- Dick-foot?
I was going to say ass-face.
It's all I could think of.
How do you even manage
in the world?
Are you just going to stand there
with your eyes closed
and mock my dick-foot?
I'm definitely not going to open them
to see your dick-foot.
That's a good point. I wouldn't do that
either. Go ahead. Open your eyes.
Wow. Holy shit.
- I thought you were getting a studio.
- Yeah, I was going to,
but then I realized we can't
both live in a studio.
- What?
- Welcome to Casa Evans and Ross.
- Trevor, I can't afford half this rent.
- That's the best part.
Don't worry about it.
I'm going to pay for your whole first year.
No, you're not.
I can't let you do that.
Michael,
I start my new job on Tuesday.
On top of that, I have my friends
and family business on the side.
Are you... That doesn't mean
I'm going to take charity from you.
Look, are you going to make me say it?
It's not charity.
I graduated and you didn't because
you took the fall for something I did.
I owe you.
Ugh!
Okay, I'll think about it.
All right.
In the meantime, think about this.
Uh, no. I can't.
I've got a date tonight.
All right, wow.
Clubfoot? Mustache? All of the above?
First dick-foot, and then clubfoot.
Are words with "foot"
all you've got now?
All right, smart guy, describe her
with one of your SAT words.
- Bigfoot.
- That's what I'm talking about.
- For the record, she's really hot.
- Mmm-hmm.
Let me get this straight.
Instead of promoting an existing partner,
you want me to make both
of you junior partners.
Well, not make us.
We've earned it.
Earned partnership status?
That's a pretty bold statement
coming from two fifth-years.
Not just any fifth years.
I mean, we're the best
fifth years this firm has
ever seen, and you know it.
May I inquire whose idea this was?
- It was both of ours.
- It was Louie's.
That's generous of you
to give him credit.
It was generous of him
to come to me with the idea.
The truth is, I wasn't going
to make anyone partner.
But I do admire your gumption.
So, here's what I'm willing to do.
I will advance one of you
if you prove to me
which one it should be.
Oh, no, see, that's the whole point.
We came in as a package deal.
You came in with a proposal.
I'm giving you a counter,
and it's take it or leave it.
What sort of proof
are we talking about?
Let's just say McKemon Motors
is in play and landing them
could go a long way
to making your case.
No way. We're not going...
All right, Daniel.
You want McKemon?
I'll get you McKemon.
LOUIS: We're going to McKemon
Motors, not your senior prom.
Why can't we just take
the car service?
Because we're going
to an engine manufacturer.
We need to show up
with a bad-ass car.
How about this little
bad boy right here?
That's no good.
- Why the hell not?
- Because it's not just the two of us.
What do you mean?
You son of a bitch.
You said you and I are going up there.
You lied to me.
Because if I didn't, you would
have never agreed to come.
- There is no way I'm going.
- Yes, you are.
I don't care if I have to tie you
to the roof. By the time we get
to McKernon, you and Mike
are going to work your shit out.
I can't believe you did that.
- The plan was to present a united front.
- And we did and he didn't go for it.
- Then you stabbed me in the back?
- I didn't stab you in the back.
- I took what he gave us.
- He didn't give us anything, Harvey.
- He pitted us against each other.
- Louis,
we've been pitted against
each other since day one.
What are you talking about?
How many of the 50 associates
we started with
do you think
are going to make partner?
I don't give a shit
about the other associates.
We toasted to making
partner together.
I don't make the rules, Louis.
Hardman does.
And as much as we say
he's an asshole,
I respect him for at least
telling us the deal out loud.
You want something out loud,
I'm gonna give you something out loud.
No way on earth am I going to let you
land McKemon Motors.
Nowhere to run to, baby
Nowhere to hide
Got nowhere to run to, baby
- Hey, what the hell?
- What the hell what?
This isn't a joy ride, Louis.
You don't want to talk,
you're going to sit in silence
until you're ready to talk.
Well, you can make me sit
in silence all you want,
but you can't make me
work it out with him.
- Then, what can, Louis?
- Excuse me?
You worked it out with Donna.
And Rachel.
You lied to Malone for Jessica.
What's it going to take
to work it out with me?
Mmm-hmm.
Well, I forgave those people
because they were victims infected
with the disease known as Mike Ross.
And now, I'm stuck in the car
with patient zero.
Okay, Outbreak. Patient zero
is the first person
actually infected with the disease,
not the disease itself.
And for your information,
I'm stuck in the same car as you.
At least you don't have to look
at the back of your own stupid, fat,
balding head.
- What's so goddamn funny?
- You two are finally talking.
I think you earned a little music.
I know you're no good for me
But free of you,
I'll never be, no
- That's it?
- Yeah.
All you have to do
is pick one of two characters.
And whichever character I don't pick
is removed from film history forever.
- It's like they never existed.
- It's a piece of cake.
Okay, Han Solo or Indiana Jones.
- I'm out.
- What's the problem?
You just said it was going
to be a piece of cake.
The problem is you just picked the two
greatest characters of all time.
- You're right about that. I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
Let me start with something
easier for you.
- Butch or Sundance.
- Mmm. Check, please?
(GIGGLING)
Yeah, we're done.
No.
This is really nice.
Yeah, I'm having a really good time, too.
So, when do I get to hear
the answer to what you do
- besides being a bike messenger?
- Who says I do anything?
Look, Mike, there's nothing wrong
with being a bike messenger.
But I'm serious about my life.
I'm not going to law school just to
cash out. I really want to help people.
Like, bike messengers
don't help people?
No, not in the way that a man I want
to be in a relationship with does.
Well, then, today is your lucky day.
I knew it. Where do you go?
Mmm-mmm. You first.
Where do you go?
- NYU.
- Columbia.
- I win.
(mum-nus)
- Good morning, Jessica.
- Daniel. I still haven't received...
This year's budget. I was just
on my way to give it to you.
And I thought you hadn't gotten around
to it because you were too busy
- pitting Harvey against Louis.
- You disapprove.
I don't mind a little
healthy competition.
But I do mind the empty promise
of partnership.
What makes you so sure
there's no reward at the end?
The last time we discussed this,
you said Harvey wasn't ready.
And you said Louis wasn't.
Well, I'm giving them both
the chance to prove it.
- So, partnership is on the table.
- Partnership was already on the table.
What makes you so sure
it's going to be Harvey?
Because Harvey will do
whatever it takes to win.
If doing whatever it takes is the criteria,
my money is on Louis.
What are you talking about?
I think we should continue
this conversation in my office.
(MIKE CLEARING THROAT)
Hi, I got a delivery
for a Zoltan Freastmeisterson.
I'm afraid there's no one
in this office with that name.
- I'm afraid you're mistaken.
- Really?
Because I'm willing to bet that there's
no one on this planet with that name.
Okay. Fine. If you could just point me
towards Kumquat McGillicuddy's office,
I'll be on my way. Because I certainly
did not bike down here
with two fictitious deliveries just to tell
you what a great time I had last night.
Good, because I have
a lot of work to do.
So, if you could please just hop on
that little bike of yours and...
- NATHAN: Claire?
- Yeah.
When you're finished flirting
with Quicksilver here,
you might want to get down to I.N.S.
Hector Suarez just got taken in.
Shit. His visa's expired.
They're going to send him back
- to the Dominican Republic.
- Wait. Um, maybe I can help.
- No offense. I don't know how you can...
- No, no, Nathan,
he's not just a bike messenger.
He's in law school.
- Really? Where are you in law school?
- Uh, Columbia.
And he happens to know visas
better than either one of us.
- Well, I really can't pay you, so.
- Um, I don't need any money.
- I just want to help.
- All right, Columbia, be my guest.
We've got a hearing
Tuesday morning, 9 a.m.
Mike, that is amazing.
Thank you.
Oh, no. Don't thank me yet.
I haven't even done anything...
Um, this might not be relevant, but
I actually saved Kumquat McGillicuddy's
life this morning. So...
I'm gonna go do some work.
CLAIRE: Thank you.
- Mr. McKemon.
- Harvey Specter.
Mr. Specter, would you mind telling me
why I have two different
Pearson-Hardman lawyers
on my schedule today?
I don't know, but after this,
you won't need to meet the other one.
- You're cocky.
- I'm right.
You're also traveling a little light.
Where's your PowerPoint presentation?
- I don't need a PowerPoint presentation.
- Why is that?
Because every lawyer in the city
has tried to dazzle you,
and you're still looking
for a date to the big dance.
Because they don't know
what you're looking for.
What exactly am I looking for?
Loyal'!!-
You're right.
I built this company
from the ground up.
And everybody that started with me
is still here.
And I know why.
You don't downsize in the bad times,
they stick with you in the good times.
And no other lawyer
has figured that out.
Not a single one.
Well, I'm the one, Avery.
Which is why I know you don't want me
dumping you for a bigger
client down the line.
How do I know you won't do that?
Because that's not the way I work.
Well, it's a hell of a nice sentiment. But
how do I know you're not full of shit?
I'm glad you asked.
Because here's my
PowerPoint presentation.
Okay-
I have a hearing tomorrow
against Fletcher Engines.
You win that, you're my lawyer.
LOUIS: Okay, just don't change lanes.
Don't change lanes.
Don't do it! Great, you know what...
This is ridiculous.
You drive like a savage animal.
- Louis, be a man and suck it up.
- Suck it up?
I'm sitting in the death seat.
Fine, I'll pull over and you can sit
in the back with Mike.
Okay. I'm not sitting
in the back with a fraud.
And before you even think of it,
you're not putting him
- up here and sticking me back there.
- Then, what do you want, Louis?
Because there is no way in hell I'm
letting you behind the wheel of this car.
It's crystal goddamn clear.
You and I sit in the back
and he chauffeurs the both of us.
Whoa. No. Even if Harvey
would agree to that...
Shut the hell up. You're not talking,
you don't get to refuse.
I'm not refusing, Louis.
I don't know how to drive.
Holy shit.
- You wanted to see me?
- Uh, yes.
I heard you did well
with Avery McKemon.
Well, then, you heard wrong.
Because I killed it with Avery McKemon.
- Congratulations, Harvey.
- Thank you, Daniel.
You're welcome.
Unfortunately, we can't represent
McKernon Motors after all.
Why not?
Well, it turns out Fletcher Engines
wants to sign with us.
Because they found out
I'm about to land McKemon.
Yes. And they're three times
the size of McKemon Motors.
Well, I don't care how big they are.
I'm not dropping my client.
Yes, you are.
- This was your plan all along.
- Of course it was.
- It's how the world works.
- I don't give a shit how the world works.
- I gave my word to Avery McKemon.
- Watch yourself, Harvey.
I haven't gotten where I am
by watching myself, Daniel.
And I don't appreciate being
used as a stalking horse.
Well, you may not appreciate it,
but let me remind you,
you work for me.
And I'm giving you the chance
to show me you understand that.
Let me remind you, you said
partnership was on the table.
I'm going to hold you to that,
and so will Jessica.
Hey, fart taster. I thought
you were coming over.
What, nothing? It's a classic.
I'm implying your job
is to literally taste...
Hey, Trevor, I'm
in the middle of something
- so I'll come over later. Okay?
- In the middle of what?
That girl I told you about,
she, uh, she interns at a legal clinic
- and I am, uh, helping her with a case.
- Dick-foot gave you homework?
Okay. First of all, from now on,
her name is Claire.
And second of all,
this is important, so...
Dude, what the hell
are you talking about?
I might have told her
that I'm in law school.
(CHUCKLES)
Holy shit.
- You will do anything to get laid.
- I'm not trying to get laid.
I really like this girl,
and I have zero chance
with her if all I am
is a bike messenger.
Yeah, well, you're definitely
going to have no chance
if she finds out
that you lied to her.
Trevor, I don't want
to talk about this anymore.
You don't really want
to talk about anything anymore.
- It's about the apartment, isn't it?
- Yes, it's about the apartment.
Okay, you want the truth?
I haven't given you an answer
because of Grammy.
You think I didn't know that?
Then, you also know
she's never forgiven you
for what happened in college,
and she is never ever going
to let me to live with you.
Then, explain to her that this is my way
of making up for what I did in college.
- That is never gonna work.
- You know what, Michael?
If you're going to do all of this
for some girl you just met,
maybe it's time you stood up
to Grammy for me.
How did it go against Fletcher Engines?
You cut 'em off at the knees
or put 'em in the ground?
They put me in the ground.
And on top of that, it was
in front of Avery McKemon.
- You lost in court?
- I didn't just lose, I looked like a fool.
Harvey, what happened?
The general counsel for Fletcher Engines
knew every move I was going
to make before I even made it.
How could he?
Because Hardman
must have tipped him off.
- You really think he would do that?
- I wouldn't have yesterday,
but I sure as hell do today.
- Well, then, you have to go to Jessica.
- And say what?
Hardman's Managing Partner.
She's not.
I don't have any proof, and I never will.
- Well, then, what are you going to do?
- I don't know,
but I have less than 14 hours to dig
through 1,000 pages of patent law.
Ugh!
If only there was somebody in the office
who was an expert on patent law.
Donna, I am not going to Louis.
He'll never help me.
Well, that's too bad.
Because if you can't figure out
how to patch things up with Louis,
then you don't deserve
Avery McKemon or that partnership.
What's all this?
Um.
A grandson can't order in
and set a table for his grandmother?
A grandson can do whatever he wants,
but the answer to your question is no.
- You haven't even heard what it is yet.
- I know what it is,
because I've been waiting for it
since that kid graduated.
And you are not going
to live with him.
That boy is the reason
you got kicked out of school.
You're the one that told me
to tell the Dean the truth.
Well, that was before I knew
it would cost you graduating.
And he's trying to make it up to me.
He's going to pay for
my whole first year's rent.
That will not make up for putting
your whole life into a tailspin.
- It's a head start.
- No, it's not a head start.
That boy is going to drag
you back down with him.
Grammy, I'm never going
to let that happen!
Goddamn it, I forbid it!
I'm sorry, Michael. I lost my temper.
But I, I know what he does to you
and I know he'll always be the same.
Has it occurred to you
that maybe I'm not the same?
What's changed?
I met someone.
I'm going to figure out a way
to finish school and,
and then, I'm going
to go to law school.
Good. Then do it from here.
What's on your mind, Mike?
You look lost in thought.
I was just thinking
about my grandmother.
We took a train trip to D.C. once.
(SIGHS) We played "I Spy."
That's a nice story, Mike,
but we are not playing "I Spy."
I'll play. It will remind me
of dominating Esther
on our trips to see
our smelly Aunt Frida.
All right, if it will get you
and Mike talking. Sure.
I spy a fraud. Probably never
even knew his grandmother.
All right, goddamn it. You got a problem
with me, take it up with me.
But don't ever talk about
my grandmother again.
Oh, I forgot.
The poor orphan from New York City
who I should feel sorry for
- because he never learned to drive.
- I'm telling you,
- watch yourself.
- Why, because I hurt your feelings?
- Louis!
- I don't care.
For all I know, you're probably
not even an orphan.
Louis.
It sure as hell wouldn't be the first time
a con man tried to make that claim.
- That's enough.
- No, it isn't.
Yes, it is.
Pull the car over right now.
I'm going to beat the shit out of him.
- Hey, you got a minute?
- Oh, wait. Let me just turn my back
- so I can give you the right angle to...
- You were right.
We should've stuck together.
I get it. You need my help
because you got your ass
wiped in court this morning.
You're right. I did get
my ass kicked this morning,
- but it wasn't a fair fight.
- What are you talking about?
Hardman accessed my computer
and fed the other side my game plan.
Okay, I'm still waiting for the part
where I'm supposed to give a shit.
Hardman did it because I refused
to dump McKernon for Fletcher
after I gave him my word.
And why should I help you when
you couldn't live up to your word to me?
I did live up to my word.
We went to Daniel.
- Oh, bullshit.
- No, it's not bullshit.
I welcomed your idea with open arms.
And by the way, when he asked
whose idea it was, I gave you the credit.
You see, Harvey,
that's the part you will never understand.
I didn't want the credit.
I wanted us to be a team.
- Then let's be a team right now.
- You don't want to be a team.
You want me to help you get McKemon
so you can make partner.
I want you to help me so I can keep
my word to Avery McKemon.
And when I become partner,
I'll keep my word to you.
What the hell word is that?
That someday, what you wrote on that
napkin goes up on the goddamn wall.
You seem to have done
a lot of work here, Mike.
- Oh, it's no big deal.
- It is a big deal.
Mike found a loophole
in the Immigration Act of 1975,
- and it's going to blow you away.
- I don't know about that.
But it may help Hector Suarez
stay in the country.
That's great. And you're more
than welcome to, uh, stay and watch.
Unfortunately, Claire,
I need you to run back to the office.
Marshall called in sick, and I need
someone to handle the walk-ins, so...
Okay-
- Call me. Tell me how it goes.
- Yeah.
(DOOR CLOSING)
What the hell are you doing? That's...
Going to keep Hector Suarez
in the country?
Yeah.
Yeah, nothing's going
to keep him in the country.
So, what I'm going to do
is buy him some time
so he can get his affairs in order
and then I'm going to
give his children a chance to stay.
(SCOFFS)
I'm just...
I'm sorry. Are you jealous
of me and Claire, or...
NATHAN: Hey, look, I'm not jealous.
And I was waiting for her to leave
- to save you the embarrassment.
- Embarrassment of what?
- That's good work.
- I'm not talking about the work.
I'm talking about
your bike messenger by day,
law student by night bullshit.
All right, you don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, what are you going to tell me next?
Your roommate is a stripper
who's in medical school?
Tell me right now.
I call Columbia, your story holds up.
That's what I thought.
Forget who I am and take
a look at that folder.
- This is a man's life.
- Don't touch me.
If you know what's good for you,
you'll stay the hell away from Claire.
HARVEY: Daniel.
Did you know that some of these species
can live up to 200 years?
Fascinating. Did you know Fletcher
Engines is picking up the pieces?
- I guess congratulations are in order.
- I'm not here for a pat on the back.
I'm here to tell you,
you're making me partner.
Partner?
I never said signing McKernon
was the key to making partner.
All I said was landing them could go
a long way toward making your case.
Bullshit. You said partnership
was on the table.
And I said I was going to hold you to it.
And I'm going to right now.
You don't hold me to anything.
But I did say partnership
was on the table. And it is.
Just not for you.
What are you talking about?
Well, I can't very well
make you partner after I just
told Louis I'm making him partner.
What?
You don't get it, do you?
This isn't about bringing in business.
This is about figuring out
who would do whatever it takes.
- I did whatever it took.
- You didn't do a thing.
You had the chance
to triple our business
- and all you had to do was take a knee.
- You mean bend a knee.
Yes. That's exactly what I mean.
But you're an arrogant little boy
who would rather win than get in line.
Well, what the hell did Louis
do to get in line?
He did whatever it took.
Please get away from me.
Nathan told me everything.
Wait, please.
Let me explain, okay?
No. Explain what?
That you're a sociopath?
I'm not a sociopath. I'm the same guy
that you hit it off with.
No, you're not. You lied to me.
Yes, I am. And I didn't mean
to lie to you, okay?
- I was going to tell you the truth.
- Then, why didn't you?
Because you said you wanted to be
with a guy who was doing something
- good with his life, and I wasn't.
- So, what?
Now, you're here to tell me
that all of a sudden,
you want to dedicate your life
to helping people
- or some other lie like that?
- It's not a lie.
And what I did would have
helped Hector Suarez.
- Yeah, but you only did it...
- Claire, please, you have to believe me.
After I met you, I decided
to get my shit together.
I am trying to get my shit together.
Okay, Mike. You know
what I hate more than guys
who don't have their shit together?
It's guys who lie about
getting their shit together.
Claire.
Louis, fill up the tank.
I'll be back.
Well?
Well, what?
You heard what he said.
Fill up the tank.
Yeah, I did hear what he said.
He said, "Louis, fill up the tank."
Well, where I come from,
it's people who didn't go to college
who fill up gas tanks.
Yeah. And where I come from,
if you take another step...
Oh, the tough kid from the city
is gonna beat my ass?
Louis, I'm telling you right now.
You ruined my life.
You ruined my firm.
Louis!
(CHOKING)
(COUGHING)
(SOBBING)
- HARVEY: You son of a bitch.
- Wait, Harvey.
Tell me right now you weren't the one
that gave Fletcher Engines
my game plan.
Hardman told me he wasn't going
to make you partner, anyway.
And once he offered it to me,
all I had to do was...
Sell me out.
How is what I did any different than
you going after McKemon Motors
in the first place?
If you don't understand that
on your own, you never will.
So, from now on, you stay on your side
of the yard, I'll stay on mine.
No, Harvey, listen to me.
You told me you would fight
to get our names on the wall
once you got on the other side.
I can do the same for you.
Did you hear what I just said?
I don't want you doing shit for me.
Oh, so, it would have been okay
if you were the one who got there first?
It would have been okay if you'd gotten
there first fair and square.
Because then I would have believed you
when you said you wanted to be a team.
I do want to be a team, Harvey.
That's why I helped you after.
No, you don't!
You don't want to be a team.
You just want to have it both ways,
because you're a disloyal rat. You always
have been and you always will,
no matter what it says on your door.
Well, like you said, we've been pitted
against each other since day one.
You asked me how many
of the 50 associates we started with
would make partner.
Well, you know what?
I don't give a shit about the other 49,
because I'm the one who did.
I'm the one who did.
And now, you get the hell out of my face
because I have work to do.
You know he did that on purpose, right?
Did what on purpose?
He asked you to fill the tank
because he knew what you'd do.
Knew what I would do?
What about what you would do?
He knew that, too.
- Louis.
- You never even said you were sorry.
I am sorry, Louis.
I'm sorry that I lied to you.
I'm not a con man, Louis.
Every single other thing
I ever told you was true.
You want to know something
that I've never even admitted to myself?
I never learned to drive for the same
reason I never went to law school.
Both my parents were
killed in a car accident and
ever since then, I've never been able to...
Get behind the wheel.
And then Harvey gave me
a license and I took it.
You were 11 years old.
I mean, you must have felt so alone.
I thought you said you didn't believe
I was an orphan.
I looked it up.
I had to once I found out that
you never went to law school.
You mean once you found out
that I'm a fraud.
You're not a fraud, Mike.
You just never went to law school.
Okay, Frazier, you get a grape.
Ali, I got you a fruit punch.
You two work your shit out?
I'll take that as a yes.
Let's get the hell out of here.
- I should never have lied to her.
- Oh, screw her, man.
If she doesn't like you for who you are,
she doesn't deserve you.
It's not Claire's fault.
It's mine.
I know you're into her
and everything, but trust me
there are plenty of other fish
in the sea.
You don't know that.
For all you know, I'm never going
to meet another girl like her again.
- (SIGHING) Michael.
- Okay. Trevor,
if I'm going to have to listen
to whatever you're about to say,
I'm going to need a joint first.
Come on. I thought you were trying
to turn your life around.
I'll turn my life around tomorrow.
But tonight, I'm a bike messenger, so...
- Dude?
- Trevor.
All right. Fine.
I know Grammy doesn't want
you living here,
but you can crash
here tonight if you want.
Donna!
Is something wrong?
Why would something be wrong?
Because I don't believe
you've ever been in my office before.
No, nothing's wrong.
And I know it's not my place,
but I'm here to tell you
that I think you're making a mistake.
Is this about me not giving
people off for Columbus Day?
You know this isn't about that.
Harvey laid it on the line with Daniel,
and you didn't have his back.
Donna, I've had Harvey's back
since the day I met him.
For your information, when I found out
what Daniel was up to,
I had him guarantee
partnership was on the table.
And then you let him
give it to the wrong man.
- That is on Harvey, not on me.
- What are you talking about?
Daniel was worried
that Harvey couldn't put the firm's
best interests ahead of his own,
and Harvey proved him right.
Or maybe you're just
telling yourself that
because you don't
want to stand up to Daniel Hardman.
Donna,
there's a reason why you are
where you are and I am where I am.
And that is because
one of us sees the bigger picture.
You knew about Fletcher Engines?
What I know is that
Harvey's time will come.
And if this little incident
gets him to think about
other people for a change,
then I'll take it.
You're up early.
I'm up early because
I couldn't sleep.
Where were you all night?
You know where I was.
I was staying at my new apartment.
- I thought we'd settled this.
- You settled it, I didn't.
(SIGHS)
- I'm telling you, that kid just...
- Grammy,
for as long as I can remember,
you've been calling him
that kid or that boy, or worse.
His name is Trevor,
and he's my best friend.
I'm going to do this thing
with or without your blessing.
But it sure would be nice to have it.
Okay, Michael.
I'm not going to lie to you
and pretend I approve. But...
You're a grown man
and I respect your decision.
- I love you, Grammy.
- I love you, too.
Thank you. I believe
that's all I need to know.
Thank you for your time, Ms. Pearson.
I will wait to hear from you.
Oh, one more thing.
Does your father know
you came to me to for a job?
- I, I...
- Did you really think
I didn't know you were
Robert Zane's daughter?
Is that why you're interviewing me?
Because if it is, I would like to remove
myself from consideration.
If you don't want to work for your father,
that's your business.
I'm hiring you because
I like what I see.
Hiring me?
You start Monday,
if that's not too much trouble.
I will be the first one in.
Aren't you going to ask me why I don't
want to work with my father?
I know why.
I have a dad just like yours.
- He has his own law firm?
- He's a surgeon.
But it's the same damn thing.
(SIGHS)
- How are we on time?
- We're perfect.
But I'm not going in there.
You two are.
What are you talking about?
I said I was giving you 50% of McKemon.
I didn't say I was keeping the other 50%.
Oh. So, you finally realized they need
an upgrade in representation.
Easy, Frazier. You'd still be out cold
at that gas station
if I hadn't saved your ass.
Okay, I would have
gotten out eventually.
Not from where I was standing.
I'm slippery. I told you,
I wrestled in high school.
- I checked on that, he did.
- See?
And now you're fighting for him?
Okay, I guess my job here is done.
- Wait, where are you going?
- I'm taking the car back to the city.
Then what the hell
are we supposed to do?
Ray's waiting on the other
side of the parking lot, isn't he?
He'll drive you two back
when you're done.
Wait, you know what? I have a better
idea. How about you take Ray,
we take the car, and I teach Mike
how to drive on the way home?
- You'd actually do that?
- Yeah, I would.
- HARVEY: No way.
- You don't trust me?
I don't trust you as far as I can throw
you. You're a goddamn fraud.
- That's what I said.
- Harvey, seriously. Come on, I promise.
Okay, I know you will.
Louis, you make one dent in this car,
Mike's back on the street
and your name's off the door.
You think he was serious
about what he just said?
Come on.
LOUIS: Well, I'm just a little nervous
because I feel like I drank
that power drink and it has
a lot of sodium in it.
LOUIS: Actually,
it's like drinking a hot dog.
LOUIS: But, um, the doctor says
it raises my blood pressure.
MIKE: I'm gonna need you
to let me do the talking in there.
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English