(MIKE READING)
You're good with me working
on the takeover with Logan?
As long as we don't let
that affect this...
We won't.
I do always get what I want.
And what I wanna do with this company
is strip it down, flip it over...
- That's enough. We're done.
- You're right. We are.
When I told you that our relationship is
now purely professional, I was serious.
What's not purely
professional about lunch?
Unless you mean the sex
that will be following lunch?
Phillip. Your son. You lost him.
And that's what this company
is to you now. Your family.
I lost both of my parents
when I was 11 years old.
So, I know a little something
about needing family.
Since when does the SEC
go around intimidating
law firms by going after their clients?
They don't, but they will when Eric
Woodall starts there next week.
(DOOR CLOSING)
(SIGHS)
- MIKE: Another all-nighter?
- Yeah.
- Work or school?
- Work.
- What were you working on?
- You know what I was working on.
I'm so sorry, but I'm so tired
I have to go get some sleep...
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- ...before I go back to the office.
Hey, I haven't seen
you in two days.
- Give me five minutes.
- Okay.
But I can't be responsible
for anything that I say.
Wow. Okay.
In that case, is Logan going
after another board member?
- Nice try.
- Mmm.
- Is he running out of cash?
- I can't tell you that.
Did you love him?
How long have you been
waiting to ask me that?
You know, just when you were
at your weakest and most vulnerable.
I did love him.
But I don't love him now.
- I love you.
- Mmm.
Who ended it?
- Does that matter?
- It does to me.
I ended it.
Now, do you have any other burning
questions, or can I go to sleep, please?
Um, let me see.
What's the most expensive
thing you ever shoplifted?
Were you a mean girl?
Are you interested in taking
a pole dancing class?
You know what?
We'll get into that later.
Sweet dreams.
God, enough about you.
I want to talk about me.
- We were just talking about you.
- Not enough.
All right, fine. Let's talk about Harvey.
So, guess what he's been up to.
What?
He found the master tapes
for his father's solo album.
He's working on buying them.
He's been trying to find them
ever since he lost his father.
Oh, I see why you're telling me this.
You're trying to humanize Harvey
because you're afraid
of what this fight
is going to do to us.
I'm afraid because of what
it's already doing to you.
I'm talking Ali-Frazier.
- Come on, Donna.
- Listen to me.
They started out like brothers,
then they went
toe to toe three times
and Joe Frazier went to his grave
hating Muhammad Ali.
- I didn't know you were a boxing fan.
- I'm a Harvey fan.
So am I.
And that's why I'm giving him my best.
- Thanks for the coffee. (KISSES)
- You're welcome.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
- You're in late.
- I was up late.
Working on my stuff?
Working on a lot of stuff.
What can I help you with?
- I wanted to talk to you.
- About?
Well, when I told you before
that I'm not the same guy
that I used to be, what I meant was
I got caught up in
emotion back then.
I'm not caught up
in emotion anymore.
And?
And that means that I'm going to have
to do some calculated things,
and I needed to know
that you're okay with that.
Why wouldn't I be?
You know why.
Logan, you don't have to come and
have these little check in talks with me.
I am a big girl,
and I know how these things work.
So, just do what you have to do
and stop worrying about me.
Great.
Harvey, what the hell's going on?
At the moment, I'm 18 minutes away
from owning Steve McQueen's
Shelby Cobra.
You know what I'm talking about.
Last time I saw you, you told me
you were going to get me this company.
I just found out
Walter Gillie funded his pension.
- Did you think they wouldn't fight back?
- I expected them to fight.
Right now, we're getting our ass kicked.
Well, what scorecard
are you looking at?
Because we just got them to give up half
their war chest just to stay in the fight.
I don't give a shit
what the scorecard says.
- I want a knockout.
- Well, it doesn't work that way.
It can if you hit them below the belt.
- Logan.
- Save it.
When my father
went up against Carl Icahn,
he said that you waited
till he wasn't looking,
you walked up behind him,
and you shot him in the back.
Walter Gillie isn't Carl Icahn.
I'm not talking about Walter Gillie.
I'm talking about Mike Ross.
I don't care who you're talking about.
That Icahn deal
was completely different.
The only difference I see is that this deal
is against your surrogate son.
So. Are you willing
to do this or not?
You want below the belt?
I'll give you below the belt.
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
Louis, we talked about this.
It's just so weird to see him
in my old office. You know?
It's like when you drive by the house you
grew up in and there's another family
in there and all you want to do is
break in and make yourself soup.
- You know that feeling?
- Well, it depends on the soup.
- Pfft. Mushroom barley.
- Then no.
Hey, did you get him that apology gift
I told you to get him?
Except instead of scotch, I got us
two front row tickets to the ballet.
Oh.
Well, it's the thought that counts.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Louis. Can I help
you with something?
Yes.
You and me, we, uh,
got off on the wrong foot.
Words were said.
Hurtful caricatures were drawn.
And I did some bad things, too.
- Water under the bridge, Louis.
- Well, no. Not to me.
See, um, I once was told
that actions have consequences.
And I want to turn things
around by inviting you
to the American Ballet Company's
production of Giselle.
- The ballet?
- Yeah. You and me, tonight.
Well, Louis, I would love
to go to the ballet with you,
I really would,
but I have Knicks tickets tonight, man.
And I... I never miss a game.
All right. I'm going to let it go
that you're choosing basketball
over, uh, Giselle.
But I really need to make this up to you,
Jeff. I, I can't be in the red.
I am always, always in the black.
And I don't mean
that in a racial sense.
Well, now that you mention it,
I could really use some advice.
- About the case?
- About Jessica.
I just pulled Adam Grieves
as opposing counsel.
And long story short,
he hates me.
And I could really use Jessica's help
to run some interference. But...
I'm the new guy, it's only my second
case, and I don't know what to do.
Well, I tell you what I'm going to do.
I'm going to get you front row tickets
to Jessica Pearson's help.
Okay, Harvey.
You didn't bring me here
to make me choke
down these Brussels sprouts.
No, I didn't.
But you are going to have
to choke down something else.
Let me guess.
This is about Walter Gillie.
No, it's not about Walter.
It's about the line of credit
that you're about to stop giving him.
- And why on earth would I do that?
- Because if you don't,
I have a feeling that every
Pearson Specter client
that you currently do business with
is suddenly going to move
their accounts to Chase.
You really want to cripple
his company that badly?
His company's already dead.
He just doesn't know it yet.
That doesn't give you
the right to threaten me.
If I were threatening you,
I'd come right out and say it.
If you don't do this tomorrow morning,
you lose two billion dollars'
worth of deposits.
- You son of a bitch.
- MIKE: That he is.
What are you doing here, Mike?
What do you mean? I just came
for the Brussels sprouts.
You know howl know
how good they are?
How?
Because this is where
Harvey brings bankers
to strong-arm them
into doing some bullshit.
- Don't listen to him.
- MIKE: No, he should listen to me.
I'm Walter Gillie' partner.
And if he cuts off our funding
at any point in the next two months
following this lunch,
then the next time you're talking
about these Brussels sprouts
will be in front of a grand jury.
Oh. And, Vernon,
don't take it personally.
He did the same thing to the guy
from Leeds
at the exact same table
seven months ago.
Louis. I got your memo.
And if you want to get an antique
diving bell for your new office,
it's on your dime.
Okay, that's bullshit, but whatever.
- Um, I'm here about Jeff Malone.
- I'm not the principal.
You two are going to have to work
your shit out on the playground.
But you see, that's just it.
We already did.
Something's not right.
Why are you here?
I'm here because
you need to run interference.
I thought you just said
you worked it out.
No, not with me.
With Adam Grieves at the SEC.
He has it in for Malone.
Louis, I'm glad you two are going to be
walking to school together from now on.
But I hired Jeff Malone
to handle the SEC
not to get me to handle
them for him.
You know, you're always telling me
not to make enemies.
And for the first time since Harvey,
I have just made a new friend.
So, I'm asking you.
Please do it for my friend.
Louis.
If you won't do it for him,
please do it for me.
I just had a very interesting
chat with Louis Litt.
Louis is a very interesting guy.
Did you know he's never
eaten an olive?
I did not.
But I do know you fed him some bullshit.
- That doesn't sound like me.
- Really?
Because he thinks we need
to work together
because there's bad blood
between you and Adam Grieves.
- I don't like to talk about it.
- Of course not.
Because you and Adam Grieves
play basketball every Wednesday.
What happens on the court,
Jessica, stays on the court.
I thought I was clear
about boundaries.
Well, listen. If that's really how you feel,
why don't you just tell Louis
that you want to bow out
because you don't trust
yourself around me?
Yeah, I didn't think so.
See you tomorrow.
What happened to going
below the belt?
I went below the belt.
The referee stepped in and
threw a grand jury in my face.
Well, I wasn't asking you to go
below the belt with the company.
I was asking you to go below
the belt with Ross.
What are you talking about?
I'm saying you hire a private investigator
to find every skeleton in his closet,
he wakes up in the morning
and it's all over the front page.
Logan, that's not going
below the belt, that's just nuts.
You're full of shit.
You don't want to do this
because you don't have the stomach
to do it to your boy.
No. I don't want to do it because
we're on a path to win this thing.
And I let you bait me
into doing what I already did
because I thought
you were just a little impatient.
But now, I'm starting to
realize what it really is.
What is that?
Who's full of shit now?
(SIGHS)
- This has nothing to do with Rachel.
- You got there pretty damn fast.
Hey. I asked you to put Mike Ross down
with one punch.
You said you would and you didn't.
So, either do what I'm asking
or I'll do it myself.
- You can't do it, Harvey.
- Yes, I can.
Logan's going to do it anyway.
At least this way, it will be me.
What's the difference
if you hire somebody to look into Mike
or Logan does?
You know damn well
they're going to uncover his secret.
- I don't know that and you don't, either.
- Yeah, I do.
No one's ever found it before.
Because you were hiding it from people
who weren't looking for it,
not from people who are.
What do you want from me, Donna?
I want you to get Mike to give up.
Well, I'm not going to do that
because I know he's
not going to give up.
- How do you know that?
- Because I know.
This is Mike we're talking about.
And if it were anyone other than Mike, I'd
have an article in the Journal tomorrow.
- That's not what you told Logan.
- Because I goddamn lied to Logan.
And it didn't work.
Now, I'm going to do what I have to do.
Well, the least you can do is warn him.
He's on the other side.
I'm not going to warn him.
That's not how it works.
Well, maybe you should
think of something
that won't ruin his goddamn life.
Hey. You ready to get
down to business?
- Yes, I am.
- Good.
I was thinking that maybe
we could do all this over lunch.
It's 10:30.
- There's a lot to discuss, Jessica.
- No, there isn't.
We need to bury them in paperwork.
No, we don't. We just need to come up
with a legitimate reason
why Brooks made that trade.
There is no legitimate reason.
I didn't say there needs to be one,
Jessica. I said we need to find one.
You are taking to defense
like a fish to water.
Well, you didn't bring me in here just for
my genetically superior bone structure.
- Did you?
- Mmm. No.
That's what I brought him in for.
Hey. Sorry I'm late.
I was just getting up to speed.
You brought Louis in.
Of course. Three heads are
better than two.
Unless you have an objection.
(CLEARS THROAT) No.
Are you kidding me?
I would never turn down
a threesome. Right, buddy?
- I hear ya.
- Good.
Because Jessica and I were just having
a little difference of opinion
about what to do next.
Yes. And I'm sure Louis,
the man that I hired,
the man who owes
his very career to me,
will see things my way.
I don't want to step
on anyone's toes.
No, Louis, you're not stepping
on anyone's toes here.
And to be fair, I think
you're an amazing attorney
who doesn't owe anyone anything.
Ooh. Do you work out?
(LAUGHING)
I, I try to stay fit.
Try? Mission accomplished.
(LAUGHING)
Can we get to the point?
Lou... Louis,
Jeff and I have two different approaches
to this case.
Exactly. Go for the knockout
punch or bore them to death.
Well, when you frame it that way...
I can't believe you're using
that old debate team trick.
Farm boy strong,
that's what you are.
Jessica, what debate team trick?
Calling my approach
"bore them to death"
and yours a "knockout punch."
Man, you're really good at this.
Have you done this before?
Sure have.
Look, Jessica,
you can make assumptions
about how this farm boy's going
to come down on this all you want to,
but I think we all pretty much
know he's playing on my team.
Jeff, you're right.
You are right.
And in fact, I think that because you
and Louis see eye to eye on this case,
that you should work together
and I should bow out.
You actually think that bothers me?
Because now, I've got this
farm boy all to myself, Jess.
Just you and me, cowboy.
Just like Ernie and Bert.
- LOUIS: Jeff Malone is in love with me.
- What?
I was just in a meeting with him, and
he started off by patting my shoulder.
He's a jock, Louis.
That's just how they are.
No. He was then rubbing my shoulders.
Then, he touched my arm.
He's all over me.
- Wow. What was the meeting about?
- It doesn't matter. Donna,
his arguments are loaded
with double meaning.
Who invokes the penal code
in an SEC case?
He said "penal"?
Three times. The third time,
we were just talking about
the Glass-Steagall Act,
which is purely civil. And it's...
God damn it, woman.
Do I have to draw you a map?
I mean, come to think of it,
athletes coming out is all the rage now.
And guess what his
favorite sport is. Basket
- ball.
- Oh, my God.
- Shut the front door.
- No, I want to shut the back door.
Okay, Louis.
Now that we've finnly
established his gayness,
why would he think you're gay?
I mean, you're...
(MAKES EXPLODING SOUND)
(HITS DESK)
...straight as an arrow.
I may have said that I eat cock
for breakfast, lunch and dinner.
What?
It was a different kind of cock, Donna.
- It wasn't.
- Okay. Louis.
What exactly do you
want from me?
I want you to tell me
what I should do about it.
I'm going to tell you exactly
what you're going to do about it.
- Nothing.
- What do you mean nothing?
I mean don't give him anything back.
He'll get the message.
It'll pass.
(CHUCKLES)
Donna, I don't think you understand
the power of my sexuality.
What are you doing?
Oh, you know. It's just
a little something for your file.
I have a file?
- That information's classified.
- Wait. Why?
- It's in your file.
- Oh, shit.
There's a secret, it will be
thrown under the table
Harvey Specter.
If you'd be more comfortable,
I have a couple rocks
you could crawl out from under.
Most people would go with some
tall weeds I could hide behind.
Most people don't take
these fights personally. I do.
- That's exactly why I'm here.
- Meaning?
I came here to tell you
something man to man
because I know what
this company means to you.
If you knew what this company meant
to me, you wouldn't be trying to steal it.
Walter, I know how your son died.
Get the hell out of my office.
Not before I tell you that
Mike Ross was a drug dealer.
Bullshit he was.
And I'm calling security,
and if you're not gone
by the time they get here,
theirjob's going to be
getting me off you.
Fine, I'll go. But ask him.
Ask him if he ever dealt drugs.
Ask him if he ever refused
to take a drug test.
Ask him if he was ever
high at work.
I said get out.
And ask him if on the very day he came
to me looking for a job,
he had a briefcase filled
with marijuana.
This is how you do this?
Come here "man to man"
and use my son's death
to take my company from me?
Well, you are nothing
but a piece of shit.
You're right. I am a piece of shit.
But that doesn't make what I'm
telling you any less true.
Walter. What are you doing here?
I'm having second thoughts.
- About the takeover.
- About you.
I'm sorry. I don't understand...
Have you ever been involved
in a drug deal?
(SCOFFS)
Walter, look,
I'm trying save your company here.
And I'm here to find out what kind
of man I'm in business with.
So, I'm going to ask you again.
Have you ever been
involved in a drug deal?
What did Harvey tell you?
Looks like he told me the truth.
The truth is that Harvey can't beat us,
so he's trying to divide us.
And he's using your son to do it.
Just like you used his memory
to make you my partner.
- To save your life's work.
- Another lie from another liar.
You two deserve each other.
We're done.
- Mike, are you okay?
- I don't care who you find.
I want you to hire someone
and get every piece of dirt
there is on Logan Sanders.
- Uh, okay.
- Just do it.
- Where are you going?
- To take care of something else.
Couple of things.
It's Porter's birthday. I got him that weird
zucchini cake he likes from the Bronx.
- What cake?
- Somebody returned Stuntman's chair.
It was missing?
And the "no questions asked"
memo in the kitchen worked.
- What did it stop?
- Ooh. It's not important.
- None of these things are important.
- Oh, and one more thing.
Louis thinks Malone is in love with him.
Your secret's safe.
And you're welcome.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey, Louis.
- Do you have a minute?
- Ah, it's about all I have.
- Because I'm, uh, super, super busy.
- Yeah, well, listen.
I just wanted to check in and see
if you're ready to pull an all-nighter.
I just got all the brokerage tapes in, and
I figured we could just grind it out.
- Tonight?
- Tonight.
Unless you want to go right now,
and just pound it out all at once.
Okay, that's it.
I mean, you have got this all wrong.
Jeff, I like you. As a friend.
Right, Louis. I like you, too.
I think I've made that perfectly clear.
Too clear, man. Too clear.
I mean, enough with
the come-ens already.
- What?
- Yeah. I mean, I... I get it.
You know, we're a perfect match.
You know, if you go that way.
Ebony and ivory.
But I play a different instrument. So...
Oh. Louis. No...
- Look. (STAMMERING)
- It's just...
I just don't want there to be,
you know, just awkwardness.
Especially since Jessica just bowed out
and it's just me and you now.
Right.
(SIGHS)
Well, now that you've seen right
through me, Louis, I...
lam disappointed.
Are you going to be okay?
To be honest, I'm feeling
a little raw right now.
Oh, shit.
(SIGHS) I'm sorry-
Maybe it's best if you just told Jessica
that she needs to step back in.
- Yes.
- Yeah.
Can do. (LAUGHING) Yeah.
- Get up.
- You here to fight me?
Oh, should I wait for you
to turn your back?
That seems to be more your speed.
I'm sorry. Were you expecting me
to give you a call?
No, I was expecting you
to be a human being.
From where I'm sitting,
I was a goddamn saint.
Oh, yeah? How's that?
If I didn't do what I did, Logan was going
to hire a private investigator
- to smear you up and down the block.
- So, what?
You know what.
I shot you in the knees,
so he wouldn't shoot you
in the face. You're welcome.
You know what, Harvey? I'm going
to take a pass on the "thank you"
and instead skip right to the part
where I call you a piece of shit.
You know what? I'm getting
a little tired of hearing that.
And what does that make you
for threatening to bring
criminal charges in that restaurant?
You deserved criminal charges for
what you were doing in that restaurant.
You didn't have a problem
when we did it seven months ago
to the guy from Leeds.
Seven months ago, you weren't
lying to somebody about me.
I didn't lie. And seven months ago,
you were goddamn here.
So, that's what this is about.
You can't stand that I got out of here
and that I'm succeeding without you.
Without me?
I made you.
Without me, you're nothing.
Right there.
That's who you are, and that's why I left.
Bullshit.
Don't lay that on me.
You left because you needed
to feed that huge ego.
E90? Ego?
If I stayed here, you know what would
have been hanging over my head
for the rest of my life.
Which is why I told you to move
somewhere nobody ever knew you.
But you stayed here.
So, that thing is still over
your goddamn head, and I stopped it!
I don't care what you think you stopped.
You're going to go to Walter Gillie and
you're gonna make this thing right.
- It is right. It's over. You lost.
- Nothing's over.
And you're the one
who lost something today.
What are you talking about?
You went personal,
I went personal.
Your father's master tapes?
I've got 'em.
Those tapes have nothing to do
with this deal.
They do now.
Harvey.
- I did this.
- What?
The tapes. Mike found out
about 'em from me.
I've been meeting him for coffee,
just because I wanted
to make sure that everything
was okay between the two of you.
And I never, ever thought
he would do something like this.
- I am so, so sorry.
- It's not your fault, Donna.
- What are you going to do?
- Nothing.
The tapes have nothing
to with this deal.
The second I believe
they do, I'm done.
Ugh. Perfect timing.
Do you want me to get rid of him?
I'll handle it.
What part of "drag Mike Ross through
the mud" did you not understand?
The part where you come off looking
like a rich, vindictive douchebag.
That's not your call to make.
Based on your years
of experience in takeovers?
Here's something they didn't teach you
in snowboarding school,
or wherever the hell you went
before you decided to be a grownup.
Never destroy anyone in public
when you can accomplish
the same result in private.
Meaning?
I severed Mike's ties with
Walter Gillie. It's over.
You know, you told me
that Mike Ross wasn't a threat,
and then he handcuffed
us with a TRO.
You said that you'd take him down
with one blow, and then he got back up.
So, here's something that I did learn
in snowboarding school.
When someone talks shit,
I demand proof.
Proof of what?
Logan, we won.
You don't need to...
Need to what, come off like
a rich, vindictive douchebag?
I want proof that he's giving up his bid.
And if I don't get it by the morning,
I'm going to call my private investigators
and I'm going to finish what I started.
- Where are you going?
- Where do you think I'm going?
To get Mike to sign an
agreement to give up his bid.
- You can't.
- Why not?
Because you were right.
He's never gonna listen to you.
Donna, I know you're feeling
bad about the tapes, but...
- That has nothing to do with it.
- Then what are you saying?
I feel guilty that I told him.
But what he did, that's on you.
And the reason
he's not going to listen to you
- is because you acted like an asshole.
- Excuse me?
He came in here wanting an explanation
for why you did what you did,
- and you threw gas on the fire.
- I gave him an explanation.
Yeah, you told him he was nothing.
You know what?
About a half an hour ago,
you told me this was all your fault.
A half an hour ago,
I was thinking about what I did.
I wasn't thinking
about what you said to him.
It doesn't matter what I said to him.
leaved him.
Harvey.
You said before if it had been
anybody other than Mike,
you would have done what Logan
wanted without blinking an eye.
Well, if anybody other than Mike
had walked in here the way he did,
you would have shown him
the tiniest bit of compassion.
He bought those tapes
before he ever walked in here.
Those tapes were not the first
thing that he told you about.
But you made damn sure
they were the last.
So, you just flagged me
down to call me an asshole?
No, I flagged you down to tell you
that he's not going to listen to you.
But he might listen
to somebody else.
Just heard from Louis.
He has the stomach flu.
So, I'm going to have
to step in tonight.
Oh. That's too bad.
This wouldn't have anything to do
with him thinking
you're in love with him, would it?
No idea.
Feel like sushi?
Jeff, you can play
all the games that you want,
but an all-night review of the evidence
is a waste of my time.
So, why don't you get
a couple of associates
and I will see you in the morning?
Listen.
If you don't want to be here, that's fine.
But I am going to do this by myself
because I don't have
associates do my work.
And why is that?
Do you really want to know why?
Dalton Foster was a con man who
somehow convinced tenninally ill people
to sign over their insurance policies.
Anyway, it was my first big case.
So, I decided that I would get some help
going through the evidence,
just like this.
The help screwed up.
Dalton Foster walked.
Six months later,
he pulled the exact same scam.
Only this time, the problem
was one of his dying clients
had a miraculous recovery.
So, one day, Dalton came up
from behind her
and he beat her to death
with an aluminum bat.
So, am I glad you're here, Jessica?
Yes.
Did I take advantage of Louis?
Absolutely.
I may play games to get us together,
but I never play games with a case.
Never.
You have a minute?
- This must be serious.
- Why is that?
Because you usually just
tell me what to do.
Remember when you said if I want you
to deliver a message to Mike,
I should come to you directly?
You want me to get him to give up.
If Mike doesn't give up tonight,
Logan is going to hire someone
to dig up everything
they can on him.
That's why you went to Gillie.
You had no choice.
That's not the way Mike saw it.
You know, you could have come
to me before you did that.
I'm coming to you now.
HOW do I bill it?
The same way we bill everything.
Say it took twice as long as it did.
Okay, I take it back. My strategy?
My strategy isn't knockout punch.
We should have called it
"needle in a haystack."
- Getting frustrated?
- This guy?
This guy does not shut up.
I now know about his bronchitis,
his problems with his dry cleaner,
but absolutely no explanation
whatsoever about why he cashed out.
Oh, you mean besides being tipped that
he invested in a giant Ponzi scheme.
- Wait.
- What?
It's a call with an analyst predicting
a downturn in small cap stocks
in the next quarter.
Listen.
The Ponzi fund was made up
of small cap stocks.
It's a legit reason for him
to have cashed out.
Exactly what we need
to get the charges dropped.
And exactly the kind of call a junior
attorney might have missed.
So, do you see why we needed
to do this together?
Yes, I see.
What is it?
(SIGHS)
I have responsibilities
that you just don't want to understand.
(SIGHING) No, I don't.
I am the only woman partner
at this level in the city.
If word got out that I hired a partner
that I was in a relationship with...
- What? You'd be disbarred?
- You think this is a joke.
I think you're making excuses
for keeping me out of your life, Jessica.
And I'm calling you on it.
Oh, what the hell is that
supposed to mean?
It means that I'm making you
a promise, all right?
That no one,
no one will ever find out about us.
So, if that's what you're really afraid of,
if that's what's truly holding you back,
then it is off the table.
I'm sorry.
(DOOR OPENING)
Hey.
So, I know we said we're not supposed
to talk about the deal...
Why did you lie to me?
What are you talking about?
When I asked you about you and Logan,
you said that you ended it.
According to this,
you swore it was him.
This is my deposition
from his divorce.
You read this?
Why... Why would...
He looked into me,
I looked into him.
This is looking into me.
You still haven't
answered the question.
Mike, I told you the truth.
Logan was trying to patch things up
with his wife.
And he asked me to...
To back his story. So, I did.
You lied for him.
You loved him that much.
- I told you that I loved him.
- Yeah, but you didn't tell me that.
And I have been sitting here all night
wondering why you wouldn't...
Why wouldn't you tell me that?
I'm going to tell you now.
We had an affair.
We fell in love.
And he wanted to marry me,
and I said no.
And then, three months later,
he had a change of heart
and he wanted to get back with his wife
during his divorce proceedings.
So, he asked me
to help him and I did.
But when he wanted to marry me,
I said no because he wasn't the man
I want to spend my life with.
You are.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- Surprise. What?
- (WHISPERING) You have to go.
- What? What are you talking about?
- She's here.
Logan. ls there somebody
at the door?
Just"
I um“-
I'm from Pearson Hardman.
And I...
I had a few files
to bring your husband.
Where are they?
They're. They're right here. Um...
- Get out.
- Allison, what the hell?
ALLISON: it is 7:30 in the morning.
You think I'm an idiot?
- LOGAN: What are you talking about?
- ALLISON: I know that that's her.
- LOGAN: Oh, God. I told you I'm not...
- ALLISON: Stop lying to me.
ALLISON: At least be a man
and admit that that's her.
LOGAN: I don't even
know that girl. Okay?
And you think that
if I was having an affair,
that I would have it with a paralegal
from my father's firm?
Rachel.
I want you to stop the
personal attacks on Mike.
I know it sounds terrible, but...
And it's how the game is played.
I don't care. I want you to stop.
Look, can we talk
about this inside, please?
- I understand that you've...
- No. Look.
You say you're a changed man.
But what you're doing now, it's...
It's not a change for the better.
It's for the worse.
You told me this wasn't
going to be a problem.
And you stood
right here and told me that you
didn't love your wife.
And then, three months later,
you asked me to lie for you
so you could get her back.
- Rachel...
- You don't have to stop this
because you're some changed man.
You have to stop this, Logan,
because you owe me.
Okay-
Louis.
Listen. I was up late.
I haven't had my coffee.
So, can we talk about
whatever this is in, like, an hour?
I'll be quick.
I ran into your enemy this morning.
You remember, Adam Grieves?
He asked me to tell you that you guys
are still on for ball on Wednesday.
- Listen, Louis...
- Everything you told me was bullshit.
You're not trying to get into my pants.
You're trying to get into Jessica's.
You thought you could move
your way up the ladder,
and you used my friendship
to cozy up to her.
- Louis. That's just not true.
- Well, then, what is it?
Why did you lie to me
to get me off this case?
Tell me what I'm missing here, Jeff?
- That's what I thought.
- Louis, please...
For once, I let my guard down
and believed that someone genuinely
liked me without a hidden agenda.
I will not make that mistake again.
LOGAN: I'm here to see Mike Ross.
What the hell are you doing here?
- I came to see you.
- I have a meeting.
I came to apologize.
For what?
For trying to win dirty.
I can't undo what I've already done,
but I can stop doing it.
I don't want to win that way.
That sounds like something
your publicist would tell Forbes.
Why don't you don't tell me
why you're really here?
You want the truth?
I don't want to hurt Rachel.
MIKE: Walter.
- I have nothing to say to you.
- Walter, please.
- You have 30 seconds.
- Okay. Look. I get it.
I tried to tell you
there's more to the story.
You didn't want to hear it then
and you don't want to hear it now.
But you need to hear this.
Whether you like me or not, I am the only
one in your comer and you know it.
I started this company
with no one to trust but myself.
If that's how I go out,
so be it. We're done.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that because
I'm going to be in your comer, anyway.
I just bought another
two percent of your stock,
which means I'm saving your
company with or without you.
Time's up.
I don't want to see you again.
- Jeff, it's late.
- It's not about us.
- Woodall.
- It started.
How many?
Seven clients, seven subpoenas.
All coming tomorrow.
It's time for you to
start earning your money.
You get me a present?
It's from Mike.
It's my dad's tapes.
He said they're yours.
- You got him to back down.
- No, but I got Logan to back off.
How did you manage that?
That's between me and my client.
You know you could have
come to me first.
I'm coming to you now.
After all is said and done
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English