(HARVEY READING)
Sheila Amanda Sazs,
will you marry me?
Yes, I'll marry you.
When we have kids, world, watch out.
- Louis, I don't want kids.
- Sheila, I'm gonna be a father.
Mike Ross is not coming
back to this firm.
You heard Louis.
He already gave him the job.
I want to know why the hell
you came back.
What matters is that I'm staying,
because this is where I belong.
This makes it look
like Forstman's payment
never went to any offshore accounts,
- and that you never took a piece of it.
- That's forgery.
Which is less of a crime
than what you did.
I had no choice!
HARVEY: Bullshit, you had no choice!
You could've said no at any
goddamn point along the way.
JESSICA: One thing is for sure.
When all this is over,
I'm gonna fire the shit out of you.
I wouldn't be back here
if it wasn't for Louis.
I'll take care of it.
LOUIS: Dear Harvey and Jessica,
I put all of you in jeopardy
for my own personal gain.
Effective immediately,
I, Louis Litt,
am resigning
from Pearson Specter.
Please take care of my home.
Ain't nothing wrong
with this chemistry
with this place for me
Tell me now,
tell me now
Can you show me how,
show me how
To understand,
understand
Give me a second.
You're not dressed for it,
but maybe we can get you
some trunks, go a few rounds.
I think I've already
gone a few rounds.
I need your help.
Anything. What can I do for you?
Clients. I need clients.
Louis, the bylaws say that...
Come on, Harvey. You think
I don't know what they say?
I wrote the bylaws.
Yeah, and who'd you
write 'em for, huh?
Jessica. And she's not gonna
make an exception for you.
- Maybe she'll make one for you.
- She's not going to.
Harvey, do you think
I want to be here?
I tried to get interviews
at six different firms,
and every one of them
said the same thing.
It's a blood bath out there.
Which means if I can't
bring business with me,
I might as well move to Siberia,
because I'm never gonna
find a job in this city.
- Louis...
- Harvey,
I'm not asking for the moon.
Just three companies
that I brought to the firm myself
when they were nothing.
- Let me talk to Jessica.
- Thank you.
Tell me now,
tell me now
What makes a good man,
good man
Harvey, you don't look busy.
Would you like to attend
the International Securities
Law Symposium?
That depends.
Is it in Vegas, Miami or Rio?
- Poughkeepsie.
- Send Paul Porter.
What can I do for you?
I just saw Louis.
- No. He's not getting any clients.
- He just wants three.
Letting them go won't break us.
No, it won't. But it will open
the floodgates for every partner
that ever thought of leaving
and taking their clients.
He's not "every partner,"
and he's worked his fingers
to the bone for both of us.
And he's asking for a crumb.
And I give him that crumb,
and next thing you know,
all the cookies in
the cabinet are gone.
You don't know that.
I do know that instead of talking
about giving Louis' clients away,
you should be working
on keeping your own.
Jessica, I'll find a way to keep VersaLife.
But that has nothing to do with Louis.
- We owe the man something.
- And I'm giving him something.
My phone rings and he gets
a glowing recommendation,
instead of me saying that he left
after committing a felony.
No one's gonna call
if he can't get in the door.
That's on him. Not on me.
Are you sure we should be doing this?
You really want those vultures in
bankruptcy picking through his stuff?
Just, it doesn't feel okay
going through his things.
Rachel, you haven't heard from him.
I haven't heard from him.
If we don't pack up his stuff, who will?
DONNA: I guess you guys
had the same idea I did.
BOTH: Yeah.
- He didn't take that, either?
- No.
I just cleaned it. It was smudged,
and I didn't want to
give it back to him dirty.
He must have been
in such a hurry.
He was in a hurry 'cause
he was ashamed. (SIGHS)
Come on. Let's get this over with.
- Jessica. What...
- Am I doing here?
I'm here to tell you
that I know you know the truth
about Louis' resignation.
- I don't know...
- Yes, you do.
And I'm guessing you didn't like it.
You're right. I didn't.
Because I don't think
that he deserves to be fired.
That's funny, because I think
you both deserve to be fired.
- What are you...
- You knew what he did
and you said nothing.
So, that's why you're here.
To fire me.
No. I'm here to give
you a second chance.
Those don't look like my case files.
They're not. But I didn't come
empty handed. I got you something.
- A job?
- General counsel at Procter and Gamble.
Procter and Gamble?
What is that, a joke?
They're in Cincinnati, which is,
like, American for Siberia.
It's American for number 31
on the Fortune 500
and it's a chance to make a fresh start.
Whose idea was this "chance?"
Her Majesty?
Oh, yeah, I bet she'd love that.
Ship me off and never see me again.
Louis, it was my idea.
And you should take it.
Would you take it?
No way on earth.
You know why? Because this is Rome,
you're a gladiator, and so am I.
Then, be a gladiator. Take this job
and fight your way back here.
I don't have to go to Cincinnati
to fight my way back here.
I can goddamn fight Jessica.
(SIGHS)
See the money, wanna stay
for your meal
Get another piece of pie
for your wife
Everybody wanna know
how it feel
Everybody wanna see
what it's like
I'll even eat a bean pie
I don't mind
Me and missy is so early
Busy, busy making money
All right!
All step back
I'm 'bout to dance
The greenback boogie
You here to pick up your things?
I'm here to pick up
the three clients that are mine.
Those clients, like everyone this firm
represents, belong to me.
And there's nothing you can do about it.
Oh, yes, there is.
'Cause pursuant to the bylaws,
you're required to inform clients
of any attorney's departure.
If you fail to do so,
prior to me giving you formal notice
they're up for grabs.
Well, you wrote the bylaws.
I'll take your word that's what they say.
Oh, I see. You don't think
I can take 'em from you, huh?
Well, I'm the one who brought them in
and answered their call
at 4:00 in the morning
when all you did was take your cut.
Is that all I did?
Yes. And that's why I'm gonna win them,
because I deserve them.
And that's what it always
is with you, Louis, isn't it?
- What you deserve.
- You're goddamn right it is!
And you have some nerve telling me no
after all I've done for you.
What you've done is break the law.
And I'm still willing
to give you a good recommendation.
I don't need your bullshit
recommendation. I need clients.
And if you're not gonna give 'em to me,
you better strap in,
because I'm gonna take them.
Louis. You haven't returned
any of my phone calls.
I don't like contact
during transitional periods.
- But you didn't even say goodbye.
- What is there to say, Katrina?
Well, when you're ready,
I would love to take you out for dinner.
We can't do that.
You're on the other side now.
- What are you talking about?
- I gave Jessica notice.
I'm going after three clients.
- Louis...
- No, no, no. We're gonna go do battle.
And I do not want to put you in the
position to fraternize with the enemy.
You're not the enemy. Louis...
Jessica had me contact
all of your old clients in person.
She what?
You can't approach them.
It's over.
I have to get going.
Louis. I am so sorry.
I didn't want to do it.
Don't be. If it had to be somebody,
I'm glad it was you.
HARVEY: I'm in the middle of a merger.
What's so important that I had
to come down to your shitty office?
This used to be your shitty office.
And after that, it belonged
to six other people,
- five of whom are now gone.
- What's your point?
That things can change
in the blink of an eye.
- Louis.
- Yes, Louis.
It took all of 10 seconds
to scrape his name off the wall.
How long do you think it's gonna
take Jessica to scrape off mine?
What are you looking for, Mike?
Harvey, Jessica sees me
as a huge problem.
The solution is just to get rid of me.
I don't want that to happen, so I need
to solve an even bigger problem.
And you want me to
give you a bigger problem.
I just got back. I need you to give me
the biggest problem you've got.
Fine. Sterling Pharmaceuticals
is merging with Pfizer.
Come on, smart guy.
You wanted to solve the problem,
- you better be able to identify it.
- There is no problem.
They merge,
they only make up 26% of the market.
That's, that's not
over the limit per 10b-6.
Iii]
Shit.
VersaLife puts us over the limit.
We have to drop them.
Unless we figure out
a way around 10b-6,
like I told Jessica I would.
You told her that? Harvey,
no one has ever been able to do that.
Listen to me. You want to make
a splash? Part the Red Sea.
Oh, no.
- "Oh, no" what?
- You have that look on your face
like you want me to have
some emotional conversation
I don't feel like having.
You know what, Harvey? I just came in
here to see if you needed anything.
- I don't.
- Okay. Fine.
Listen, I know that this whole thing
with Louis is upsetting you.
No, what's upsetting me
is you saying you're here
to see if I need anything when
you really want to talk about Louis.
I'm worried about him.
He's in a really bad place.
You think I don't know that?
That's why I tried to help him.
I got him a job on a silver platter
and he threw it in my face.
- And he shouldn't have done that.
- Yeah.
Then, why are you here?
Because I still think
we can help.
- Donna...
- Harvey,
you did a good thing
by getting him that job.
It was the right instinct.
But it was the wrong city.
Yeah, I can't get him
anything in New York.
I'm not talking about New York.
Then, what the hell
are you talking about?
Nice grouping-
How'd you know I'd be here?
Because you go mudding when
you're happy and you come here
- when you're looking to blow off steam.
- Well, I am blowing off steam,
Donna, and I'm not finished. So,
unless you can handle a pistol, do me
a favor, please just leave me alone.
Uh, how do you...
Connecticut Junior Pistol Championship
Finalist, three years in a row.
What years?
Ask me that again,
and I will use this on you.
- Is there anything you can't do?
- No, there isn't.
Including talking Harvey
into getting you another job.
So, where is it this time?
Cincinnati? Minneapolis?
Anchorage, Alaska?
Boston.
- Sheila.
- Yes, Sheila.
You got Harvey to do this for me?
I got him to give you
his word he will do it.
But after you
turned down Cincinnati,
he's not gonna make the call
unless you say you're on board.
- I can't.
- What do you mean, you can't?
Donna, Sheila values strength.
She's gonna see this as me coming
to her at a time of weakness.
Louis, you go to Boston with
the sole purpose of being with her,
she's gonna see that
as a sign of love.
Tell him to make the call.
Okay, Kyle, I think the question
you have to ask is,
"Where do I see myself in 10 years?"
And unfortunately, the answer
is not as a Harvard graduate.
Idiot.
Louis. What are you doing here?
I'm here to take you back.
I... I don't understand.
The way we left...
I don't care how we left it.
Not a day has gone by
that I haven't thought of you.
And I can't hold
it back anymore.
Sheila, I love you.
And I want us to be together.
Louis, this is wonderful, but,
it's just a lot to take in.
To believe that you're
really ready to commit.
How is this for ready?
I'm taking a job in Boston.
- What?
- I quit Pearson Specter.
(LAUGHS) Oh, my God...
I can't believe it.
(CHUCKLES)
- You did all that for me?
- Yes.
Well, I...
- Well, what?
- I got a job in Boston for you.
Louis, did you make that decision
before or after you quit your old job?
- What difference does it make?
- It makes a huge difference.
You don't call for six months.
And then, one day,
you wake up, quit your job
and suddenly, I'm supposed
to fill the hole in your life?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not like that.
- Okay, then, what is it?
- I mean, do you know
how hard it was for me to not call you?
I was trying to move on.
Then, why didn't you move on?
Because I realized that I don't
need New York. I need you.
Louis, geography was
the least of our problems.
No, I know. And I want you to know
that I've come around on that.
You don't "come around" on children.
I don't want them and I'm not going
to change my mind.
You don't have to,
because I've changed mine.
Okay, and I believe
that you believe that.
Well, then, if you... I'm just sensing
that you don't know where I'm...
Louis, when I asked if you'd quit first,
I was asking because
if I, if I believed that you were
really ready to give up children,
I would run into
your arms and never let go.
But if you're doing this
because you're down and out...
But that's just it.
Do you understand
that I was going to change
my entire work schedule
weeks ago for you?
Before all this.
You were going to.
But you didn't.
Sheila, please. You have
to understand where I'm...
It was good to see you, Louis.
Please go.
I see frustration.
You see me getting
my ass kicked by FTC Rule 10b-6.
- And?
- Harvey needs an update
and I don't have shit.
And if you were Harvey
and he was Jessica,
you'd say you're all over it.
I can make that happen.
- Donna.
- I'm all over it.
Send a bottle of Johnny Walker Blue
to Jonathan Palmer
and get him tickets
to the next Sox game.
And then, find out
when his wife's birthday is,
his kid's birthday,
his dog's birthday.
How am I supposed to...
I don't care how you do it.
Figure it the hell out.
Harvey, this is a "thank you" to him.
Why are you so mad at me?
It's not a "thank you."
It's an apology
for you talking me into getting him
to give Louis a job.
He didn't even show up
to the interview.
And what's happening
with our VersaLife problem?
- I'm all over it.
- Yeah.
"All over it" means
that you don't have dick.
Next time I see you,
have something.
(SIGHS)
Jonathan Palmer's in Boston.
Harvey got Louis a job there
because of Sheila, didn't he?
- Yes.
- Donna,
if he didn't show up for the interview
it means it didn't work with Sheila.
Shit. He's gonna be devastated.
- You bring him his box of stuff yet?
- No, but I'm going to right now.
- Let me do it.
- Listen to me.
Harvey's pissed at you
because you don't have anything
and Louis needs me.
Donna, I am here because that man
put my wellbeing before his own.
He gave up going
after Sheila for me.
For all I know, that's why it didn't
work out for him up there.
It's... The least I can do
is comfort him when he's down.
Go.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Come in. Come in.
What are you doing here?
Your stuff has been sitting
on your desk for days.
I wanted you to have it.
Okay. I'll need it
for my new office.
You got a job?
- Not yet, but I will.
- Oh.
Order of the Coif.
Yeah. Look who graduated
magna cum laude.
Summa, actually.
For all the good it'll do me.
I know there's gotta be
a story behind this key.
Yeah? From one
of your first cases?
Mike, do me a favor, please.
Just stop it, will you?
- Stop what?
- Stop asking questions
that you already know the answers
to just to stay here longer.
- Louis, I'm not...
- You're not what? Examining me?
Yes, you are. You're just
making small talk while
you look around the room
to see if there are any
- sharp objects in the vicinity.
- That is not why I came here.
Well, it wasn't to deliver
a box of my shit.
Look, when I was drowning,
you threw me a lifeline. Okay?
Okay. That's nice of you to say,
and I appreciate you
bringing over my things.
But they're not exactly a lifeline.
- I heard about Boston.
- What'd you hear?
That Harvey got you a job
and you didn't even show up.
Well, why would I?
When the love of my life rips out
my heart and then stomps on it?
- Louis, I'm just trying to help.
- Well, you can't!
I don't have Sheila.
I don't have a job.
And right now,
I'd just prefer to be alone.
ROBERT: No.
Well, I don't care what he says.
Fifteen percent of bullshit
is still bullshit. Dick.
What can I do for you, Mike?
Well, I can see you're busy, sir,
so I'll just jump right to it...
Hold it right there.
If this is your asking me
for Rachel's hand in marriage,
you know you're going
about it the wrong way.
Sir, I think if I were gonna do that,
I'd have the foresight to ask your wife
how to approach you first.
Good answer.
(CHUCKLES)
- I'm actually here about Louis Litt.
- Yeah, I heard he resigned.
He did and he's looking for a job.
A fellow like that should have his pick.
Well, the partnership agreement
prohibits him from taking clients.
- Ooh. Shit.
- Yeah.
Yeah, Jessica doesn't
play around, does she?
She took his firstborn too?
Look, I know it's bad
out there, but...
Bad? It's the apocalypse
and I'm not running a soup kitchen.
If a partner can't bring me clients...
(CLEARS THROAT)
What's that?
Those are Louis' billables
for the last 15 years.
Mmm-
This guy ever sleep?
And he doesn't just bill.
He trains the associates,
he publishes,
he will give his life to you.
And you want me to do this
because you're with my daughter.
I want you to do this because
I've never asked you for a thing,
and the first time I am,
it's a favor for someone else.
That's the kind of man
that your daughter is with.
So, it's because you're
with my daughter.
You're gonna see it
how you're gonna see it.
But the real question is,
what are you gonna do about Louis Litt?
I'll meet with him.
- But there's no guarantee.
- That's all I can ask.
You tell my daughter
to give her old man a call sometime.
Yes, sir.
Hey.
You look happy.
I am happy.
Because today, I did a good thing.
You're going to let me paint the bedroom
"robin's egg blue?"
I said I did a good thing.
I didn't say I did a ridiculous thing.
(CHUCKLES)
I got Louis a job interview in New York.
- What?
- Mmm-hmm.
- That's amazing.
- Yeah.
Oh, I love you.
Let me fix you
a drink to celebrate.
Well, you should fix
one for yourself, too,
because I couldn't have
done it without you.
What do you mean?
I mean the interview's
with your dad.
What?
I went to your dad for Louis.
It's really sweet.
Iii]
Let's just say there's a reason
that I didn't go to my dad
to pay for law school.
I thought you said it was
because you wanted to do it yourself.
It is. But other people
don't have a problem
going to their parents because
they don't have to wait
for the other shoe to drop.
What are you talking about?
He's not gonna give
something for nothing.
So, you mean, after this,
he's gonna want something from me.
I don't know.
But he's gonna
want something from someone.
If it gets Louis a fresh start,
I really don't care.
ROBERT: (CHUCKLING)
Oh, man. Really?
- You've got to be kidding me.
- No.
- You ate there, too?
- Every Tuesday for the last five years.
- Oh. Wednesday.
- BOTH: Chicken parm day.
Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
More like Christmas to me.
- Oh, I believe it.
- Oh, Louis, this has been a pleasure.
But it's time that we got down
to the crux of the matter.
You want to know why I resigned.
Well, I did call Jessica and she gave you
a glowing recommendation.
And we both know that's bullshit.
- You want to know the truth.
- Did I say anything about the truth?
I'm just making sure
you know I know that it's bullshit.
But my truth is,
I don't care why you left.
All I care about is
what you're gonna take.
What?
You take one client,
I could give a shit how big it is,
and I'll make you
a senior partner on the spot.
Wait a second. Mike Ross said
I was not required to bring business.
This isn't about business.
This is about balls.
I don't need another grinder,
I need a lawyer
who can kick a door in. And the door
in question is Pearson Specter's.
You want to see if I can break
my partnership agreement.
You're damn right, I do.
Because if you can't do that,
then what the hell good are you?
(SCOFFS) You're no
different than Jessica.
(CHUCKLES) I'll take
that as a compliment.
If you'll excuse me,
Sylvia will validate you on the way out.
Yeah, well, Robert, this is, uh, New York.
I take a cab.
It's just my way of saying
"get the hell out."
LOUIS: Well, how long is "a little while?"
- Do you have any...
- Louis.
Excuse me.
- Katrina, what are you doing here?
- You know what I'm doing here.
This isn't your client anymore.
You're prohibited from contacting them.
- No, I'm not here to see...
- Neubacher Capital?
Yes, you are.
Just like you're going to go see
Carver Tech and Blackthome Simons.
- How do you know that?
- Because they called me.
- What are they saying?
- It doesn't matter what they're saying.
It's plain as day
you're trying to poach them.
- Does Jessica know?
- Not yet,
but if you keep doing this,
she's gonna find out.
Yeah, well, let her sue me,
'cause I don't have any other choice.
- What are you talking about?
- Robert Zane offered me senior partner
if I can break the partnership agreement.
That is a major law firm in New York.
I'm not gonna get
a better chance than that.
- Louis...
- Look, tell Jessica if you have to.
I don't want to get
you in trouble. Okay?
But I just lost my job.
And I just lost the woman I love
for the second time all in one week.
Now, I have this chance
to turn my life around
with this one client.
I'm gonna take it.
Louis.
You want one client,
I'll give you one client.
What? Wait, no.
When you agreed to take me on,
I swore that I would be loyal to you.
And if I'm not loyal now,
then I never was.
Katrina, if you do this
and Jessica figures it out,
she will fire you.
And I cannot live with that.
That won't matter if you get the job
and you take me with you.
Give me the goddamn name.
What?
I'm gonna tell you something
and I don't want you to overreact.
From the look on your face,
I'm not making any promises.
I just got an email from Louis.
He's going after VersaLife.
Get me Ray.
- What are you gonna do?
- Get me Ray!
Harvey, it was just
a notification email.
- You don't even know where he is.
- Yes, I do.
What are you talking about?
That notification is
required by the bylaws.
He's doing it at the last second,
I guarantee you he's walking
in VersaLife's door right now.
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Not "doing," "did."
I just signed VersaLife.
- You have no right.
- Please. I have every right.
Because when I quit, Jessica
only notified my clients, not yours.
Because she didn't think I had
enough balls to go after you head-on.
That wasn't her, that was me because
I didn't think you would stoop this low.
Oh, too bad. You exposed your flank
and now you're too late.
Yeah, you can see
the fear in my eyes.
Excuse me.
I told you, you're too late.
To tell them an unemployed clown
just sold them a pile of bullshit?
You mean the bullshit that you have
to drop them as a client?
The Pfizer merger.
FTC Rule 10b-6.
They were not pleased
that you kept them in the dark.
You are a son of a bitch.
Who's the clown now?
You're a son of a bitch.
I'm only taking one client
that you're gonna have to drop, anyway.
The least you could do
is be a gentleman about it.
A gentleman? I got you two jobs.
Two jobs in Siberia!
Out of Pity-
I got you those jobs
out of compassion.
Just like when I fought for Jessica
to not fire you in the first place.
But when I take VersaLife back,
it's gonna be without
any feeling for you at all.
What happened? I lost them,
but I'm gonna get them back.
What I want to know is how the hell did
Louis find out that we had to drop them?
I don't know. People know shit.
People don't know shit.
People get told shit.
Jessica, I know I wanted
to throw him a bone,
but I did not tell him.
I wasn't talking about you.
- I was talking about Mike Ross.
- Bullshit. Mike didn't...
Tell me you didn't have him
working on VersaLife.
- That doesn't mean...
- I knew it.
He was working on VersaLife.
He owes Louis
for bringing him back here.
That is motive and opportunity.
You just want him gone
by any means necessary.
Oh, I think I have been
more than clear about that.
Yeah, well, try another theory
because Mike would never do this.
Oh, there are a lot of things
you never thought Mike Ross would do.
Sell out an old man's company.
Get in bed with a billionaire.
Cut his boss out of a deal.
- Jessica...
- People change, Harvey.
And to top it all off, Louis
is taking VersaLife to Robert Zane.
Mike Ross' future father-in-law.
Why don't you think about that?
Mike, I need to know
what you have on VersaLife.
It was me.
- What was you?
- Louis going after them is my fault.
- What did you...
- I went to Robert Zane
and I asked him to give Louis a job.
That's it? You didn't
tell him about VersaLife.
Of course not.
You think I would do that?
Never mind what I think.
You went to one of
our biggest competitors
and put him together
with a desperate Louis.
I did it because Louis
was desperate. All right?
I went to see him the other
day to bring him his stuff...
The other day?
You're telling me when you were
supposed to be helping us
keep our client, you were busy
giving them to Louis on a silver platter?
I was, but I also figured out
how to get them back.
Why didn't you tell me then?
'Cause I was trying to
think of a better option.
What the hell's wrong
with this option?
It involves going to Walter Gillie.
Well, look who decided to drop by.
The man who lost me my company,
and his partner, who tore it to shreds.
Walter, I understand how you must feel.
So, why are you here?
Because we have a proposition for you.
- Does it involve an apology?
- It is an apology.
You want me to buy VersaLife?
We want you to buy
a division of VersaLife.
The division that makes that drug.
They've been working
on anti-addiction meds for years.
Look at the results.
This one works.
HARVEY: But it's a money-loser,
and it's gonna take years.
They don't have the capital,
the patience, or the will.
But you do.
And let me guess. You two are here
out of the goodness of your hearts.
You want the truth?
He'd be here whether this was
for his own good or not.
For me, I'm here because
it gets me out of a jam.
So, you can stick it
to us if you want to.
But if you do that,
you're gonna miss the chance to save
a lot of other people just like Phillip.
Don't ever talk to me
about Phillip again.
- Walter...
- No.
This is how all this started.
With you using my son.
No. I'm the one
who used your son.
I used him to get
control of your company.
But everything Mike did from the second
he met you was to save your company.
Because when it comes
to caring about people,
he's twice the man that I am.
And by the way,
he never gave up on you
and he never sold you out.
- Bullshit.
- You're right. It is.
Mike, no.
The truth is,
is that I gave you my word.
I told you I would never sell you out.
And then, I got into bed with someone
that I never should've trusted
- and I lost you your company.
- Yes, you did.
And that company was your family.
It gave you purpose.
But you still have money,
and this is a purpose.
Walter, if you don't want
to do this, I get it.
But I need you to understand
that the only reason I even
thought to come to you
in the first place,
is that I am gonna regret
what I did to you for the rest of my life.
- MIKE: Can I come in?
- Of course.
I hope you're not,
uh, furious with me.
I'm not mad.
- You're not?
- No.
Well, good.
(CHUCKLES) I wanted to, um,
thank you for setting up
that meeting with Robert Zane.
I just hope you understand that,
if I had a choice,
I never would've gone after VersaLife.
But I had no choice...
Louis, we took them back.
What? But you had to drop them.
Not anymore.
We convinced them to sell
their trial drug division.
Of course. You drop
a drain on their earnings,
their stock price goes
right through the roof.
And their market share
falls below the threshold.
- But who the hell would buy it?
- Walter Gillie.
(CHUCKLES)
Of course. Walter Gillie.
- Louis. Listen...
- Mike, you won.
- You're a brilliant lawyer.
- You are a brilliant lawyer.
I'm a brilliant lawyer
who's never gonna work again.
Hey, stop. That is not true.
(STAMMERING) Look at
everything that you have.
A Harvard Law diploma.
Summa cum laude.
Order of the Coif.
Those are the credentials
of a Supreme Court Justice.
Yeah, that and 2 bucks
will get me a seat on the subway.
But thank you for, uh, having
the decency to tell me in person.
Louis, come on.
Let me... Let me...
Let me stick around for a while.
We'll have a couple of drinks.
You can tell me
the story about that key.
Mike, I know what you're trying to do.
How's not the time.
Please go.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Come in.
You're not Louis Litt.
No, I'm not. But if you're
expecting him to show up,
- it's gonna be a long wait.
- You here to take his spot?
I'll give you senior partner right now.
I'm here to tell you
you're not getting VersaLife.
I'm sorry.
I don't know who that is.
It's the company
you tried to poach from me.
- You seem upset.
- I'm not upset.
I just wanted to remind you,
you once told me
I was a piece of shit
for using your daughter against you.
Now, you turn around
and use Louis against me.
- That's not the same.
- It is to me.
I may fight with him,
but he's still my family.
- Then, why did he leave?
- That's between me and Louis.
I wanted VersaLife,
but it's not worth gloating over.
So, why are you really here, Harvey?
I'm here to ask you
to take Louis anyway.
- And why would I do that?
- 'Cause you're a smart man.
If you do it, I'll owe you one.
I don't need you owing me one.
Why don't you take the night
to think about it?
Because if there's
one thing I've learned,
you can never have
too many favors in the bank.
You wanted to see me?
I heard about VersaLife.
Good work.
It wasn't you.
No, it wasn't.
You know I thought it was you.
Harvey didn't tell me, but I didn't
just fall off of the turnip truck.
No, you didn't.
What?
Every damn time I think
there's no upside to having you,
you do some shit to make me think
it's actually nice to have you around.
So, we're good?
We're good after you bill
a few more hours tonight.
Well, that's gonna
have to wait until later,
because I am definitely
going out to celebrate.
You've earned it.
Jessica.
She did what Harvey
would've done for you.
- Jessica.
- Katrina.
Is this about...
I can either fire you
or you can resign.
The choice is yours.
You know.
I know.
Then, why are you being
so nice about it?
Because letting you go is enough.
And you also don't want
to antagonize me,
since I'll be
working for Robert Zane.
You haven't heard.
We got VersaLife back.
Louis won't be going to Zane,
and neither will you.
I wish you luck.
You'll have my letter of resignation
on your desk in the morning.
Because my mind is gone
To find a stone
you can write my name on
To dig a hole in the ground
For my broken crown
in my golden casket
And my mind is gone
To find a stone
you can write my name on
To dig a hole in the ground
so I can lay down
- What took you so long?
- What are you, the bathroom monitor?
If I were, I'd say you've gone
three times in an hour.
Yes, and this is our third drink.
You know they have
medicine for that, right?
- You saying I'm old?
- Yes.
But I'm also saying I know you
haven't been going to the bathroom.
All right. You want the truth?
I've been calling Donna.
Oh, my God.
That is so great.
You guys finally decided
to take the plunge.
I wanted to know
if Robert Zane called me back.
- Called you back about what?
- I asked him to hire Louis, anyway.
- You're kidding.
- I'm not.
I even told him if he did,
I'd owe him one.
- Hmm.
- What?
Oh, I'm just trying to figure out
at what point in the last week
you decided to become a pussy.
Oh, so, doing something
nice for someone makes you a pussy.
- I didn't say that exactly.
- Yes, you did.
Let's go through some of the nice things
you've done for people.
You know what, Harvey?
Guilty as charged. I am nice.
And if that makes me
a pussy, then so be it.
Then, it's settled.
You're a nice pussy.
Miss, can I get a cosmo
here for my friend?
Go ahead. Order another drink.
Just be careful,
'cause you're gonna be in the bathroom
in another five minutes.
You're going back
to the prostate again?
What, like you've never
repeated jokes before?
- I have no idea what...
- What I'm talking about?
Let's see. Uh, you see,
that's funny because blah-blah-blah.
Or by blah-blah-blah,
I mean blah-blah-blah.
- And...
- Okay I get it.
Oh, I'm just getting started.
I could do this all night.
Yeah, you know what?
Now, I have to go to the bathroom.
Go for it. Take your time.
No rush.
(WHISPERING) If it hurts, call someone.
Louis. What are you doing here?
- Waiting for Harvey.
- Harvey's not here.
Then, you'll have to do.
Look. Louis, I know
you've been through a lot.
- But Harvey's gonna...
- I don't give a shit
- what Harvey's gonna do.
- Okay, you're scaring me.
- You know what an Oscar looks like?
- What?
Academy Award.
Bald guy.
I mean, of course we all know
what it looks like.
But especially you.
You're an actress.
It's the highest
honor in your field.
I mean, of course you don't
need to be told what it is.
- What are you talking about?
- See, the highest academic honor
at Harvard Law
is the Order of the Coif.
You don't get a trophy.
You get three things.
You get a parchment
to hang on your wall,
a medal to wear at graduation,
and this.
Now, this key doesn't
say "Order of the Coif."
it doesn't say anything.
It's just a symbol.
What does that have to do with Harvey?
It doesn't. It has to do with Mike.
You know what, Louis?
It's been a long day...
It's about to get longer.
See, Mike asked me about this.
And I thought he was... (CHUCKLES)
I thought he was trying to get my mind
off of my problems.
But then, he did it again.
And it got me to thinking.
Mike graduated
magna cum laude.
He's in Order of the Coif.
- But he didn't recognize this.
- So, he forgot a stupid key.
Mike Ross doesn't forget anything.
You see, the reason he didn't recognize
this was because he never got one.
Because he didn't go to Harvard.
Louis, we've been down this road before.
Mike is in the Harvard database.
But he's not in the yearbook.
And, according to his credit report,
his address during his law school years
was in New York.
He even paid rent the first
of the month in person.
- Well, I'm sure there's a...
- Sit down!
Last year, you told me
not to tell Sheila about Mike's file.
You acted like you cared about me.
You didn't give a shit about me.
- You cared about you and Harvey,
- No.
- And Mike, and Jessica...
- Louis, that's not true.
- Well, let's call Sheila right now.
I know all of the numbers by heart.
I mean, she may not be
interested in me anymore,
but she will definitely be interested in
a fraud claiming that he went to Harvard.
I'm sorry.
You're sorry?
You've been lying to me since
the day Mike Ross arrived.
I knew Harvey and Jessica
never really accepted me.
But I thought you were different.
- I thought you were my friend.
- I am your friend, Louis.
No, you're not.
And don't you ever
say that to me again.
Where are you going?
To see your friend, Jessica.
Louis knows.
Louis.
I know you're a stickler for the rules,
so I figured I'd
just come by to return my ID.
You want an explanation.
I wanna see you perp
walked through the bullpen
with your pretty little jacket
draped over your handcuffs.
But until then,
yeah, I'll take an explanation.
When I found out
the truth about Mike Ross,
- it had already been done.
- By Harvey.
Right after he made
senior partner over me?
That's when he hired the fraud?
That's the correct timeline, right?
Yes.
So, instead of turning him in,
you cover it up.
- Louis...
- And the one time that I do something,
you don't cover it up at all.
You throw me to the wolves.
I saved you from the wolves.
Then I ask you
for the smallest gesture,
just to allow my career
to continue with dignity,
and you couldn't muster
the tiniest shred of compassion.
What do you want me to say?
I want you to tell me you're a liar!
And a hypocrite!
And I want you to say you're sorry.
I am a liar.
And I am a hypocrite.
But I will not say I'm sorry.
Because I did what I did
to protect this firm.
Well, it looks like the captain's
about to go down with her ship.
Bullshit. You want something.
- Oh, I told you. I want to see you...
- In handcuffs?
If that were true,
the police would be here instead of you.
No.
You wanted to see me squirm
before asking me
for what you really want.
I'm not gonna give you the satisfaction.
So, you might as well spit it out.
You asked me what I wanted
once before and I told you.
And then you told me
that I couldn't have it.
But now, I can.
Pearson...
Specter...
Lift.
Adaptation: BTI Studios
English