[Script Info]
Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.27,0:00:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That was close,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.60,0:00:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太喜欢清晨彩弹的味道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}God,I love the smell of paintballs in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.89,0:00:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是很搞笑  拉杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah,still finny,Raj.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.90,0:00:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没办法去山脊了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's no way we can get to the ridge.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.64,0:00:19.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,化学部的人完全把我们堵死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The chemistry department has us completely cut off.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.89,0:00:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,河床呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But what about the creek bed?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.40,0:00:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被药理学部门拿下了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The pharmacology department controls that,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.50,0:00:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们全都吃了兴奋剂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And they're all hopped up on experimental steroids.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.30,0:00:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完了  我们死定了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's it then. we're doomed.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.43,0:00:29.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在该承认我们会沦落至此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I think the time has come to acknowledge that
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.69,0:00:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是因为某人没参加\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}we are paying the price for some of us failing to attend my
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.17,0:00:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的物理学部门战略会议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Physics department paintball strategy meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.56,0:00:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了  我妈妈得了微血管扩张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I told you my mom has spider veins.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.80,0:00:40.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带她去激光治疗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I had to take her to the laser clinic.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.80,0:00:44.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也跟你说了  我要看医嘱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I told you I wanted to see a doctor's note.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.00,0:00:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要定个策略\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We need a plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.76,0:00:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"上帝之锤"怎么样  -我忘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How about operation hammer of the gods? I forget.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.53,0:00:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪个是"上帝之锤"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Which one is hammer of the gods?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.70,0:00:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们藏到停车场的垃圾桶后面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We hide behind the dumpsters in the parking
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.58,0:00:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伏击去尿尿的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Lot and ambush people when they come to pee.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.63,0:00:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No go.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.36,0:00:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,垃圾桶那边完全是天文学部门的领地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The dumpsters are deep in astronomy department territory.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.73,0:00:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该不成问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That shouldn't be a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.93,0:01:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金星白天都显现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Venus is up during the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.43,0:01:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们估计都在望天呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They're probably just all staring at the sky.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.53,0:01:06.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  我们现在要战术性撤退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right, what we need now is a tactical retreat.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.30,0:01:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们看了那集《星际之门》吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did you see the episode of stargate
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.12,0:01:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}where they found themselves on a planet
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.71,0:01:12.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,类似雅典和斯巴达文明的星球上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}with a culture based loosely on earth's athens and sparta?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.26,0:01:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not important.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.06,0:01:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德  拉杰和我一起冲出大门逃跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Leonard, raj and I are going to burst out the door and run away.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.60,0:01:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德掩护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard will cover us.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.83,0:01:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不是我逃跑你掩护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why don't I run away and you cover me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.43,0:01:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你用胜利来换取带你母亲看病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because you chose your mother's veins over victory.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.06,0:01:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,数到三\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}On three.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.36,0:01:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二  三  闪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}One, two, three, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.56,0:01:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须带她去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I had to take her!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.43,0:01:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都快到穿泳衣的天气了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's almost bathing suit weather!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.10,0:01:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我投降  别开枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I surrender! don't shoot!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.03,0:01:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们从那边走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They went that way!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.03,0:01:46.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德  我是你的队友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard, I'm on your team.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.20,0:01:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱斯利  谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, leslie, thank god.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.16,0:01:51.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们小队的其他人呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where's the rest of your squad?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.73,0:01:54.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们把我留下来等死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ah, they left me here to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.60,0:01:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What about yours?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.13,0:01:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Dead, all of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.46,0:01:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.53,0:01:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.53,0:02:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是友军误伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was friendly fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.83,0:02:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就是不听话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They just wouldn't listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.73,0:02:09.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们被包围了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, we're surrounded,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.83,0:02:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能等着被俘虏  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So I guess there's nothing for us to do
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.40,0:02:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者被干掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but wait to be captured or killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.06,0:02:18.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最难受的是等待\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hmm, that's the worst part, the waiting.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.83,0:02:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道有颗带有你的名字的子弹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All the while knowing that there's a
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.35,0:02:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,始终会在那里等着你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Paint pellet out there with your name on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.56,0:02:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大大的死亡湿球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, the big wet ball of death.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.53,0:02:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更能让你感觉自己还活着  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Kind of makes you feel more alive, doesn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.80,0:02:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It kind of does.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.30,0:02:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是别浪费时间吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I say we make every moment count.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.40,0:02:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.50,0:02:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么可做的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How exactly do we do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.40,0:02:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德  你怎么不掩护我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard, why aren't you covering us?!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.26,0:02:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们快被杀光了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're getting slaughtered out here!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.26,0:02:58.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,战场就是地狱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}War is hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.82,0:03:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《生活大爆炸》\N第二季  第16集
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.83,0:03:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们早上看了新的预算备忘了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did you guys see the new budget memo that went out this morning?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.57,0:03:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又减少了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, more cutbacks.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.53,0:03:30.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太无法接受了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Unacceptable.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.08,0:03:32.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就想不明白  他们干嘛不直接放弃你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It baffles me why they don't simply let some of
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.82,0:03:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就有更多钱给我做试验了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You go so that there's money available for my research.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.07,0:03:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我烦恼什么吗  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know what baffles me, sheldon?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.74,0:03:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就你的成绩来看  我看是任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Based on your academic record, any number of things, I imagine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.54,0:03:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-伙计们  -莱斯利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, guys. hey, leslie. hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.14,0:03:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德  我帮你拿到高速原型机的批准了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard, I got the approval for the rapid prototyper you wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.64,0:03:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  莱斯利  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's great, leslie. thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.80,0:03:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,互帮互助而已啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You scratch my back, I scratch yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.67,0:03:57.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What was all that about?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.10,0:03:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, uh, no big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.20,0:04:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们让莱斯利管一些自由经费\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They gave leslie control of some unrestricted grant money.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.14,0:04:07.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那挠背和"喵"又是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, okay, but what's with the back- scratching and the meow!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.20,0:04:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得挠背的隐喻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I believe the back-scratching metaphor
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.21,0:04:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常指投桃报李的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Generally describes a quid pro quo situation where
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.97,0:04:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一方提供物品或服务给另一方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}One party provides goods or services to the
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.31,0:04:16.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,报答一种类似之举\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Second party in compensation for a similar action.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.04,0:04:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.14,0:04:23.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于"喵"  我感觉听起来像非洲的麝猫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The meow, that sounded to me like an african civet cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.14,0:04:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说完了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you done?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.57,0:04:25.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.30,0:04:32.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管名字里有猫  但其实麝猫不是真的猫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Despite what the name suggests, the civet cat is not a true cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.74,0:04:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now I'm done.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.94,0:04:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道我怎么想吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know what I'm thinking?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.47,0:04:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得霍华德并不是用挠背做隐喻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm thinking howard wasn't making a back-scratching metaphor.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.17,0:04:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得确有挠背一说呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm thinking there was some actual scratching involved.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.30,0:04:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  霍华德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What about it, howard?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.82,0:04:52.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想说是因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I didn't want to say anything 'cause I
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.03,0:04:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你和莱斯利以前好过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Know you and leslie have a little history.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.60,0:04:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't care about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.85,0:05:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  我其实早就想说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Great, 'cause I've been dying to say something?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.11,0:05:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在彩弹小屋里!  两次!\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In the paintball shed! twice!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.25,0:05:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是为什么你没有掩护我们撤退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is that why you didn't cover our Escape
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.03,0:05:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还让我们像牲口般被屠宰?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and let us get cut down like animals?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.61,0:05:10.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对此我非常抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, yeah, sorry about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.37,0:05:14.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阵前脱逃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Dereliction of duty in the face of the enemy is
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.59,0:05:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是要被送交军事法庭的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}a court-martial offense.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.88,0:05:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管他什么军事法庭[德语]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Court-martial, schmort-martial,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.93,0:05:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱斯利·温克尔是第五个和我做过爱的女生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Leslie Winkle is the fifth girl I've ever had sex with.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.91,0:05:24.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  不包括付费的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, for free.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.58,0:05:28.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你还拿到了高速原型机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And plus, you got a rapid prototyper.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.98,0:05:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老兄 那玩意可不便宜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's an expensive piece of equipment, dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.75,0:05:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们剩下的人的预算就被啃到见骨了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And the rest of us have had our budgets cut to the bone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.45,0:05:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以这样看这个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, one way to look at this is that I'm getting new equipment,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.43,0:05:39.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有了新设备  你们没有  这不公平\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And you're not, and that's unfair.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.78,0:05:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更好的角度是 我有女人而你们没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But a better way to look at this is that I'm getting sex and you're not,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.96,0:05:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么比这更好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And that's delightful.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.05,0:05:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有东西都不响应了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The whole thing froze.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.41,0:05:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.58,0:05:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷静点  能解决的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Calm down. we'll figure it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.91,0:05:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么能冷静得了?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How can I calm down?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.25,0:05:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的整个购物车都要被清空了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm gonna lose my whole shopping cart.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.85,0:05:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我选了三个小时的鞋就这么一扫而空了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's three hours of picking out shoes just shot to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.65,0:05:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  佩妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello, penny.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.98,0:06:00.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗨  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello, sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.75,0:06:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你坐在我的专座上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're in my spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.88,0:06:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备坐这么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you planning on sitting here?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.11,0:06:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我要去漫画店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, I'm going to the comic book store.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.38,0:06:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我坐哪有什么区别?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then what difference does it make?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.91,0:06:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么区别?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What difference does it make?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.11,0:06:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好戏登场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.51,0:06:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的专座\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That is my spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.95,0:06:17.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这个不断变化的世界里  这是不变的一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In an ever-changing world, it is a single point of consistency.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.28,0:06:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假设我的生命用一个建立在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If my life were expressed as a function
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.36,0:06:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四维直角坐标系中的方程来表示的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}on a four-dimensional cartesian Coordinate system,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.92,0:06:28.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个座位从我坐上那一刻开始 就成为了 (0,0,0,0)\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That spot at the moment I first sat on it would be zero-zero-zero-zero.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.34,0:06:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啥?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.11,0:06:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要坐他的专座\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't sit in his spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.34,0:06:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.21,0:06:40.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满意了?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Happy?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.04,0:06:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有不满意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not unhappy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.08,0:06:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱他 不过他也太极品怪胎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Boy, I love him, but he is one serious wackadoodle.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.08,0:06:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  电脑修好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, that should do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.41,0:06:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太感谢了  真是我的恩人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, thank you. you are a lifesaver.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.24,0:06:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你订了可真不少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's a lot of shoes you ordered.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.34,0:07:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可悲的是其实这些对我来说真的不算多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, you know the sad thing is, it's really not.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.08,0:07:05.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你们的彩弹枪?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ooh, is this one of those paintball guns?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.34,0:07:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  你下次应该和我们一起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. you ought to come out with us sometime.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.24,0:07:08.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  不过还是算了  我从内布拉斯加来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, no, thanks. I'm from nebraska.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.98,0:07:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里  当我们对什么东西开枪的时候 要么是我们要吃它们  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When we shoot things, it's because we want to eat them
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.78,0:07:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么是让他们别妨碍我和男友办事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}or make them leave our boyfriends alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.71,0:07:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子  你心跳在狂飙 我果然魅力无边啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Boy, your heart's racing. I must've really gotten you going.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.41,0:07:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一半是你的原因   一半是我先天就心律紊乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, it's partly you, partly my transient idiopathic arrhythmia.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.38,0:07:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真性感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sexy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.44,0:07:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我可以假定你的感受是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Can I assume that you likewise found the experience...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.11,0:07:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你满足了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Satisfactory?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.41,0:07:54.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我原本打算的措辞  不过当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That wasn't quite the word I was looking for, but sure,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.81,0:07:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我合格了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll do this pass-fail.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.98,0:08:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我给你弄的那个原型机如何啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, are you enjoying that prototyper I got you?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.24,0:08:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很赞啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, it's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.41,0:08:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工程院里的每个人 都羡慕得要命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Everybody in the engineering department is eating their hearts out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.78,0:08:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很幸运使得旁人痛苦万分的感觉很好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Isn't it nice when your good fortune makes others miserable?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.91,0:08:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般人理解不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, most people don't get that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.08,0:08:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德  我回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard, I'm home!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.51,0:08:20.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, great.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.44,0:08:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,读书俱乐部的活动取消了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Book club was cancelled!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.74,0:08:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叶太太颈椎又出问题了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That thing on phyll's neck opened up again!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.71,0:08:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我忙着呢  老妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm busy, ma!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.78,0:08:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忙到不能帮妈妈把拉链解开啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Too busy to help your mother with her zipper?!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.84,0:08:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您别进来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't come in, ma!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.48,0:08:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.51,0:08:38.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有客人在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's got company!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.18,0:08:46.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又开始心律紊乱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, there's the arrhythmia.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.41,0:08:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是犹太人嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is she jewish?!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.94,0:08:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是犹太人么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you jewish?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.84,0:08:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- No. - yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.78,0:08:57.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那行  你们好好玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, then you kids have fun!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.78,0:09:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘了防护措施\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Use protection!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.74,0:09:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得他会注意到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You think he'll notice?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.21,0:09:16.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有这种可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's a chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.51,0:09:19.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, what are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.14,0:09:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我们?"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"we"?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.64,0:09:23.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你错了  曾经有一个我们的机会摆在你面前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, you had your chance to be "we"
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.91,0:09:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在一年半以前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}For, like, a year and a half now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.98,0:09:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  你是你  你完蛋了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Right now, you are "you," and you are screwed.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.08,0:09:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为什么要告诉他是我干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why do we have to tell him I did it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.91,0:09:36.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们不会告诉他是我干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, we're not gonna tell him I did it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.34,0:09:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样行么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, okay, how about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.94,0:09:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们告诉他有人闯进来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We tell him somebody broke in.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.54,0:09:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就为了向沙发上射击彩蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just to shoot the couch with a paintball gun?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.11,0:09:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我就会相信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry, I buy it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.28,0:09:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在嗑药的那么多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All those people are on drugs.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.14,0:09:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以告诉他  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We could tell him
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.54,0:09:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们想要这个沙发别打扰和男友办事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}they wanted the couch to stay away from their boyfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.24,0:09:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.68,0:10:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把它翻过来不就行了?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What if we just flip it over?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.08,0:10:04.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There. looks fine, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.34,0:10:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐印\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Mm, butt print.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.01,0:10:08.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有明显的坐印\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's no discernible butt print.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.91,0:10:11.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.48,0:10:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  坐印\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There, butt print.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.88,0:10:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太小  太...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's too small and too...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.44,0:10:19.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漂亮了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Perfect.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.48,0:10:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.88,0:10:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.34,0:10:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘  自然点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Shh. act normal.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.88,0:10:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sheldon!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.01,0:10:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,漫画店逛得怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How was the comic book store?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.48,0:10:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不错  新一期的《闪电侠》来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fine. the new issue of flash is out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.04,0:10:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  很好  你走回来的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Great, great. did you walk the whole way?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.31,0:10:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面有点冷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's a little chilly.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.34,0:10:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库什帕利送我回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Kooth Rappali picked me up.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.38,0:10:40.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是很棒吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Isn't that terrific?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.58,0:10:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他真是个好朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He is such a good friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.74,0:10:44.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道有朋友的最大好处是什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know what the best thing about friends is?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.01,0:10:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会无来由地说个不停\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They don't talk incessaly for no particular reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.54,0:10:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  朋友之间会宽容小错误的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, friends forgive the little things.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.81,0:10:53.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得回去洗头了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, I gotta go home and wash my hair.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.64,0:10:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你敢  小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't you dare, missy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.38,0:11:01.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  闪电侠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello, fastest man alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.31,0:11:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想观赏我看完你的整本漫画书吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Want to see me read your entire comic book?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.98,0:11:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要再看一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Want to see it again?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.58,0:11:27.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点不对劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Something's wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.01,0:11:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.01,0:11:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也说不上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.38,0:11:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是感觉不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It doesn't feel right.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.84,0:11:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know what you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.61,0:11:56.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个  佩妮干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, that. Penny did that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.94,0:12:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.88,0:12:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么不坐在办公椅那吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why don't you just eat in your desk chair?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.71,0:12:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么不坐在办公椅那吃?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why don't I just eat in my desk chair?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.14,0:12:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.91,0:12:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的办公椅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That is my desk chair.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.24,0:12:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我工作的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That is where I work.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.41,0:12:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在办公椅那吃饭  也不在专座上工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't eat in my desk chair and I don't work in my spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.28,0:12:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在办公椅那工作  在专座上吃饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I work in my desk chair and eat in my spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.68,0:12:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常怪胎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wackadoodle.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.98,0:13:01.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个简单的解决办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, there's kind of an obvious solution here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.58,0:13:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.31,0:13:10.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  问题解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There. problem solved.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.21,0:13:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人关心你要坐在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nobody cares where you're going to sit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.24,0:13:13.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又不疯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're not crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.68,0:13:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  但问题并没解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Excuse me, but the problem is not solved.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.21,0:13:21.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如你的脑袋不小心被截掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If your head had been accidentally amputated,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.76,0:13:24.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安个狗的脑袋在上面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And we transplanted a dog's head in its place,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.44,0:13:26.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫"问题解决"吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Would that be "problem solved"?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.48,0:13:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如是你的脑袋  问题就解决了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If it were your head, it would be.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.31,0:13:33.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  我很  很抱歉  但就一周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sheldon, I am really, really sorry, but it's only for a week.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.14,0:13:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能通融点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Can't you be a little bit flexible?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.28,0:13:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  抱歉  我没细想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, sorry. I didn't really think that through.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.61,0:13:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你声称说一周就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You claimed it's going to be a week,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.85,0:13:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我对你选的干洗店没信心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I have no faith in your dry cleaner.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.41,0:13:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.58,0:13:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你注意到他柜台上的标志了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did you notice the sign on his counter?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.31,0:13:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是全职干干洗的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's not a full-time dry cleaner.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.14,0:13:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还配钥匙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He also makes keys.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.54,0:13:54.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到老天的份上  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, for god's sake, Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.61,0:13:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专注是很重要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Focus is important.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.11,0:13:58.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迈克尔·德倍基[心脏手术创始人]做心脏移植手术之余\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Was Michael Debakey a wedding planner
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.14,0:14:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做婚礼策划吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in between heart transplants?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.24,0:14:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚历山大·弗莱明午夜会变身理发师吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did Alexander Fleming moonlight as a hairdresser?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.48,0:14:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"谢谢你发现了青霉素"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"thanks for discovering penicillin.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.04,0:14:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"来个蓬蓬头吧"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now how about we try a bouffant?"
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.28,0:14:13.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来我今晚要有"性"福了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ooh, looks like I'm gonna have sex tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.41,0:14:14.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宝贝...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, baby...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.88,0:14:16.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他右手在召唤他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}His right hand is calling him?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.18,0:14:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  是莱斯利·温克尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, it's Leslie Winkle.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.84,0:14:23.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一段时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's a long story.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.74,0:14:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我十分钟后接你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll pick you up in ten minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.51,0:14:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位  再见[法语]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Gentlemen, adieu.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.61,0:14:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为今晚我们要玩《光环》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I thought we were going to play halo tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.94,0:14:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我怎么做  莱纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What am I supposed to do, Leonard?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.44,0:14:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有女人在那饥渴地想和我做爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's a woman out there anxious to have sex with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.51,0:14:40.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You understand, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.21,0:14:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  一点都不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No. not at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.18,0:14:48.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  我得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nevertheless, I must depart.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.24,0:14:49.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  我说过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}By the way, did I tell you?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.61,0:14:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱斯利"活动"了一下  让我参加日内瓦研究之旅\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Leslie pulled some strings and got me on the
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.69,0:14:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,观测欧洲原子核研究委员会的超级对撞机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Research trip to geneva to check out the cern supercollider.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.64,0:14:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不公平\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's not fair.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.88,0:14:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你甚至不是物理学家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're not even a physicist.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.08,0:14:59.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  有两个角度看到这个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, there are two ways of looking at this...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.11,0:14:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.04,0:15:01.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.34,0:15:06.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有提高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're improving.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.74,0:15:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.74,0:15:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真人实战确实有助于提高\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It helps when I get to practice with a real woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.98,0:15:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.31,0:15:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周六我姐结婚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Saturday my sister's getting married.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.04,0:15:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你陪我去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I-i want you to come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.18,0:15:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要求宾客穿半正式礼服的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's black tie.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.21,0:15:24.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天  我真的不想去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, gee, I'd really rather not.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.04,0:15:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.24,0:15:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去婚礼时  一般都骗骗搞搞胖伴娘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When I go to weddings, it's to scam on chunky bridesmaids.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.54,0:15:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有约的人了  我不知该怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know what I would do with a date.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.64,0:15:37.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我理解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, all right. I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.08,0:15:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.54,0:15:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  你去不了日内瓦那件事我真抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, I'm really sorry about that geneva trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.18,0:15:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.34,0:15:45.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, didn't you hear?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.64,0:15:47.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得减少去的人数\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I had to reduce the number of people going
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.54,0:15:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你就被刷下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and you didn't make the cut.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.51,0:15:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When did that happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.48,0:15:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大约12秒之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}About 12 seconds ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.28,0:15:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.51,0:16:00.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说 我要是不去那婚礼就不能去日内瓦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you saying if I don't go to the wedding, I can't go to geneva?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.64,0:16:03.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不想这么说出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Actually, I'm trying not to say it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.44,0:16:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉但是这让我感到有点不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, I'm sorry, but that makes me a little uncomfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.31,0:16:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How so?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.68,0:16:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样看起来好像你在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because it's like you're controlling
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.00,0:16:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用研究旅行和新设备来控制我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Me with new equipment and research trips.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.78,0:16:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我不这样控制你的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, if I weren't controlling you with
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.58,0:16:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}new equipment and research trips, Then I'd be uncomfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.78,0:16:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How so?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.84,0:16:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就会弄得像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}'cause then we'd be in, like,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.52,0:16:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是来真的一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A real relationship with feelings and all that crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.84,0:16:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那说到底  我不就是一个你买来玩的性爱玩具嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, bottom line, I'm just a bought-and-paid-for sex toy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.11,0:16:35.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不不  也不全是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No. no, not at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.34,0:16:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也算是个尤物了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're also arm candy.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.58,0:16:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.24,0:16:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.04,0:16:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈我要借一套礼服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, ma, you got to rent me a tux!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.58,0:16:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就要?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.74,0:16:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做什么爱还要用正装的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What kind of sex are you having up there?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.98,0:17:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛蹲在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why are you crouching there?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.14,0:17:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的专座\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is my spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.18,0:17:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还能蹲哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where else am I supposed to crouch?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.98,0:17:10.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  你老家?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know. texas?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.71,0:17:14.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.81,0:17:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚刚从干洗店里拿来的  像新的一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fresh from the cleaners, good as new.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.38,0:17:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Really? great.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.38,0:17:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  看  焕然一新\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sheldon, look. good as new.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.28,0:17:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从那个配钥匙店   我严重怀疑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}From that key maker, I highly doubt it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.71,0:17:23.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Come on, sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.84,0:17:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试了再说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just give it a try.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.18,0:17:28.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.04,0:17:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  舒舒服服的 (0,0,0)\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There, nice and comfy cozy. zero, zero, zero.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.84,0:17:38.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个零\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's one more zero.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.58,0:17:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你忘掉了时间坐标\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You forgot the time parameter.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.81,0:17:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我坐下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sit on the damn couch.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.58,0:18:07.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.94,0:18:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思  不行 这有什么问题啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What do you mean, "nope"? What's wrong with it?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.96,0:18:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这没问题  他有问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nothing, it's what's wrong with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.36,0:18:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这两个完全一样的好不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's exactly the same...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.83,0:18:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮  佩妮  让我来搞定好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Penny, penny, I think I know what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.46,0:18:22.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  我要告诉你一些坏消息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sheldon, I have some bad news.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.56,0:18:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}More?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.03,0:18:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm afraid so.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.33,0:18:28.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你礼拜一的腰果鸡丁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know the cashew chicken I get you monday nights?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.90,0:18:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  四川宫的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yes. from szechuan palace.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.66,0:18:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四川宫两年前倒闭了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Szechuan palace closed two years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.93,0:18:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.26,0:18:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我的鸡丁哪里来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where did my cashew chicken come from?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.33,0:18:42.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,金龙饭店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Golden dragon.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.96,0:18:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.33,0:18:53.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  这不可能的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, this isn't right.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.53,0:18:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外卖盒子一直是四川宫的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Our food always comes in szechuan palace containers.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.93,0:18:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们倒闭的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, well, before they went out of business,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.36,0:19:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我买了四千个他们的盒子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I bought 4,000 containers.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.26,0:19:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后藏在我车子后面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I keep them in the trunk of my car.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.83,0:19:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.06,0:19:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天哪  一切都不同了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, this changes everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.93,0:19:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这样他就不会去想坐垫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I thought that might take his mind off the cushion.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.00,0:19:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是真实  什么是虚假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's real? what isn't?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.46,0:19:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么才能知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How can I know?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.80,0:19:22.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你编故事的是不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You did make that up, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.06,0:19:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倒希望是编的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, god, I wish I had.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.26,0:19:26.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Leonard?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.73,0:19:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, buddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.63,0:19:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是不喜欢这个垫子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I still don't like this cushion.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.57,0:19:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先  佩妮感谢你能加入我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ok first of all, penny, thank you for coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.00,0:19:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你买的鞋子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thanks for the shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.47,0:19:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮射击很牛叉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Penny is an amazing shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.84,0:19:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我们这次很可能会赢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I think we have a real chance to win this week.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.67,0:19:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么策略\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's the plan?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.67,0:19:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我们先跑出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay. now, we all run out.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.40,0:19:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿和我在树那边切断他们的左路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sheldon and I will cut to the left behind these trees.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.84,0:19:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉杰 和霍华德 还有莱斯利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Raj, howard and leslie
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.49,0:19:51.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们从石头后面包抄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}flank to the right behind the rocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.20,0:19:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样佩妮的视野就开阔了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then we'll all have a great view as penny
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.95,0:19:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后她把视野内所有敌人消灭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Runs out and kills everyone else in sight.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.87,0:19:57.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们开始前还有一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just one thing before we start.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.84,0:19:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What is it, sheldon?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.64,0:20:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What the hell?!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.77,0:20:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为我的坐垫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That was for my cushion.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.94,0:20:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  佩妮是我们唯一的希望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sheldon, penny was our only hope.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.50,0:20:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起莱纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry, leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.57,0:20:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,君子报仇十年不晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But revenge is a dish best served cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.64,0:20:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Screw that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.07,0:20:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不能射我  她已经死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She can't shoot me. she's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.36,0:20:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  你不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's right. you can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.13,0:20:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  如果我们要堕入无政府主义混乱的话...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, if we're going to descend into anarchy...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.00,0:20:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们慢慢打  我们先走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.76,0:20:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等你们去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.93,0:20:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,投降  然后午饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Surrender, then denny's.
