[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.28,0:00:03.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,《生活大爆炸》前情提要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Previously on The Big Bang Theory...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.03,0:00:08.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我得到了普林斯顿大学的夏季研究奖学金\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was offered a summer research fellowship at Princeton.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.41,0:00:13.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,普林斯顿吗  很不错的大学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Princeton. A fine institution.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.00,0:00:17.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,阿尔伯特·爱因斯坦教过书的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The place where Albert Einstein taught,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.63,0:00:21.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德也是在那里拿到博士学位  所以那学校可能没落了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and where Leonard got his PhD,so it may have gone downhill.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.01,0:00:28.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,记住  我为你感到骄傲  你做什么我都支持你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And just remember, I'm proud of you. And I support you in all that you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.02,0:00:30.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  意义重大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you. That means a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.60,0:00:34.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有一件事  如果你在工作中碰到一位男性科学家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, and one last thing.If you find yourself working with a male scientist,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.60,0:00:38.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他和我一样聪明一样高大  留着雷神索尔的发型\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who's as smart as me, as tall as me,and has hair like Thor,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.98,0:00:42.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要你马上远离现场  立刻给我打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}well, then, I want you to step away from the situation and call me immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.17,0:00:45.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs22\bord1\shad0}时至今日
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.20,0:00:47.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还适应吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How are you settling in?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.74,0:00:50.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,挺好的  普林斯顿的校区很棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pretty well. Princeton has a beautiful campus.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.83,0:00:52.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我学了几个新泽西的有趣小知识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, I've learned some fun facts about New Jersey
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.08,0:00:54.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你能拿去跟别人打开话题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to help you make small talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.00,0:00:58.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想知道他们的州鸟或谋杀率吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you like to know the state bird or the murder rate?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.71,0:01:01.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说出来都会吓你一跳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They're both shocking.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.13,0:01:04.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实我想听的是你的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, I want to hear about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.93,0:01:06.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那边还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How are things at home?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.26,0:01:09.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我这边看到东部金翅雀或者被谋杀的几率\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I'm a lot less likely to see an Eastern Goldfinch or be murdered,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.97,0:01:11.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,肯定比你低\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll tell you that.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.73,0:01:13.81,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I miss you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.98,0:01:15.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也想你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I miss you, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.35,0:01:18.94,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有件事很奇怪  今天早先我用介词结尾了一个句子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's so strange,earlier today I ended a sentence with a preposition
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.11,0:01:21.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而你却不在我身边纠正我语法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you weren't there to correct my grammar.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.90,0:01:24.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我对你这遭遇感到抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry you had to go through that.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.20,0:01:29.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实呢  我正是因为这事而开始想念你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In fact, that's when I started to really miss you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.87,0:01:34.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才分裂了不定式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know you just split an infinitive.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.37,0:01:39.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你要好好教育我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did I? Are you gonna teach me a lesson?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.05,0:01:43.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.38,0:01:48.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这样很不乖  在"to"跟动词之间插入副词\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It is naughty to put an adverb between the word "to" and the verb stem.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.22,0:01:52.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你要怎么惩罚我啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What are you gonna do about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.06,0:01:55.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要告诫你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm going to admonish you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.52,0:01:58.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,狠狠地告诫吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Vigorously?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.27,0:02:01.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也只会这么告诫人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's the only kind of admonishing I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.31,0:02:22.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(156.6,76,156.6,75.2)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H232727&\fs10\t(0,271,0.4,\fs47)\fscy80\t(271,1481,1,\fs48)}生
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.31,0:02:22.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(156.6,108,156.6,107.2)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H232727&\fs10\t(0,271,0.4,\fs47)\fscy80\t(271,1481,1,\fs48)}活
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.31,0:02:22.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(185.4,88,185.4,87.2)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H070729&\fs12\t(0,271,0.4,\fs50)\fscy110\fscx90\t(271,1481,1,\fs48)}大
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.31,0:02:22.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(212.4,79.2,212.4,78.4)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H010044&\fs8\t(0,271,0.4,\fs40)\fscy\t(271,1481,1,\fs41)}爆
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.31,0:02:22.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(237,86.4,237,85.6)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H050061&\fs8\t(0,271,0.4,\fs40)\fscy\t(271,1481,1,\fs41)}炸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.31,0:02:22.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(189,242.4,189,244)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H2D2F2F&\fs3\t(0,271,0.4,\fs18)\fscy110\fscx90\t(271,1481,1,\fs18.5)}第十季  第二十四集[本季终]
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.51,0:02:31.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾米走后  谢尔顿还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How's Sheldon doing with Amy gone?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.39,0:02:34.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最近三个晚上我带他去剪了头发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, the last three nights I've had to take him to get a haircut,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.56,0:02:37.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去火车模型店  去了隔壁市还有在卖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to the train store, and to a Walgreens in Arcadia
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.31,0:02:39.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,"好版本布洛芬止痛药"的连锁药店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}where they still have the "Good ibuprofen."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.06,0:02:43.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在问问我  艾米走后  我还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now ask me how I'm doing with Amy gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.65,0:02:45.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-艾米走后你还...  -闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How are you doing with... - Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.11,0:02:49.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果有需要  我们可以帮忙啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If you'd like, we can help you out.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.61,0:02:50.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that would be great.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.78,0:02:52.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是我帮你  我是有老婆孩子的忙人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, not me, I've got a wife and child,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.28,0:02:55.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但这家伙闲到在社交媒体上发牙线洁牙的视频\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but this one posts video of himself flossing on Instagram.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.37,0:02:59.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我发的是教程好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was a tutorial.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.71,0:03:02.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以  我很乐意陪陪谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And yes, I'm happy to keep Sheldon company.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.96,0:03:05.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  今晚他想去家居店看看梯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Great. Tonight he wants to look at ladders at Home Depot.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.76,0:03:06.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他为什么会需要梯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, why does he need a ladder?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.92,0:03:10.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他不需要  他就是喜欢看看  记得带本书打发时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He doesn't, he just likes looking at them. Bring a book.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.97,0:03:15.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位  还记得诺维茨基博士吗  她又回来加州理工读博士后啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gentlemen. You may remember Dr. Nowitzki, She's back at Caltech for her postdoc.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.81,0:03:18.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-你好啊  -你们好  我去帮你拿张椅子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hello. - Hello. Oh, let me bring a chair for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.64,0:03:22.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  诺维茨基博士要跟我说说 她在欧洲核子研究中心的研究\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, thanks. Dr. Nowitzki's going to tell me about the work she did at CERN.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.61,0:03:26.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且她还给我带了免税三角巧克力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And she brought me this duty-free Toblerone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.65,0:03:27.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好爱吃这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. I love those.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.70,0:03:30.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们坐别桌吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's sit somewhere else.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.74,0:03:36.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚发生什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What just happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.95,0:03:40.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一个陌生人用巧克力棒诱拐走了谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A stranger just lured Sheldon away with a candy bar.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.92,0:03:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等  她不是以前一直围着他转的女研究生吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait, isn't she the grad student that used to follow him around?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.92,0:03:45.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs16\bord1\shad0\an8}上次出场是第2季第6集
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.50,0:03:49.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是呢  在他还没进入青春期  鸡鸡没发育的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yeah. Back before he hit puberty and grew man parts.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.38,0:03:53.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们觉得他们有什么猫腻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So what do you guys think that's about?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.47,0:03:55.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,据我对谢尔顿的了解  啥都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Knowing Sheldon, nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.18,0:03:58.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟我说说你的标量场暗能量实验\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, tell me about your scalar dark energy experiment.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.35,0:04:01.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你先跟我说说你最新的圈量子理论论文\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not 'til you tell me about your latest paper on quantum loop theory.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.02,0:04:04.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定是那种要先吃甜点才吃正餐的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You must be one of those dessert before dinner people.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.57,0:04:09.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他居然引她发笑了  果真是有猫腻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He just made her laugh, something's wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.03,0:04:13.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们看到她看他的眼神了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you see the way she's looking at him?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.70,0:04:16.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到了  就像当年伯纳黛特看我那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Like Bernadette used to look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.66,0:04:19.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说过多少次了  关上浴室门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I keep telling you, close the bathroom door.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.75,0:04:23.04,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们看到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ah, did you see that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.21,0:04:25.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她摸了他的手  他都没甩开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She just touched his hand and he didn't swat it away.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.71,0:04:27.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,到底怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.55,0:04:31.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最简单的解释通常也是最正确的解释\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, the simplest explanation is usually the right one.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.34,0:04:34.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-什么解释  -那不是谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Which is?  -That ain't Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.89,0:04:42.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们不止共进午餐  莱纳德说谢尔顿还把她逗乐了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not only did they eat together,Leonard said he made her laugh.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.27,0:04:45.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那不算什么  华仔说她还碰了谢尔顿的手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's nothing, Howie said she touched his hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.40,0:04:46.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他用洗手液清洁了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Did he Purell?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.57,0:04:48.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,并没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.40,0:04:52.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真不敢相信莱纳德提了三角巧克力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I cannot believe Leonard mentioned the Toblerone
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.57,0:04:54.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,却没提到这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but left that part out.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.24,0:04:56.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们该打给艾米吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Should we call Amy?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.49,0:04:58.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  如果没什么的话我们不该让她担心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know; we shouldn't worry her if it's nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.12,0:05:01.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那我们再等等  等掌握多一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess we could wait till we have more information
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.41,0:05:03.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-这妹子的情况再说  -行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-about this girl.  - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.04,0:05:09.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得跟艾米住在一起会不会莫名其妙激起谢尔顿的性欲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you think living with Amy has somehow stirred up Sheldon's sexual appetite?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.64,0:05:18.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能有那种想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How can you think that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.22,0:05:22.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么恶心的句子你居然也说得出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why would you even put those words together?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.02,0:05:25.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好啦  那我们达成共识  他不会采取任何行动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, then we agree.He's not making any moves,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.60,0:05:27.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是那个博士妞拉蒙娜太主动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it's this Dr. Ramona chick.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.77,0:05:30.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诺维茨基  我上网查了她  人还挺俏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Nowitzki. I Googled her, she's pretty cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.86,0:05:34.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  莱纳德只告诉我  三角巧克力棒里有坚果仁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? All I got from Leonard was the Toblerone bar had nuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.91,0:05:42.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听这个  我看见一把折叠关节梯  带双腿水平校准\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And get this, I saw an articulating ladder with dual-leg leveling,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.79,0:05:46.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以在不平坦的地面提供稳定性和适应性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}which delivers stability and adaptability to uneven terrain.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.46,0:05:49.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听起来今晚过得很充实啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sounds like a big night.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.96,0:05:52.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊  拉杰还讲了一个超好笑的笑话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Raj made the funniest joke, he said,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.30,0:05:55.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他说"哪一把梯子最适合拿来自杀上吊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Which is the best ladder to use to hang myself?"
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.97,0:06:01.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以你一直都有事情做  你不会孤单吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So you're keeping busy? You're not lonely?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.85,0:06:05.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,完全不会  我傍晚跟莱纳德和拉杰一起外出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, not at all. I've had outings with Leonard and Raj in the evening,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.44,0:06:07.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对了  我还跟诺维茨基博士一起吃了午餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and-- oh, I had lunch with Dr. Nowitzki.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.02,0:06:09.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who's he?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.19,0:06:10.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,诺维茨基博士是女的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Dr. Nowitzki is a woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.48,0:06:13.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  你什么时候认识她的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh. Really? Uh, when did you meet her?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.44,0:06:15.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很多年前吧  那会她还是研究生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Many years ago. Back when she was a grad student.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.03,0:06:20.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她一直对我的研究超级感兴趣  现在她在加州理工学院做研究\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's always been a huge fan of my work,and now she's doing research at Caltech.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.70,0:06:23.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,超级迷妹  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Huge fan, you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.75,0:06:26.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我觉得你会喜欢她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes. I think you'd like her.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.46,0:06:29.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她智商超群  就跟你一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's extremely intelligent, just like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.67,0:06:33.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,跟你不一样的是  她是金发高妹  还曾是奥运会的游泳选手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Unlike you, she's tall, blonde and used to be an Olympic swimmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.09,0:06:38.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了  我很快打回来给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's terrific. I'll call you right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.01,0:06:44.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾米  我就给了你们一个任务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, hey, Amy. I gave you one job!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.27,0:06:49.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,帮我看着他是有多难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Keep an eye on him. How hard is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.06,0:06:54.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们以为你说的看着他是别让他瞎跑到车流中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We thought you meant not letting him run out into traffic.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.36,0:06:58.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-他就跑进过一次  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Which he only did once. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.12,0:07:01.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们为什么不告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why didn't you tell me?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.57,0:07:03.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不想让你担心啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We didn't want you to worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.33,0:07:04.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我该担心吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Should I worry?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.99,0:07:07.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不用  拜托  那可是谢尔顿  什么事都不会发生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. Come on, it's Sheldon. Nothing is gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.08,0:07:10.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一开始跟他约会时  你也是这么说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's what you said to me when I started dating him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.17,0:07:13.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在五年过去了  结果咧结果咧  有事发生了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And then five years later,bingo-bango, something happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.42,0:07:16.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  但你三个月后就回来啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, but you're gonna be back in three months.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.55,0:07:17.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们不会明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.05,0:07:20.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那瓶番茄酱的屁股  老娘已经费劲拍了那么久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've been smacking that ketchup bottle for a long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.72,0:07:24.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在那女的只需要将它倒过来对准她的薯条就能享受现成的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All she's got to do is tip it over and point it at her fries.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.72,0:07:26.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你希望我们怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, what do you want us to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.06,0:07:28.48,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.77,0:07:30.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能受了新泽西州的谋杀影响\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Might be the New Jersey talking,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.81,0:07:33.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但这个诺维茨基浪蹄子必须消失\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but this Nowitzki broad needs to disappear.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.11,0:07:36.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,用不用这样啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.44,0:07:40.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,据我们所知  就是两名科学家一起吃午餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As far as we know,all that happened is two scientists had lunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.41,0:07:43.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  可其中一名科学家是一名金发高妹奥运游泳选手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, but one of those scientists is a tall, blonde Olympic swimmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.08,0:07:46.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  谢尔顿不看外表\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on. Looks don't matter to Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.91,0:07:50.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为他的眼中只有你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because he only has eyes for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.75,0:07:54.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-少拍马屁  -多谢  我胡乱拼凑瞎说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Nice try.  -Thanks. I was scrambling.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.92,0:08:00.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是不可理喻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's unbelievable.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.26,0:08:04.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿跟别的女人吃午餐  而我老婆居然把我吼了一顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sheldon has lunch with another woman and somehow my wife yells at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.93,0:08:06.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮也把我骂了一顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Penny laid into me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.43,0:08:10.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,显然  我过分专注在优质的瑞士巧克力棒上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Apparently, I'm overly fixated on premium Swiss chocolate bars.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.15,0:08:13.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你应该不能吃那玩意吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can you even eat those things?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.94,0:08:17.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,提前一个半小时吃一片防胀气咀嚼片  吃完后马上吃止泻药就没事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If I take a Lactaid a half-hour before and some Pepto right after.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.78,0:08:19.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听起来很麻烦啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sounds like a lot of work.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.90,0:08:21.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  但也值了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Eh, I'm worth it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.82,0:08:25.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们  别偏题  我们该对诺维茨基采取行动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Guys. Focus. Should we do something about Nowitzki?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.99,0:08:27.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比如什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like what?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.20,0:08:31.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她现在单身  所以如果其他人约她出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, well, she's single, so if somebody else asks her out
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.75,0:08:34.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她答应的话  就证明她对谢尔顿没兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and she says yes, then we know she's not into Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.63,0:08:35.88,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我上吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.84,0:08:44.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,无意冒犯  斯图尔特  但那位女性是个博士[医生]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No offense, Stuart,but th-th-the woman's a doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.60,0:08:47.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那又如何  医生都喜欢我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So? Doctors like me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.10,0:08:52.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我每次去找我的医生看病  他都叫很多其他医生进来看我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whenever I see mine he calls in a bunch of other doctors to have a look.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.23,0:08:57.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她不是那种医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's not that kind of doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.07,0:08:59.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是她的损失\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, her loss.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.40,0:09:02.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,人称真医学奇葩就是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I've been called a genuine medical oddity.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.33,0:09:10.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实我本来是想毛遂自荐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, I was going to suggest me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.70,0:09:13.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  谁都比那谁强\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Great. Anybody's better than, mmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.50,0:09:19.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  他们只取走了我的脾脏和胆囊  我的情感还在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me. They took out my spleen and gallbladder,not my feelings.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.18,0:09:31.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-诺维茨基博士 很高兴见到你   -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Dr. Nowitzki. Good to see you.  - Good to see you, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.31,0:09:32.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我能和你一起坐吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}May I join you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.68,0:09:33.98,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.56,0:09:38.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.86,0:09:44.24,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该打给吉尼斯  那可能破了被拒绝速度的记录\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We should call Guinness, that might be a record.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.49,0:09:49.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她一看就是正在吃工作午餐  不希望被打扰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's clearly having a working lunch and preferred to eat alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.45,0:09:52.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,库珀博士  这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dr. Cooper, over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.37,0:09:56.71,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我本来可以让她很开心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I could have made her very happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.21,0:10:00.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你乖乖走开  我想她应该开心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You kept walking. I think you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.67,0:10:05.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真觉得我们有理由担心吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you really think there's reason to worry?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.43,0:10:07.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  她绝对在倒追谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, she's definitely going after Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.76,0:10:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我勾引过她  但她拒绝我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I made a play for her and she shot me down.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.76,0:10:11.72,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可那根本证明不了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, well, that doesn't prove anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.89,0:10:15.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  女人有一百万个拒绝拉杰的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, there's a million reasons a woman would shoot Raj down.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.52,0:10:18.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  一百万个那么夸张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like, really, a million?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.06,0:10:20.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  几百个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine, hundreds.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.23,0:10:21.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.57,0:10:26.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重点是  这可能根本没什么  我们都反应过度了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The point is this could be nothing and we are all overreacting.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.16,0:10:30.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家好  这位是我朋友 诺维茨基博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, everybody. This is my friend, Dr. Nowitzki.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.24,0:10:31.41,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,大家好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.58,0:10:32.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.62,0:10:36.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚去游泳了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We just went swimming.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.38,0:10:44.92,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你真的进泳池里了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And you actually got in a pool?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.59,0:10:46.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一开始怕得要死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was scared,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.84,0:10:50.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但我告诉自己  这只是个大浴缸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I told myself it's just a big bathtub.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.47,0:10:54.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后我再度怕得要死  因为我浴缸里有很多陌生人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Then I got scared again 'cause there are all these strangers in my bathtub.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.73,0:10:56.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我为他感到骄傲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was proud of him
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.93,0:10:59.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很多人第一天都不敢把脸埋进水里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a lot of people don't put their face in the water on the first day.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.77,0:11:02.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是为了躲避一只蜜蜂  但那也算数\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I was hiding from a bee, but it still counts.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.78,0:11:06.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,麻烦让个位子给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can I just squeeze in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.74,0:11:12.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  你跟艾米联系过了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So, Sheldon, have you talked to Amy?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.83,0:11:13.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有啊  我们今早视频聊天了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yes, we Skyped this morning
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.12,0:11:15.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我睡前会再跟她联系一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm sure I'll check in with her before I go to sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.04,0:11:17.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿总说起她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sheldon talks about her all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.96,0:11:19.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我等不及见她了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I can't wait to meet her.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.29,0:11:20.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That is true.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.46,0:11:23.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她一直在问艾米会离开多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She keeps asking how long Amy's going to be gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.76,0:11:29.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拉蒙娜  自我介绍一下吧  你有男朋友吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, so, Ramona, tell us about yourself. Do you, do you have a boyfriend?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.63,0:11:33.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德  你老婆就坐在旁边  你干嘛呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Leonard, your wife is sitting right here. What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.31,0:11:38.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的工作很忙  没什么时间谈恋爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, my work doesn't leave me a lot of time for relationships.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.94,0:11:41.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一点你已经表达得很清楚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think you made that very clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.48,0:11:44.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她曾是欧洲核子研究中心美国团队的一员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She was part of the American team at CERN.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.07,0:11:47.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们探测到希格斯玻色子时  我就在现场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had a front row seat when they detected the Higgs boson.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.44,0:11:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  我和彼得·希格斯通过信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you know, I've corresponded with Peter Higgs.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.44,0:11:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs16\bord1\shad0\an8}英国理论物理学家  提出了希格斯机制  曾获诺贝尔物理学奖
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.36,0:11:52.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你想看看他的信吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Would you like to see some of his letters?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.82,0:11:54.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-当然了  -我去拿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Absolutely. - I'll get them.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.99,0:11:57.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我跟你一起去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, hang on, I'll come with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.58,0:11:59.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真好玩  像玩耍约会一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, fun. Like a play date.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.83,0:12:03.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我说错了  纠正我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, correct me if I'm wrong,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.00,0:12:07.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但我们不是该阻止这种事的发生吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but isn't that exactly what we were supposed to stop from happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.46,0:12:09.51,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我都舍身用肉体隔开他们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I threw my body at them,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.67,0:12:11.68,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你还想要我怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}what else did you want me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.68,0:12:15.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得该打电话给艾米吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You think you should call Amy?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.18,0:12:17.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你有手有嘴  你打啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got fingers and a mouth, you call her.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.89,0:12:22.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Here you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.52,0:12:24.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这些信都是彼得·希格斯写给你的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are these all from Peter Higgs?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.69,0:12:26.61,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不不不  有很多不同的名人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, no, no, no. They're from many famous people.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.02,0:12:29.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看到没  比如这封信来自帕特里克·斯图尔特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See? Oh, like this one. This is from Patrick Stewart.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.02,0:12:29.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs16\bord1\shad0\an8}英国演员  出演过《X战警》X教授一角
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.57,0:12:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,信上说  如果我再去他家  他就会放狗来跟我"会一会"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It says if I come to his house again,I get to meet his dogs.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.29,0:12:39.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.67,0:12:44.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  谢尔顿  -你好  艾米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Hello, Sheldon. - Oh, hello, Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.33,0:12:47.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又想你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was missing you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.17,0:12:50.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也想你  时机正好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I miss you, too. Hey, this is good timing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.30,0:12:52.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还记得我之前跟你提过的诺维茨基博士吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Remember that Dr. Nowitzki I told you about?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.01,0:12:54.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她就在这儿呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She's right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.80,0:12:57.18,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sh-she's what?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.43,0:13:00.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.52,0:13:02.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.98,0:13:04.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,幸会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So nice to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.40,0:13:11.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,稍等  喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hang on. Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.40,0:13:15.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有点迟了  莱纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A little late, Leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.70,0:13:17.74,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.91,0:13:20.08,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德这个时候打电话给你做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is Leonard doing calling you at this hour?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.79,0:13:22.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not important.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.66,0:13:26.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我得跟你说  这样似乎有点不合适\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I must tell you, that seems a little inappropriate.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.29,0:13:28.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-你同意吗  -同意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Don't you agree?  -I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.38,0:13:29.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.92,0:13:31.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都这样认为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We both think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.43,0:13:37.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我快疯了  你们谁过去一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, this is making me crazy. Somebody's got to go over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.60,0:13:39.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你有腿有脚  你去啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You got feet and legs, you do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.60,0:13:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要和我一起去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Will you go with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.77,0:13:46.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去了做什么  冲他们摇硬币罐吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}To do what? Shake a can of nickels at them?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.36,0:13:50.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们太杞人忧天了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're being ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.19,0:13:54.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那么漂亮的女人是不可能试图勾引谢尔顿·库珀的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's no way a woman that attractive is trying to seduce Sheldon Cooper.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.24,0:13:58.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你的自我安慰牌打完了没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You done trying to make yourself feel better?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.62,0:14:02.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没  我还没打种族歧视牌呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No. I haven't played the race card yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.79,0:14:06.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想打断聚会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, I hate to break up the party,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.12,0:14:10.42,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但艾米说我累了  必须上床睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but Amy says I'm tired and have to go to bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.59,0:14:14.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴见到大家  多谢你们的晚餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It was nice seeing everybody.Thank you for dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.92,0:14:16.01,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-不客气  -我们的荣幸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Sure. - Our pleasure.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.18,0:14:17.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,随便啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whatever.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.43,0:14:21.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-要送我上车吗  -当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Walk me to my car?  -Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.64,0:14:23.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起送\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We'll all go.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.66,0:14:40.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,借过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.50,0:14:54.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  我过去下  好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Pardon. I just need to... yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.14,0:15:07.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真好玩  像玩"马里奥赛车"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was fun. It was like Mario Kart.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.36,0:15:13.44,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,拜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.53,0:15:15.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.28,0:15:19.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是关于莱纳德和艾米的事吗  我也不爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wh-- Is this about Leonard and Amy? I don't like it either.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.03,0:15:25.54,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在女人方面经验不足\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I know you don't have a lot of experience with women,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.70,0:15:28.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但拉蒙娜似乎对你有意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but Ramona seems to have a romantic interest in you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.42,0:15:32.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这根本没道理  她知道我有女朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That doesn't make any sense. She knows I have a girlfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.34,0:15:34.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有时候女人不在乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, sometimes women don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.55,0:15:36.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有时候这令她们更想要这个男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sometimes it makes them want a guy even more.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.05,0:15:41.14,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可能是这样  但诺维茨基博士只是朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That may be true,but Dr. Nowitzki's just a friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.30,0:15:43.64,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  如果她没穿那件突显\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In fact, I wouldn't have even noticed she's a woman
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.80,0:15:46.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她胸部的泳衣的话  我都没注意到她是女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}if she hadn't worn that bathing suit that highlighted her bosom.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.52,0:15:52.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们换个说法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Um... ...let's try this.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.69,0:15:56.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把你自己想象成那种喜欢收集限量版玩具公仔的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Think of yourself as one of those limited edition toys people like to collect.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.03,0:15:59.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我一直是这样想的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I already do.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.66,0:16:02.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你就会明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, then you get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.57,0:16:06.91,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为我是独一无二的  我更有价值\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because there's only one of me,I'm more valuable.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.08,0:16:08.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.54,0:16:09.58,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Although,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.75,0:16:13.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾米已经把我从包装盒中拿出来玩过了  我掉价了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Amy's already taken me out of my package and played with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.42,0:16:19.84,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别管玩具这个比喻了  也许\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's forget the toy thing, okay? Um, maybe...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.01,0:16:24.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮  感谢你的关心  但我不觉得事情是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Penny, look. I appreciate your concern,but I don't think that's what's happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.93,0:16:27.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你觉得事情是怎样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right. What do you think is happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.85,0:16:30.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得诺维茨基博士是一位友好的同事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think Dr. Nowitzki is a friendly colleague.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.10,0:16:34.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你和莱纳德需要见婚姻咨询师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I think you and Leonard need to see a marriage counselor.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.69,0:16:39.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我需要去更新简历加上游泳这项特殊技能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I need to update my resume to include swimming as a special skill.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.91,0:16:50.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别这样看着我  我尽力了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't look at me like that, I tried.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.46,0:16:59.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你吃了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, did you eat yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.30,0:17:02.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,吃了早餐  没吃中餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, breakfast yes, lunch no.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.22,0:17:03.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我服用了止咳糖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I did have a cough drop,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.59,0:17:06.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但这是介于吸和吃之间的行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but that really rides the line between sucking and eating.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.97,0:17:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  我给咱俩做了三明治\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, perfect. I made us sandwiches.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.77,0:17:11.31,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是周到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How thoughtful.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.48,0:17:13.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢你  -没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}-Thank you.  -No big deal,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.69,0:17:15.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢和你在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I enjoy spending time with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.52,0:17:17.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.48,0:17:19.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,问一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Question:
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.32,0:17:23.11,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是想和我发展恋爱关系吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}are you seeking a romantic relationship with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.70,0:17:25.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果我是呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What if I were?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.87,0:17:29.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这会引起一系列的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that would raise a number of problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.29,0:17:31.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们是同事  我现在有女友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We're colleagues.I'm currently in a relation...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.01,0:17:42.34,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,恕我失陪一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Excuse me a moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.32,0:18:45.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,艾米  艾米  艾米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Amy. Amy. Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.05,0:19:04.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意嫁给我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Will you marry me?

