[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.2.2012.322
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.68,0:00:06.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉杰 衣服标签跑出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Raj, your tag is sticking out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.36,0:00:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  这是我大概两年来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you. That was the closest I've come to sex
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.21,0:00:10.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,离做爱最接近的一次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in, like, two years.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.47,0:00:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我觉得有点恶心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now I feel a little gross.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.94,0:00:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这话更让我觉得像做爱了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're only making it seem more real for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.97,0:00:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我老婆好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, that's my wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.44,0:00:22.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有人让她觉得做爱很恶心  那也只能是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If anyone's gonna make her feel gross about sex, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.95,0:00:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能聊点除了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Can we please talk about something
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.39,0:00:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我悲催的情场之外的事情吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}other than my depressing love life?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.02,0:00:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那聊聊佩妮悲催的演艺事业吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How about Penny's depressing acting career?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.91,0:00:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是有些不顺遂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, it's been a little tough,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.43,0:00:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但佩妮是在勇敢追梦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but Penny's following her dreams,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.95,0:00:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我心中的小本子里  那才不悲催\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and in my book, that is not depressing.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.09,0:00:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢支持\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Aw... Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.63,0:00:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的小本子书名是《撒谎骗炮大全》吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is that book called Lies I Tell to Get Sex?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.58,0:00:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这书是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is that a real book?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.56,0:00:44.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果真有  我一定拜读啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I would totally read that book.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.18,0:00:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你看完能借我也读读吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Can I borrow it when you're done?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.88,0:00:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,姐就跟你们分享一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, I'll have you guys know
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.90,0:00:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我上周才推掉一部戏约\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I turned down a part in a movie last week.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.08,0:00:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要推掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why would you do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.18,0:00:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那角色太狗屎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because it was crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.29,0:00:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我以前演过的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's a sequel to that awful
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.44,0:01:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs40\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}第七季第一集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.44,0:01:00.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀手猩猩电影的续集\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}killer gorilla movie I was in.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.53,0:01:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《杀人恶猿》吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Serial Ape-ist?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.66,0:01:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是在电影里被砍死了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I thought you died in that.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.10,0:01:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She does.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.87,0:01:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在电影的42分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}42 minutes in.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.10,0:01:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时她正裸身淋浴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}while showering topless,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.45,0:01:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是跟其他学生会女生打完枕头仗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}16 minutes after brief side butt
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.04,0:01:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还小露了一下侧屁的16分钟后被杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}during a pillow fight with her sorority sisters.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.37,0:01:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有过目不忘的记忆力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have an eidetic memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.81,0:01:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他忘吃什么药我就不知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know what his problem is.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.67,0:01:20.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这集里没有淋浴戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, well, there are no shower scenes in this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.69,0:01:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们试图从我遗体中克隆出新的我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They just try to clone me from my corpse,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.38,0:01:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我的基因跟杀人猩的基因混到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but my DNA gets mixed with the ape's DNA
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.39,0:01:28.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我得用猩猩的巨手巨脚到处跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I end up running around with giant gorilla hands and feet.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.35,0:01:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我漏掉什么点了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Am I missing something,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.73,0:01:33.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这角色不就是完全为她而设的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}or isn't that the part she was born to play?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.45,0:02:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的不去演这电影吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So are you really not gonna do this movie?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.03,0:02:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这个角色对我的演艺生涯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, I don't think it's the kind of part
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.42,0:02:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有丝毫帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that's good for my career.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.29,0:02:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是很多知名演员刚出道时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, but don't a lot of famous actors
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.42,0:02:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不都是从垃圾电影开始演的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}get their start doing bad movies?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.55,0:02:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但梅丽尔·斯特里普应该没碰到过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, I don't think Meryl Streep ever had to say...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.72,0:02:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs40\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}梅丽尔·斯特里普  美国电影史上最伟大的女演员之一
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.08,0:02:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"得制止这双猩猩手再去杀人"的电影吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"must keep gorilla hands from killing again!"
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.42,0:02:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她真演了  一定也很赞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If she did, it would be amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.74,0:02:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这女人真是演什么像什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That woman can do no wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.43,0:02:26.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对演艺界完全不了解\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I-I don't know anything about show business,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.26,0:02:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以如果你觉得推掉有酬工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}so if you think it's reasonable to turn down paid work
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.82,0:02:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续花光自己的积蓄是正确的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and just burn through your savings,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.23,0:02:32.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我绝对相信你脑子没抽风\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sure you know what you're doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.04,0:02:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们该走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I think we're gonna go.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.72,0:02:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.73,0:02:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是在取笑别人失败的事业吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We were making fun of failed careers.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.28,0:02:47.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都还没聊到真正的大笑点霍华德身上呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We didn't get to tap the juicy vein that is Howard's.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.17,0:02:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你不是在同一间大学工作吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, I work at the same university you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.83,0:02:53.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  但就像鹰眼侠也在复仇者联盟中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yes, and Hawkeye's in the avengers,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.29,0:02:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有听过人喊"救命啊  鹰眼侠"吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but no one ever says, "Help, Hawkeye!"
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.60,0:02:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能问你个问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Can I ask you something?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.19,0:03:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你总是要吐槽贬低我老公啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why do you constantly feel the need to put down my husband?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.08,0:03:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他一定是吐槽出于情  贬低更是爱吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, I'm sure he does it out of love.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.84,0:03:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我男朋友不也这么对我  好让我对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The same way my boyfriend makes me feel terrible
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.97,0:03:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的人生决定感到难受吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}about my life choices.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.14,0:03:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们真的要走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I think we're gonna go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.38,0:03:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用不用  这不是吵架\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, no. This is not a fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.46,0:03:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是本来很高兴有人给你戏约嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I-I was just excited that someone offered you a part
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.53,0:03:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但后来有点惊讶你居然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and a little surprised that you'd rather sit at home
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.25,0:03:21.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,宁愿在家闲着  也不愿意去演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and do nothing than take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.43,0:03:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在是吵架了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now it's a fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.50,0:03:29.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们那边说清楚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, with that sorted out,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.77,0:03:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也很乐意来回答你的问题  伯纳黛特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm happy to answer your question, Bernadette.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.73,0:03:33.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是霍华德先开始的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard started it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.38,0:03:35.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都没干好吗  我就坐着而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I didn't do anything. I was just sitting here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.81,0:03:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是指今晚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I wasn't referring to this evening.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.44,0:03:39.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10年前  我与他初次相见时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ten years ago, upon first seeing me,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.83,0:03:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你老公说我长得像《星球大战》里的C-3PO\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}your husband claimed that I looked like C-3PO
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.83,0:03:42.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs40\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}金色的人形机器人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.31,0:03:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,与皮·威·赫尔曼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and Pee-wee Herman.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.31,0:03:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs40\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}上世纪80年代的喜剧电视  电影角色\N与谢尔顿外形有些神似
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.29,0:03:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他还叫我C-3P威赫尔曼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And he called me C-3P-wee Herman.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.80,0:03:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10年后还是很好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Still funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.88,0:03:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那都是10年前了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That was ten years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.90,0:04:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在9年11个月又3周前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nine years, 11 months and three weeks ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.42,0:04:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他随后又偷偷换掉了我教课的幻灯片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}he followed that up by replacing the slides for my lecture
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.56,0:04:08.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,改成了一张裸身肥女人弯腰露屁股的照片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}with photographs of nude fat women bending over.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.73,0:04:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.87,0:04:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他那堂课在教宇宙的气体云嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The lecture was on cosmic gas clouds.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.31,0:04:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,胖子放屁成宇宙云  超好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's funny!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.37,0:04:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时我在  真的超好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I was there. It was funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.73,0:04:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而在那之后  他开始了长达10年的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In any event, that began a decade-long progression
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.94,0:04:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各种羞辱  恶整  还给我订各种奇怪杂志\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}of insults, pranks and unwanted magazine subscriptions.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.01,0:04:31.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直到现在  我还每个月都收到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To this day, I still get a monthly copy
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.94,0:04:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《老奶奶床战老奶奶》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}of Granny on Granny.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.68,0:04:37.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了出乎意料好玩的智力游戏页面之外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Which, other than its surprisingly fun puzzle page,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.60,0:04:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,整本都龌龊不堪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is complete filth.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.85,0:04:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你陪走到停车位那\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thanks for walking me to my car.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.24,0:04:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我也想谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Actually, it's for both of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.89,0:04:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚我看了电影《西区故事》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Last night, I watched West Side Story,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.89,0:04:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs40\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}由音乐剧改编成电影的音乐歌舞帮派爱情故事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.43,0:04:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在有点害怕街头帮派\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I'm a little freaked out by street gangs.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.23,0:04:53.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么拉杰找不到女友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why can't Raj find a girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.86,0:04:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来这问题找不到答案啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The mystery continues.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.22,0:04:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我不喜欢你挖苦我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't appreciate your sarcasm,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.83,0:05:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还有两个街区  所以我唯有忍忍了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but we've still got two blocks to go, so I'll put up with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.34,0:05:06.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你网上交友进行得如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Whatever happened with your online dating?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.08,0:05:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人回复我  所以我也懒得登上去看了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No one was writing me back, so I stopped checking my profile.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.11,0:05:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在遇见谢尔顿前  我也准备要放弃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Before I met Sheldon, I was ready to give up, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.62,0:05:14.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还曾去拜访过我的妇产科医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Once, I even dropped in on my OB/GYN
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.69,0:05:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只为寻求跟人类有肉体接触的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}just to get some human contact.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.92,0:05:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貌似我的前列腺也好久没检查了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It has been a while since I got my prostate checked.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.92,0:05:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我遇见了谢尔顿  你看我们现在进展多快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then I met Sheldon and look at where we are now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.72,0:05:28.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有吗  你们交往三年才接过一次吻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What? You've kissed, like, once in three years.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.88,0:05:32.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒是  你爱干嘛干嘛吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's true. Do whatever you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.97,0:05:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.94,0:05:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在想  或许你和我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Listen, I was thinking you and I could
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.22,0:05:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以试着成为更好的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}probably try to be better friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.39,0:05:45.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.80,0:05:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们现在就好得有点过分了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I was thinking what we have now is a bit much.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.03,0:05:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  我昨晚和伯纳黛特谈过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Seriously, I was talking to Bernadette last night and...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.40,0:05:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说得很有道理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}she made some great points.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.79,0:06:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都认识彼此这么长时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You and I have known each other a long time,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.91,0:06:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后面的我没听进去  因为她把胸罩脱掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I didn't hear the rest 'cause she took her bra off.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.85,0:06:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Very well.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.61,0:06:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你觉得我们应该如何增进友谊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How do you propose we move forward?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.87,0:06:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先我们可以停止羞辱对方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Uh, for starters, we could stop insulting each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.10,0:06:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个主意真棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's a great idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.70,0:06:20.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本着我们休战新协议的友好精神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And in the spirit of our new arrangement,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.68,0:06:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会掩饰我对你想出这主意的惊讶之情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I will mask my surprise that you came up with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.91,0:06:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  这周末太空总署邀请我去休斯顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Anyway, I got invited to do a little talk at NASA
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.84,0:06:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做一个小演讲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in Houston this weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.22,0:06:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们给我提供了两张机票  但伯纳黛特去不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They gave me two tickets. Bernadette can't go.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.79,0:06:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想跟我一起去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want to come with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.11,0:06:38.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以顺便去看看你妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You can visit your mom,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.35,0:06:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以带你参观太空中心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I'll show you around the space center.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.18,0:06:44.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have one question.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.34,0:06:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个恶作剧吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is this a prank...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.97,0:06:47.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会不会我们一到达休斯顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}where we land in Houston
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.83,0:06:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里会张贴着你做好的通缉令\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and you've made up wanted posters
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.62,0:06:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面是我长着小胡子的照片  和一个西班牙名\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that have my face with a mustache and a Spanish name
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.58,0:06:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我会被逮捕并被遣送回南美洲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and then I get arrested and deported to South America?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.44,0:06:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.38,0:07:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就放心了  因为我肯定料不到你会这么玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm glad because I would not have seen that coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.85,0:07:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾米  我想请你帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Amy, I could use some help.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.40,0:07:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜猜  是不是有位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh. Let me guess. There's an...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.80,0:07:10.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着皮衣的男大学生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}undergrad in a leather jacket
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.27,0:07:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在饮水机那里打着响指[西区故事中的混混]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}snapping his fingers by the water fountain.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.06,0:07:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认真想过你昨晚说的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I thought about what you said last night,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.48,0:07:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我再次登上交友网站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I went back on the dating Web site
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.48,0:07:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看见了这个女生的个人资料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I was looking at this girl's profile.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.77,0:07:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她太完美了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She's amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.14,0:07:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她长得不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, she's cute.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.47,0:07:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还很聪明  美国大学优等生荣誉学会会员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And smart. Phi Beta Kappa.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.51,0:07:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从她没有喉结这点可以判断出\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And judging by her lack of Adam's apple,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.04,0:07:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她这辈子一直都是女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}she's been female her entire life.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.46,0:07:35.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢女人这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I like that in a woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.25,0:07:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  你需要我帮什么忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Great, so what do you need me for?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.30,0:07:40.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一晚没睡给她写了一封信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, I was up all night trying to write to her,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.11,0:07:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想先听听你的意见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but I wanted to run it by you first.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.97,0:07:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.43,0:07:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"艾米丽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Emily,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.25,0:07:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的脸颊就像被露珠吻过的花朵那么娇嫩"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}your face is like a precious dew-kissed flower..."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.89,0:07:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  很有震撼力吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know. Powerful stuff, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.30,0:07:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.18,0:07:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该做自己  而不是像个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're supposed to be yourself, not all...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.76,0:08:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,饥渴又吓人的变态\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}desperate and creepy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.03,0:08:04.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是那样的变态啊  那到底还要不要做自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, I'm getting some mixed messages here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.21,0:08:08.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就写一些普通的东西  比如"我看了你的资料\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just say something normal like, "I saw your profile.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.29,0:08:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,似乎咱俩有很多共同之处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Looks like we have a lot in common;
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.42,0:08:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有空一起去喝杯咖啡吧"  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- let's get a cup of coffee sometime."  - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.85,0:08:14.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"喝咖啡时  我会嫉妒咖啡杯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Where I can be jealous of the cup
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.67,0:08:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它能碰触你红宝石般的双唇"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}touching your ruby lips."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.31,0:08:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者干脆你帮我写吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Or you just write it for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.86,0:08:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不要假扮你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not gonna pretend to be you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.39,0:08:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是要你假扮我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't want you to pretend to be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.97,0:08:26.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以当我的网络泡妞搭档\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You can be like my, uh, online wingman.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.22,0:08:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好比如果我们是在酒吧遇到她  你就在一旁使劲夸我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Like if we met her at a bar and you talked me up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.07,0:08:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我应该跟她说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, what would I say to her?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.08,0:08:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉她我是个什么样的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just tell her what I'm really like.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.08,0:08:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你觉得有帮助的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And, if you think it'll help,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.35,0:08:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以说你曾见过我换衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that you saw me changing once
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.65,0:08:41.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的鸡鸡让你想到美洲虎肌肉发达的尾巴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and my package reminded you of the muscular tail of a jaguar.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.07,0:08:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用你自己的话去表达吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Use your own words.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.78,0:08:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你载我去药房\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thanks again for taking me to the pharmacy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.00,0:08:57.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别客气  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, it's no problem. Is everything okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.11,0:08:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事  这只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, I'm fine. It's just some, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.77,0:09:01.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为我的旅行准备的胃药\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}stomach medication for my trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.07,0:09:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然可能性极小 但不排除\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's the remote yet distinct possibility
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.03,0:09:07.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可能会沦落到南美洲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that I may end up in South America.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.74,0:09:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得以前我会问你一些蠢问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Remember the old days when I would've said something dumb
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.81,0:09:13.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如像"为什么"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}like "why?"
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.73,0:09:19.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这声音听起来不妙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Uh, that doesn't sound good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.35,0:09:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还记得以前我会指出你上车后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Remember the old days when I used to point out
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.28,0:09:25.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该检查发动机警示灯是否亮着吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that your check engine light was on?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.92,0:09:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-记得  -少女  准备重温旧梦吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Yes. - Well, get ready to stroll down memory lane:
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.19,0:09:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮  你检查发动机...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Penny, your check engine...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.28,0:09:31.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道灯是亮着的  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, I know it's on, Sheldon!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.54,0:09:32.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别别别  不要啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.88,0:09:35.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在可付不起修车费\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I cannot afford this right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.29,0:09:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许只是小问题而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe it's just something minor.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.92,0:09:49.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好消息是那警示灯灭了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ooh, good news, the light just went out.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.59,0:09:56.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是各玩各的还是组队玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are we playing individual or teams?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.20,0:09:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,组队有意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Teams are fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.28,0:09:58.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样的话  那我希望和我的好朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, in that case, I'd like to be partnered
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.67,0:10:00.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德组队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}with my good friend Howard.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.40,0:10:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可霍华德从来都跟我组队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I'm always on Howard's team.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.07,0:10:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们才是最好的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're best friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.60,0:10:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种默契好到能完成对方的句...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The kind who finish each others...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.38,0:10:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不觉得我们有做这..  -这种事  你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- I really don't think we do tha... - ...do that! See?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.61,0:10:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,修车行怎么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, how'd it go at the mechanic?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.05,0:10:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不太妙  能借一步说话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not great. Can I talk to you for a sec?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.64,0:10:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.42,0:10:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能跟你们一起去休斯顿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe I can go with you guys to Houston?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.09,0:10:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在买机票是不是有点...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Isn't it a little late to get plane tick...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.34,0:10:29.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...有点晚吗  没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}...plane tickets? Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.75,0:10:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你别再闹...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Will you please sto...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.56,0:10:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...别再闹了  好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}...stop that? Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.86,0:10:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不知道该如何是好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.65,0:10:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的车坏了  彻底报废了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My car threw a rod and it's totaled.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.10,0:10:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我工作也没了  又买不起新车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can't afford a new one, I have no job,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.78,0:10:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我连试镜都没办法去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and now I can't drive to auditions.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.39,0:10:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.99,0:10:44.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这件事你不爱听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know it's a sensitive subject,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.90,0:10:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你能重新考虑一下那个电影角色吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but can you reconsider that part in the movie?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.22,0:10:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我考虑了  我打了电话  人家不要我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I did. I called them. The part's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.60,0:10:51.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个角色已经被别人抢走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They gave it to someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.35,0:10:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在那姑娘马上就要一夜成名\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now that girl's gonna get discovered and become famous
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.54,0:10:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后去访谈秀大聊特聊她是如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and go on Letterman and talk about
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.67,0:10:56.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从一部廉价的猴子电影中一举成名的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}how she got her big break on a cheap monkey movie
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.85,0:11:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都多亏了某个傻妞当初不屑去演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}all because some dumb girl thought it was beneath her.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.45,0:11:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你至少还在访谈秀上被提起了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}At least they talked about you on Letterman.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.43,0:11:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样  你想去哪儿  我都开车载你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Come on, I can drive you wherever you need to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.55,0:11:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么可能  你和我不一样  你有工作呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How? Unlike me, you have a job.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.43,0:11:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我唯有回去当我的服务员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm just gonna have to go back to being a waitress...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.84,0:11:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这将成为我一辈子的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}...like I will be for the rest of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.73,0:11:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德  你麻利一点好不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Leonard, would you wrap it up?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.94,0:11:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都在等你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're waiting on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.61,0:11:21.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  是不是我苦难的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry, is the fact that my life's falling apart
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.63,0:11:24.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打扰到您崇高的桌游了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}interfering with your board game?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.07,0:11:26.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It is.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.67,0:11:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你错了  吾友霍华德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You were wrong, friend Howard.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.23,0:11:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她完全能理解我们的状况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She completely understood.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.22,0:11:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在忙吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, you busy?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.33,0:11:38.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不忙  什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No. What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.59,0:11:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾米丽回信了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Have you heard back from Emily?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.83,0:11:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.93,0:11:43.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Great! And?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.49,0:11:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怕她觉得你俩不合适\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I'm afraid she doesn't think you're right for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.80,0:11:51.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给了你一个这么简单的任务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I give you one simple thing to do--
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.73,0:11:53.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,联系一个素未谋面的陌生人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}contact a complete stranger
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.56,0:11:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她爱上我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and make her fall in love with me--
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.67,0:11:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你却连这都办砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and you blow it!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.47,0:12:00.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把你的好都告诉她了  可是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I told her what a good guy you are, but
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.28,0:12:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她觉得你不肯亲自给她写信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}she thought it was a bad sign
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.90,0:12:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就不是什么好兆头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that you didn't write to her yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.15,0:12:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她觉得你显得太害羞  太被动了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She thought it made you seem too shy and passive.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.13,0:12:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家才不害羞和被动呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not too shy and passive.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.70,0:12:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你马上回信给她   把我的话告诉她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You write her back and tell her I said that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.30,0:12:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然  等你有空的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, when you have a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.51,0:12:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明晚我会试着改变她的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look, I'll see if I can change her mind tomorrow night.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.25,0:12:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天晚上有什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's happening tomorrow night?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.83,0:12:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要和她出来喝咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm meeting her for coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.21,0:12:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.14,0:12:26.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们后来发了几次邮件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, we just... we e-mailed back and forth a bit,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.06,0:12:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发现我俩还挺合拍的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and we kind of hit it off.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.41,0:12:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我找到了梦中情人  你却要把她抢走  -才不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- I find a girl I like, and you're stealing her?! - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.62,0:12:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是发现两人有很多共同点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We just ended up having a lot in common.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.93,0:12:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都是哈佛毕业  我们都喜欢乔叟[英国作家]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We went to Harvard, we like Chaucer,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.83,0:12:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都疯狂喜欢缝花被子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}we're both hardcore into quilting.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.47,0:12:41.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的一字一句都像是冷冷的酸雨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Your words fall like acid rain
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.47,0:12:44.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我破碎的心上胡乱地拍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}on the wounded petals of my heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.49,0:12:47.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.38,0:12:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说他马上就下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He says he'll be down in a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.54,0:12:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.93,0:12:54.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不确认你车里没有空气清新剂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, he's not coming out until he sees proof
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.11,0:12:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就不会出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you don't have an air freshener in your car.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.41,0:13:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个周末你肯定度日如年了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is gonna be a long weekend for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.87,0:13:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明明是你要我这么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're the reason I'm doing it!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.76,0:13:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是让你们不要再互相攻击了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I said to stop insulting each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.68,0:13:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又没叫你和他一起共度浪漫周末\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I didn't tell you to take him on a romantic getaway.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.18,0:13:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么知道你都说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How do I know what you said?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.85,0:13:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都怪你和你那对"化言语为无声"的大咪咪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Damn you and your noise-cancelling breasts.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.76,0:13:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.80,0:13:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好啊  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Hi. - Hey, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.29,0:13:21.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要去德克萨斯了  开心吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You excited for Texas?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.70,0:13:23.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然开心了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, very much so.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.49,0:13:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能和真正的宇航员去太空总署  千载难逢啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's not every day you get to tour NASA with a real astronaut.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.06,0:13:30.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个真正的宇航员是谁呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who's the real astronaut?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.65,0:13:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,巴斯·奥尔德林[传奇宇航员]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Buzz Aldrin.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.00,0:13:36.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh. Yay!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.19,0:13:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.84,0:13:51.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.18,0:13:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.12,0:13:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What now?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.99,0:14:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去上厕所了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have to go to the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.13,0:14:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是刚去了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You just went to the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.18,0:14:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没上  因为感觉不太安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I didn't use it because it didn't seem safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.94,0:14:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我曾多次发邮件  马桶还是没加装安全带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Despite all my e-mails, the toilet didn't have a seatbelt.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.17,0:14:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在也还是没有啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, it still doesn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.79,0:14:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  前面贪杯喝苹果汁时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I realize that, but safety concerns went out the window
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.64,0:14:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把安全问题抛之脑后了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}two apple juices ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.84,0:14:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.01,0:14:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么这么心烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why are you getting annoyed?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.17,0:14:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我努力当一个更好的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm trying to be a better friend,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.84,0:14:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不断说些烦人的话  做些烦人的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but you constantly say and do irritating things.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.07,0:14:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么时候  -什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Like when? - When?!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.94,0:14:31.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前在车里时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How about in the car?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.89,0:14:34.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是宇航员  你知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm an astronaut, and you know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.35,0:14:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是不愿承认  因为你嫉妒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You just don't like admitting it, because you're jealous.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.76,0:14:42.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, truth be told,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.77,0:14:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候的确梦想过上太空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}as a child, I did dream of going to space.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.49,0:14:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些宇航员是我的英雄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Those astronauts were my heroes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.61,0:14:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.04,0:14:52.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也上太空了  我挺难接受的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}when you got to go, it was hard for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.90,0:14:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.06,0:14:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这让我意识到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because it made me realize
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.08,0:14:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个人就能被太空总署送上去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}they'll just send anyone up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.78,0:15:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不打算让我出去了吗  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Aren't you going to let me out? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.56,0:15:05.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是需要上洗手间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I still need to use the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.64,0:15:07.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你  发挥创意吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here you go. Be creative.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.30,0:15:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦  害怕小小的乱流吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's the matter? Scared of a little turbulence?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.94,0:15:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不害怕  乱流只是大气中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, turbulence is just the equalization
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.34,0:15:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昼夜温差的均衡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}of diurnal temperature variations in the atmosphere.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.18,0:15:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一点也不怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not scared at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.72,0:15:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,苹果汁  别出来啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, apple juice, stay where you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.53,0:15:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这算什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, this is nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.87,0:15:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以"假宇航员"身份\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I experienced way worse
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.23,0:15:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乘飞船垂直降落重返地球时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}when I was plummeting back to Earth,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.09,0:15:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那滋味才叫一个难受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}apparently not being a real astronaut.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.97,0:15:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  刚才那下挺严重的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, that was a big one.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.72,0:15:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我收回刚才的话  我害怕乱流\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I take it back. I'm scared of turbulence!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.30,0:15:43.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把呕吐袋还给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm gonna need that bag back.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.00,0:15:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定要这么做吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You sure you want to do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.36,0:15:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  我为什么不想要回原来的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. Why wouldn't I want to get my old job back?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.54,0:15:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到大家一定"很有意思"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It'll be fun to see everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.12,0:15:53.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最后一次跟大家说的是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I haven't talked to them since I said,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.67,0:15:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"姐辞职了  奥斯卡颁奖礼见  贱人们"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"I quit. See you at the Oscars, bitches."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.78,0:15:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  早搞完早收工\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Come on, let's just get this over with.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.66,0:16:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"早搞完早收工"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Let's get this over with."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.12,0:16:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这是要开车送你去芝士工厂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Am I driving you to the Cheesecake Factory,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.78,0:16:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是我们要做爱啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}or are we having sex?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.07,0:16:07.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想逗你乐一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm just... I'm trying to lighten the mood.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.77,0:16:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道  谢谢  -抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- I know. Thank you. - Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.62,0:16:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太丢人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's just so humiliating.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.16,0:16:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太丢人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So humiliating?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.73,0:16:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这是要开车送你去芝士工厂还...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Am I driving you to the Cheesecake Factory...?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.31,0:16:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我不说了  我不说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry. I'll-I'll stop. I'll stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.07,0:16:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  别这么伤心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Come on, don't look so sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.00,0:16:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你永远不知道未来会发生什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You never know what's gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.08,0:16:23.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许今晚会非常棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe tonight will be great.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.42,0:16:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我知道你在努力安慰我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sweetie, I know you're trying to make me feel better,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.14,0:16:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你这么体贴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I love you for that,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.00,0:16:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这让我更难受了  而且我有点讨厌你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but it's making me feel worse, and I kind of hate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.76,0:16:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是你的车啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This isn't your car.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.96,0:16:36.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我想我们开你的车去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know. I thought we'd take yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.50,0:16:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.99,0:16:43.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然不是豪车  但至少你去试镜能有代步工具\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's nothing fancy, but it'll get you to auditions,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.28,0:16:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少现在  你不用回去做服务员了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and at least for now, you don't have to go back to waitressing.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.70,0:16:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道该说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know what to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.30,0:16:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么也不用说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't say anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.92,0:16:56.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.80,0:16:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以说"谢谢你"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, you could say, "thank you."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.99,0:17:00.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确送了辆车给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I did just buy you a car.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.85,0:17:06.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我承认拉杰什\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look, I admit that it's odd
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.58,0:17:08.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不亲自写信给你是有些奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that Rajesh didn't write to you himself,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.46,0:17:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你了解他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but if you get to know him,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.71,0:17:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就会知道他只是个亲切的普通人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you'll see he's just a sweet, regular guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.01,0:17:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为有趣的对比  他来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}As a counterpoint, here he is,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.33,0:17:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不速之客兼大汗淋漓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}uninvited and visibly sweaty.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.71,0:17:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  艾米丽  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Hello, Emily. - Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.42,0:17:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾米告诉我你担心我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Amy told me you were concerned that
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.77,0:17:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能太过被动与害羞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I might be too passive and shy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.45,0:17:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问你个事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let me ask you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.15,0:17:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个被动的人会闯进这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Would a passive guy barge in here
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.83,0:17:28.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着你的眼睛说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to look you in the eye and say,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.38,0:17:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"嘿  露水吻过的鲜花  你好啊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Hey, dew-kissed flower, what's up?"
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.31,0:17:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  但没有下限的变态可能会说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, but a weird guy with no boundaries might.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.46,0:17:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这是另外的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Uh, okay, that's a separate issue.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.19,0:17:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们先把这问题摆一边  专注于"被动"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let's put a pin in that and just focus on the passive thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.97,0:17:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.23,0:17:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们周五还去乔叟读书会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are we still going to go to that Chaucer reading Friday?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.49,0:17:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我还是一个人去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, I think I'm just gonna go by myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.22,0:17:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算不上是我最棒的初次约会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not my best first date.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.30,0:17:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也算不上是最差劲的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, but not my worst, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.96,0:18:05.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就以前对你说过的刻薄话做过的刻薄事道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry for every mean thing I ever did or said to you!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.15,0:18:07.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也道歉  全是我的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry, too! It's all my fault!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.92,0:18:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有你这个朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you weren't my friend,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.12,0:18:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的人生会若有所失\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}there'd be a hole in my life!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.79,0:18:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you, Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.45,0:18:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就好像剧集《萤火虫》被砍了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Kind of like when Firefly was cancelled.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.59,0:18:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但失落感没那么严重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But not as big.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.22,0:18:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,机长已经关闭了安全带指示灯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The captain has turned off the fasten seat belt sign.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.63,0:18:31.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位可以在机舱内走动了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're now free to move about the cabin.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.26,0:18:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-结束了  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- It's over. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.07,0:18:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是不是应该松开对方的手了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Should we stop holding hands now?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.63,0:18:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-等会吧  -太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- In a minute. - Okay, good.

