[Script Info]
;Auto-Generated by SPDSRT

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.00,0:02:45.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs24\1c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HFF8000&}生活大爆炸\N{\fs22\1c&H00FFFF&\3c&H000000&}第三季第十七集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.35,0:00:06.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我总是出力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why do I always have to carry the heavy stuff?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.09,0:00:07.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很简单啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, it's very simple.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.89,0:00:10.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在我们这群一无所有的破烂科学家当中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In our ragtag band of scientists with nothing to lose,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.99,0:00:12.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我负责动脑子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm the smart one,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.42,0:00:13.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,沃罗威茨负责搞笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wolowitz is the funny one,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.79,0:00:15.85,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,库萨帕里是一个奋力想要融入我们的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and Koothrappali is the lovable foreigner
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.89,0:00:18.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但是以失败告终的可爱的老外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}who struggles to understand our ways and fails.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.65,0:00:23.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你别无选择  只有肌肉男了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That leaves you, by default, as the muscle.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.39,0:00:27.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再多搬一层  我就肌肉难了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}One more floor, and I'd be the pulled muscle.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.49,0:00:31.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来的正好 我要饿死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, it's about time. I'm starving.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.09,0:00:33.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个  其实我们没带中国菜回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Um, well, we didn't actually get Chinese food.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.65,0:00:36.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-为什么啊  -淡定 这个更赞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Why not?  - Don't panic. This is better.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.29,0:00:39.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧 你们不会用食物换了魔豆吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, no. You didn't trade the food for magic beans, did you?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.79,0:00:42.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.42,0:00:44.25,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,况且严格来说  魔豆也是食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And technically, magic beans would be food.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:46.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,虽然吃了它们怪浪费的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Although eating them would be quite a waste,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.42,0:00:47.75,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,因为你可以种植它们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}since you could plant them,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.79,0:00:49.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,然后一夜之间  就会长成一株巨大的豆茎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and overnight, have a giant beanstalk,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.35,0:00:52.22,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,足够一个小城市吃的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}which would provide enough roughage for a small city.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.25,0:00:54.45,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实有时候我根本没听你说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, sometimes I don't listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.49,0:00:57.15,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只是看着你的下巴一上一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sometimes I just watch your jaw go up and down.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.42,0:01:00.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们去中餐馆的路上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We were on our way to the Chinese restaurant
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.35,0:01:01.62,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,貌似看见了亚当·韦斯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}when we thought we saw Adam West,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.69,0:01:03.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,（亚当·韦斯特:《蝙蝠侠》的扮演者）
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.62,0:01:02.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我们就跟着他走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}so we followed him.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.72,0:01:03.82,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁是亚当·韦斯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who's Adam West?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.85,0:01:06.02,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁是亚当·韦斯特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who's Adam West?!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.05,0:01:09.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德  你们性交之后都聊些什么啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Leonard, what do the two of you talk about after the coitus?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.75,0:01:14.52,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我猜是  "哇塞  4分钟  新纪录啊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My guess is, "Hey, four minutes! New record!"
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.72,0:01:19.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才负责搞笑啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's why I'm the funny one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.69,0:01:22.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正呢  我们跟着他到了旧货出售摊儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Anyway, we followed the guy to this garage sale,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.15,0:01:23.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那卖的东西都超赞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and they had the coolest stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.72,0:01:24.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他们正好关门大甩卖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They were closing up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.82,0:01:26.65,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这一箱子东西才60块\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We got this whole box for 60 bucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.69,0:01:28.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们还没来得及看清都有什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We didn't even get to go through it all.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.09,0:01:29.35,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说不定有什么宝贝呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There could be anything in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.39,0:01:32.12,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看看有没有新女朋友 说不定你需要一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There a new girlfriend in there? 'Cause you might need one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.15,0:01:33.95,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.99,0:01:37.32,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过有《捉鬼敢死队》的原版终稿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But there is an original final draft Ghostbusters script
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.35,0:01:39.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上面真的有黏液的污迹哎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}with actual slime stains!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.95,0:01:41.55,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, you're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.59,0:01:42.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个是《捉鬼敢死队2》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's Ghostbusters 2.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.82,0:01:44.05,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没看头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Never mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.50,0:01:47.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我滴神啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.53,0:01:53.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是阿福娃娃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}An Alf doll.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.93,0:01:56.38,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我11岁时  我妈在我爸去世后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When I was 11, my mother got me one 
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.38,0:01:58.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,给我买了一个 让我能睡好觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to help me sleep after my dad left.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.70,0:02:02.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我那时候会假装 爸爸是去了蜜胺树脂星球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I used to pretend that my dad had moved to the planet Melmac,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.93,0:02:07.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而阿福会把他带回我身边的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and Alf was going to bring him back to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.36,0:02:09.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但它从来也没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But he never did.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.30,0:02:12.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸在哪儿  小玩偶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where's my daddy, puppet?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.36,0:02:18.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.36,0:02:21.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太伤感了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That is so sad.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.40,0:02:23.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不  更伤感的是你居然不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, what's sad is that you don't know
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.60,0:02:26.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,亚当·韦斯特是电视版蝙蝠侠的扮演者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Adam West was TV's Batman.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.70,0:02:55.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,史波克的脑袋(波克:《星际迷航》中的人物)\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here's Spock's head with no body.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.20,0:02:59.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,T先生的身子(Mr.T:《星际迷航》中的人物)\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here's Mr.T's body with no head.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.70,0:03:03.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,啊在这儿  史波克的身子配T先生的脑袋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, yeah, here's Spock's body with Mr.T's head.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.47,0:03:08.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我同情那些没有逻辑的傻瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I pity the fool who's illogical.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.60,0:03:13.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我要回家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, I'm just gonna go home
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.97,0:03:17.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,做一个烤干酪  然后上eHarmony 意淫去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and make a grilled cheese and window-shop on eHarmony.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.83,0:03:16.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,（eHarmony:美国线上交友网站）
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.17,0:03:20.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好的  拜拜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.73,0:03:22.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,妥了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.33,0:03:25.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,哇塞  快看  《夺宝奇兵》的连连看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ooh, look, an Indiana Jones connect-the-dots.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.77,0:03:27.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有潜水侠的手办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And an Aquaman action figure.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.93,0:03:30.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好像有人给他画了个小弟弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Looks like someone drew a penis on him.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.23,0:03:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事儿  看我擦掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ooh, that'll come off.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.27,0:03:43.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都看不下去了喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You see what you're doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.63,0:03:46.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,停下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stop that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.10,0:03:47.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真赞啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fascinating.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.37,0:03:48.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.80,0:03:51.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是《魔戒》里的魔戒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It appears to be a Lord of the Rings ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.23,0:03:52.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上面居然还刻着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh. It's even got
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.73,0:03:54.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,精灵语呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}the Elvish engraving on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.30,0:03:55.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是精灵语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's not Elvish.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.63,0:03:58.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是用精灵语的字母写的魔多语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's the language of Mordor written in Elvish script.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.17,0:04:03.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,"魔戒全属至尊御"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"One Ring to rule them all."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.17,0:04:08.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,（出自《魔戒》台词）
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.00,0:04:05.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,"至尊指引诸魔戒"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"One Ring to find them."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.63,0:04:08.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,"至尊魔戒唤众戒"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"One Ring to bring them all."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.23,0:04:11.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,"众戒归一黑暗中"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"And in the darkness bind them."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.10,0:04:15.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我靠  咱们好宅啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Holy crap, are we nerdy.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.90,0:04:20.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我调查了一下这个魔戒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, I was doing some checking on the ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.07,0:04:22.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等下  谢尔顿  那边桌子上的是番茄酱吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hold on. Sheldon, is there ketchup on that table?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.30,0:04:24.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是滴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yes, there is.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.57,0:04:29.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有个好玩的事儿 起初 番茄酱是酱汁的总称\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, here's a fun fact. Ketchup started out as a general term for sauce,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.13,0:04:32.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,特别是那些加了草本植物和香料的 蘑菇或腌鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}typically made of mushrooms or fish brine with herbs and spices.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.43,0:04:35.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,早期流行的主材料包括蓝莓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Some popular early main ingredients included blueberry,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.17,0:04:38.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,凤尾鱼  牡蛎  四季豆  还有葡萄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}anchovy, oyster, kidney bean and grape.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.93,0:04:42.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没事儿  我去拿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, that's okay. I'll get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.63,0:04:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听我说  我仔细观察了魔戒 看上去有点奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Listen, I was looking at the ring, and it seemed a little weird.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.23,0:04:48.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,上面竟然没有版权声明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No copyright notice on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.80,0:04:52.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就拿给我一个哥们儿看  这么说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, I took it down to this buddy of mine who deals with--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.33,0:04:55.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他专门和收藏界的黑市 做交易\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}shall we say-- the seedy underbelly of the collectibles world.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.93,0:04:57.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,黑市\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Seedy underbelly?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.40,0:04:59.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你那个黑市淘来的手提式相位枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, your black market phasers,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.73,0:05:00.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,（出自《星际迷航》）
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.77,0:05:01.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有乌拉中尉在电影中穿过的内裤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}your screen-worn Lieutenant Uhura panties,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.93,0:05:03.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就那些东西呗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that kind of stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.53,0:05:07.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这个神秘兄弟是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who's this mysterious buddy you suddenly have?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.50,0:05:09.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是我认识的一个家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just a guy. I know a guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.57,0:05:12.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-艾迪·克里斯波吗  -我不能告诉你  别问了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Is it Eddie Crispo? - No, I can't tell you who it is. Stop asking.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.27,0:05:13.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还能是谁  肯定是艾迪·克里斯波\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who else could it be? It has to be Eddie Crispo.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.90,0:05:15.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我认识很多黑道人物  好不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know lots of dangerous people, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.00,0:05:19.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-说一个  -艾迪·克里斯波\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Name one. - Eddie Crispo.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.07,0:05:25.17,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样 他说这个不是仿品 而是真品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Anyway, he said this isn't a replica. It's the real deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.20,0:05:28.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你说这就是索伦在末日火山\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you're suggesting that that is the actual ring of power
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.17,0:05:30.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,打造的至尊魔戒[指环王情节]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}forged by Sauron in Mount Doom,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.43,0:05:32.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我会用极为不屑和\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I look at you with an expression of exhaustion
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.87,0:05:34.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,嘲笑的表情看着你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and ever so slight amusement.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.97,0:05:40.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他不是说这是魔戒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's not saying it's a magic ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.87,0:05:42.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're not, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.80,0:05:44.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没错  但差不多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, but it's close.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.83,0:05:46.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,看里面的标记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look at the markings inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.33,0:05:48.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那是生产标记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Those are production markings.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.63,0:05:51.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,为拍摄《指环王》  共打造了九枚戒指\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nine rings were made for use in the {\i1}Lord of the Rings movies.{\i0}
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.60,0:05:53.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三枚送给了剧中演员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Three were given to members of the cast.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.43,0:05:54.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的都被销毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The rest were destroyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.90,0:05:56.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了一枚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Except one.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.67,0:05:59.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被偷的一枚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}One was stolen.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.40,0:06:01.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先生们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Gentlemen...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.47,0:06:05.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这就是至尊魔戒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}this is the one ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.10,0:06:09.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,归我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Mine!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.20,0:06:12.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不  不是你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, it is not yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.47,0:06:14.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们一起去要的箱子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We all went in on the box together.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.10,0:06:16.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对  但是我在箱子里找到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, yes, but I found it in the box,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.43,0:06:18.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,海难救助法明确规定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and the laws of maritime salvage clearly state
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.53,0:06:20.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,找到沉海宝藏的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that the finder of a sunken treasure
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.43,0:06:22.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,即视为宝藏的主人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is the owner of the treasure.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.03,0:06:23.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这怎么符合海难救助法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How is this maritime salvage?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.93,0:06:26.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,除了没有水  怎么不符合\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Other than the lack of water, how is it not?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.37,0:06:28.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等  谢尔顿  先别发疯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait, wait. Sheldon, stop being crazy for a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.90,0:06:31.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这种东西值多少钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How much is something like this worth?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.10,0:06:33.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这么抢手的东西很难估价\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, it's tough to say since it's hot,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.73,0:06:35.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不过在黑市里  我朋友估价\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but on the underground market, my guy figures...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.83,0:06:36.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是指艾迪·克里斯波吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Your guy Eddie Crispo?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.87,0:06:39.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是滴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.27,0:06:44.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他估价一万到一万五\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He figures ten, maybe 15 thousand.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.93,0:06:46.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,既然值这么多钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, that's a lot of money.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.43,0:06:49.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明智之举是用它投资更实用的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The wise thing to do is invest it in something practical.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.57,0:06:51.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,比如水上摩托艇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Like a jet ski.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.30,0:06:54.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你要摩托艇干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why do you want a jet ski?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.27,0:06:57.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,电影里有钱又帅的人都骑摩托艇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All the wealthy and beautiful people in movies ride Jet Skis.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.60,0:06:59.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这不可能是巧合\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That can't just be a coincidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.30,0:07:01.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能卖它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We can't sell it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.50,0:07:03.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要保存它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We have to keep it
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.10,0:07:04.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,珍惜它  爱护它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and love it and polish it,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.43,0:07:05.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只能偶尔拿出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and only take it out occasionally
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.90,0:07:07.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,去公园里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}when we go to the park
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.23,0:07:10.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,重演电影里喜欢的场景\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and reenact our favorite scenes from the movies.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.23,0:07:14.27,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听着有意思  其实很无聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's sad how great that sounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.30,0:07:15.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位  这是偷来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Guys, it's stolen.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.50,0:07:17.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,应该还给彼得·杰克逊[指环王导演]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It should go back to Peter Jackson.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.13,0:07:18.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他制作的电影  魔戒应该属于他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He made the movies; it belongs to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.97,0:07:20.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,行啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.17,0:07:22.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,可以换给他  只要他答应\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He can have it back as long as he promises
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.53,0:07:24.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,让我演下一部电影里的霍比特人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to make me a hobbit in his next movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.80,0:07:26.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没有犹太霍比特人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There are no Jewish hobbits.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.90,0:07:28.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,显然你没在岁首节[犹太新年]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Clearly, you've never been to my house
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.77,0:07:31.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来我家吃饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}for dinner on Rosh Hashanah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.03,0:07:33.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能敲诈彼得·杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We are not blackmailing Peter J...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.43,0:07:34.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,够了  魔戒哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right, where's the ring?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.93,0:07:37.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我的魔戒吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You mean my ring?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.23,0:07:38.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这是干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.33,0:07:39.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔戒无人看护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The ring was unguarded.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.50,0:07:41.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就这么放着台面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was just sitting on the table.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.27,0:07:42.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁都能拿走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Anyone could have taken it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.73,0:07:44.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,证据  我拿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Proof? I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.67,0:07:47.20,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-给我  -大家理智点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Give me that. - Look, let's be reasonable.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.23,0:07:49.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都对魔戒抱有不同的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We all want to do different things with the ring,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.60,0:07:52.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但你们的想法太傻  我要的可是摩托艇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but your ideas are stupid, and I want a jet ski.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.53,0:07:54.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我找到的  魔戒是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I found it. The ring is mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.27,0:07:57.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白  为啥每次都不能我说了算\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't understand why in this group I never get my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.97,0:08:04.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,有哪次不是你说了算\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You always get your way.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.17,0:08:08.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你把魔戒给我  才是每次我说了算\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll stipulate to that if you give me the ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.47,0:08:09.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,各位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.63,0:08:10.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,喜欢我给你们上的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Enjoying your food that I actually
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.00,0:08:12.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不是你们点的菜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}brought you instead of promising food,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.67,0:08:15.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我随意找的一堆垃圾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but bringing you a box of random crap?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.80,0:08:16.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,很好吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, it's delicious.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.93,0:08:18.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是讽刺的话不太新鲜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The sarcasm's a little stale, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.90,0:08:21.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要不这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, how about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.07,0:08:22.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,确定如何处理魔戒前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Until we figure out what to do with the ring,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.93,0:08:24.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,由佩妮来保管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Penny holds on to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.10,0:08:24.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么戒指\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What ring?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.00,0:08:27.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这枚戒指\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.17,0:08:29.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在找东西吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Looking for something?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.53,0:08:33.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你能保管几天吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Will you hold on to this for a couple of days?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.87,0:08:35.47,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-为什么  -这是部电影的道具\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Why? - It's a prop from a movie,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.50,0:08:37.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们正为此争吵呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And we're kind of fighting over it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.47,0:08:39.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只想说清楚  我男朋友给我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, just to be clear, the first piece of jewelry
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.17,0:08:40.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,第一件珠宝是电影里的道具\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}my boyfriend gives me is a prop from a movie,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.90,0:08:42.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而且我还不能拥有它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I don't even get to keep it?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.40,0:08:46.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果你三年前跟了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you had gone out with me three years ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.10,0:08:48.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你现在应该能收到我姑婆艾达\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}by now, you'd have my great Aunt Ida's brooch
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.53,0:08:52.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,塞进猫肚子从德占比利时偷运出的胸针\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that she smuggled out of occupied Belgium in a cat.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.20,0:08:55.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,现在感觉我还好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How am I looking now?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.10,0:10:00.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你打我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You hit me!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.37,0:10:03.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我在流血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm bleeding!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.47,0:10:06.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.27,0:10:08.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿想偷魔戒  我给了他一拳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sheldon tried to take the ring and I punched him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.90,0:10:10.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,干得好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's my girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.33,0:10:20.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, Sheldon,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.00,0:10:23.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,被一个女人家揍的感觉如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}how's it feel to get beaten up by a girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.06,0:10:27.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,反正不是第一次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's not the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.00,0:10:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在子宫里我那胞姐就开始欺负我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have a twin sister whose assaults began in utero.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.56,0:10:35.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,如果当年我能一直坚定的吸收掉她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If only I'd had the presence of mind to reabsorb her,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.56,0:10:37.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我也就多了一颗长毛的痣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}then I'd have a mole with hair in it
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.60,0:10:41.00,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样也不会收到那些无聊的圣诞贺卡了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}instead of a tedious yearly Christmas letter.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.60,0:10:42.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,先生们  你们还没有觉悟吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Gentlemen, have you come to the realization
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.97,0:10:44.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,最明智的选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that the only reasonable course of action
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.80,0:10:46.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就是卖了魔戒再分钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is to sell the ring and divide the money?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.60,0:10:47.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.77,0:10:48.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就怕你这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I was afraid of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.87,0:10:52.80,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.83,0:10:54.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在孟买问候大家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Greetings from Mumbai.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.47,0:10:56.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我是拉杰的律师  文卡塔斯·库萨帕里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I am Raj's attorney, Venkatesh Koothrappali.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.97,0:10:58.97,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,也是我表哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Also my cousin.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.00,0:11:00.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你居然还找了个律师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You brought a lawyer?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.47,0:11:01.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这个不用回答\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't answer that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.90,0:11:03.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就直说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll get straight to the point.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.87,0:11:05.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的委托人准备放弃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My client's prepared to surrender
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.90,0:11:07.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,他在这枚魔戒上的一切利益\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}any interest he has in the ring
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.37,0:11:10.07,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,来交换两辆川崎水上摩托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in exchange for two Kawasaki Jet Skis.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.10,0:11:13.10,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,两辆水上摩托是不可能的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're not giving him two Jet Skis.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.13,0:11:14.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听着  大家都成年人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look, we're big boys,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.53,0:11:17.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们何不都退一步海阔天空呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}why don't we just cut to the chase and meet in the middle?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.23,0:11:19.67,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一辆水上摩托就够了 怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}One Kawasaki Jet Ski. Done and done.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.67,0:11:24.30,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,半辆都不给\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No Jet Skis.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.63,0:11:26.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  不谈水上摩托了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right, forget the Jet Skis.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.77,0:11:29.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么 这是我们的底线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Forget the Jet Skis? That was our line in the sand!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.53,0:11:31.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就这点招数吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What happened to "tear them a new one?"
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.43,0:11:35.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那你要我怎样 他们态度强硬 我们输了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What can I say? They played hardball. We lost.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.27,0:11:36.57,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这没用的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're useless.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.60,0:11:38.40,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你来雇我时我就说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I told you that when you hired me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.43,0:11:39.87,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要下线了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm signing off now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.90,0:11:43.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,记得联系你妈 她担心你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Call your mother. She worries.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.27,0:11:47.21,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗 向别人介绍自己的律师表兄时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, just so you know, if we're bringing in cousins who are lawyers,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.21,0:11:50.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要准备好被雷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}prepare for shock and awe.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.93,0:11:52.28,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你们  我来了结这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know what? I am ending this.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.28,0:11:53.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮不想再保管魔戒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Penny didn't want to hold the ring anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.59,0:11:56.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她还给了我  现在我手上 我要寄回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She gave it to me. I have it. I'm sending it back.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.49,0:11:58.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔戒呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where's the ring?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.23,0:12:00.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你是指这个魔戒吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You mean this ring?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.76,0:12:03.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,下次在公共厕所里排尿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Next time be aware of your surroundings
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.49,0:12:05.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,记得要耳听八方环顾四周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}while urinating in a public men's room.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.69,0:12:06.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,快给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Give me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.89,0:12:07.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才不  这是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, it's mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.93,0:12:08.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都有份\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's all of ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.03,0:12:12.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-得了  这也太荒唐了  -那就放手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Okay, now, this is ridiculous!  - Then let go!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.86,0:12:14.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,偏不  你干嘛不放手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not letting go. You let go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.23,0:12:15.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要我说  谁坚持到最后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I say this ring belongs
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.69,0:12:17.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔戒就归谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to the last person who can hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.76,0:12:19.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,行啊  我们回家再开始吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fine. But can't we go home and start this?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.96,0:12:22.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,当然 那现在先放手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sure. Let go of the ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.49,0:12:24.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  那就从现在开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right, it starts now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.99,0:12:31.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今晚科幻频道有巨虫电影联播\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You do realize there's a giant bug movie marathon
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.93,0:12:34.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们都还记得吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}tonight on the Syfy Channel.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.86,0:12:50.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,慢  我的笔记本还没拿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait, my laptop.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.63,0:13:04.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这也太白痴了  一点也没意义了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, there's a point no when this becomes idiotic.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.59,0:13:07.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,刚我们这样开车的时候你咋不说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And it wasn't when we were driving like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.09,0:13:11.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我好心建议你们三个放弃吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I would advise the three of you
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.09,0:13:12.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再怎么死撑也是徒劳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that resistance is futile.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.73,0:13:14.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的耐性可是出了名的好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have endless patience.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.39,0:13:16.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我曾和惠普的客服人员\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I once spent two-and-a-half hours on hold
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.63,0:13:18.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,耗了整整两个半小时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}with Hewlett-Packard customer service
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.63,0:13:21.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,就为投诉他们客服态度差劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}just to complain about their customer service.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.26,0:13:25.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你少和我吹嘘耐性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want to talk about endless patience?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.29,0:13:27.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮逼我看完了整整\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Penny made me watch all five seasons
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.33,0:13:29.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,五季的《欲望都市》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}of Sex and the City.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.59,0:13:33.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老兄  那玩意有六季\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There are six seasons, dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.59,0:13:35.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,噢  杯具\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, crap!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.23,0:13:39.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别这么说嘛  第六季很赞啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, no, the sixth season is great.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.26,0:13:43.29,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,凯莉刚分手  伤心地去了巴黎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We go to Paris with Carrie and get our heart broken,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.33,0:13:44.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,而大人物又突然出现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and then Mr. Big shows up,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.56,0:13:47.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我们都很好奇  她是否还能再相信他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}we don't know if we can trust him again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.56,0:13:49.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真是跨越地球的爱恋啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's a wild ride.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.63,0:13:53.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我要开门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Door.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.63,0:14:02.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,同志们  屈膝[法语 芭蕾舞动作]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, everybody, and plie?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.03,0:14:12.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再踮立[法语 芭蕾舞动作]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And releve?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.09,0:14:18.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们干什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Whatcha doin'?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.19,0:14:20.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,谁坚持到最后  魔戒归谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Last one holding the ring decides its fate.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.96,0:14:22.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这很蠢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know, it sounds silly.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.19,0:14:24.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才不会呢  你是我男友啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, no, no, no, you are my boyfriend.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.13,0:14:26.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,情人眼里出西施嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nothing you do is silly to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.16,0:14:28.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,多谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.09,0:14:32.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,顺便说下  这可是维多利亚的秘密内衣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}FYI-- this is a bag from Victoria's Secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.03,0:14:41.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,老子不干了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm out.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.56,0:14:53.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  老妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry, Ma,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.56,0:14:55.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没办法  我要在办公室加班\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have to stay late at the office.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.56,0:14:57.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,才没有  他在骗你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, he's doesn't! He's lying to you!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.03,0:15:00.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能消停点吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Will you be quiet?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.69,0:15:02.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,要隐私的话  放开手就行了啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, if you want privacy let go of the ring.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.56,0:15:04.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm so glad
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.39,0:15:07.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,终于能来这家异教徒的脱衣舞俱乐部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}we came to this gentile strip club!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.23,0:15:08.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.46,0:15:11.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,再给你个培根  塞她们丁字裤里去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}here's more bacon to tuck into the shiksa's G-string!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.76,0:15:15.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我再打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll call you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.66,0:15:17.69,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你实在太贴心了  还特地打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I think it's lovely you call your mommy
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.73,0:15:19.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你妈  你赶不回去吃晚饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and let her know you're going to be late for dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.56,0:15:20.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,据我所知\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}From what I know about these things,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.83,0:15:22.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,没能按时喂奶的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}if a woman doesn't breast-feed on time,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.69,0:15:25.53,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咪咪会很不舒服的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}it's very uncomfortable for her boobies.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.56,0:15:28.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别跟我谈我妈的咪咪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't you talk about my mother's boobies!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.63,0:15:30.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,听着不爽的话  放手啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you're offended, let go of the ring
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.26,0:15:32.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,赶紧回家找你妈吃奶去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and go on home to your mother's boobies.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.79,0:15:34.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,太好了  太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Excellent, excellent.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.36,0:15:36.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩耗吧  我就能笑到最后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Tire each other out, the ring will be mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.16,0:15:38.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德  何不谈谈拉杰他妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard, why don't you go after Raj's mother?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.93,0:15:42.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不然咱谈谈你妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why don't we go after {\i1}your{\i0} mother?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.43,0:15:44.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尽管谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.39,0:15:46.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我又没有恋母情结\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have no illusions about my mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.53,0:15:48.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,她就一个和蔼可亲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She is a kind, loving,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.49,0:15:50.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,笃信上帝  极端右翼的德州人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}religiously fanatical right-wing Texan
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.53,0:15:52.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,头长得有点不合比例\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}with a slightly out-of-scale head
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.59,0:15:54.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还对佩珀汽水有点上瘾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and a mild Dr. Pepper addiction.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.86,0:15:58.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么要补充的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Anything you'd like to add?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.36,0:16:00.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这样说根本没用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's not gonna get you anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.39,0:16:01.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得给他来点狠的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Better pull out the big gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.89,0:16:02.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.89,0:16:05.09,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,咱来谈谈你祖母\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let's talk about your grandmother.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.13,0:16:06.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.89,0:16:09.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不许说我奶奶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I call no Meemaws.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.46,0:16:10.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想想看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Think about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.93,0:16:15.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你奶奶肯定得跟人上床  才会有你妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The only way your mother was born was your Meemaw had sex.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.36,0:16:18.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我不想听这些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't want to hear this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.79,0:16:22.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就放手  走一边去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then let go of the ring and walk away.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.23,0:16:23.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,想都别想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Never.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.66,0:16:24.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.86,0:16:26.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我敢说  你奶奶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'll bet your Meemaw
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.06,0:16:28.49,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,不仅仅是为了传宗接代才跟人上床的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}didn't just have sex to have your mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.53,0:16:32.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我敢说  她肯定也享受性爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I bet she had sex because she liked it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.46,0:16:34.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,别说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.89,0:16:36.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,对  奶奶也并不圣洁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, Meemaw did the nasty.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.63,0:16:38.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我叫你们闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I said stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.43,0:16:40.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,说到他痛处了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're getting to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.26,0:16:41.23,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瀑布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Waterfalls!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.26,0:16:41.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.03,0:16:43.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,瀑布\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Waterfalls.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.23,0:16:44.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,惊涛拍岸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Crashing waves.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.23,0:16:45.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潺潺溪流\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Babbling brooks.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.56,0:16:48.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你这是干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.46,0:16:49.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,潜意识信息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Subliminal messaging.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.69,0:16:51.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,通过这让你们产生尿意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm going to make you want to pee.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.26,0:16:54.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,滴水的水龙头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Dripping faucets.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.76,0:16:56.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,漏水的水槽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Leaky gutter.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.79,0:16:59.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,尿尿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Peeing.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.66,0:17:01.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,这招根本不管用  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's, it's not working, dude.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.39,0:17:04.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,已经管用了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh-ho-ho, it's working all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.46,0:17:06.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我想上厕所\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I have to pee.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.76,0:17:08.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就放开魔戒去啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then let go of the ring and go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.59,0:17:11.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,其实  我也想上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, actually, I wouldn't mind going, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.06,0:17:12.56,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.59,0:17:13.93,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数到三\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Um, on the count of three.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.96,0:17:15.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,一  二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}One, two...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.39,0:17:16.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,等等  先说清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait, just to clarify.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.63,0:17:20.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,数到三  是都站起来还是直接尿尿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When you get to three, do we stand up or do we pee?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.83,0:17:25.96,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,都站起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We stand up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.99,0:17:28.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,明智之选\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Excellent choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.63,0:17:30.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,三\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Three.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.33,0:17:37.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我有预感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Something tells me
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.63,0:17:41.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,今天真不该穿绒面革皮鞋的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}this was a bad day to wear suede shoes.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.19,0:17:59.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我做到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've done it!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.19,0:18:01.06,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've won!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.09,0:18:03.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔戒是我的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The ring is mine!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.46,0:18:05.66,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's mine!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.26,0:18:15.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,得彻底清洗下  让它更漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're going to clean it up and make it pretty.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.39,0:18:17.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My own.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.89,0:18:19.83,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My love.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.47,0:18:25.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,（谢尔顿华丽变身《魔戒》中的咕噜[Gollum]）
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.86,0:18:21.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My precious.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.56,0:18:32.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔戒呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where's the ring?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.49,0:18:36.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,在联邦快递的盒子里  回它原来的地方去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's in a FedEx box on its way back to where it came from.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.39,0:18:39.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,（索伦在末日山的火焰中铸造了至尊魔戒）
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.39,0:18:39.46,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,末日山的火焰之中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The fires of Mount Doom?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.49,0:18:42.16,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,彼得·杰克逊(《魔戒》导演)在新西兰的办公室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Peter Jackson's office in New Zealand.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.19,0:18:43.39,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,本就不是我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It wasn't ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.43,0:18:44.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你早就退出了比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You quit the game!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.89,0:18:46.26,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根本没资格拿走魔戒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You had no right to take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.29,0:18:47.86,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我走进来的时候  你们都睡着了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I came in here, you guys were all sleeping.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.89,0:18:49.79,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔戒掉在地板上  没人拿着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The ring was on the floor. No one was touching it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.83,0:18:52.36,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,那就该重新开始  直到产生最后的赢家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, so then we start the game over until there's a winner.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.39,0:18:54.73,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,根本不会有什么赢家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There wasn't ever going to be a winner.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.76,0:18:57.19,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,只会有一个手握魔戒的自私鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There was going to be a selfish, petty person with a ring
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.23,0:18:59.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,和三个反目的好友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and three people who used to be his friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.06,0:19:00.33,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,你们真想这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is that really what you guys want?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.36,0:19:01.59,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真想的话  随便吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}'Cause if it is, fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.63,0:19:03.99,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你们也没什么好说的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't want anything to do with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.03,0:19:06.13,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,还有  厕所里怎么回事我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I don't know what happened in that bathroom,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.16,0:19:07.76,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,但我才不会去清理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but I am not cleaning it up!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.59,0:19:27.89,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我的宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My precious.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.50,0:19:46.63,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I knew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.67,0:19:51.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把宝贝还我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Give us the precious!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.97,0:19:54.70,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-快给我  快给我  -放开我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Give me! Give me! - Get off of me!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.73,0:19:56.77,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,-把魔戒给我  -魔戒是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Give me the ring! - It's mine!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.80,0:19:59.43,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,真该跟健身房那笨蛋约会看看的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ugh, gotta go back to dating dumb guys from the gym.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.47,0:20:00.90,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把魔戒给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just give me the ring!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.93,0:20:02.03,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把魔戒给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Give it to me!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.07,0:20:03.37,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,把魔戒给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Give me the ring!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.40,0:20:04.50,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,我让你给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I said give it to me!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.53,0:20:06.60,Default,,0000,0000,0000,,魔戒是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's mine!
