[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Normal
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 1
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.00,0:00:06.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个跟蝙蝠人有关的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I have a question about Batman.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.00,0:00:06.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}以下这段"蝙蝠侠"将以"蝙蝠人"代替
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.36,0:00:10.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蝙蝠人是个穿得像蝙蝠的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Batman is a man who dresses up like a bat.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.77,0:00:15.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人蝠是半人半蝙蝠的混种生物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Man-bat is a part man, part bat hybrid.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.77,0:00:15.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}与蝙蝠侠同一家公司出品的漫画人物
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.81,0:00:19.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果人蝠打扮成人去打击犯罪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now, if Man-Bat dressed up as a man to fight crime,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.92,0:00:23.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他会变成人蝙蝠人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}would he be Man-Batman?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.95,0:00:26.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会  他会变蝙蝠人蝠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, he'd be Bat-Man-Bat.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.42,0:00:30.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是人蝙蝠人不应该是蝙蝠人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But wouldn't Man-Batman just be a Batman
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.42,0:00:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}如蜘蛛人就是被放射性蜘蛛咬过后\N才获得类似蜘蛛般的能力
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.29,0:00:32.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被放射性人类咬过之后的样子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that was bitten by a radioactive man?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.42,0:00:34.50,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但蝙蝠人本来就是人啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But Batman is a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.50,0:00:37.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才说人被赋予人的能力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're talking about a man who would have the powers of a man.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.55,0:00:39.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是人类吃了人人果实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's just Man-Man.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.49,0:00:42.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但人人其实不就是人而已吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, isn't Man-Man just man?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.65,0:00:44.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但要是人人穿成像蝙蝠呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But what if Man-Man dressed as a bat?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.42,0:00:45.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是蝙蝠人啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, that's just Batman.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.42,0:00:47.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不对  一个人穿上蝙蝠装\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, if a man dresses as a bat,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.49,0:00:49.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是蝙蝠人  但如果是人人穿上蝙蝠装\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's Batman, but if Man-Man dresses as a bat,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.46,0:00:51.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是蝙蝠人人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}that's Batman-Man.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.15,0:00:55.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样算回答了你的问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So does that answer your question?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.07,0:00:57.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没问我的问题呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I haven't asked it yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.16,0:00:59.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是克莱尔  我得先走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that's Claire. Got to run.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.99,0:01:01.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你跟艾米丽复合了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I thought you were back with Emily.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.55,0:01:04.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实我...  同时在跟她们交往[看]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, actually I'm... seeing both of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.84,0:01:09.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是指躲在她们窗外草丛偷看的"看"吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You mean like through their window from behind a bush?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.29,0:01:13.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  我是指同时跟两个女生交往\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'm actually dating two women.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.42,0:01:14.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回头见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Later.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.27,0:01:16.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.54,0:01:19.25,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这多少年来不敢跟女人说话的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The guy who for years couldn't even talk to women
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.25,0:01:20.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,居然突然就开始脚踏两条船\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is suddenly going out with two of them?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.90,0:01:22.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这怎么可能  -对啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- How is that possible? - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.52,0:01:25.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科学家一直试图用计算模型模拟这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Scientists have tried to reproduce it with computational models,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.38,0:01:29.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但所有尝试中  最后世界都会爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but, in each case, the world blows up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.88,0:01:36.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  这家伙居然能享齐人之福\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Seriously, that guy's dating two women?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.32,0:01:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(156.6,76,156.6,75.2)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H232727&\fs10\t(0,271,0.4,\fs47)\fscy80\t(271,1481,1,\fs48)}生
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.32,0:01:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(156.6,108,156.6,107.2)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H232727&\fs10\t(0,271,0.4,\fs47)\fscy80\t(271,1481,1,\fs48)}活
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.32,0:01:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(185.4,88,185.4,87.2)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H070729&\fs12\t(0,271,0.4,\fs50)\fscy110\fscx90\t(271,1481,1,\fs48)}大
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.32,0:01:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(212.4,79.2,212.4,78.4)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H010044&\fs8\t(0,271,0.4,\fs40)\fscy\t(271,1481,1,\fs41)}爆
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.32,0:01:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(237,86.4,237,85.6)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H050061&\fs8\t(0,271,0.4,\fs40)\fscy\t(271,1481,1,\fs41)}炸
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.32,0:01:56.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\move(189,242.4,189,244)\fad(50,0)\bord0\shad0\fn方正兰亭特黑_GBK\c&H2D2F2F&\fs3\t(0,271,0.4,\fs18)\fscy110\fscx90\t(271,1481,1,\fs18.5)}第九季  第二十一集
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.12,0:02:08.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么买了一个派对潜艇堡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What, why did you get a party sub?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.03,0:02:10.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家要来玩  这样感觉有意思啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}People are coming over; it looked fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.16,0:02:12.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只是要一起看《权力的游戏》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, we're only watching Game of Thrones.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.13,0:02:15.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但派对潜艇堡意味着会有派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}A party sub implies it's a party.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.04,0:02:18.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你会出席已意味着不会有派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Your attendance implies it's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.04,0:02:20.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢派对的程度与一个普通人无异\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I like a party as much as the next man,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.94,0:02:23.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前提是这普通人并不喜欢派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}as long as the next man doesn't like a party.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.43,0:02:25.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了  你别忘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, by the way, don't forget,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.49,0:02:28.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天是我们的室友协议季度大会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}tomorrow is our quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.01,0:02:30.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  我们不需要每三个月就开一次会吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, Sheldon, we don't need a meeting every three months.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.39,0:02:32.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个提议感觉就很值得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, it sounds like the kind of thing one would bring up
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.22,0:02:34.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在明天的季度大会上提出呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}at a quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.64,0:02:37.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真走运  会议刚好在明天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Lucky for you it's tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.06,0:02:39.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告诉你  我是不会参加的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, you know what? I'm not going.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.52,0:02:41.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须得参加\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, you have to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.79,0:02:45.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天是佩妮首次主持效忠宣誓呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's Penny's first time leading the Pledge of Allegiance.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.35,0:02:48.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个会议根本就是浪费时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This meeting is a waste of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.22,0:02:49.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如决定要不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Whether we make the switch
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.19,0:02:51.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从早餐谷物产品A换到产品B这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}from Post Raisin Bran to Kellogg's Raisin Bran
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.34,0:02:54.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要经过议会程序来定好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}should not require parliamentary procedure.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.71,0:02:58.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道其中一款里的葡萄干上有糖吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You realize one of them has sugar on the raisins.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.52,0:03:00.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正都是你一个人吃啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're the only one who eats them!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.92,0:03:02.66,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你居然有幸能提出意见呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And yet you get to weigh in.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.66,0:03:05.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,民主  就是这么酷  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Democracy-- it's pretty cool, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.68,0:03:07.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不参加  你也逼不了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not going; you can't make me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.22,0:03:09.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们就走着瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, we'll just see about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.20,0:03:10.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么啦怎么啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is the problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.33,0:03:12.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说明天不来参加室友协议季度大会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He says he's not coming to the Roommate Agreement meeting tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.81,0:03:16.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我不是白背了效忠宣誓词吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, why the hell did I memorize the Pledge?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.74,0:03:19.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝玩得愉快  我反正不参加\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You have fun. I will not be attending.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.44,0:03:20.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行啊  你要是不想参加\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, fine. We don't have to have
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.73,0:03:22.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以后可以不办室友协议季度大会啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a Roommate Agreement meeting if you don't want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.48,0:03:24.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢  -但这件事需要经过投票表决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Thank you. - Of course, it will require a vote.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.58,0:03:27.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遗憾的是  我的正式木槌放在房间里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Unfortunately, my official gavel is in my bedroom,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.36,0:03:31.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但好在我的旅游随身木槌在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but luckily, I have my travel gavel.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.81,0:03:34.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在耍白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're being ridiculous.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.24,0:03:36.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个动议"谢尔顿是在耍白痴"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There's a motion on the floor, "I'm ridiculous."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.31,0:03:37.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人附议吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do we have a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.79,0:03:38.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无人附议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There is no second.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.70,0:03:39.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动议驳回\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}The motion is denied.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.67,0:03:41.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次请确保有人会投票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Next time, make sure you have the votes first.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.16,0:03:42.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才也太丢人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was embarrassing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.68,0:03:45.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能跟他说说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can you please talk to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.89,0:03:47.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要跟他争这事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, why are you fighting him on this?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.26,0:03:50.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我受够了什么事都得顺他意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because I am tired of him always getting his way.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.14,0:03:51.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又不需要这傻逼大会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We don't need a stupid meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.26,0:03:52.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们甚至都不需要狗屁《室友协议》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}We don't even need a Roommate Agreement,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.70,0:03:56.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我还真希望这潜艇堡能招来派对呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I hope that sandwich does cause a party!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.73,0:03:58.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是会来参加你的大会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I will still come to your meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.65,0:04:01.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望如此啊  明天可是拍照日\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I should hope so. Tomorrow's picture day.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.11,0:04:04.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么站他那边啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you taking his side?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.49,0:04:05.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为这事对他很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because it's important to him,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.64,0:04:07.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们签署《室友协议》时  就同意了这事啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and when we signed the Roommate Agreement, we made a deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.98,0:04:11.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你再这么讲话  很快就要荣升扛旗者了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Y-You keep talking like that, you're gonna make color guard.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.70,0:04:17.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-天啊  我真是心力交瘁  -对啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Man, I'm worn out. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.19,0:04:20.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想象一下如果真像游戏里那么跑动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Imagine if we were actually moving.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.92,0:04:23.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦  我是说自从我开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, it's just, ever since I started dating
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.61,0:04:28.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟克莱尔和艾米丽同时交往  真是精疲力尽啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Claire and Emily at the same time, it's exhausting.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.11,0:04:29.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这就精疲力尽啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're exhausted?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.43,0:04:31.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你试过孕妇书里每五页就折个角\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Try folding every five pages in a pregnancy book
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.75,0:04:34.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好让你老婆觉得你有读  你才知道累\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so your wife thinks you read it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.10,0:04:36.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但兄弟  你很幸运了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But, dude, you're so lucky.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.97,0:04:40.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每晚能在家与你相爱的女人共度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Getting to stay home at night with the woman you love.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.15,0:04:41.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确很幸运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I guess I am lucky.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.78,0:04:44.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  如果你同时和两个女人约会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You are, because dating two women,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.96,0:04:47.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  我都不记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, I can't even remember
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.91,0:04:50.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上一次我睡在自己家是何年何月了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}the last time I slept in my own apartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.70,0:04:54.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我每天醒来就想  "这是克莱尔还是艾米丽家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I wake up and I'm like, "Am I at Claire's or am I at Emily's?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.44,0:04:56.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是某个我想不起芳名的新妞家"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is there a third girl I've forgotten about?"
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.33,0:04:57.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Like...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.01,0:05:00.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我在谁家香闺啊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Where am I?"
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.19,0:05:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Raj.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.95,0:05:03.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准妈咪  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, how's the mommy-to-be?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.75,0:05:05.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好  有点小累\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Good. A little tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.15,0:05:09.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感同身受  我最近和好几个妹子约会来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I feel you. I've been dating multiple women.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.70,0:05:11.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定不跟我们一起看《权力的游戏》吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You sure you don't want to come watch Game of Thrones with us?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.64,0:05:12.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们自己慢慢看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You guys have fun.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.64,0:05:14.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去床上窝着看书就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm just gonna snuggle up in bed with a book.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.83,0:05:17.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来好爽啊  一个人独占一张床\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, that sounds great-- a bed to yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.93,0:05:21.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都想不起那种感觉是什么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can't even remember what that's like.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.00,0:05:26.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你熟悉最新的《权力的游戏》剧情吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Are you up-to-date on Game of Thrones?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.09,0:05:27.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Mm, I think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.55,0:05:29.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,龙呀  雪僵尸啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dragons, snow zombies,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.65,0:05:31.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有凡是长得帅的家伙都死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and all the hot guys are dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.90,0:05:34.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我可不确定了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.28,0:05:36.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,席恩·葛雷乔伊的长相\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Theon Greyjoy looks pretty good
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.00,0:05:38.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对于没了小弟弟的人来说  相当不错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}for a guy who had his genitals cut off.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.21,0:05:43.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哎哟喂  有人还在闹小情绪呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh-oh, somebody's still pouting.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.45,0:05:44.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Leave me alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.43,0:05:45.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是因为掉了一根"小棒子"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If it's because you lost a stick,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.94,0:05:48.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道它在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I know where it went.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.21,0:05:51.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不好笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Not funny.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.16,0:05:52.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明知道会和好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know you're gonna make up with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.08,0:05:53.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不能直接跳到握手言和的那刻吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Can we just skip to that part?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.29,0:05:56.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  因为我是这里唯一一个成熟的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, of course, because I'm the only adult around here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.05,0:05:57.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗  唯一成熟的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? The only adult?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.52,0:05:59.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, that's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.23,0:06:01.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚我要看的节目可是标识为M.A.的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tonight I'll be watching a show rated M.A.,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.45,0:06:04.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是成年观众  你个小屁孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and that stands for "Mature Audiences," buster.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.55,0:06:07.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"唯一成熟的人"可不会因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, you would think "the only adult"
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.18,0:06:09.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些蠢事而破坏别人整晚的情绪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}wouldn't let something silly ruin our entire night.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.33,0:06:11.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还以为你会理解我不爽的原因呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'd think you'd understand why I'm annoyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.94,0:06:14.49,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你来参加大会  不就没这些事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All this could be avoided if you'd just come to the meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.49,0:06:15.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家不想参加\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.83,0:06:17.14,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是一个大会而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, it's just a meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.14,0:06:19.10,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一个简单的大会  -不要再提大会两个字了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- One simple meeting. - Stop saying "meeting"!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.10,0:06:20.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 大会  大会  三四五六七 *\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* Meeting, meeting, bo-beeting *
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.37,0:06:21.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 你不想听  我却偏要提 *\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* Banana-fana, fo-feeting *
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.81,0:06:23.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 大灰  打毁  答慧 *\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* Fee-fi mo-meeting... *
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.20,0:06:24.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带来了我的招牌菠菜蘸酱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I brought my famous spinach dip.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.82,0:06:25.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾米  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yo, Amy, just one second.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.97,0:06:28.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,* 大会 *\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}* Meeting. *
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.09,0:06:34.01,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道自己想要个儿子还是女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm not sure if I'm hoping for a boy or a girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.01,0:06:35.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果生的是儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, if it's a boy,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.53,0:06:37.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就得教他玩接投球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm gonna have to teach him to play catch.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.76,0:06:40.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就得上网去查怎么玩接投球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Which means I'm gonna have to Google "How to play catch."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.48,0:06:44.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果生的是女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If it's a girl, I mean...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.83,0:06:47.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们那么天真无邪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}they're so innocent and...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.05,0:06:48.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你知道男人都是什么鬼样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you know how guys are.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.60,0:06:50.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的  男人都不是好东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Totally, guys are the worst.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.72,0:06:53.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I mean, look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.74,0:06:56.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让艾米丽给我做了意大利烘蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I let Emily make me a frittata
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.84,0:07:00.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后把吃剩的留在克莱尔的冰箱里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I kept the leftovers in Claire's fridge that night.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.00,0:07:02.30,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真是个渣男\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm such a dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.07,0:07:06.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你又来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}There you go again.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.60,0:07:08.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我是不是抱怨得太多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm sorry, have I been complaining about it too much?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.86,0:07:11.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实你现在是在假抱怨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Actually, what you're doing is pretending to complain,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.84,0:07:13.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真显摆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but really trying to brag.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.24,0:07:14.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么能这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How could you say that?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.55,0:07:16.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"人家真希望可以安静喝完一杯茶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Oh, I wish could enjoy a cup of tea
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.99,0:07:21.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而没有裸女在我身上跳来跳去"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}without a naked girl bouncing up and down on me."
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.04,0:07:23.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未说过这话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never said that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.61,0:07:26.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"人家记不得掉在沙发里的胸罩到底是谁的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Don't you hate it when you can't remember whose bra it is
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.63,0:07:29.47,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是好讨厌哦"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you found wedged in your couch?"
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.92,0:07:32.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  这话我说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, that I said.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.45,0:07:35.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这是真实的问题啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But that's a real problem!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.35,0:07:37.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把一个妹子的胸罩给了另一妹子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You give a girl another woman's bra,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.13,0:07:39.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那晚上就别想和那妹子滚床单了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and you will not be having sex with her that night.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.44,0:07:42.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许还能和另一个妹子睡  但这妹子绝对没戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe the other girl, but not her.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.76,0:07:50.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's going on with him?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.41,0:07:51.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为了参不参加\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, he's all bent out of shape
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.75,0:07:53.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,室友协议大会而闹别扭呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}about having a Roommate Agreement meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.92,0:07:57.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这年头完美出勤率貌似不够酷炫了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Apparently, perfect attendance isn't cool anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.13,0:07:59.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  他会想明白的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't worry, he'll come around.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.95,0:08:01.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能理解他为什么不高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I get why he's annoyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.95,0:08:03.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你不明白到底是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, then you don't understand what's happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.83,0:08:04.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}See...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.27,0:08:06.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德拒绝出席\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Leonard refused to participate
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.76,0:08:09.54,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个强制性的室友协议季度大会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in a mandatory quarterly Roommate Agreement meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.54,0:08:13.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是以巴特·辛普森为榜样养育下一代的恶果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This is what a generation raised on Bart Simpson looks like.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.54,0:08:13.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}《辛普森一家》中的叛逆儿子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.93,0:08:15.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明明自己也爱看《辛普森一家》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You love The Simpsons.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.22,0:08:17.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家喜欢的是丽莎·辛普森\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I love Lisa Simpson.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.22,0:08:17.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}《辛普森一家》中的聪明女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.85,0:08:22.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能理解他的感受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I know how he feels.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.34,0:08:25.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不喜欢咱俩的恋爱协议大会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never enjoyed our Relationship Agreement meetings.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.04,0:08:26.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.27,0:08:28.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前都是假装的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You were pretending?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.77,0:08:30.03,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.03,0:08:31.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.46,0:08:34.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不相信  我能分清真假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't believe you. I could tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.19,0:08:40.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"哇  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"Oh, Sheldon,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.85,0:08:42.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从未想过在常务委员会里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never thought re-filing a matter
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.94,0:08:48.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重审一个议题会如此让人目眩神迷"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in a standing subcommittee could be so fascinating."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.26,0:08:52.46,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得这是真是假\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hmm, what do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.12,0:08:55.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你分不清吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You don't know?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.56,0:09:02.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是说了什么惹你不高兴了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, did I say something to upset you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.23,0:09:03.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.63,0:09:05.82,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  因为通常我们都肩并肩一起上楼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Really? Because usually we walk side by side,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.82,0:09:07.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而今天我爬了两层楼梯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I just went up two flights of stairs
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.57,0:09:09.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是跟在后面盯着你的屁股\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}staring at your bottom.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.10,0:09:12.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,消停会儿吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just drop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.56,0:09:14.99,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我知道是怎么回事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, I think I see what's happening here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.99,0:09:16.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嫉妒我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're jealous of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.27,0:09:17.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.39,0:09:19.84,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么好让我嫉妒的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What could you possibly have that I would be jealous of?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.84,0:09:20.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我有什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not what I have,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.95,0:09:23.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是我跟多少人一起"分享"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}it's how many people I'm having it with.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.63,0:09:28.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  谢尔顿  我们去对面看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Come on, Sheldon, we'll watch Game of Thrones over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.04,0:09:28.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乐意之极\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Gladly.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.73,0:09:30.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  走吧  我高兴还来不及呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, good, go. You know, it'll be nice to
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.55,0:09:32.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终于看剧的时候没人在旁边说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}watch an episode without someone saying,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.07,0:09:33.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我看过原著\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}"I read the books.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.15,0:09:35.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别太喜欢上这个角色"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't get too fond of this character."
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.16,0:09:38.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不全是因为他们会死啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's not always because they die.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.18,0:09:40.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,举个例子  某角色是因为跟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In one case, it's because they've become involved
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.00,0:09:42.16,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太古之初就有的地下的森林之子扯上关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with underground tree people from the dawn of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.16,0:09:43.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  但我不会说是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, but I won't say who it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.76,0:09:45.90,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是布兰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It's Bran!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.56,0:09:48.00,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait, what is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.00,0:09:50.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德是个混球  所以我们要在这边看剧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Leonard's being a jerk, so we're gonna watch over here,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.27,0:09:51.81,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们俩想跟我们一起看吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Do you guys want to watch with us?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.81,0:09:53.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要不跟他一起看就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}As long as I don't have to watch with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.59,0:09:55.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  我也不想跟你一起看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fine, I don't want to watch with you either.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.11,0:09:56.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll go over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.06,0:09:57.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭什么你来选\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why do you get to pick?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.26,0:09:58.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那你去那边好啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, then you go there!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.34,0:10:00.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老子爱去哪儿就去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't tell me where to go!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.87,0:10:02.07,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德  你快进来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Howard, just come in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.07,0:10:03.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这边  拉杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah, come on, Raj.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.87,0:10:06.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着  艾米有做菠菜蘸酱吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Wait, did Amy make her spinach dip?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.06,0:10:06.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She did.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.79,0:10:09.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老子会帮你吃光光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And I'm gonna eat it all!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.48,0:10:18.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到底发生什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So what the hell happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.71,0:10:21.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对谢尔顿的胡闹失去了耐心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I just ran out of patience with Sheldon's nonsense.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.58,0:10:23.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深有同感  我也受够拉杰了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Tell me about it. I've had it with Raj, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.87,0:10:24.92,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实男人像女人一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, like women,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.92,0:10:26.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个月也会有荷尔蒙变化周期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}men have a monthly hormone cycle.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.71,0:10:29.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睾丸激素的下降会导致男人易怒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Dips in testosterone can cause irritability.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.45,0:10:30.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Interesting.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.62,0:10:32.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我的男性周期刚好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe my male cycle synced up
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.24,0:10:35.61,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟拉杰的女性经期同步了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}with Raj's actual period.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.75,0:10:40.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果谢尔顿的睾丸激素下降  他要变成蝴蝶了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If Sheldon's testosterone dipped, he'd become a butterfly.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.43,0:10:46.37,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能有人上门赔礼道歉了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Maybe someone's here to apologize.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.17,0:10:48.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.83,0:10:52.40,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯图尔特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stuart.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.76,0:10:58.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是换装派对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is this not a dress-up party?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.26,0:11:00.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.71,0:11:05.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从一开始就不是换装派对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Was it ever a dress-up party?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.78,0:11:08.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.42,0:11:11.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德  你是不是告诉我这是换装派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Howard, didn't you tell me it was a dress-up party?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.09,0:11:12.41,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.47,0:11:27.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据说如果不爽霍华德  就应该来这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I was told this is where to go if I'm mad at Howard.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.63,0:11:32.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帮您把斗篷挂起来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}May I take your cloak?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.90,0:11:34.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.17,0:11:37.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这玩意一直被卷进我自行车的链条里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}This thing kept getting caught in the chain of my bike.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.41,0:11:39.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来给你说明一下情况\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I'll catch you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.97,0:11:43.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮不爽莱纳德  莱纳德不爽我和佩妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Uh, Penny is angry at Leonard, Leonard's angry at me and Penny,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.21,0:11:44.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不爽莱纳德和艾米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm angry at Leonard and Amy,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.96,0:11:46.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉杰不爽霍华德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Raj is angry at Howard,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.63,0:11:49.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不爽乔治·R·R·马丁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I'm angry at George R.R. Martin
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.63,0:11:49.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}《权力的游戏》的原著作者
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.04,0:11:52.19,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为他不出新书  害我不能跟莱纳德剧透\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}'cause there are no new books for me to spoil for Leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.96,0:11:55.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和霍华德怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}So what happened with you and Howard?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.18,0:11:58.35,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他嫌我不停说跟克莱尔和艾米丽约会的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Says I was talking too much about dating Claire and Emily,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.35,0:12:00.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说他就是嫉妒我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I accused him of being jealous.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.33,0:12:01.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也嫉妒你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm jealous.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.72,0:12:03.71,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最接近跟两个女人约会的一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Closest I've come to dating two women
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.71,0:12:06.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我跟一个女人约会的那次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was that time I dated one woman.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.24,0:12:12.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不知道你怎么受得了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know how you put up with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.11,0:12:14.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他简直有病  居然开个会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's impossible. I mean, holding a meeting
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.56,0:12:17.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来决定我们该买哪个早餐麦片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to decide what breakfast cereal we should buy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.11,0:12:20.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有脆浆果的那款脆脆船长麦片  行了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Yeah. Cap'n Crunch with Crunch Berries, move on.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.20,0:12:25.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  艾米  谢谢你挺我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Anyway, Amy, thank you for sticking up for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.11,0:12:27.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  我完全不在乎这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, I honestly couldn't care less.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.79,0:12:29.93,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没听错吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sorry?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.93,0:12:32.09,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挺你是因为有时我不爽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, I just took your side 'cause sometimes I get annoyed
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.09,0:12:34.70,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮和谢尔顿的关系那么亲近\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}at how close Sheldon and Penny are.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.70,0:12:36.53,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们吵个不停好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, they argue all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.53,0:12:38.24,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有很亲啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They aren't that close.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.24,0:12:40.83,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁总在他不高兴时安慰他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who's always comforting him when he's upset?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.83,0:12:42.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-佩妮  可... -是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- Penny, but... - Who's the only one
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.22,0:12:44.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能让他生病时把药吃下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}who can make him take his medicine when he's sick?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.31,0:12:45.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试过把药藏进他的花生酱里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I try to hide it in his peanut butter,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.88,0:12:48.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他吐了出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but he spits it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.09,0:12:50.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.96,0:12:53.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你知道佩妮让他在《室友协议》里加了条款\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And did you know she has him add things to the Roommate Agreement
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.75,0:12:57.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她既能得到想要的  又不用跟你吵架吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}so she can get her way and not fight with you about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.21,0:12:59.79,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个贱人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.87,0:13:05.96,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你乐什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why is that funny?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.96,0:13:08.86,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  我喜欢幸灾乐祸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't know. I like the pain of others.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.26,0:13:12.48,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你对这个肯定喜闻乐见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, then you'll enjoy this.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.48,0:13:15.58,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伯纳黛特对你和库萨帕里也是一样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Bernadette does the same thing with you and Koothrappali.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.58,0:13:16.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她才没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, she doesn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.59,0:13:18.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她总是替他说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She defends him all the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.21,0:13:19.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她才没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}She does not.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.68,0:13:23.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是谁告诉你  不要再对他开甘地玩笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who told you to stop making all those Gandhi jokes about him?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.33,0:13:25.73,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, she did.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.73,0:13:28.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有人力资源部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}And human resources.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.53,0:13:34.59,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得是谁让库萨帕里去人力资源部投诉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Who do you think told Koothrappali to go to human resources?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.59,0:13:37.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个贱人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.16,0:13:42.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对  的确挺乐的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're right, it feels good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.49,0:13:47.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  游戏时间马上到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}All right, it's almost game time.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.80,0:13:48.69,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.69,0:13:51.60,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《权利的游戏》  "游戏"时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Game of Thrones, game time?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.49,0:13:55.52,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也能俩女友啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Two women, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.49,0:14:01.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能是艾米脑子终于转过来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, perhaps it's Amy coming to her senses.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.19,0:14:03.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.91,0:14:06.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实你没必要利用谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, you don't need to use Sheldon to get your way with me
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.12,0:14:07.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在愚蠢的《室友协议》里搞定我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}in a dumb Roommate Agreement.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.51,0:14:08.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁告诉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Where'd you get that from?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.56,0:14:09.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾米\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}From Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.20,0:14:12.55,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,艾米  你为什么告诉他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Ugh. Amy, why did you tell him that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.55,0:14:14.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你总是替谢尔顿说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Because you were defending Sheldon like you always do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.91,0:14:16.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有总替谢尔顿说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't always defend Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.57,0:14:18.38,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有  你知道你自己对他有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, yes, you do. You know you have a weird
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.38,0:14:22.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,诡异的姐弟加埃利奥特与ET情感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}brother-sister-Elliott-E.T. Relationship with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.19,0:14:22.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn微软雅黑\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}埃利奥特是电影《E.T.外星人》中\N与E.T.感情深厚的男主角
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.36,0:14:24.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你对他的诡异情感呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What about your weird relationship with him?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.12,0:14:25.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's different.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.18,0:14:26.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就像是鬼片里不怕死的小女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'm like the little girl in Poltergeist
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.63,0:14:29.56,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他就是电视里的那个妖魔鬼怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and he's the creepy thing in the TV.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.39,0:14:31.95,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,各位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Um, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.95,0:14:34.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食物里是不是有坚果啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Were there any nuts in that food?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.17,0:14:35.88,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该没有  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I don't think so. Why? Well...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.48,0:14:38.45,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是有不祥的感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}just a feeling.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.32,0:14:49.33,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它就叫意大利三明治\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}It just said "Italian sub."
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.33,0:14:52.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想到意大利香辣肠里会有开心果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I had no idea mortadella has pistachios in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.27,0:14:54.65,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思小知识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Interesting fact:
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.65,0:14:59.42,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在意大利语中  意辣肠的前半段有死亡的意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}In Italian, the "Morta" In "Mortadella" means death.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.60,0:15:02.08,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.45,0:15:05.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没说"有趣"小知识  我又不是冷血怪物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I didn't say "fun" fact. I'm not a monster.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.99,0:15:08.57,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不会有事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}He's gonna be okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.17,0:15:11.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就是有趣小知识了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Now it's a fun fact.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.11,0:15:15.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  这种事情真能让人更理智看问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Boy, stuff like this really puts things in perspective.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.76,0:15:17.51,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么穿成这样子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Why are you dressed like that?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.51,0:15:20.13,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德骗我这是个换装派对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Oh, uh, Howard thought it'd be funny
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.13,0:15:22.27,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得看我出糗很有意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}to tell me it was a costume party.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.27,0:15:23.32,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这太坏了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That wasn't nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.32,0:15:27.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过他差点死了  我们扯平了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}No, but he almost died, so we're cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.65,0:15:31.98,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细想一想  其实今晚就像\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You know, if you think about it, tonight was kind of like
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.98,0:15:34.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现实版的《权力的游戏》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}a real-life Game of Thrones.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.39,0:15:35.31,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.31,0:15:37.43,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德吃下开心果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, Howard eating that pistachio
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.43,0:15:39.44,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像乔佛里被毒死那幕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}was like when King Joffrey got poisoned.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.44,0:15:42.15,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可那是谋杀  这是意外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay, well, that was murder, this was an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.15,0:15:43.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.62,0:15:46.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你利用谢尔顿去干那些肮脏勾当\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}But you using Sheldon to do your dirty work
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.97,0:15:50.20,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正像瑟后利用御林铁卫执行她的命令一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}is like when Cersei used the King's Guard to do her bidding.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.42,0:15:53.39,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑟后是靠卖肉操控男人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Cersei uses her body to manipulate men.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.39,0:15:56.18,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮只是带我去了乐高店\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Penny just takes me to The LEGO store.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.67,0:15:59.68,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  那这个呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Okay. Oh, how about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.68,0:16:02.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯图尔特穿得像个守夜人的兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Stuart's dressed like a brother of the Night's Watch,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.28,0:16:04.04,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而他们没女人睡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and they don't have sex.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.04,0:16:04.89,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说得好  -没有错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- There you go. - That's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.89,0:16:06.80,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没瑕疵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Fair enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.00,0:16:12.21,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没事吧  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}- You all right? - I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.21,0:16:15.05,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是觉得被人像抱婴儿一样抱下楼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Just a little embarrassed I had to be carried down the stairs
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.05,0:16:16.72,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点丢人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}like a baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.03,0:16:17.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.19,0:16:21.63,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Let's get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.63,0:16:22.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太吓人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That was scary.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.91,0:16:24.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重点是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Well, the important thing is
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.28,0:16:26.29,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过那个三明治会毁了一切的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I said that big sandwich would ruin everything,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.29,0:16:27.97,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被我言中了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and I was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.93,0:16:33.91,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,琼恩·雪诺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Hey, Jon Snow!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.91,0:16:37.85,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的马上怎么还有个篮子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How come your horse has a basket on it?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.73,0:16:43.12,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的脑袋上怎么还有张脸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}How come your head has your face on it?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.02,0:16:47.06,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《权力的游戏》里可不会戴自行车头盔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}They don't wear bicycle helmets in Game of Thrones.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.06,0:16:49.22,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然你装扮有瑕疵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}You're thematically inaccurate,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.22,0:16:52.78,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我为你的安全意识点赞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}but I applaud your commitment to safety.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.85,0:16:56.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们就没别的正经事可干了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Don't you guys have anything better to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.26,0:16:58.23,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比看一个穿皮草斗篷的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Better than watching a guy in a fur cloak
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.23,0:17:00.62,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑妇女车还重要的事吗  没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}ride a girl's bike? Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.03,0:17:03.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}That's it,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.26,0:17:06.94,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们刚刚失去了漫画店里的厕所特权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}you just lost bathroom privileges at the comic book store.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.71,0:17:15.87,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有篮子的马  一群傻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Horse has a basket on it. Stupid...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.24,0:17:27.02,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.57,0:17:30.28,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德  莱纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Leonard. Leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.28,0:17:31.67,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.67,0:17:35.26,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还一直没机会问你那个蝙蝠人的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I never got to ask my question about Batman.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.43,0:17:38.64,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.64,0:17:42.75,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果蝙蝠人被一个放射性的人蝠咬了后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}If Batman were bitten by a radioactive Man-Bat,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.75,0:17:46.11,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后穿成人蝠的样子去打击犯罪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}and then fought crime disguised as Man-Bat,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.11,0:17:49.17,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他是人蝠人蝠人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}would he be Man-Bat-Man-Bat-Man
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.17,0:17:53.36,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是人蝠人蝠蝙蝠人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}or simply Man-Bat-Man-Bat-Batman?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.09,0:17:59.76,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在人蝠装的底下还穿着蝙蝠人装吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}Is he still wearing the Batman suit under the Man-Bat suit?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.23,0:18:04.34,Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,容我思考一下再回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H62A8EB&}I'll be back.

