[Script Info]
Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.98,0:00:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.39,0:00:07.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,X-10(先进网络技术)已经联网了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The x-tens are online.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.51,0:00:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生们  我现在要通过这台电脑发射一个信号		\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Gentlemen, I am now about send a signal
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.64,0:00:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,连接到我们当地的互联网服务供应商\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}From this laptop through our local isp
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.50,0:00:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以光速在光纤电缆中传输到旧金山  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Racing down fiber-optic cable at the speed of light
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.35,0:00:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再通过地球同步轨道卫星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To san francisco, bouncing off a satellite
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.66,0:00:20.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反射到葡萄牙的里斯本\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In geosynchronous orbit to lisbon, portugal,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.86,0:00:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那里数据将\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where the data packets
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.00,0:00:23.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切换到跨大西洋海底电缆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Will be handed off to submerged trans-atlantic cables
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.81,0:00:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最终汇聚到加拿大新斯科舍省的哈里法克斯  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Terminating in halifax, nova scotia
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.80,0:00:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再通过微波中继跨越整个大陆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And transferred across the continent
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.18,0:00:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后回到我们的互联网服务供应商\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Via microwave relays back to our isp
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.37,0:00:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而X-10的接收器就连接着这个...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And the x-ten receiver attached to this...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.21,0:00:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Lamp.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.27,0:00:39.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快看  快看  我鸡皮疙瘩都起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look at me. look at me. I've got goose bumps.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.29,0:00:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们试试音响  准备好了没\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are we ready on the stereo?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.17,0:00:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快试试音响\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Go for stereo.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.91,0:01:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.72,0:01:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hi. hello. hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.08,0:01:08.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,声音有点大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's a little loud.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.16,0:01:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题  马上关小它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No problem-- turning it down.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.67,0:01:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,旧金山  里斯本  哈里法克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}San francisco, lisbon, halifax...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.23,0:01:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  好了吧(法语)\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And voila.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.83,0:01:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.87,0:01:19.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  等等  你是不是没明白我们在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hang on, hang on. do you not realize what we just did?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.70,0:01:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白  你们用电脑把音响关小了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, you turned your stereo down with you laptop.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.30,0:01:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是  我们通过互联网走了地球一圈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, we turned our stereo down by sending a snall
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.30,0:01:27.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发送了一个命令把音响关小的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Around the world via the internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.18,0:01:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其实这样一个遥控装置\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, you can just get one of those universal remotes
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.16,0:01:32.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在瑞帝优上(美国电子产品零售企业)里有买  而且很便宜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}At radio shack. they're really cheap.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.50,0:01:34.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  你还是没明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no. You don't get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.53,0:01:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德  开启公共接入功能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard, enable public access.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.10,0:01:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,公共接入已开启\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Public access enabled.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.70,0:01:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不赖  伙计们  我先走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Boy, that's terrific. I'll see ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.87,0:01:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别  等等  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, hang on, hang on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.90,0:01:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到没?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}See?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.35,0:01:51.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.85,0:01:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在中国四川省的某个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Someone in szechwan province, china
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.53,0:01:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在通过他的电脑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is using his computer
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.69,0:01:57.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,远程开关我们的灯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To turn our lights on and off.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.26,0:02:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那倒是很方便\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, that's handy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.22,0:02:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我提个问题  为什么要做这个?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here is the question. Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.37,0:02:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们可以做到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because we can.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.58,0:02:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们发现了远程遥控汽车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They found the remote-control cars.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.50,0:02:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  等等  车顶上是什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, wait, wait, what's on top of that?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.97,0:02:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无线网络摄像头  打个招呼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wireless web cams. wave hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.69,0:02:20.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那辆大货车来自德克萨斯州的奥斯丁  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The monster truck is out of austin, texas,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.61,0:02:22.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而"蓝毒蛇"正在被一个来自\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And the blue viper is being operated
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.50,0:02:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以色列特拉维夫郊区的人控制\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}From suburban tel aviv.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.78,0:02:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也许应该穿条裤子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You may want to put on slacks.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.79,0:02:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.10,0:02:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快停下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ew, stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.48,0:02:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  离我远点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No leave me alone
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.47,0:02:40.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个红色雪佛兰是谁控制的?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who's running the red corvette?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.20,0:02:41.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That would be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.52,0:03:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《生活大爆炸》\N第一季  第09集\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The.Cooper.Hofstadter.Polarization
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.43,0:03:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们知道吗  在将来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, in the future
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.67,0:03:09.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我们能把大脑取出来放到罐子里时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When we're disembodied brains in jars,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.94,0:03:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们回过头看看这八小时  会觉得那真无聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're going to look back at this as eight hours well wasted.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.51,0:03:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想被放到罐子里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't want to be in a jar.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.99,0:03:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想把我的大脑放在机器人身上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I want my brain in an android body.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.15,0:03:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好身高八英尺  身材健美\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Eight feet tall and ripped.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.58,0:03:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我支持你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.42,0:03:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是要确保假使我成了合成人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I just have to make sure that if I'm a synthetic human,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.55,0:03:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也还得是犹太人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'd still be jewish.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.06,0:03:31.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我答应过我妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I promised my mother.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.41,0:03:36.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜你还得给你那机器人鸡鸡做个包皮手术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I suppose you could have your android penis circumcised,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.01,0:03:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那是你的犹太教主\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But that's something
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.66,0:03:41.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和机器人制造者需要讨论的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Your rabbi would have to discuss with the manufacturer.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.10,0:03:44.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更不用说每到周六  你还得把电源关了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not to mention you'd have to power down on saturdays.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.53,0:03:48.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  这信怎么在垃圾桶里?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sheldon, why is this letter in the trash?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.97,0:03:51.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一封信旁边自动生成一只垃圾桶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, there's always the possibility that a trash can
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.80,0:03:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有可能出现的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Spontaneously formed around the letter,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.18,0:03:55.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但奥卡姆剃刀定律\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But occam's razor
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.23,0:03:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会认为是有人把它给扔了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Would suggest that someone threw it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.00,0:04:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是实验物理研究院寄来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's from the institute for experimental physics.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.06,0:04:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们希望我们能在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They want us to present our paper
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.96,0:04:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,主题为玻色-爱因斯坦凝聚的会议上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}On the properties of supersolids
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.66,0:04:06.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做我们超固体性质的论文演讲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}At the topical conference on bose einstein condensates.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.49,0:04:08.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我扔之前看过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know, I read it before I threw it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.30,0:04:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,容许我把问题阐述地更清楚些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, if I may drill down to the bedrock of my question
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.46,0:04:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要扔了它呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why did you throw it out?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.16,0:04:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我没兴趣站在万豪国际酒店的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because I have no interest in standing in the rose room
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.66,0:04:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玫瑰间里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Of the Pasadena Marriott
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.99,0:04:20.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去面对一群互相不认识但又喜欢评头论足的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In front of a group of judgmental strangers
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.33,0:04:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不会意识到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who wouldn't recognize true genius
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.88,0:04:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他们面前做演讲的人是真正的天才\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If it was standing in front of them giving a speech.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.72,0:04:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果我在那  我会这么认为的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Which, if I were there, it would be.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.88,0:04:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know, sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.70,0:04:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些主题为玻色-爱因斯坦凝聚的会议\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Those topical conference on bose einstein condensates
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.91,0:04:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后的庆功会都是超赞的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Parties are legendary.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.76,0:04:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提那些庆功会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Forget the parties.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.23,0:04:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提那些庆功会?  你个白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Forget the parties? what a nerd.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.03,0:04:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么别的荣誉我不知道的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are there any other honors I've gotten that I don't know about?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.86,0:04:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,UPS有没有快递过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did ups drop off a nobel prize
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.30,0:04:43.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我的诺贝尔奖?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}With my name on it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.96,0:04:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德  你千万别误会  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Leonard, please don't take this the wrong way,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.60,0:04:47.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过你得诺贝尔奖的那天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But the day you win a nobel prize
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.13,0:04:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我开始研究\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is the day I begin my research
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.06,0:04:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉伯飞毯上那些穗状雄花图案的风阻系数的那天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}On the drag coefficient of tassels on flying carpets.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.60,0:04:54.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才那些侮辱中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ooh, the only thing missing
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.73,0:04:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一没有提到的就是"你妈妈"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}From that insult was "your mama."
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.76,0:04:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我补充一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I got one.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.62,0:05:01.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德  你妈妈的研究方法问题实在太多...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, leonard, your mama's research methodology is so flawed...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.23,0:05:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴  霍华德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Shut up, howard.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.50,0:05:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  我们得去参加这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sheldon, we have to do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.03,0:05:06.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, we don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.33,0:05:08.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得吸取营养  排除毒素\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We have to take in nourishment, expel waste,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.63,0:05:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且吸入足够的氧气来维持我们细胞鲜活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And inhale enough oxygen to keep our cells from dying.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.10,0:05:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其它任何事都不是必须的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Everything else is optional.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.26,0:05:15.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那我这么说吧  我要去参加\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, let me put it this way, I'm doing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.90,0:05:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能  我是第一作者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You can't. I'm the lead author.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.86,0:05:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别逗了  之所以你是第一作者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Come on, the only reason you're the lead author
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.30,0:05:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为这是按名字字母排序的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is because we went alphabetically.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.03,0:05:23.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我让你这么认为的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I let you think we went alphabetically
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.83,0:05:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好让你不用面对这一耻辱性的事实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To spare you the humiliation
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.23,0:05:26.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是这篇论文是我想出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Of dealing with the fact that it was my idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.80,0:05:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我有意要说得那么直白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not to put too fine a point on it,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.56,0:05:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但事实是  我在可怜你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I was throwing you a bone.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.46,0:05:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.43,0:05:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着  这个假说的实验证明是我设计的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Excuse me, I designed the experiment that proved the hypothesis.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.76,0:05:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它根本就不用证明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It doesn't need proving.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.02,0:05:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么说  整个学术界就会那么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So the entire scientific community
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.83,0:05:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不加任何质疑地相信你的话?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is just supposed to take your word?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.26,0:05:44.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是会  是他们应该那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They're not supposed to, but they should.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.16,0:05:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了  我不管你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right, I don't care what you say,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.03,0:05:48.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去参加会议并展示我们的成果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm going to the conference and I'm presenting our findings.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.23,0:05:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不允许\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I forbid it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.19,0:05:52.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不允许?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You forbid it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.69,0:05:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我没有因为我们的成果而得到好评  那没人可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If I'm not taking credit for our work, then nobody is.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.36,0:05:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这么说你承认这是我们俩的成果?  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So you admit that it's our work? no.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.10,0:06:00.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说一遍  我是在可怜你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Once again, I'm throwing you a bone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.20,0:06:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并且再说一遍  不用谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And once again you are welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.46,0:06:08.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他不会吧(模仿莱纳德)\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, no, he didn't
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.80,0:06:12.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和谢尔顿现在怎样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, how's it going with sheldon?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.30,0:06:14.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们还是谁也不理谁吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you guys still not talking to each other?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.26,0:06:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不但还是不跟我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not only is he still not talking to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.03,0:06:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还会这么瞪着你  并做这么个动作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But there's this thing he does where he stares at you
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.23,0:06:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试图把你的脑子弄爆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And tries to get your brain to explode.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.70,0:06:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像那种经典的高科技电影里的扫描器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, like in the classic sci-fi movie scanners.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.66,0:06:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Like... bzzz...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.88,0:06:30.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Never mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.36,0:06:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这件怎么样?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How about this one?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.12,0:06:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以告诉别人说  我是物理学家  但我也是个有趣的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It says, I know my physics, but I'm still a fun guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.55,0:06:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道现在还有做灯芯绒外套\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wow, I didn't know they still made corduroy suits.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.71,0:06:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不做了  所以我才一直留着它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}They don't.That's why I saved this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.73,0:06:44.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  让我再看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, well, let's just see
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.39,0:06:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有什么别的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What else you have.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.30,0:06:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着这个...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, here, take this...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.33,0:06:52.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和这个  这个  还有这些...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And this, and this, and these...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.40,0:06:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有这些你都要让我试穿?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is this all stuff you want me to try on?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.23,0:06:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  这些是我想让你扔了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, this is stuff I want you to throw out.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.16,0:06:58.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说真的  甚至不要把它们捐作慈善\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh. seriously, don't even give them to charity.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.55,0:07:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这不是在帮助任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You won't be helping anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.58,0:07:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.71,0:07:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是坎多(对抗魔人的守卫国度)的瓶中城\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's the bottle city of kandor.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.73,0:07:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗  坎多曾经是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You see, kandor was the capital city
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.63,0:07:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,克里顿星球(还是星球大战)的首都\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Of the planet krypton.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.93,0:07:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它被天才在克里顿爆炸前缩小了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was miniaturized by brainiac before krypton exploded,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.40,0:07:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后被超人拯救了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And then rescued by superman.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.73,0:07:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh. nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.83,0:07:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是女孩子不看这些的时候比较好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's a lot cooler when girls aren't looking at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.58,0:07:27.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿上这个试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here, why don't you put these on
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.09,0:07:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再看看有没有合适的T恤和运动外衣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}While I find a shirt and a sport coat that match.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.72,0:07:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我马上回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Great, I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.89,0:07:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去哪里?  就这样换了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where are you going? just put 'em on.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.00,0:07:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.26,0:07:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还害羞啊?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, are you shy?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.60,0:07:35.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  我没害羞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, I'm not shy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.80,0:07:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心  我不会看的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't worry. I won't look.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.06,0:07:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你不会看  你为什么要看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I know you won't look. why would you look?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.06,0:07:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也没什么好看的...倒也不是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's nothing to see... well, not nothing...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.50,0:07:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  把裤子穿上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sweetie, put the pants on.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.30,0:07:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿了穿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Putting 'em on.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.71,0:07:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟谢尔顿在演讲这件事情上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, you know, isn't there maybe some way
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.33,0:07:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就没有互相妥协的余地吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You and sheldon could compromise on this whole presentation thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.76,0:07:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.05,0:07:52.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,科学家从不妥协\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Scientists do not compromise.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.73,0:07:54.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的大脑被锻炼成就是把事实结合起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Our minds are trained to synthesize facts
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.66,0:07:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后得出无可辩驳的结论\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And come to inarguable conclusions.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.33,0:08:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更不用说  谢尔顿还是个怪胎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not to mention, sheldon is bat-crap crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.03,0:08:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.73,0:08:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.08,0:08:08.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个是原版\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's my original series
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.36,0:08:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太空堡垒卡拉狄加的飞行服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Battlestar galactica flight suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.47,0:08:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万圣节的时候你怎么没穿这个?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, why didn't you wear it on halloween?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.03,0:08:16.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为那不是制服  是件飞行服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because it's not a costume. it's a flight suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.46,0:08:21.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  我继续找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, all right, moving on.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.38,0:08:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羊毛针织花衬衫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, wow, a paisley shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.56,0:08:26.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它正好配我那件灯芯绒外套\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Uh-huh, it goes with my corduroy suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.42,0:08:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你是说他们得呆在一个地方  那我同意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If you mean they should end up in the same place, then I agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.92,0:08:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你唯一的领带吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is this your only tie?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.03,0:08:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,理论上  是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Technically, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.33,0:08:37.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你仔细看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But if you'll notice...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.43,0:08:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会发现这是两面的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's reversible.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.33,0:08:42.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以可以当两条用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So it works as two.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.86,0:08:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  我觉得它连一条都不算\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh sweetie, I don't even think it works as one.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.56,0:08:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你所有的衣服吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is this all your clothes?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.43,0:08:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  从我八年级到现在所有的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yup. everything since the eighth grade.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.90,0:08:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八...八年级?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The... the eighth grade?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.20,0:08:55.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从那时起就不再长了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My last growth spurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.15,0:08:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那好  我想我们还是回到这套灯芯绒外套吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, well, I guess we're back to the corduroy suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.93,0:09:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Great. yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.13,0:09:05.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了不行  扔一边去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I said no. put it down.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.36,0:09:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.88,0:09:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  潘妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello, penny.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.35,0:09:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么好东西吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get anything good?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.15,0:09:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最近一季度的应用粒子物理学报\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just the latest copy of applied particle physics quarterly.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.44,0:09:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真奇怪  怎么你的来了我的却没到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, you know, that is so weird that yours came and mine didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.58,0:09:34.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开玩笑呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was a joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.47,0:09:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给女服务生点小费\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yep, tip your waitresses.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.54,0:09:43.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这一周都在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm here all week.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.04,0:09:46.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,潘妮  为了避免你感觉更加尴尬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Penny, just to save you from further awkwardness,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.08,0:09:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们两个安安静静地走上楼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Know that I'm perfectly comfortable with the two of us
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.15,0:09:49.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我完全没有意见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Climbing the stairs in silence.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.96,0:09:51.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, yeah, okay, me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.18,0:09:53.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴巴拉上  闭紧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Zip it, lock it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.08,0:09:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放在兜里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Put it in your pocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.81,0:10:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和莱纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, you and leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.88,0:10:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, dear god.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.11,0:10:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点小误会  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A little misunderstanding, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.00,0:10:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有点小误...?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A little misundersta...?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.69,0:10:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伽利略和教皇之间是有点小误会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Galileo and the pope had a little misunderstanding.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.40,0:10:16.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎样  我今天早上跟莱纳德聊天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Anyway, I was talking to leonard this morning,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.58,0:10:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为他对于这事感到很难过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I think he feels really bad about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.50,0:10:22.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是什么感受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, how do you feel?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.28,0:10:25.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没理解你这个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't understand the question.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.91,0:10:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是问和最好的朋友发生争执\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, I'm just asking if it's difficult
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.88,0:10:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是不是感觉很难受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To be fighting with your best friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.11,0:10:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没那么想过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, I hadn't thought about it like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.11,0:10:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想我是否正在经受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I wonder if I've been experiencing
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.31,0:10:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,由于无意识感情上混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Physiological manifestations
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.01,0:10:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而导致的一些生理表现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}of some sort of unconscious emotional turmoil.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.02,0:10:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait. what?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.26,0:10:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天早上拉不出屎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I couldn't poop this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.60,0:10:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟他说说话吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.51,0:10:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你们一定能把问题解决的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sure you guys can work this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.94,0:10:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这肯定比我的计划更好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's certainly preferable to my plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.82,0:10:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么计划?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Which was?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.08,0:10:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用强力泻药\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A powerful laxative.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.67,0:10:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你真的应该跟他好好谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, so you absolutely should talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.87,0:11:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道莱纳德把你当朋友的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look, I know leonard values you as a friend,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.45,0:11:03.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他亲口告诉我  如果没有你那些小点子    \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And he told me himself that without your little idea,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.55,0:11:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's no way he could have
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.15,0:11:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完成这整个实验\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Come up with this whole experiment thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.38,0:11:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  "小点子"?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Excuse me. "little idea"?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.42,0:11:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  他试着跟我解释过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, I mean, he tried to explain it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.18,0:11:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有弄得很明白...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I didn't really understand it...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.21,0:11:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当然没明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Of course, you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.25,0:11:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说"小点子"?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He said, "little idea"?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.38,0:11:21.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他不是那么说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, no, not in... not in those words.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.96,0:11:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是怎么说的  确切点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In what words then, exactly?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.65,0:11:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天  确切的词是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Um, you know, gee, the exact words...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.31,0:11:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他主要的意思是说...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's more the spirit in which...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.88,0:11:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What did he say?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.81,0:11:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是碰运气预感到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You had a lucky hunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.95,0:11:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  我刚才一直在想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, sheldon, I've been thinking.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.41,0:11:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直争执这个问题还不如...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Instead of arguing about this...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.45,0:11:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再跟我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't you ever speak to me again.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.85,0:11:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什...?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wha...?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.91,0:11:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.70,0:11:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去参加会议了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, I'm leaving for the conference.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.18,0:11:59.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你演讲我那"幸运的预感"愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Have fun presenting my "lucky hunch."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.66,0:12:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢尔顿  我不是那个意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Shel, I didn't mean it like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.29,0:12:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么要那么说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then why did you say it?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.11,0:12:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  我不是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know. I wasn't...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.25,0:12:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想取悦潘妮?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Were you trying to impress penny?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.72,0:12:07.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  完全不是  有那么一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, not at all. a little bit.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.28,0:12:10.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么做有效果吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How'd that work out for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.50,0:12:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,莱纳德  准备走了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Leonard, ready to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.75,0:12:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,力比多(弗洛伊德理论)  1-0\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}libido 1.0.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.72,0:12:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我再问你一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.25,0:12:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个成果是咱们一起完成的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We did the work together.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.35,0:12:20.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就让咱们一起去做演讲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let's present the paper together.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.78,0:12:22.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也跟你说最后一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I'm telling you for the last time
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.52,0:12:25.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这是在拉皮条  这是没有尊严的  咬我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's pandering, it's undignified, and bite me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.45,0:12:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.72,0:12:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Bye, sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.00,0:12:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  潘妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Good-bye, penny.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.21,0:12:43.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在未来的某一天...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}One of these days...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.36,0:12:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.42,0:12:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的没错  这面果然更好看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're right. this side does look better.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.08,0:12:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  我没说"更好看"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, I didn't say "better."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.72,0:12:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是说"褪色少一些"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I said "less stained."
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.25,0:12:56.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚观察了下  里面大约\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}i just checked the house. there's probably
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.88,0:12:58.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有20-25个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}20-25 people in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.09,0:12:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑吧?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're kidding?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.11,0:13:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-一共就这些?  -就这些? \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is that all? "all"?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.92,0:13:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对高能物理学领域来说  25人已称得上伍德斯托克(摇滚音乐节)了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In particle physics, 25 is woodstock.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.32,0:13:07.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样啊  那不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, well, then good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.56,0:13:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没想到会有这么多人  我有点紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I wasn't expecting such a crowd. I'm a little nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.69,0:13:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  讲个笑话做开场白就不紧张了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's okay. just open with a joke. you'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.22,0:13:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,笑话  好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Uh, joke. okay,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.45,0:13:16.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个怎么样?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.65,0:13:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有个农民\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Um, okay, uh, there's this farmer,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.25,0:13:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他养了一些鸡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And he has these chickens,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.75,0:13:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是它们不下蛋  所以他去找物理学家求救\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But they won't lay any eggs, so he calls a physicist to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.22,0:13:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个物理学家便做了些计算\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The physicist then does some calculations,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.38,0:13:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后说"我有个办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And he says, "i have a solution,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.82,0:13:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过只适用于真空环境下的球形鸡(加拿大科学家凯伊的方法)"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But it only works with spherical chickens in a vacuum."
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.42,0:13:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好笑吧?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.78,0:13:47.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我...我以前听过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, sorry, I just... I've heard it before.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.48,0:13:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们进去吧  -好的 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let's roll. okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.52,0:13:49.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西服不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, nice suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.52,0:13:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一流的  是吧?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's a classic, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.91,0:13:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真应该把我的车开来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I really should have brought my own car.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.85,0:13:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此我们总结如下  数据表明\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, in conclusion, the data show
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.32,0:14:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当温度接近绝对零度时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That at temperatures approaching absolute zero,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.48,0:14:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转动惯量就会发生改变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The moment of inertia changes,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.25,0:14:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而固体就会变成一种超固体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And the solid becomes a supersolid which clearly appears
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.62,0:14:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成为一种之前未知的物质\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To be a previously unknown state of matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.15,0:14:14.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.65,0:14:19.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请问有任何问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Were there any questions?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.75,0:14:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有  那到底是什么玩意?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, what the hell was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.90,0:14:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有其他问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Any other questions?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.35,0:14:28.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是谢尔顿·库珀博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Dr. sheldon cooper here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.48,0:14:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这篇论文的第一作者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I am the lead author of this particular paper.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.38,0:14:34.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.92,0:14:39.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你  这位先生  完全跳过了一个重要部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And you, sir, you have completely skipped over the part
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.08,0:14:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时我是在公园里散步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Where I was walking through the park,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.88,0:14:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见小孩们在玩旋转木马\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I saw these children on a merry-go-round,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.95,0:14:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是这才让我想起转动惯性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Which started me thinking about the moment of inertia
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.45,0:14:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当温度接近绝对零度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}In gases like helium
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.98,0:14:49.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在气体里  比如氦气里的表现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}At temperatures approaching absolute zero.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.05,0:14:50.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有跳过  这只是个小插曲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I didn't skip it. it's just an anecdote.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.72,0:14:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是科学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's not science.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.72,0:14:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.92,0:14:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么苹果落在牛顿的头上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Was the apple falling on newton's head,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.01,0:14:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也仅仅是个小插曲?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Was that just an anecdote?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.31,0:14:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是艾萨克·牛顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You are not isaac newton.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.56,0:14:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是  是  这倒是不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, that's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.69,0:15:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我来说  不用那苹果我也会知道是地球引力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Gravity would have been apparent to me without the apple.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.82,0:15:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能不那么自大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You could not possibly be that arrogant.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.58,0:15:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你仍旧低估了我  我的伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You continue to underestimate me, my good man.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.35,0:15:08.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  如果你因为我的演讲而不高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look, if you weren't happy with my presentation,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.28,0:15:10.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你应该跟我一起来讲的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then maybe you should have given it with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.37,0:15:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我反复解释的  我不像你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}As I've explained repeatedly, unlike you,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.40,0:15:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要比我笨的人来认可我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't need validation from lesser minds.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.88,0:15:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有别的意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No offense.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.31,0:15:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你还为什么来?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So why did you come?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.82,0:15:19.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我知道你会把它糟蹋了的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because I knew you'd screw this up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.25,0:15:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才没有糟蹋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I didn't screw it up
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.25,0:15:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, please,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.18,0:15:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我承认那个球形鸡的笑话...是挺好笑  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I admit that spherical chicken joke-- that was hilarious. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.76,0:15:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过从那里开始就急转直下了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But it was straight downhill from there.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.12,0:15:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我受够了你这种高傲的态度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've had enough of your condescension.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.11,0:15:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我没有像你一样11岁就考上大学\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe I didn't go to college when I was 11 like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.99,0:15:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我是24岁才拿到博士  而不像你是16岁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe I got my doctorate at 24 instead of 16,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.49,0:15:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不是这个屋子里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But you are not the only person
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.75,0:15:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一一个比他们都聪明的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who is smarter than everyone else in this room
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.92,0:15:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没别的意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No offense.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.22,0:15:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我显然并不是这里唯一一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I am clearly not the only person
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.55,0:15:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怀着不安全感  渴望得到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who is tormented by insecurity
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.82,0:15:47.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不断的肯定  并为之饱受苦恼的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And has an ego in need of constant validation.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.78,0:15:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你承认你是个自大狂了?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So you admit that you're an egotist?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.32,0:15:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yes
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.85,0:15:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是莱纳德·霍夫斯塔德博士\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My name is dr. leonard hofstadter
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.95,0:15:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从不讨我父母喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I could never please my parents,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.48,0:15:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我需要从你们这些陌生人这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So I need to get all my self-esteem
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.22,0:15:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把自尊心都找回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}From strangers like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.22,0:15:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他更差劲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But he's worse
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.52,0:16:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  够了  -别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, that is it stop it
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.57,0:16:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不可能用意念爆了我的头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You cannot blow up my head with your mind
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.58,0:16:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那给你弄个动脉瘤也成\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then I'll settle for an aneurysm.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.68,0:16:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别弄了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stop it
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.75,0:16:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You hit me
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.65,0:16:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都看到了  他打我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You saw that. he hit me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.95,0:16:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你想爆了我的头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You were trying to blow up my head.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.29,0:16:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以还是起作用了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So it was working.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.35,0:16:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是呢  你简直是个疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was not you are a nut case
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.53,0:16:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We'll see about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.85,0:16:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把头抬起来  坐第一排的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Heads up, you people in the front row.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.65,0:16:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是辐射区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is a splash zone.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.38,0:16:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stop it
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.18,0:16:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Quit it
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.10,0:16:31.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们搞物理的经常这样?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is this usually how these physics things go?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.48,0:16:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比你想的要频繁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}More often than you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.18,0:16:39.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下  我要发功把你弄爆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stop it nerve pinch
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.78,0:16:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以让我搭车一起回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You could have offered me a ride home.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.05,0:16:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没开车把你碾过去你已经很幸运了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're lucky I didn't run you over.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.05,0:16:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不知道你在不开心些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I really don't understand what you're so unhappy about.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.38,0:16:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你求我去  我去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You begged me to come. I came.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.76,0:17:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果你还是不高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}There's just no pleasing you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.15,0:17:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  问题都在我这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're right. I'm the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.38,0:17:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是那个需要帮助的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm the one that needs help.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.95,0:17:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是很像道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, that's not much of an apology,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.58,0:17:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我接受了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I'll take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.05,0:17:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.16,0:17:12.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有什么想向我道歉?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Is there anything you would like to apologize for?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.05,0:17:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.85,0:17:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有想要爆了你的头  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry I tried to blow up your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.08,0:17:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样做没有必要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was uncalled for.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.08,0:17:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不会相信的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You won't believe this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.22,0:17:24.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人把整件事情经过用手机拍下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Somebody got the whole thing on a cell phone
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.74,0:17:26.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并上传到了Youtube\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And put it on youtube.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.35,0:17:28.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.56,0:17:30.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会这么缺德?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now who would do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.98,0:17:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That would be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.05,0:17:35.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快来看看  很有意思的视频\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, check it out. it's a featured video.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.92,0:17:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你打我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You hit me
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.57,0:17:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们都看到了  他打我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You saw that he hit me
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.67,0:17:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你想爆了我的头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're trying to blow up my head.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.69,0:17:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以还是起作用了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So it was working.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.86,0:17:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别弄了  你简直是个疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stop it you're a nut case.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.53,0:17:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们来看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We'll see about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.78,0:17:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们前排的人  把头抬起来  这里是辐射区\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You people in the front row, heads up. this is a splash zone.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.83,0:17:48.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Stop it
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.28,0:17:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停下来  停下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Quit it quit it
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.15,0:17:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要发功把你弄爆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Put you in a vulcan nerve pinch
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.25,0:17:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该剪剪指甲  真疼死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Ow, you should cut your fingernails. those hurt
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.45,0:18:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天  这套西服真的这么难看?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, geez, does this suit really look that bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.18,0:18:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提你那西服了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Forget your suit.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.42,0:18:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看我胳臂挥的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look at my arms waving.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.58,0:18:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是利他林(一种兴奋剂)上的那只红鹤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm like a flamingo on ritalin.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.52,0:18:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,霍华德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Howard,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.68,0:18:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能向我解释下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Would you like to explain to me
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.25,0:18:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你的facebook(国外交友网站)主页上有张我靠在你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why your facebook page has a picture of me sleeping
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.78,0:18:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肩膀睡觉的照片  并且标题是我和我的女友?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}On your shoulder captioned "me and my girlfriend"?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.19,0:18:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又得好好解释下了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}here comes the talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.66,0:18:36.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,(中国某地)\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}somewhere in China
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.81,0:18:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么混蛋东西嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What losers.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.26,0:18:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对呀  很大的书呆子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah. Gigantic American geeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.82,0:18:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁在搞鬼?\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Who's doing that?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.04,0:18:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个来自加利福尼亚州的帕萨迪纳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Someone from Pasadena, California named...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.32,0:18:58.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫"沃尔巫师"的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Wolowizard"
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.26,0:19:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷毙了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Awesome.
