My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went
to prison for her murder.
Then an accident made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
The night we
trapped the Reverse-Flash
in the force field, there's no reason
that the containment
system should have failed.
- I've been having these dreams.
- What happens in the dream?
Dr. Wells is the Reverse-Flash,
and he kills me.
If this is Dr. Wells,
then who have we been
working for this whole time?
A completely different person.
Oh, my God.
What the frack?
"Flash missing. Vanishes in crisis."
"After an epic street battle
with the Reverse-Flash,
"our city's very own Scarlet Speedster
disappeared in an explosion of light."
Barry, look at the date.
April 25th, 2024.
Guys, when I fought The
Reverse-Flash at Christmas,
he said that we'd be
fighting for centuries.
Wait, you can't really
think that this is from...
the future.
That would means Dr. Wells,
or whoever he is, is also...
From the future.
I have to say, I'm really digging
the brighter red suit.
And the white on the symbol?
That's dope.
Wait a second.
Suppose we now change
the color on your suit.
Will it be because we got
the idea from this picture?
That would mean we're
living in a causal nexus.
This... wow.
This is so trippy.
Like, Marty and the Polaroid trippy.
Not as trippy as the name on the byline.
Iris West-Allen?
Mazel tov?
Hebrew.
Ancient language of the Jewish people.
Uh-uh. What the hell was that?
Is someone here?
Hello?
Good evening, Barry Allen.
Uh...
H-hi.
- You know who I am?
- Of course.
Barry Allen, director
of Central City Police,
CSI Division.
Director?
I guess you get a promotion.
Also known as The Flash.
Founding member of...
What are you?
I am Gideon,
an interactive artificial consciousness.
AI.
Sick.
You know Dr. Wells?
Yes.
Do you know who he really is?
I don't understand the question.
I... I mean, what is he doing here?
W-why did he come here?
To kill you.
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Wells is in the building.
What? How do you know that?
I put a tracker on his wheelchair.
Which, if we're wrong about
him and he is paralyzed,
I'm going to hell for that one.
He's in the Cortex.
Ask questions fast.
Why did he kill Nora Allen?
Because he was angry.
About what?
That you escaped.
He's on B level. He's coming this way.
What does he want from me?
For you to be The Flash.
Maybe that's why Wells let
the particle accelerator explode,
so that you could become The Flash.
Why? I mean, for what reason?
Guys, we got to go. He's almost here.
- Hurry.
- All right.
Wait a second. Wait.
What if HAL over there tells
Wells that we were in here?
That would be bad.
If I can get into its operating system,
maybe I can disable its memory core.
Gideon, can you show us where
your operating system is?
Certainly.
Yeah. Nope.
That's not gonna happen.
Guys, he's in the corridor.
Gideon, could you just, like,
not tell him that we were here?
Of course.
I will accept any command
given to me by you.
- Barry.
- Come on.
- We got to get out of here.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Why would you accept my commands?
Because you created me.
Good evening, Gideon.
Good evening, Dr. Wells.
Is everything all right?
Everything is fine.
- Synced and corrected by ChrisKe -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Eddie.
- Thank you.
- What's the emergency?
Oh, no emergency.
I just wanted to, you know, talk to you...
Thanks.
Without Iris around
or Barry around
or Cisco around or Caitlin around.
So, in other words, you
want to talk to me alone.
What is it?
Right.
Um, so listen.
With everything going on...
Investigating Wells and
finding out about Barry...
Eddie, you cannot tell Iris about Barry.
This isn't about Barry.
I know the timing might seem off, you know,
with everything that's going on,
but I want to propose to Iris,
and I'd like your blessing.
No.
Come again?
You do not have my blessing.
That's Barry. We got to go.
Joe, I only asked as a courtesy,
out of respect.
I don't need your permission.
Really?
For three very smart people,
that was really stupid.
What if Wells had caught you in that...
- Time vault.
- Thank you.
Okay, I know we've seen
a lot this past year,
but time travel?
I did it.
- Or I will do it, I mean.
- Excuse me?
One of the two speedsters in Barry's house
the night his mother died was Barry.
I mean, The Flash. He was there.
Which means that one day in the future,
Barry will travel back
in time to that night.
Okay.
Actually, I wasn't talking about that.
I kind of already time traveled.
- By accident.
- What?
I was running to try and stop a tsunami
from hitting the city...
When was that?
A few weeks ago.
Right before you started
getting those dreams.
Oh, you mean the ones where Wells uses
his super-speeding hand
to shred apart my heart?
- Those?
- Yes, right.
So, what if they're not dreams?
What else could they be?
Memories.
I'm not following.
All right, what if,
that day, Cisco found out
that Wells is the Reverse-Flash,
and then Wells killed him?
But when I ran back a day,
I changed the timeline so
that event never happened.
If it never happened,
how can Cisco remember it?
I don't know. I don't know.
I think the important thing is, he does.
Guys, I think I've got a really bad idea.
Dad, it's been three weeks.
You barely eat or sleep.
You should probably go home at some point.
- Hey, baby.
- Hi.
I'll go home when Barry does.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Help! My son's coding.
They said he was stable.
Barry.
- Oh, my God.
- I need the room.
Just go. I need the room.
How can he be seizing?
He has no heart rhythm.
- Starting compressions.
- Epi push. Epi.
They can't save him.
But I can.
I know who you are.
You're that scientist
that Barry's obsessed with,
the one who blew a hole in the city.
Harrison Wells, and interestingly enough,
my facility is the very place
I would like to take him.
You're out of your mind.
I'm not gonna try and
convince you with promises.
But, Detective, give me a chance.
I think we already know what
you're capable of, Doctor.
You hurt a lot of people that night.
So those doctors in
there, they're good enough?
The best in the city, best in the country.
Look at them.
They have no clue what's going on.
They're baffled, and the reason for that is
what's happening inside Barry is a mystery,
and they don't have the tools to solve it.
- But you do?
- That's right.
Millions of people
used to look at my lab,
and what did they see?
They saw the future.
Well, let me take that technology,
let me take that know-how into ensuring
that your son actually does have a future.
Detective.
Let me save him.
- Hand me the paddles.
- Starting compressions.
Then save him.
Charge. 200. Pads.
Joe?
Joe, are you listening?
Yeah.
We... we have to access
Cisco's memories somehow.
Somewhere in his subconscious is the key.
The key to what now?
Getting my dad out of prison.
And how are we going to do that?
We're gonna get Wells to
confess to killing my mom.
So, this will allow Cisco
to see into his dream?
I got the idea from a journal article
on lucid dream therapy.
They think it can be used to help people
suffering from post-traumatic
stress disorder.
Traumatized, stressed?
Check and check.
The theory is that it will allow people
to objectively enter their dreams
and face their fears.
Still working on the talking part.
And you're sure this thing
isn't gonna, you know,
mess with my brain?
Oh, the amount of electricity required
to trigger lucid dreaming is harmless.
Probably.
Who's going to be lucid dreaming?
Um...
With all of the
meta-humans in Central City,
people have been seeing
some strange things...
Things that they don't understand.
And it's really just a matter of time
before psychological issues develop.
And lucid dreaming will help the doctors
better understand their fears.
Intriguing.
Of course, you still
need to guide the patient
from the outside, right?
Direct them to specific
aspects of the dream.
We're still working on a
communications interface.
When we dream,
the middle brain lights up
with electrical activity,
whereas the higher brain remains dormant.
Once we find a way to make
both parts of the brain active,
then it's just a matter
of finding the frequency
that will stimulate the language center.
Then the dreamer could speak.
He could describe his dream.
- Exactly.
- Or her dream.
It could be used for anyone.
Right, it's not gender specific.
I would try a frequency
of 45 hertz to start.
Thank you, Dr. Wells.
Well, you never cease
to impress me, Caitlin.
- Allen.
- Hey.
The Owens case.
I'm still waiting on the fiber evidence
and the ballistics report.
Are you on vacation or something?
- No, I'm so sorry, I've
just...
I've been distracted by another case.
Which is no excuse, I just...
Okay, just get me the reports when you can.
There's... there's no rush.
All right. Uh, Captain?
Is everything okay?
Yeah, since Rob and I
have been planning the,
you know, wedding, between the florist
and the hundreds of kinds of cake filling
and who can sit next to who...
Never get married, Allen.
Right.
- Oh.
- Iris.
- Barry.
- Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah. No. Yes.
That was... That was just really weird.
Captain Singh was nice to me.
Oh, well, he's in a good mood.
He's about to get married.
Lucky him. Yeah, I know, it's...
Oh, hey, can I talk to you in private?
It's... it's kind of work-related.
Okay, yeah, now's not a great time.
- I'm sorry, I've got...
- Hi, beautiful.
Hi.
Barry, can I grab you for a second?
Absolutely. Yeah.
Okay, well, can you
call me when you're done?
It's... it's really important.
Yeah. Yeah.
What's up?
Oh. O-okay.
W-what did she say?
Or, wait, you still have it, so,
duh, you haven't asked her yet.
Or you did ask her, and she said...
- I was gonna propose tonight.
- All right.
But I went to Joe to ask for his blessing.
- He said no.
- He did? He...
- Repeatedly.
- Uh, weird.
I need you to talk to him, find out why.
Uh, Eddie...
Look, I know me asking you like this,
it's a little awkward.
Yeah.
But you know how heartbroken she's gonna be
if she finds out that Joe's not on board.
Yeah. Yeah, all right.
Yeah, I'll talk to him, man.
Oh, thanks. I appreciate it so much.
- Yeah.
- And so will
the future Mrs. Thawne.
Iris Thawne.
Sounds pretty good, huh?
I have a feeling she's
gonna want to hyphenate.
Okay, can we go
over this one more time?
Yeah, you put the glasses on,
fall asleep, and start dreaming.
Not that hard.
Yeah, except I'm pretty
sure I die in this dream.
If I go back into it, am
I gonna die in real life?
I mean, what are we talking about here?
Is this Inception or Dreamscape?
Here. Drink this.
- What, am I five?
- Just drink it.
Okay, I'll drink it.
You're gonna be fine, Cisco.
Mm.
Okay.
The glasses are emitting
a low-level delta wave
which should help you fall asleep.
Okay.
I got to warn you, though,
usually it takes me a long time.
I mean...
I'm not saying I'm, like...
an insomniac or any...
Ah, so that's how you get him to shut up.
He's entering REM.
It's working.
Cisco.
Can you hear me?
You're dreaming, bud.
Okay, I
will take Dr. West to Jitters
so you do whatever it is you want to do.
Whoa.
Guys, this is mad freaky.
Okay, um, where are you?
Um, in the Cortex.
I mean, I know I'm just
dreaming that I'm in the Cortex,
but it feels so real.
What is dream you doing?
Caitlin just left.
I asked her to take Wells to Jitters.
Why... why do you want
Wells out of the lab?
I think he might have
tampered with my work.
I need to check.
Okay.
Okay, I'm walking to the bunker.
Oh, man, I love this shirt.
I thought the dryer ate it.
Focus, Cisco.
Okay, okay.
All right.
Now I'm running tests on
the containment system.
This data... It doesn't make any sense.
All the supercapacitors...
They were all still fully charged.
There's absolutely no
reason that the Man in Yellow
should have escaped.
Oh, my God.
It was just a hologram.
He tricked us.
Hello, Cisco.
Oh, God, Wells is here.
Cisco, it's just a
dream. He can't hurt you.
You better be right about that.
My name is Eobard Thawne.
Eobard Thawne.
Thawne? Like Eddie Thawne?
You killed Nora Allen.
It was never my intention.
Nora? What about my mom?
- He's confessing.
- Cisco?
He... he didn't want to kill her.
It was you, Barry.
He was trying to kill you.
His blood pressure's 200
and his heart rate is 147.
Guys, he's losing
higher brain function.
Cisco, you're gonna be okay.
It's just a dream. You're gonna be okay.
I have grown quite fond of you, Cisco.
His hand... It's vibrating.
- He's gonna kill me!
- Oh, God.
- He's gonna have a stroke.
- Get him out of there!
In many ways,
you've shown me what it's like...
Help me, please!
To have a son.
Help me!
Aah!
You're okay.
It was just a dream. You're okay.
Oh, God.
It felt so real.
- Barry?
- My mom.
That's why it's my fault.
Hello?
Where are you?
Barry.
Barry, are you there?
Dr. Wells.
Yeah. It's... sorry, yeah.
It's... it's a bad connection right now.
Where have you been?
Uh, we're... Why? What's going on?
A fire.
A huge fire just erupted.
A fire? Where?
New Brighton.
Bradford Tower High-Rise.
I know that building.
That's where Captain Singh's fiance works.
On my way.
Now move it! Go!
Get those hoses up. Move!
And tell dispatch we need
as many tankers as this city has.
- What floor?
- 21st.
God. That's where Rob works.
Please hurry.
Over here!
Dr. Wells, the sprinklers...
They're not working.
I see that.
Just get everyone out of there, Barry.
No, I can't. I can't save them all.
Dr. Wells, please, what do I do?
You create a vacuum.
Rotate your arms at super-speed.
That'll create a wind funnel
that will suck the air
right out of the room.
It's making it worse!
Barry, listen to me.
You need to move your arms faster.
I believe in you, Barry.
Rob.
I'm okay. It's okay.
I thought I lost you.
Medic!
Mr. Allen.
Tonight, at the fire,
I saw hesitation.
I saw you doubting yourself.
Why is that?
I don't know.
Uh, I guess I was afraid
I couldn't save everyone.
Right.
But if there is anything
that I have learned
in our time together, Barry,
it is that the only thing
standing in the way of you
achieving every goal
that you set for yourself
is you.
There is no limit to
how strong you will get
or how fast you will go.
Everything that you need,
you already have.
Thank you, Dr. Wells.
You know,
I couldn't have done
any of this without you.
I feel the same way about you.
It's so strange.
I mean, I look at him now,
and I know that he killed my
mom and he sent my dad to jail,
but, I mean, sometimes he's just so kind
in the moment, I actually like him.
But you never did.
- No.
Well, at least now we know how to trap him.
In Cisco's dream, he
confessed to everything.
If we can just recreate those conditions,
he'll do it again.
Man, Barr.
Taking down bad guys, pulling confessions.
I'm the cop.
I'm the one that's
supposed to be doing this.
Look, if we're gonna get him to confess,
it has to be with someone
that he truly trusts,
someone that he'll genuinely
let his guard down with.
He thinks of Cisco as a son.
Well, then we need to do
a better job protecting him
than I did protecting you.
I'm not sure what that means.
Barry, this is all because of me.
No.
I never should've let Wells
take you from that hospital.
None of this would've ever happened.
If you hadn't let him take
me, I would be dead, for sure.
But even then, I knew
something wasn't right.
Everything in my gut was
telling me not to trust him,
but I did,
because I was so desperate to see you okay.
Joe, this isn't your fault.
It's not your fault.
Look, every bad thing
that has happened to us...
All of it... It was him.
And now he's gonna pay for it.
So, Wells set up a fake showdown
with a fake opponent who
was never really there?
He figured if we saw both of them together
it would prove that he
wasn't the Man in Yellow.
This all just keeps
getting crazier and crazier.
I just talked to Dr. Wells.
He's attending a lecture downtown,
won't be back until 5:00.
All right, Cisco, you
know when he gets here
you need to be working on the trap
so he sees you set off the hologram.
Hold on, isn't that, in your dream,
when everything went all...
Kali Ma. Temple of Doom.
Yeah, that definitely happened.
But this time, I'm ready for him.
I originally designed the force field
to keep a speedster from getting out.
But I've reversed it.
Now it won't let one in.
Back up.
Barry, are you okay?
Ah.
It works.
Okay, as long as I'm inside,
Wells won't be able to get near me.
And I will be in the Cortex
watching and recording
everything that happens.
And as soon as we get
the confession we need
to free my dad, I'm moving in.
So what do I do?
Wells also threatened Iris,
so if something goes wrong here,
we need you to keep an eye on her
until Wells is neutralized.
I'll always keep Iris safe, Joe.
- What?
- Come here.
So, um, Eddie told me what happened,
that you kiboshed his proposal.
That was supposed to be between him and me.
I so agree with that.
And I... and I know that we
have a lot going on right now,
and I should definitely be the last person
pleading Eddie's case,
but I don't get it, Joe.
Why did you say no?
Because if Eddie proposes to Iris,
she's gonna get caught up in
the moment and the romance,
and she's gonna say yes.
What's wrong with that?
Again, I don't know why I'm saying this.
Because one day she's
gonna wake up and realize
she married the wrong guy.
But she'll stay anyway
because she made a promise.
I don't want that kind of life for her.
Or him.
She's got feelings for you, Barry.
She may not know how to deal
with those feelings right now,
but I know her.
They're there. Always have been.
You know that, too.
Speaking of, Iris just sent me a 911 text.
I'll be right back.
Like I said.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What's going on?
Look, Barry, I know it's not a good time.
I mean, lately, it never
seems to be a good time,
but I need you to listen to me right now.
Like... like, really listen to me.
Of course. Yeah.
Whatever you need to
tell me, I'm listening.
Okay, I mean, I know this is gonna sound
really crazy at first, but...
Everything strange that's
been going on in Central City,
it all goes back to that night.
The night that the particle
accelerator exploded.
I have gone through
every bit of information
that I've collected
since I started my blog...
Every tip, every rumor,
every strange sighting.
Nothing predates the explosion.
Whatever was released into
the atmosphere that night,
I think it changed people...
Caused them to have powers.
And I think that S.T.A.R.
Labs knew about it.
I think the Burning Man worked there,
and I think that that's how
The Flash got his powers too.
- Uh...
- So what do you think?
I...
I don't know. I mean,
it's... it's interesting.
Yeah, it's interesting.
It's... there's... there's just...
A big hole in your theory.
Um, you know...
I was affected by whatever
was released by the explosion,
and I don't have any powers.
- Obviously.
- Right, yeah.
Look, I mean, I know that
it's... It's really mind-blowing.
I mean, I haven't even talked
to Eddie about it yet, but...
Yeah, you and Eddie... How are...
everything's okay with you and Eddie?
Uh, sure. Sure.
Yeah, we're great. Why?
Uh, I... Yeah, okay, look.
I'm gonna... let me read
over all of this stuff,
and we'll definitely talk about it later.
I promise.
Just... I mean, this is crazy.
Yeah, okay, just let me just go through it,
and we'll talk later, all right?
Okay.
Hey, Barry.
It's Iris.
I don't know if you can
hear me, but I hope you can,
because I really, really
need you to wake up.
Like, the other day,
Detective Pretty Boy came into Jitters,
and he asked me out,
and I actually said yes.
See, I do dumb things like
that when you're not around.
And the house is really quiet without you.
I know that the reason that
you came to live with us
was awful.
But Barry,
you made it a home again.
You made us a family again.
We need you.
I need you.
Hello, Dr. Wells.
How was your lecture?
Oh, boring, tedious.
Platitudinous?
Couldn't have said it better myself.
Um, where... Where's Cisco?
Uh, he is in the bunker.
He thinks he finally figured
out what went wrong at Christmas.
You know, when we were trying
to catch the Reverse-Flash?
Yes, I remember that night.
Well, did he say what he's found?
Nope, just that it was important.
Hmm.
Good for Cisco.
Um... okay.
Well, maybe I'll wheel on down there,
see what he's got.
Okay.
Here he comes.
Hello, Cisco.
You've been busy.
You really are incredibly clever, Cisco.
I've always said it.
You're him.
the Reverse-Flash.
Joe was right this whole time, wasn't he?
Good ol' Joe.
Joe West had his doubts all along.
Even from that first night in the hospital,
Joe knew something wasn't right.
Cops... as inconvenient now
as they will be in a hundred years.
Come on, Cisco. We need a confession.
You killed Barry's mother.
I want to know why.
It was never my intention to kill Nora.
But from my perspective,
she was already dead.
It just happened sooner
than it was supposed to.
No. That's not an admission.
Oops.
You're not gonna get away with this.
I'm not gonna get away with it?
Oh, you're smart.
You're smart, Cisco.
But you're not that smart.
Cisco!
No!
He didn't confess.
Cisco, are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm never ever gonna sleep ever again,
but, yeah, I'm okay.
He's dead.
He didn't confess.
Joe, this was it.
My dad's gonna be in prison forever.
Barry, I'm sorry.
Hey, uh...
Whoa.
What the hell?
I told you this before.
I am always one step ahead... Flash.
Allow me to reintroduce to you
Mr. Hannibal Bates
and his incredible ability to transform
into any person he touches.
I knew that
ability would come in handy.
I did not expect it to
come in handy this soon.
You used him!
Like you used all of us!
Well, he served a purpose.
Didn't take much convincing.
Just the simple promise of his freedom.
You ruined my life! All our lives!
We stood by you after
everything that happened.
I can see how this must be
difficult for you to understand,
but trust me,
your lives now are so much better
because of what I have done for you.
You don't have to hide anymore.
We know you're not Harrison Wells.
Just tell us who you are.
A confession will get you nowhere.
You've seen who I am.
You know what I can do.
You want to kill me, go ahead.
I'm not gonna fight you.
But just tell the police what you did.
Get my dad out of prison.
I don't want to kill you, Barry.
I need you.
And...
I also did not anticipate,
as difficult as the past
15 years have been for me,
how much I would come
to love working with you.
With all of you.
And yet, that does not
change what needs to happen.
Then face me now!
Oh, we will face each other again.
I promise you. Soon.
Very, very soon.
He's in the time vault!
Barry!
It was all a set-up.
We thought we set a trap for him,
but he set a trap for us.
Oh, my God.
Iris.
We have to find Iris.
- Why?
- Wells.
He's been watching all of us.
He has surveillance
footage set up everywhere.
Our homes, my lab at the police station,
Central City Picture News.
Cisco, call me when you have a location.
I am very much enjoying this stroll.
We needed a good stroll.
Yeah.
Actually, though, would you mind
if we park here for a second?
Um...
Oh, it's my dad.
Could you call him back later?
Sure.
What's going on?
Iris, this week, when I was arrested
and it looked bad,
you never wavered.
You never lost faith in me.
Impossible.
And even though we've been
through some rough times,
I've never lost faith in us.
Iris West.
Eddie?
Eddie!
Bad timing, Detective.
Stop! Leave him alone!
Iris, no!
I know who you are.
You killed Barry's mom.
But you don't have to hurt anyone else.
Hey, Iris.
It's okay. It's me.
He took him.
The Man in Yellow, he took Eddie.
I promise I will find him, okay?
- What is happening?
- Listen to me, you go home.
Don't say anything to anyone.
I swear to you, I will
bring him back, all right?
Wait, stop.
Barry?
You might as well take that mask off.
I know it's you, Wells.
Or whoever you really are.
Well, allow to to introduce myself.
My name is Eobard.
Eobard Thawne.
I don't understand.
Why do you have my name?
Why?
Well, 'cause we're family, Eddie.
Funny, I haven't seen you
at any reunions or weddings.
That is funny.
And the reason for that
is because as far as those
guest lists are concerned,
I haven't been born yet.
So that's why you didn't kill
me that night at S.T.A.R. Labs?
This whole thing...
It's been about me?
Not a chance.
You, my friend,
are simply my insurance.
You look so young.
And I could kill you
right now so easy.
What I wouldn't have given...
All those times before
to have had you like this.
So...
helpless.
But fate,
it's tricky, isn't it?
I come here to destroy you...
And then to get home, I have to be the one
who creates you.
But I will say,
it's been an education...
Watching you grow up all these years.
Science fairs and soccer games.
No hint, no sign,
no trace of the man you will be one day
for whom I have nothing but hate.
And to be clear,
nothing is forgiven
There will be a reckoning.
I promise you, Barry Allan,
that you will die.
- Synced and Corrected by ChrisKe -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org