[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.2.2012.322
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: 
Original Script: 
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 0
PlayResY: 0
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.67,0:00:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我超想尿尿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Boy, do I have to urinate.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.99,0:00:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是有办法解决就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}If only there were a solution to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.86,0:00:13.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Seriously.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.07,0:00:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我感觉骨盆那里好像有个鱼缸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I feel like I've got a fish tank in my pelvis.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.21,0:00:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就去上厕所啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So go to the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.83,0:00:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.15,0:00:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.08,0:00:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为人家正在做决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because I'm trying to decide
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.48,0:00:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是买Xbox One呢  还是买PS4呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}between getting an Xbox One or a PS4.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.83,0:00:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"P"与尿尿同音  说出来更想尿尿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, "Pee." Why'd I say that?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.55,0:00:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原谅我要问一个白痴的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Forgive me for asking a stupid question,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.00,0:00:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你为什么在耍白痴啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but why are you being stupid?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.03,0:00:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不是耍白痴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm not being stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.49,0:00:42.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我采用的是荷兰研究员米莉亚·塔克的研究\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm employing the work of Dutch researcher, Mirjam Tuk,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.61,0:00:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她发现人们在憋尿的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}who found that people with full bladders
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.27,0:00:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能做出更好的决策\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}make better decisions.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.64,0:00:50.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当初决定搬进来之前  真不应该去尿尿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why did I pee before I decided to move in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.90,0:00:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试镜怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, how'd the audition go?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.97,0:00:54.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惊艳四座\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I killed it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.80,0:00:57.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我甚至在该哭的时刻  真掉了眼泪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I was even able to cry real tears right on the spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.08,0:00:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-太好了  -就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Oh, that's great. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.39,0:00:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等下次我超速  被警察拦下来罚款时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Next time I get pulled over for a speeding ticket,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.93,0:01:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的"水龙头"就会哗哗流\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}here come the waterworks.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.86,0:01:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的"水龙头"也要哗哗流了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Here come the waterworks!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.08,0:01:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不问为什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Aren't you gonna ask?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.07,0:01:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一天搬来这吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What is this, my first day?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.07,0:01:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天公司有件事  我能问下你们的意见吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Can I get your opinion on something that happened at work today?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.66,0:01:41.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-当然可以  -没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Of course. - Yeah, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.96,0:01:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, well, I did something
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.37,0:01:45.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能会让我看起来像一个可爱的呆瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that will either make me look like a lovable goof
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.42,0:01:50.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或一个该永生被罚下地狱的禽兽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}or a horrible monster damned to spend eternity in hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.44,0:01:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定是可爱的呆瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sure it's lovable.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.61,0:01:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得会是禽兽  说吧  发生什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm gonna go with monster. What do you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.04,0:01:57.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们办公室有位女士要退休了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, there's this lady in our office who's retiring,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.30,0:01:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同事们都把自己的祝语\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and they were passing around one of those big cards
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.74,0:02:00.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-写在一张大卡片里  -我懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- for us to sign... - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.70,0:02:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没人告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But no one told me she was in
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.14,0:02:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她周末出了严重的车祸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}a horrible car accident over the weekend
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.55,0:02:06.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时签的不是一张退休贺卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and what I was signing was not a retirement card
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.97,0:02:09.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是一张"慰问"卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but was actually a "get well" card.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.59,0:02:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我选对了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm liking my odds here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.10,0:02:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以写在卡片上的话  其实是给\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So on the card, in the hospital,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.58,0:02:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个好不容易活下来  至今仍未出院的女人看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}next to the woman who's clinging to life are the words,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.62,0:02:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"薇薇安  这都是你应得[活该]的"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Hey, Vivian. You deserve this""
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.94,0:02:26.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"至少你"走"了以后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"And at least with you gone,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.58,0:02:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有人会偷吃我冰箱里的酸奶"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}no one will steal my yogurt out of the fridge."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.54,0:02:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.36,0:02:36.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"滚地笑  笑脸"  -我听不下去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- "LOL. Smiley face." - Oh, my gosh.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.38,0:02:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"附注  希望你一路走好"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"P.S. Good luck wherever you wind up."
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.51,0:02:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一开始就该下重注赌钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why didn't I put money on this?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.24,0:02:46.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我经纪人  如果我得到那个角色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, that's my agent. If I got the part,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.65,0:02:49.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也只能屈居"今日最棒"排行榜的第二位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}it's still the second best thing I've heard all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.45,0:02:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.44,0:02:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是不是很坏呀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Am I a terrible person?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.88,0:02:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那只是误会而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No. No, it was a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.44,0:02:56.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时有想过如果她挂掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Am I a terrible person that it crossed my mind
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.19,0:02:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不会看见那张卡片了  那这样坏不坏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that she might die and never see the card?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.42,0:03:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我觉得你在挑战道德底线了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Now I think you're flirting with the line.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.80,0:03:02.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是好消息吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Good news?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.78,0:03:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我落选了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, I didn't get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.37,0:03:05.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真可惜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.60,0:03:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-很快会有新角色找你的  -好像是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- You'll get offered something soon.- I kind of did.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.23,0:03:10.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前拒演的那个垃圾恐怖片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The part in that awful horror movie I passed on
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.09,0:03:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在又回来找我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}came back around.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.48,0:03:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,显然如果我愿意  那角色还是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Apparently, it's mine if I want it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.51,0:03:14.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你会接吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you gonna take it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.62,0:03:16.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.00,0:03:18.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能哪天被车撞死就不用烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe you'll get hit by a car and die.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.30,0:03:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚地笑  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}LOL, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.41,0:03:32.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是艾米丽吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Emily, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.20,0:03:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.41,0:03:35.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你是否还记得我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I-I don't know if you remember me...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.00,0:03:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交友网站上的那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}From the dating Web site.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.74,0:03:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你因为不敢联系我  所以让你朋友代劳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Your friend e-mailed me because you were afraid to,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.15,0:03:42.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而现在却像个疯子一样跟踪我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}then you tracked me down and acted like a lunatic?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.19,0:03:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我是拉杰什·库萨帕里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yes, Rajesh Koothrappali.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.55,0:03:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Look, uh, I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.35,0:03:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想跟你道个歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I wanted to say I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.68,0:03:50.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以吗  你大概是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay? You were, like,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.78,0:03:52.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在网上遇到的最酷的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}the coolest person I ever found online,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.57,0:03:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时真的好紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I got really nervous
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.24,0:03:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是就搞砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I-I just blew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.88,0:03:59.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都已经过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Uh, don't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.16,0:04:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能让你好过点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And if it makes you feel any better,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.06,0:04:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还不是我在网上遇到的最奇怪的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you're not the weirdest guy I've met off the Internet.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.60,0:04:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我个机会试试  你还不知道我的真本事呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, give me a chance-- you don't even know me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.32,0:04:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.24,0:04:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就给你机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}here's your chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.60,0:04:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wha... Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.26,0:04:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.81,0:04:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命运给了我难得的第二次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fate has given me a rare second chance,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.42,0:04:21.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对毗湿奴[印度神]发誓  这次我绝不搞砸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I swear to Vishnu I'm not gonna blow it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.48,0:04:24.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是给你一个迷人的微笑  说两句正常的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Or normal words followed by a charming smile.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.49,0:04:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最先上市的游戏机  也就是PS1\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, first there was PlayStation-- aka PS1--
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.22,0:04:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后是PS2  PS3  现在出到PS4了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}then PS2, PS3 and now PS4.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.32,0:04:36.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很符合常理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And that makes sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.55,0:04:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就会认为在Xbox之后  会有Xbox2\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You'd think after Xbox, there'd be Xbox 2.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.32,0:04:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果不是  下一代叫Xbox360\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But no, next came Xbox 360.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.11,0:04:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而在360之后  现在出的版本叫Xbox One\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And now, after 360, comes Xbox One.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.97,0:04:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么要叫"One[一]"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why "One"?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.79,0:04:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能他们想名字的时候只花了"一"秒的时间吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Maybe that's how many seconds of thought they put into naming it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.57,0:04:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮我拿下黄油吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Can you get the butter, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.92,0:04:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  用Xbox One\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, however, with the Xbox One,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.72,0:05:00.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以通过语音指令控制\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can control my entire entertainment system
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.17,0:05:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我整个娱乐系统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}using voice commands.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.70,0:05:04.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而到目前为止  我都是用莱纳德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Up until now, I've had to use Leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.46,0:05:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就买另外一个好了  把黄油递给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then get the other one. Pass the butter.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.56,0:05:09.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买另外...等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Get... Hang on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.53,0:05:12.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你没把我这难题当一回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't feel like you're taking this dilemma seriously.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.85,0:05:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Fine, Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.51,0:05:17.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在专心听你说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You have my undivided attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.23,0:05:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  PS4的外形\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, now, the PS4 is
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.12,0:05:22.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有棱有角  霸气犀利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}more angular and sleek-looking.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.08,0:05:24.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这么帅  -是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- No way. - Yeah, well, it's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.67,0:05:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但Xbox One体型更大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But the larger size of the Xbox One
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.15,0:05:28.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮助它免除过热的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}may keep it from overheating.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.65,0:05:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁会想要自己的游戏机过热啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, you wouldn't want your gaming system to overheat.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.91,0:05:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想  当然不想啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, see? Well, you absolutely would not.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.02,0:05:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且现在Xbox One\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And furthermore, the Xbox One
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.92,0:05:36.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随机附送体感控制器呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}now comes with a Kinect included.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.96,0:05:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-随机附送吗  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Included?! - Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.90,0:05:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用额外买了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not sold separately.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.59,0:05:43.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是  PS4主机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Although...the PS4
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.91,0:05:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用的是新款GDDR5内存\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}uses cool new GDDR5 RAM,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.08,0:05:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而Xbox One还在用旧款的DDR3内存\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}while the Xbox One is still using the conventional DDR3 memory.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.35,0:05:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们为啥还用DDR3内存啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why would they still be using DDR3?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.38,0:05:53.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们脑子坏了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are they nuts?!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.63,0:05:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是啊  我也是这么想的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}See? That's what I thought.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.06,0:05:58.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们还加了嵌入式静态存储器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But then they go and throw in an eSRAM buffer.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.98,0:05:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  先停一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Whoa, whoa. Wait a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.71,0:06:01.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-"他们"是指谁  -Xbox啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Who's "they"? - Xbox.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.99,0:06:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在开玩笑啊  -我真的不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- You're kidding! - No, I am not!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.61,0:06:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这个嵌入式静态存储器应该能够\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And this eSRAM buffer should totally bridge
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.94,0:06:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弥补两家用的两种内存之间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}the 100-gigabit-per-second bandwidth gap
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.77,0:06:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每秒100G比特的带宽差距啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}between the two RAM types.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.03,0:06:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太残忍了  这让你怎么下决定啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is a nightmare. How will you ever make a decision?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.87,0:06:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我才一直举棋不定啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You see? I don't know!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.13,0:06:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底该怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What should I do?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.09,0:06:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快给老娘黄油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Please pass the butter!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.28,0:06:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我的问题  是这剧本烂爆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, it's not me, right? This script is terrible.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.74,0:06:31.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.24,0:06:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我内心对一部名叫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I had higher hopes for a movie called
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.91,0:06:37.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《杀人恶猿2  猴见猴杀》的电影  期望可"高"了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Serial Ape-ist 2: Monkey See, Monkey Kill.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.29,0:06:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,电影虽烂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, it's still possible
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.50,0:06:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你还是有机会能在里面大放异彩啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}for you to be good in a bad movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.63,0:06:44.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.86,0:06:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"有时候我觉得我已经能控制\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Sometimes I feel like I can control
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.66,0:06:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心中杀人恶猿的凶性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}the killer gorilla instinct inside of me,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.69,0:06:53.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我看到这些香蕉以后  我就...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but then I see these bananas and I...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.50,0:06:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,超级想大快朵颐  然后大开杀戒"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}just want to eat them and then kill people."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.82,0:07:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我到底该怎么做啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What am I gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.63,0:07:04.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先呢  你不该吃那些香蕉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, for starters, I wouldn't eat the bananas.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.10,0:07:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是啦  别闹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No...Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.42,0:07:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家很认真呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.36,0:07:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那这部戏的酬劳高吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Does it at least pay well?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.98,0:07:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比我在起司工厂打工的钱还少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Less than I was making at The Cheesecake Factory.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.50,0:07:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的经纪人怎么看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What does your agent think?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.73,0:07:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在考虑去起司工厂应征\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She's thinking of taking a job at The Cheesecake Factory.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.64,0:07:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧  你就直接去演吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know what, why don't you just do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.41,0:07:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能去玩个几周  赚点小钱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You'll go have fun for a few weeks, make some money--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.75,0:07:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁知道这会为你带来什么机遇呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and who knows what it might lead to?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.97,0:07:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  你看  第58页\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, look, here, page 58.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.34,0:07:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟红毛猩猩在油中摔跤  穿着比基尼哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I oil-wrestle an orangutan in a bikini.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.41,0:07:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就确定一下  是你还是它穿比基尼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Just to clarify, which one of you is wearing the bikini?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.28,0:07:36.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两人都穿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Both of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.57,0:07:40.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这电影适合合家观赏啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So it's a family film.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.80,0:07:44.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你今天的晚餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you again for dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.61,0:07:45.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.64,0:07:46.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚安\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Good night.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.67,0:07:49.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚是约会之夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Uh, it's date night.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.34,0:07:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是不是忘了什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Aren't you, uh, forgetting something?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.29,0:07:55.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.09,0:08:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有告诉你PS4的手把会发光吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did I mention the PS4 controllers light up?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.19,0:08:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.21,0:08:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们真会发光哦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.05,0:08:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝完咖啡之后  我们俩去散步了一会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And then after coffee, we went for a walk
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.24,0:08:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她跟我说她一直觉得印度人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and she told me she always thought people from India
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.52,0:08:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很神秘又有异国风情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}were exotic and mysterious.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.89,0:08:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我嘴上说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, with my mouth, I said,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.62,0:08:25.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我们跟其他人都差不多啦"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"we're just like anybody else,"
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.00,0:08:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但其实我的眼神在说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but with my eyes, I said,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.49,0:08:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"上来吧  红发妞  跳上我的魔法飞毯"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"Straight up, Red, hop on my flying carpet."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.11,0:08:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们还会约会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, you gonna see her again?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.53,0:08:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会啊  这周末我们就有安排\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, we have plans this weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.96,0:08:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而如果那晚能看到星星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And if it's a clear night,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.12,0:08:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会对她使使出浪漫天文泡妞招\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm gonna lay some romantic astronomy on her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.62,0:08:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  使给本宫看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, like what? Show me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.01,0:08:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能做对不起莱纳德的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can't do that to Leonard.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.82,0:08:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这招数一出  女人小裤裤必定落地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}This is some powerful panty-dropping stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.86,0:08:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,朕批准了  你尽管出招\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You have my blessing. Go for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.85,0:08:53.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.11,0:08:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Penny,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.54,0:09:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夜空中那两颗最明亮的星星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}two of the brightest stars in the night sky
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.33,0:09:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是牛郎星与织女星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}are Altair and Vega.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.46,0:09:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,传说中他们俩深爱着对方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And it is said they were deeply in love
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.23,0:09:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但却被永远地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but forever separated
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.03,0:09:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分隔在银河系的天河两侧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}by the celestial river of the Milky Way.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.50,0:09:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好可怜  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Oh, that's sad. - It is.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.39,0:09:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但每年都会有一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But once a year,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.97,0:09:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在每年第七个月  第七天的晚上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}on the seventh day of the seventh month,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.73,0:09:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,织女会哭得十分惨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Vega cries so hard
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.63,0:09:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这时世界上所有的喜鹊都会飞到天上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that all the magpies in the world fly up
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.19,0:09:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用它们的翅膀搭一座鹊桥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and create a bridge with their wings
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.41,0:09:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让这一对恋人能有机会相聚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}so the two lovers can be together
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.45,0:09:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然这激情团聚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}for a single night
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.84,0:09:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有仅仅一夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}of passion.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.79,0:09:36.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, that's enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.89,0:09:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快速投票  买PS4或Xbox One\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Quick poll: PS4 or Xbox One?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.10,0:09:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉杰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Raj.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.78,0:09:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-Xbox One  -佩妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Uh, Xbox One. - Penny.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.16,0:09:46.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.17,0:09:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-莱纳德  -PS4\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Leonard. - PS4.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.62,0:09:50.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-霍洛维兹  -两个都不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Wolowitz. - Both great.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.50,0:09:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-博纳黛特  -我喜欢Wii\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Bernadette. - I like the Wii.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.47,0:09:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢了  奶奶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thanks, Grandma.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.88,0:10:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的天  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Oh, my Goodness. - What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.58,0:10:04.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的前女友露西给我发了一封邮件\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I just got an e-mail from my ex-girlfriend Lucy.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.27,0:10:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说...她很想我  希望和我聚一聚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She... misses me and wants to get together.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.04,0:10:09.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哇  一男驭二女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Two women at the same time?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.10,0:10:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,厉害哦  小淫棍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Nice job, playa!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.96,0:10:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真得这么说话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.78,0:10:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是"驭二女"还是"小淫棍"的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Was it the "two women" thing or the "playa"?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.19,0:10:22.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来是小淫棍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It was the "Playa".
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.57,0:10:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What am I supposed to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.84,0:10:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该如何在艾米丽和露西之间抉择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How am I supposed to choose between Emily and Lucy?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.65,0:10:32.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何必费神去选  两个一起约嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Why do you have to choose? Date both of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.77,0:10:35.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不会同时和两个女生谈恋爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can't date two women at once.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.20,0:10:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个女人都不剩  那才是我的长项\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Zero women-- that's my sweet spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.27,0:10:40.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你没和她们上床\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Unless you're sleeping with one of them,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.38,0:10:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟其他人约会就没什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}seeing other people isn't a big deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.37,0:10:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可要是其中一人问起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But what if one of them asks me
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.54,0:10:45.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天晚上干了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}what I was up to the night before
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.31,0:10:46.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我恰好是和另一个人约会去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I was with the other one?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.79,0:10:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我该怎么办  骗她吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then, what, do I lie?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.28,0:10:50.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  -当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Yes. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.57,0:10:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说"没错"是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What do you mean, yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.95,0:10:55.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的"当然"又是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What do you mean, yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.43,0:10:57.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们约会时  你也和其他女人约会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Were you seeing other women when we started dating?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.62,0:10:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有  你有跟其他男人约会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No. Were you seeing other men?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.28,0:11:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.75,0:11:01.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有跟其他男人约会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Were you seeing other men?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.89,0:11:03.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.82,0:11:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么不问我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Aren't you gonna ask me?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.77,0:11:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  有必要问吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Come on, really?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.59,0:11:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多谢你抽空向我们指教\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you so much for letting us pick your brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.77,0:11:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  举手之劳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, happy to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.05,0:11:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.06,0:11:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的事业现在发展\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, I'm having an impossible time
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.56,0:11:25.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,极其不顺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}getting my career off the ground,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.15,0:11:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正好有个超级烂片找我去演\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I got offered a role in this crappy horror movie,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.57,0:11:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不知道该不该接受这个角色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I just don't know if I should take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.37,0:11:32.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我自己也接过一些让我觉得丢人的片子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, I have certainly taken some jobs that I've been embarrassed by.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.84,0:11:36.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《星际迷航》也算不上丢人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I wouldn't exactly call Star Trek embarrassing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.67,0:11:39.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的不是它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I wasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.54,0:11:43.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也没说它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Me, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.74,0:11:45.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你怎么看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, what do you think,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.51,0:11:48.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做这件事有什么专业上的坏处吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is there a professional downside to doing it?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.26,0:11:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很难讲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, it's tricky.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.48,0:11:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当然希望选自己喜欢的工作来做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You want to take projects that you're excited about,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.67,0:11:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有时你也不得不为五斗米折腰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but sometimes you also have to pay the bills.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.07,0:11:57.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当你在做片场演自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}When you're on the set working on something
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.61,0:11:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心里觉得超烂的片子时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that you just know in your heart is bad--
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.82,0:12:01.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是指《星际迷航》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}not Star Trek...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.65,0:12:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我传送上去[星际迷航台词]   我超爱这戏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, beam me up. I love it!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.45,0:12:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正  这些工作很可能会毁掉你的信心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Anyway, those jobs can be soul-crushing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.92,0:12:12.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是担心这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's what I'm afraid of.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.46,0:12:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我小时候出演过《与我同行》\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, I was in Stand By Me when I was a kid,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.13,0:12:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这片子当时可火爆了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and it was a huge success.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.59,0:12:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这之后我演了不少烂片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The terrible movies I did came after that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.00,0:12:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想象一下我当时的感受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I mean, imagine how that feels.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.77,0:12:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定很不堪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Sounds rough.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.22,0:12:24.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  演艺界很残酷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm telling you, this business is brutal.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.53,0:12:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到今天  我还是很讨厌去试镜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}To this day, I hate going on auditions.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.78,0:12:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一走进去  就可以感受到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, I walk in, and I can just
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.64,0:12:32.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}feel them thinking...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.18,0:12:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"这孩子以前多可爱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}"He was such a cute kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.88,0:12:36.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时光真是把杀猪刀啊"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What happened to him?"
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.18,0:12:39.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果我没能接到这个角色\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And then I don't get the job,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.72,0:12:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也永远不知道原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I can never find out why.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.62,0:12:44.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  我深受打击\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Honestly, I get so depressed,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.95,0:12:49.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有时候好几周  我连床都爬不起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}there are entire weeks that I can't even get out of bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.53,0:12:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的话对我们帮助太大了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, this was helpful.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.30,0:13:00.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那位住院的同事最近如何啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Any news on your coworker who's in the hospital?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.00,0:13:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她好可怜  动了18个小时手术\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Poor thing, she was in surgery for 18 hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.81,0:13:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然活下来了  但情况仍然危急\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}She's alive, but she's still in critical condition.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.28,0:13:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不幸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.41,0:13:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的好消息是  她还没来得及看卡片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The one bit of good news is they put her
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.48,0:13:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就被医生用药物陷入昏迷状态了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in a medically induced coma before she read the card.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.62,0:13:12.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也算是不幸中的万幸吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, you know, silver linings.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.02,0:13:19.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和我结婚时  就这个样子了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Were you like this when I married you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.32,0:13:23.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心了  兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Don't worry about it, buddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.66,0:13:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  回见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay, bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.80,0:13:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是威尔  他情绪恢复得好多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That was Wil-- he's feeling a lot better.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.42,0:13:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的名字出现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Apparently, he's 12-down
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.60,0:13:31.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《电视指南》纵横字迷的第12行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in the TV Guide crossword puzzle.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.62,0:13:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有帮你做出决定  到底要不要接那部戏吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Did he help you make a decision about the movie?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.87,0:13:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没  那你想好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No. Did you figure out
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.07,0:13:37.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要如何应对那两个女孩了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}what you're gonna do about the two girls?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.62,0:13:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老实说  我想好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}As a matter of fact, I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.38,0:13:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些年来我深陷恐惧之中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've spent so many years living in fear,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.06,0:13:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢面对新的事物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}saying no to new experiences,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.00,0:13:45.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但从现在起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but from now on,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.18,0:13:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要积极接受一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm gonna say yes--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.89,0:13:48.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接受爱  接受挑战  拥抱生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}yes to love, yes to adventure, yes to life;
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.24,0:13:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管什么事  我都会勇敢地去接受\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}whatever it may be, the answer's going to be yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.99,0:13:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙绝对孤独终老  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}He's gonna die alone, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.62,0:13:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-没错  -绝对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Yeah. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.63,0:13:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以你为荣  谢尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm proud of you, Sheldon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.30,0:14:01.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也以自己为荣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, I'm proud of me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.07,0:14:02.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了全面的研究\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've done all my research,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.43,0:14:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发起了一个非正式的民意投票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I conducted an informal poll,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.36,0:14:06.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我现在清楚明白地知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I've arrived at the rock-solid certainty
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.26,0:14:07.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做的选择是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've made the right choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.76,0:14:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在心情一定非常好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, that's got to be a good feeling.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.98,0:14:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.48,0:14:13.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-可是...  -我靠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}- Although... - Oh, crap.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.28,0:14:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当年我逼我爸不买录影带系统\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I had the same feeling when I made my dad
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.73,0:14:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而去买另一家产品时  心情也是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}buy a Betamax instead of a VHS.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.62,0:14:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还只是小孩而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You were just a little kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.16,0:14:23.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  一个选错了格式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, a little kid who picked the wrong format
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.12,0:14:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,录"麦克尼尔和莱尔报导"的孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to record The MacNeil/Lehrer Report.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.12,0:14:25.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs40\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}PBS台的新闻节目  83年便已改名
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.76,0:14:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还曾确信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I also was certain
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.39,0:14:31.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高清DVD会胜过蓝光呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}that HD DVD would win out over Blu-ray.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.22,0:14:32.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那时候多大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How old were you then?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.28,0:14:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大到应该知道哪种更好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Old enough to know better.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.14,0:14:36.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在想想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know, and now that I think about it,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.82,0:14:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾经站在一箱子iPod前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I stood in front of a case of iPods
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.98,0:14:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我却买了Zune\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I bought a Zune.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.07,0:14:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么是Zune\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What's a Zune?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.28,0:14:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是说啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.52,0:14:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一款MP3播放器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}It's an MP3 player
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.76,0:14:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,制造商正是生产Xbox的这家[微软]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}brought to us by the makers of Xbox.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.43,0:14:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What... no, what are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.13,0:14:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  快拿回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No, no, pick that back up.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.35,0:14:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这个好  你都做足研究了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know it's good. You did the research.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.55,0:14:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果我错了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But what if I'm wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.73,0:15:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.36,0:15:02.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如我买给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How about I buy it for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.96,0:15:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How about
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.04,0:15:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我两个全买给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I buy you both?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.85,0:15:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我的电视上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You know I only have one slot available
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.83,0:15:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个槽可以用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}in my entertainment center.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.32,0:15:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我就给你买个新电视\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Then I'll buy you a new entertainment center.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.33,0:15:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想得到容易\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, yeah... okay, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.02,0:15:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但买哪个牌子好呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But which one?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.36,0:15:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.67,0:15:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听说如果扔硬币\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I've heard that if you flip a coin,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.83,0:15:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以告诉你  你真正的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}it will tell you how you actually feel.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.74,0:15:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为结果要么让你失望\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because you'll either be disappointed
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.05,0:15:25.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么令你激动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}or excited by the outcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.02,0:15:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Interesting.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.27,0:15:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正面是PS4\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}So, heads it's PS4,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.45,0:15:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背面是Xbox One\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}tails it's Xbox One.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.04,0:15:33.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}All right, I'll try.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.29,0:15:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.30,0:15:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一枚硬币\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A quarter.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.17,0:15:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也可以还给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Could have given it back to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.00,0:15:46.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是一种选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That was a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.40,0:15:55.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You look...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.08,0:15:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今晚看起来真漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}you look really pretty tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.72,0:15:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.85,0:15:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的外套也不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I love that jacket.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.13,0:16:01.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thank you. Thanks, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.81,0:16:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起  我做不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm sorry. I can't do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.40,0:16:07.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的前女友给我发了电邮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My... my ex-girlfriend e-mailed me,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.52,0:16:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我周六会和她见面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and I'm seeing her Saturday...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.82,0:16:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴你觉得我外套好看  是克鲁牌的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}And I'm glad you like it-- it's from J. Crew.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.52,0:16:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.84,0:16:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的朋友们告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}My friends told me it was okay
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.75,0:16:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时和多个人约会没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}to see more than one person at a time,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.54,0:16:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我感觉我在欺骗你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but it-it feels like I'm being deceitful.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.37,0:16:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会和她复合吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you getting back together with her?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.87,0:16:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.62,0:16:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I-I... I have no idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.46,0:16:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是你会怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What would you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.34,0:16:30.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,通常第一次约会  我会谈谈音乐什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Uh, usually on first dates, I talk about music and stuff,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.72,0:16:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但既然说好了你是怪人  就谈这个吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but I was promised weird, so let's do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.05,0:16:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们之前有多认真\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How serious were you two?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.95,0:16:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Well, to be honest,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.86,0:16:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只约会过四次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}we only went on four dates,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.80,0:16:42.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拥抱过两次  吻过一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}hugged twice, kissed once,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.48,0:16:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有一个充满了性暗示的握手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and there was a handshake loaded with sexual innuendo.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.10,0:16:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Wait, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.37,0:16:52.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个你从没"睡"过的女生发了电邮给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}a girl you never slept with sent you an e-mail
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.87,0:16:55.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你内疚到你觉得必须告诉我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}and you felt so guilty about it that you had to tell me?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.70,0:16:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.21,0:16:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺可爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}That's kind of adorable.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.51,0:17:01.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Are you... are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.31,0:17:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为一般约会到了这个环节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because this is the part of the night
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.91,0:17:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我说了傻话  女生就直接走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}where I've said something stupid and the girl usually leaves.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.09,0:17:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还没走啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I'm still here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.83,0:17:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但现在你让我怀疑你到底有什么毛病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Yeah, but now you make me wonder what's wrong with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.86,0:17:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚认识\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We just met.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.28,0:17:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必告诉我  你约会的其他人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You don't need to tell me about other people you're seeing.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.11,0:17:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.60,0:17:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为"我同时和两个女生约会"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Because "I'm dating two women"
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.63,0:17:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本上是我唯一可吹嘘的潮男事迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}is basically the only cool thing I can say about myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.25,0:17:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一方面  Xbox One的摄像头更好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}On the one hand, the Xbox One has a better camera...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.83,0:17:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但PS4可随意换硬盘\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but the PS4 has a removable hard drive.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.55,0:17:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有何想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Thoughts?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.23,0:17:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的腿麻了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I can't feel my legs.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.19,0:17:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思  两位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Oh... I'm sorry, guys,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.03,0:17:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商店五分钟前就关门了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}but the store closed five minutes ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.10,0:17:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还没决定好买哪个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}But I haven't decided yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.92,0:17:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就明天再来买\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}You'll have to come back tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.91,0:17:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,收银机已经关了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}The registers are closed.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.01,0:18:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们去吃点东西吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Let's get you some food.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.52,0:18:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃了东西后你就会感觉好些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Y-You'll feel better after you eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.51,0:18:07.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.75,0:18:09.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想吃什么  泰国菜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}What-what do you want, like, Thai food?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.88,0:18:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是汉堡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}A... A burger?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.33,0:18:13.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人家不知道嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}I don't know!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.46,0:18:27.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看  一枚硬币\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Hey, look, a quarter!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.05,0:18:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉如何\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}How's that feel?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.26,0:18:38.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.00,0:18:40.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全"不后悔"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Not like regret at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.89,0:18:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,佩妮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Penny?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.79,0:18:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是同事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}We're working together!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.39,0:18:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14\c&H4bc2ef&}Awesome!

