My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously, on "The Flash"...
His name is Geomancer.
I'm waiting on the man in red.
The Velocity-7's wearing off.
- You hurt?
- Only my pride.
Jesse's my daughter.
Zoom has her.
Daddy, please help me.
Don't let him take me, Daddy.
I told you we're a team.
Now you're a part of it.
We're gonna help you save Jesse.
We're not sending you
through alone.
We're going to Earth-2.
Just remember what
Jay said, okay?
Things here are all
sorts of trippy.
Caitlin...
If you knew me at all,
you would know that
I hate the name Caitlin.
I'm Killer Frost.
Look out!
Dad!
You killed my father,
you evil bitch.
You shouldn't have
palled around with a breacher.
- Flash, save us!
- No!
Zoom wanted him alive.
You know what Zoom will do
if you don't obey him.
No!
Argh!
Look around, Flash.
This is the last place
you'll ever see.
I know you're here,
Harrison Wells,
and you did not come alone.
You can try to hide...
But I'm the fastest man alive.
I will scour this city
until I hunt you down.
And when I do,
all of you will feel my wrath.
CCPN is reporting that
Dr. Harrison Wells,
the infamous founder
of S.T.A.R. Labs
who uncharacteristically
has gone unseen
for nearly four months
is now a wanted man.
These images and messages
went up moments ago
throughout Central City by Zoom.
Have you seen channel 52?
You're not safe here, Dr. Wells.
Zoom's looking for you.
I know what he's doing.
Alert security.
Evacuate S.T.A.R. Labs.
Lock down the facility.
- What about you?
- Don't worry about me, Henry.
Just get everyone
out of here now.
Now! Go!
Harry!
Don't shoot!
Damn it, Ramon.
Where's Allen?
- Zoom took him.
- What?
We tracked down Deathstorm
and Killer Frost,
met my doppelganger, Reverb...
super evil guy,
super evil powers.
The three of them almost
took down Barry until
Zoom showed up,
killed Cisco-2,
killed Deathstorm for
hurting a speedster.
But then he left
Killer Frost alive
and then took off with Barry.
How are you still alive?
Looks like he cares
even less about me
than you do, Harry.
No, no.
Zoom doesn't do anything
by accident.
Did he follow you here?
I've seen "Heat"
like 50 times, okay?
I know how to shake a tail.
He didn't follow me.
But check this out.
I jacked these from
my dead ringer.
I think we can
tweak these puppies...
use them to find Zoom.
Damn it, Ramon,
we don't have time for this.
Zoom is hunting us...
Zoom is hunting us!
We need to make
an alternate plan,
because if we don't, Zoom...
Stop thinking like that, okay?
We're gonna find Jesse,
and we're gonna find Barry.
I know we will.
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Okay, whoever's
responsible for this,
oh, ho, ho...
boy, we're gonna have words,
the two of us, okay?
This is...
this is not okay.
Barry-2.
Dr. Wells,
this is very disappointing.
I mean, the two of you
should be ashamed of yourselves.
You can't just lock someone
in a room like this.
How long was I in here for?
Barely a day.
One day?
Oh, jeez, my wife's
gonna be worried sick.
- Dr. Wells.
- Yeah?
Doctor, I'm not sure
if you're aware of this,
but my wife is
a very well-respected detective
in the Central City
Police Department.
She's got to be very upset.
Whoa, this is heavy.
It certainly is.
And I'm sorry, fellas,
but I demand to know
what the heck
is going on here this instant.
Barry, this is
a very long story.
One that we don't have time
to tell right now.
We're sorry we locked you
in that room
for a day, but right now,
you need to leave.
You need to gather...
He's here.
Do not move.
Ugh!
Where are Wells and his friends?
Dr. Wells, hey,
what the heck is going on?
Oh, Zoom's after us.
Zoom? What do...
Why would Zoom be after you?
That's part of that long story
I was telling you about.
I don't know if I can
deal with something like this.
- You have a time vault?
- Yeah.
I'm an enemy of Zoom,
and I need a place to hide
when something like
this happens.
- Get in!
- Yes, sir.
That's Zoom!
Ramon...
Shut him up.
Okay.
Breathe, breathe, breath,
breath...
Fake wall.
He's not gonna fall
for another fake wall.
We need to move.
We need to find
a different place to hide
and make a plan.
Wait, wait...
hey, hey, hey, hey.
No.
I think before we do anything,
you have to explain
to me everything
that is going on here.
You're wasting your time.
I used to think
I could escape too
when I first got here.
There's no way out.
Who is that?
I don't know.
He's been here since Zoom
brought me to this place.
Stop, okay?
Just... just please stop.
Jesse, I think he might
be trying to help us.
Nothing is gonna help us.
That's not true.
We're gonna get out of here.
Your dad's gonna find us,
I promise.
You sure have a lot of faith
in a man who only
cares about himself.
You know, I actually
thought that
at first too.
It's not true.
Every decision that he's made...
every action he's taken
since we've met...
has been to save you.
Your dad hasn't given up
on you, Jesse.
Don't give up on him.
Believe what you want,
but the only reason
that you're still alive
is so I can kill you
in front of your father.
And the only reason
your father's still alive...
Is to get me your speed.
Once he does that,
he will die too.
Up after the break,
earthquake-causing meta-human
leaves citizens shaken
and wondering,
where is The Flash?
It's finished.
Breach stabilized again.
Barry, Cisco, and Wells
have 20 hours to get back.
You're amazing.
When it comes to
stabilizing breaches, maybe...
not so much when it comes
to fighting meta-humans.
You were a little rusty.
I was too slow.
Geomancer's still out there,
Caitlin.
He has to be stopped.
I have to be ready in case
he attacks again.
How much longer till
the Velocity...
8.
Velocity-8 is ready?
I need to finalize
the compound...
make sure the extracellular
matrix stays intact
so you don't lose
your speed as fast.
Okay, great.
What is it?
After your last encounter
with Geomancer,
I ran some tests.
The Velocity-7 is reacting
with the damaged cells
in your body.
It's causing more
cellular degeneration.
Well, I have faith
that the next batch
won't do the same thing.
Jay, I can't keep
giving this to you
if it's hurting you.
If it'll help me
defeat Geomancer,
you might have to.
Till Barry gets back,
I may be the only chance
this city has.
I don't know how
this is possible,
but you somehow made basketball
sound more boring than baseball.
Fix this.
Scott Evans, your new editor.
- Oh, Iris...
- West, I know.
You wrote the story about
the recent Geomancer attack.
- Yeah, I did.
- I'm not running that.
What, why?
It's a fluff piece to try
to make people feel good.
What they need to know
is the truth;
The Flash might not always
be there to save them.
You disagree?
I think that he's saved
a lot of people
in this city.
But where is he now?
I need to run a real story.
Okay, uh...
what if I could get you
an exclusive
with the meta-human
that fought Geomancer?
This... this other Flash.
What, you friends with him too?
Just, um, give me a little time.
Fine, but if it's the same
as the other crap
that you wrote,
I'm gonna run something
about how The Flash
may not be the hero
we all dreamed he was.
Iris...
hey, Iris.
Barry, where were you
last night?
Oh, my God.
My father died yesterday,
and you never even came home.
I know, I know.
I heard.
I'm so, so sorry.
You... you heard?
You were there, Barry.
I actually was not there.
I'm... I'm gonna...
yeah, okay.
Okay, look.
Come to my lab.
Just come up to my lab.
I'm gonna explain
everything, okay?
I'm gonna explain it.
So the Barry from yesterday
was not you?
No.
No, look, I... I know
that this is hard to believe,
but I mean, it is just like
that sci-fi series,
"Commander Carl, Space Marshal
of the Galaxy,"
where Carl gets sucked
into a black hole
and ends up on another planet
that he thinks is Earth,
but really it's Earth...
of another universe.
Have... have you guys not s...
oh, it's a seminal episode.
You should check it out.
So that's why
you weren't wearing
your wedding ring yesterday.
Well...
And... and that...
that kiss was... was so...
I'm... I'm sorry.
He got frisky with you?
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay, I'm gonna have to
find this guy
and give him a piece of my mind.
Don't give him too much.
Your husband tells us
you've been tracking Zoom.
Yeah, I've been trying to.
Why?
- We need to find his lair.
- Lair?
He's a bad guy;
I'm calling it a lair.
Zoom is looking for you.
Why are you going after him?
Zoom has my daughter
and our Barry, and we need
to rescue them both.
Look, I want to find Zoom
just as much as anybody,
but no one can track him.
The only person who would know
where he would be hiding someone
would be a meta that's
worked with him.
A meta like Killer Frost?
Yeah, maybe.
But Zoom kept her
alive yesterday
because she always obeys him.
There is no way that she's
gonna tell you where he is.
I'm not so sure about that.
If she loved Deathstorm as much
as my Caitlin loved Ronnie,
I think she'd be more than upset
at Zoom for killing him.
Look, finding her is gonna be
just as hard as finding Zoom.
But if anyone can do it...
My husband can.
Right, yes.
I can, actually.
Um, all right.
Okay, well it looks like
Patty Spivot was a CSI tech
on most of
the Killer Frost cases.
She's pretty thorough, so...
What's that?
Oh, this is Killer Frost
meta-data
collected from numerous
crime scenes...
DNA trace movements,
facial recognition,
temperature fluctuations
specific to her.
My algorithm compiles
all the data
and gives us an approximate
location.
It works on most metas,
except for Zoom, of course.
He's too fast...
never leaves a trace.
Okay.
Looks like the best bet's
the woodlands.
Best CSI in Central City.
You know where that is, right?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Wait, I'm going with you guys.
- You're gonna need some help.
- Okay.
Iris, I...
Barry, Zoom and his followers
are the reason that
my father is dead.
If I can stop him from
killing anyone else,
I'm gonna try.
Okay, then I'm coming too.
- No.
Barry, this is not what you do.
I know that.
But I also know Joseph
didn't like me too much,
but he was my father-in-law.
If you're going,
I am coming with you.
All right.
You can come, but you stay
out of our way.
That's not Morse code.
I know he's trying to
tell us something.
We just have to
find the pattern.
There's no pattern, Barry.
You know, your dad,
who I'm pretty sure
is one of the smartest people
to live on either of our Earths,
told me the only person
smarter than him
was you.
He said that?
If that's true,
we work together...
I know we can figure this out.
Worth a shot?
Okay.
Well, he never goes past five.
What?
He never goes past five knocks
without pausing.
Right? Listen.
Hey, you're right.
I think...
I think I know what that is.
It's a five-by-five tap code
used by POWs.
That would only get us
to 25 letters,
and there's 26 in the alphabet.
Not if you combine C and K.
They sound the same.
Let's try it out.
- Worth a shot.
- All right.
There it is.
Looks different than before.
That's because I realized
that there was a flaw
with Velocity-8,
so I reformulated
the extracellular matrix, and...
Velocity-9.
You know what they say:
ninth time's the charm.
Hey.
Hey, Iris.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm just a little
worried about the time.
Well, don't worry.
They'll make it back before
we close the breach.
Um, actually I was here
to talk to you about
something else.
Oh.
Yeah, sure.
What is it?
Well, my new editor
wants me to write
a scathing article
on The Flash not being able
to protect Central City
from Geomancer.
Really?
Yeah.
I was hoping to write
an article about you instead...
something that would calm people
until Barry got back.
You know, Iris,
I don't know if
that's the best idea.
Well, I think that if people
knew that there was someone
that could protect them,
it would...
it would really help.
Would you just think about it?
Some crazy alarm's going off.
Yeah.
Don't even think about running.
There's a new Flash in town.
You know, the one with
the shiny helmet.
Not the speedster
I was hoping to crack,
but let's see just
how fast he is,
Central City.
Give me the Velocity-9.
Jay, we have no idea
how long it will last.
We don't have time to
figure that out, Caitlin.
Jay?
I'm okay.
That just took a lot out of me.
But it sure felt good.
That was amazing, Jay.
Thanks. I kind of
surprised myself,
to be honest.
Caitlin deserves all the credit.
Looks like your Velocity-9's
a winner.
I still need to run some tests.
Iris, about the interview, um...
I think that I have
everything that I need.
Great.
'Cause I could really use a nap.
I'll, uh, be downstairs.
Two down, five across.
- It's J.
- J?
That's what you're tapping...
the letter J?
All right, what's next?
A.
All right.
Five down...
Four across.
Y.
J-A-Y?
You're spelling "Jay."
As in Jay Garrick?
He's... he's alive.
But he's on my Earth.
Hey, hey...
stop, stop...
hey...
stop...
look, I'm sorry.
I don't know what you mean.
Jay Garrick didn't come with us.
Look, just keep tapping, please.
We don't understand.
Please.
Don't talk to them again.
I'm gonna get out of here.
And I'm gonna destroy you.
All I need from you
is your speed, Flash.
And you only need
to be barely alive
for me to get it.
Stop!
Barry...
Barry, are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Zoom just showed me how to
get out of this thing.
You're sure this is the place?
This is definitely the place.
You lost?
Or just back for more fun?
We just came here to talk.
Oh, really?
Do you bring your little toys
to every conversation you have?
Or do you just want to
see me burn again?
Considering you killed
my father,
the thought has crossed my mind.
Tell us...
where does Zoom
keep his prisoners?
You really don't know
how to use your abilities,
do you, breacher?
It's a work in progress, Elsa.
Zoom killed the love
of your life.
This hurts,
even for somebody with
a heart as cold as yours.
And you think that would
make me turn on Zoom?
Enemy of my enemy
is my friend, right?
What... don't tell me it doesn't
work like that over here.
If I tell you,
he'll kill me.
But if I kill you
and take you to him,
I bet he'd be pretty
pleased with me.
Maybe even let me off my leash.
So take a wild guess.
What do you think
I'm gonna choose?
Move!
Argh!
That did not go as planned!
Her name starts with Killer.
This comes as a shock to you?
- We got to move now!
- Yeah, yeah.
- I will cover you.
- Okay.
No, no, no,
hey, that's a horrible idea.
Hey, no!
Hey, hey, no!
Hey, guys...
Where are we going?
Oh, God.
Argh!
Stop...
or you'll never make
another icicle again.
I can't believe it.
What is it?
I think I figured out
how to save Jay's life.
Hey, Jay...
uh, wake up.
Come to the cortex.
It's important.
It certainly is.
What do you want?
I like to watch heroes fall
and never get back up.
He always gets back up.
Hard to do that when the Earth
swallows you whole.
Where is it?
Aw, don't go.
We're having so much fun.
Oh, my God!
Caitlin!
Caitlin, are you okay?
Looks like this new Flash
isn't much of a hero after all.
Let's see what a seven
will do to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Nice shot.
I was aiming for his leg.
Where is Zoom's lair?
Where is it?
If I tell you,
he will kill me.
He'll kill you anyway, Caitlin.
Stop calling me that.
It's not my name.
Yes, it is.
You just don't want to hear it
because it reminds you
of someone you used to be.
Trust me, I know that person
very well.
You don't know anything
about me.
I know the Caitlin Snow
on my Earth.
I know that when
she loves someone,
that person is her world.
That person was Ronnie Raymond.
And he died too.
It devastated her,
and I can see it's doing
the same to you.
Zoom took that.
His daughter...
my friend...
he's gonna take them
away from us,
just like he took
Ronnie from you.
Caitlin...
all you have to do is tell us
where he's keeping them.
And then you'll never
hear from us again,
and you can go.
Please.
Fine.
I'll show you where it is.
But that's it.
Uh, where are we going?
Ascension Cliffs.
Argh!
Gah!
Look, are you sure you
want to keep doing that?
You know, if Zoom catches you,
he's gonna hurt you again.
I don't understand why
I can't phase through this.
Well, your body would need
to have the same resonance
as the glass walls.
I should be going
more than fast enough.
It's something else.
Maybe you're resonating
at a different frequency.
Yeah, your Earth vibrates at
a different frequency than mine.
Same reason Cisco can't vibe.
Is there any way to
make up the difference?
Only if I can go faster.
Wow, wow, wow.
We're going up there?
That's where Zoom's lair is.
A place only a speedster
could get to.
There are like
the Cliffs of Insanity.
So how do we get up there?
I can make you something
to climb on, darling.
Are you serious?
You want us to...
what, just climb to the top
of those cliffs...
on ice?
Got any better ideas?
No, ma'am,
I'm just, you know, I...
I've got... you know,
I'm wearing wingtips here.
They, um, don't have much tread.
Barry.
Barry, um, maybe you
should stay behind.
- Yeah?
- No... hey, no.
I'm not letting you
go up there by yourself.
It is okay if you
don't want to go...
if you don't want to do this.
You are my wife.
I'm not leaving your side.
- Okay.
- Can we go?
- Yeah.
- I'm ready.
Let's go before
I change my mind.
You really think handcuffs
can stop me?
I know they can...
just like this boot
on your neck.
It dampens your power.
Same goes for
the six-by-six cell
you'll be calling home
at Iron Heights.
All right, let's go.
Caitlin.
So sorry I didn't come sooner.
That's okay, um...
can I show you something?
My cells...
they've stopped degenerating?
How is this even possible?
It appears that when
the Velocity-9
is in your system,
it kick-starts
your latent regenerative
capabilities,
and your cells
repair themselves.
And do you think you can
get this to work permanently?
I don't know, but I think
we're on the right track.
Caitlin, I don't know
what to say.
This is... you are...
What was that?
The speed cannon.
Geomancer's tremors
must have damaged it.
Okay, come on.
Come on!
The breach isn't stabilized.
We need to fix this fast.
Otherwise they're never
gonna be able to come back.
So that was the sound
that we heard.
Please tell me it's not
as bad as it looks.
- Uh...
- Come on, seriously?
They still have an hour left.
What if they're trying to get
through the breach right now
and they can't?
Okay, the jolt disrupted
the quark matter.
The electromagnetic
insulators are failing.
How do we fix this in time?
I don't know if we can.
Barry?
Cisco?
Dude, we made it.
How did you find this place?
Had some help.
Don't even get me
started on this guy.
Out of my way.
Dr. Wells...
Stand back.
I'm here.
Come on, let's get you out
of here.
Okay.
- Frost?
- A little help?
Not part of the deal.
- Frost!
- Hey, hey, hey.
Bringing us up here wasn't
part of the deal, either,
but here you are.
Something tells me you're not
as cold as I thought you were.
Maybe, maybe not.
What's going on?
Why... why isn't it working?
I don't know.
I've never had this
problem before.
Dr. Wells...
Carbyne.
It's some form of carbyne.
This cell's made out of
some form of carbyne.
You'll never be able to
freeze him out of there.
You can't phase out of there?
Just go, all right?
Before Zoom comes back.
We're not leaving you here.
I can't get out of this cell.
I've tried
a lot.
I'm not fast enough
to phase through this.
You got...
just leave, all right?
Just leave.
Do you know what we did
to get here, Barry?
We convinced her...
Killer Frost...
to show us the way.
Then we climbed some
insanely steep cliffs
outside on footholds
made of ice...
ice.
And all of us risked our lives,
knowing Zoom was after us,
to rescue Jesse...
and you.
Now, I don't know you,
and you don't know me,
but I can tell you that today,
I... I did things that
I never thought possible,
because I needed to prove
to my wife
and to myself that I could.
Now, if I can do
the impossible today,
so can you.
I'm just Barry Allen,
but you're The Flash.
If you tell yourself
you can phase out of there,
you'll do it.
Okay, let's go.
- Go, come on.
- Wait, wait!
Hey, hey, hey!
We're not leaving him.
Barry, there's no time.
He's not going anywhere,
and neither are any of you.
Thank you
for bringing them to me.
You double-crossed us?
He killed Ronnie!
Guess my heart is as cold
as you thought after all.
I can't believe you.
Just so you know,
you would be very disappointed
in you right now.
Zoom.
Let them go.
All you need is me and Barry.
You're right.
I may not be able
to kill you yet,
but I can kill them.
No, no!
No...
I told you I'd kill you
in front of your father.
No! No!
No...
Get out of here.
Caitlin.
You were right.
He killed Ronnie.
Thank you.
I'm not leaving without him.
Barry, there's no time.
There's no time!
I can't hold him forever.
Hey, I'm coming back for you
when this is over, all right?
Go!
I'm coming back!
Jay, we need to do something.
Our only chance is to reboot
the electromagnetic insulators
and hope the quark matter
redistributes equally.
How do we do that?
We have to do it manually.
But you can't be near
the stabilizer rings
when they power on,
or you'll get
sucked into the breach.
Not if I create a vortex
to counteract the pull.
You can't do both
at the same time.
Cait...
I have to try.
I'll help you.
What?
Dad, no.
Look, if it brings Barry
back to this Earth,
I'm doing it.
You sure?
The more we talk about it,
the less sure I'll be,
so let's just do it.
Okay.
There's an override switch
on every stabilizer ring.
- I'll create the vortex.
- Yeah.
And you flip all of them.
They should all reboot.
Got it.
Once that's done,
you power up the cannon.
- The breach should stabilize.
- And what if it doesn't?
We're all out of luck.
The Velocity-9 is running out!
Jay!
I guess now we know how long
the Velocity-9 lasts.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I just hope they are.
I'm fine. I'm just a mess.
You need to get out
of Central City, all right?
Any place you think
you'll be safe from Zoom.
Yeah, we, um...
we have some family
in Atlantis that can help us.
Yeah, okay, good.
You may not have been
struck by lightning
over here like I was,
but today, you risked your life
to save somebody
you didn't even know.
That's a hero, Barry.
Thank you both.
Barry...
is my father still alive
on your Earth?
Yeah, he is.
Give him a hug for me, will you?
I will.
Hey.
You guys need to get
someplace safe too.
Where are you going?
The only place we can.
- Dad, we can't just leave.
- We have to, honey.
What, you want me to leave
everything I have here?
My friends, my family...
I mean, my life.
You don't have a life
here anymore.
Either do I.
Zoom is too powerful.
I can't stop him.
And as long as he is here,
he's gonna hunt us down
until we're dead.
Wells, if you're coming
with us, we have to go.
It's almost time.
I don't care what time it is.
After all we did to
stabilize this breach,
we're not closing
until they show up.
Y'all hear me?
Cisco!
Get ready to close
the breach for good...
Zoom's coming!
Forgetting someone, Flash?
Let him go.
Close the breach.
Tell Jesse I love her.
Tell her yourself.
Argh!
It shouldn't be
taking this long.
Close it!
Close it now!
You did it...
you made it!
Barry.
No!