ZiMuZu.tv
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop the evil speedster Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
and I saw him murder the woman I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm going to do everything in my power
to change the future,
and I'm the only one fast enough to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
You wanna open S.T.A.R. Labs to the public?
- In two weeks? - Soft open.
I'm Alchemy.
Turning innocent people
into meta-humans worshipping the Savitar?
An article used to be written by Iris West-Allen.
Something's changed with our future.
- Barry. - No!
What you saw was one possibility of the future.
Then I can stop this from happening.
I--I don't understand. Where are we?
Home. I don't know...
what's gonna happen in the future.
All I know is right here, right now,
I wanna spend every moment I can with you.
Don't!
- Don't do this! - Barry--
You lose, Barry.
No!
Babe, are you okay?
- Yeah... - Yeah.
Just a bad dream.
Go back to sleep.
Yeah, sure. I'm not completely wide awake
after hearing you scream in your sleep.
You wanna talk about it?
No, you know what I wanna do?
I'm gonna unpack.
It's been a month.
Do not change the subject, Bartholomew.
Bartholomew?
Am I in trouble?
Well, this is the third night in a row.
I know something else that's happened three nights in a row.
It's a fire.
Richmond Heights.
Go, Wally's gonna beat you there.
- What? - I just...
I just really love you.
Detective Patterson just ran inside.
He hasn't come out yet.
The fire department will not make it here on time.
Help!
I'm trapped in here!
We gotta get him out of here.
This place is up in flames any second.
- You see the soot around this door? - Yeah.
'Cause the fire has no ventilation,
so if we open the door now,
the sudden inrush of oxygen will cause an explosion.
Help!
Okay, so what do we do?
Create an exit point for the heat and smoke,
and remove all the oxygen at the same time.
- Which will put out the fire. - Help me!
When I say so, open the door, all right?
Now.
Flash, thanks.
Two of 'em.
Oh, man, that was so dope. How do you stay so calm?
You're like scary calm in the middle of a fight.
It's just experience, Wally.
That's why it's important for you to shadow me for a while,
and try to learn everything I know.
And then I get to kick some ass.
Let me give you some advice, Wally.
Being a superhero's not about kicking ass.
Well... nope, actually that's a straight-up lie.
There's a lot of ass-kicking involved.
Just keep doing what you're doing--
Watching me. You're doing great.
I gotta go to breakfast with Dad,
but I'll catch up with you guys later.
Yo, that's where--  mm-- Nope.
- You okay? - My suit goes there.
Ah, two suits, one mannequin.
That is what we call a conundrum.
No, I--
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, these things have just been on the fritz lately.
It makes me feel like a criminal.
Hasn't been on the fritz, okay?
Uh, maybe if you charge the battery, like I told you to.
Oh, I'm just supposed to hook myself up to an outlet,
like I'm some sort of human tablet?
Either you charge the cuffs,
or you go all Frozone on us again.
Or... you could fix them for me?
Or I could fix 'em.
- Sumptuous day, brethren. - Oh, boy.
- Good morning, H.R. - Oh, not just good.
It's g-r-r-eat, and why is that?
Because I'm finally ready to announce
that the new S.T.A.R. Labs museum is ready for its opening--
soft opening-- so come.
Let's take the tour.
This could've been avoided. You know that, right?
I just don't see why you're defending the yellow guy.
Yes, he goes everywhere The Flash goes,
but this morning, for example, he's just standing back,
waiting for the warehouse to burn down.
Well, maybe he's training with The Flash.
- You know, learning the ropes? - Okay, well, we send
rookie cops out on patrol, expect them to perform.
Look, I think the yellow guy's gonna surprise you.
Once he gains a little bit of experience,
he's gonna give The Flash a run for his money.
You know what I think? I think maybe he's just not that fast.
- Or maybe he's just a coward. - You don't get paid to think.
- And Kid Flash ain't no coward. - Kid Flash? Okay.
There it is. The name says it all.
Hey, I say we just send him to Keystone.
We already have a Flash.
Wally.
- Did you hear any of that? - Any of what?
Nothing, it was just a cop being stupid.
- Take you to breakfast? - Please.
Behold.
- You did all this? - Yeah.
Well, I don't wanna take all the credit.
I'm too modest to do that, but yeah.
Uh, who exactly is paying for all this?
That's a great question.
Olga!
Allow me to introduce you to your new coworkers.
Everybody, this is Olga.
- Da. - Hi.
Oh, and she doesn't really speak English so much,
but she's great. So right over here,
we have the ticketing and the admissions.
Over there, our specialty coffees--
Oh, uh, that reminds me. Caitlin...
Initially, I had you targeted for ticketing,
but it occurs to me, with a few lessons in foam art,
you could very well man up-- excuse me-- woman up
our cappuccino stand. What do you think?
H.R., I think Caitlin's gonna have plenty to do as it is.
Can I ask you a question?
Do you want to eat pizza pockets for every meal
for the rest of your life? You don't; nobody wants that.
What you want is an income,
and we collectively need a cover for S.T.A.R. Labs
for our continued operation.
He makes some good points.
Now for the pi¨¨ce de r¨¦sistance...
Welcome to S.T.A.R. Labs.
I'm sorry, did you make a hologram of me?
Oh, Francisco, you made it perfectly clear
you didn't want to be a tour guide.
You're not. You're a virtual tour guide.
Guess what. That falls under the umbrella
of not wanting to be a tour guide.
- On we go. - My name is Francisco Ramon.
I wasn't always the esteemed engineer you see before you.
It was my love of science
that allowed me to overcome my tough upbringing
and join S.T.A.R. Labs, before our beautiful
and handsome founder, Harrison Wells, stepped down.
I hope my love of science will inspire some among you
to join the scientific community.
Thanks.
Here's the thing.
I don't sound anything like that.
My love of science-- my love of science...
My...love...of...science.
Yeah, I'm gonna need you to take a look at that.
I can't do it...
'Cause I have important things to do, so--
- Oh, wha--oh, hey! Ugh! - Right now, so...
Guys, I gotta run an errand. See ya later.
Where you going?
- Ah, hello you. - Hey.
Am I in for another kidnapping?
Okay, I deserve that.
No, um, I just came to check on you.
We haven't seen much of you since Christmas.
That's very sweet of you. I'm doing well, thank you.
You know, what Savitar did-- forcing you to hurt people--
Savitar was controlling me, okay?
As far as I'm concerned, my conscience is clear.
Really?
Then why the Zolpidem? Are you having trouble sleeping?
Why don't we stop playing games, Dr. Snow,
and you tell me what you actually came for
rather than accusing me of having insomnia?
I actually need your help.
How can I help you?
Well, you're the world's foremost specialist on meta-humans...
Yes, this much is true.
And I need you to help me get rid of my powers.
I've tried everything.
I've run every test-- blood, DNA--
and I can't reverse this.
I need to get rid of my powers before...
Before what?
Before I hurt someone else... the way I hurt you.
I don't cure meta-humans.
I put them in prison.
You're on your own, I'm afraid.
No, no, no, no.
Please.
Okay.
Can I open my eyes yet please?
Um, yeah, but just one second.
- Okay. - Just, um...
yeah--okay, open 'em.
I know you wanted to unpack slowly,
like a normal couple, but I don't know--
between our jobs and the S.T.A.R. Labs museum and--
do you hate it?
Uh, n-no, no, I don't hate it.
You do. I just--I don't--
I just wanna give you the home that you deserve.
- I... - Barry, you have.
I love our loft.
Look... what I don't love
is you not talking to me about these nightmares.
I don't know. I mean, I've seen
a lot of terrible things in my life.
The nightmares, they're just a part of me.
Yeah, but, Barry, I have been with you
through all those terrible things.
This is different.
It feels different.
What are you not telling me?
I'm sorry.
Oh, that's a robbery in progress.
That is a robbery in progress.
I'm sorry.
Go.
See, I'm living with someone now,
so I can't have criminals constantly interrupting
our alone time.
Flash.
Morillo was found guilty
of grand theft and aggravated assault
after he was caught by The Flash.
That gun.
I've never seen anything like that in my life.
- I want a gun like that. - What happened out there?
Your telemetry readings dropped precipitously.
I don't know, but...
It caught me off-guard.
I've gotta run an errand. I'll be right back.
Okay, so we're up against a guy with a futuristic rifle
that steals jewelry and looks like a pirate.
A pirate. Right, then...
we shall call this scurvy lad boy
the name of Plunder. Plunder, agreed?
Jared Morillo, aka Plunder...
Okay, aren't you supposed to be working on, like,
- your museum, or something? - Aren't you supposed to be
helping me, Francisco, with me hologram?
Um, that's not my problem.
Yeah, I just wanna show you something.
Why do I feel like I'm walking into a trap?
Anyway, I'm gonna get CCPD to monitor
all the jewelry stores in the city.
This guys must be pretty full of himself,
knowing he escaped The Flash, so ten to one, he'll be back.
- All right. - When he is,
we'll be ready for him, though, right, Barry?
No, not we, Wally.
This--you're still training.
Have you seen my times in the Speed Lab lately?
- I¡¯m almost as fast as you. - Okay, this isn't about speed.
This is about gaining knowledge and experience,
so please just trust me, all right?
Look, I am as overprotective a father as you can get,
but I gotta be honest, Barry,
I'm--I agree with Wally.
I don't know, Joe. Let's just see what else
we can find on this guy before we let Wally loose.
Okay, well, remember, the best way
to teach somebody something is to throw them in the deep end.
That's how I taught you how to swim.
That was-- I'm still mad about that.
You can swim now, can't you?
Yeah.
Got your text.
Hi. Come and take a seat.
Look, I--I know I was... rude yesterday.
Yeah, you were a world-class jerk.
Yeah, there is a reason.
Because you are a world-class jerk?
Fair enough.
Listen, I've been trying really hard not to think
about my alter ego, about what he did,
and seeing you, it just...
it brought it all back.
Look,
what Alchemy did was not your fault.
Tell that to Dave Frieman, Ben Edwards, Jorge Gonzales.
These men were part of the CCPD task force
that Savitar murdered.
I should've died, not them.
Julian, what you're feeling, it's completely normal.
It's called survivor's guilt.
But it wasn't your fault, okay?
You're a victim too.
I--I tortured people
and nearly killed my best friends.
I didn't ask for these powers,
just like you didn't ask to be used by Savitar.
Yeah.
I just don't know how to move forward.
Why don't you come join us at S.T.A.R. Labs?
You can help Team Flash fight meta-humans.
- You're being serious? - Yeah.
Barry and the team, they'd be thrilled to have you.
I would be thrilled to have you.
I'll give it some thought.
Thanks for coming.
Tell me why I'm in here fixing your hologram.
Well, I'm just so persuasive. As a matter of fact,
my partner on my Earth, Randolf, used to say,
"Why, H.R., you could convince a cowboy
to buy dirt in a sandstorm." Cappuccino?
Didn't you just have one of those?
Oh, yeah.
Look, I gotta order more parts for this thing.
Yeah, no, go ahead. Price is no object.
How's it going?
You know, S.T.A.R. Labs museum,
gift that keeps on giving, so...
- Okay. - Barry, cappuccino.
- Hi, uh, no--uh, good. - Okay--all right.
- Sorry. - You know I'll double down.
- Yeah, no-- - Sure.
Um, I just actually wanted to ask you something...
about your scientific, uh,
- romance novels? - Oh, my novels, yeah, sure.
- Please, ha--have a seat, yeah. - Okay.
Ask any--anything you want. Any questions.
- Yep--all right, cool. - Yeah.
I was just wondering  if you've ever written about time travel.
But more specifically traveling to the future.
Oh, no, my best seller-- oh, hey,
"The Future Ain't What It Used to Be"--
that was--
it was all about-- it was all about this guy
who's actively trying to prevent his own murder.
Won the Nebula Award. It's well-received.
Yeah.
Um, so this character-- your character--
uh, was he able to change his future?
More specifically, if he allowed certain events to occur naturally,
was he only cementing the very timeline
that resulted in a horrible event later?
There were two schools of thought.
One faction--one group of fans--they believed,
you know, the future's ever-changing.
You know, it's not fixed, and so
you could make of the future anything you wish.
- Right. - Another group of fans
vehemently disagreed with it. They said, "No, no, no.
The future is fixed, and you can't change it
no matter how hard you try."
Where do you come down?
On a fixed or ever-changing future?
Well, I think that a man often meets his destiny
on the very road he takes to avoid it.
- Meaning? - Meaning...
- the future is fixed. - Yeah.
Yo, there's a robbery at the Payson Hotel.
- Go. - Yeah.
Bring that chopper back.
You just couldn't resist another heist, huh?
Oh, what's the fun in one and done?
Avoiding a 15-year jail sentence
in Iron Heights would've been nice,
but you're forcing my hand.
I guess it's a little late for that now.
Eh, guess again.
Barry, behind you!
I can't shake these things, Cisco.
- Shake faster. - Huh?
He means phase.
Barry, what are you waiting for?
After he was caught by The Flash...
Watch out!
No, Wally.
I caught that whole thing, man.
Anything you wanna say to camera?
Oh, for real?
Uh, what up, Central City? The name's Kid Flash.
Wally, congratulations. That was amazing.
Great job, Wally.
Kid Flash! Let 'em know.
That's how it's done.
We just deposited Plunder in Iron Heights.
- Yes, you did. - His real name is Jared Morillo.
Turns out he's wanted
for a string of robberies from here to Star City.
Wally, what was that?
I mean, you're supposed to be shadowing me.
Wait, you're mad at me? I thought--
Observe and learn. That's it.
That's it!
Barry, ease up. Wally just saved your life.
I'm sorry, Wally, but if you can't learn to follow orders,
this deal between us, it's over.
Okay. Who's ready for--
oh, man. Wallace, B.A.,
you're supposed to be dressed for the museum opening.
H.R., we're speedsters. We have time.
- Nobody likes a braggart. - Yeah, but we were actually
talking about something important before you showed up,
- so... - You--
- Okay, you clean up well... - Thank you.
I like the way you dress.
Guys, this is a very, very big deal for all of us.
Come on! Don't be late to the part-ay!
Wally.
Look, I'm gonna go over to CCPD
and fill out this Morillo paperwork.
Whatever the reasoning you have, for ragging on Wally,
- please get over it. - Mm.
Caitlin
where is everybody? Nobody's here.
No one showed up.
A custom--our first customers!
Welcome. Welcome to the grand
S.T.A.R. Labs museum opening,
and today, for your ticket price of admission--
today only--you also get a free steaming cup of joe.
- Ticket price? - Yep.
I thought this museum was free.
did you find us through social media? 'Cause--
Welcome--welcome...
- Olga! - Da.
- The thing-- it's doing the thing.
Folks, no--wait, do--oh!
Wait--no, wait, half-price! Half! Quarter--
I'll make a new pot of coffee.
- Don't bother. - No one's coming.
This isn't working. I don't know why.
You see this?
Do you see what you've done, H.R.?
You have distracted us for months, so what?
So that you could feel useful? You're not useful.
This museum isn't useful.
You know what?
- That's mean. - Yeah, well, I guess
I learned that from your doppelganger,
and at least he contributed something.
guys, there's another customer.
Hey, welcome to S-- ah, it's Julius, you guys.
What are you doing here?
Well, uh, I've given it some thought,
and I'd like to accept your invitation.
Invitation for what?
Did you ask Julian to join
Team S.T.A.R. Labs?
I know, he's an acquired taste, but--
Yeah, well, he is Dr. Alchemy,
the big bad's little bad, so...
Yeah, he--he gave Wally his powers.
- That, I don't mind. - Guys, I need his help.
I'm sorry, Cisco, but these cuffs, they aren't cutting it.
Every night, when I go to bed,
I'm afraid that I'm gonna wake up...
be her.
Maybe Julian can think of something that we haven't.
Barry...
when your mom was murdered,
Joe and Iris, they took you in.
Cisco, when Dante died,
I slept on your couch to keep you company.
The things we see, the things that we face...
no one can do this alone.
Trying is the biggest mistake that you can make.
He hasn't told anyone that Barry's The Flash.
I think we can give him a chance.
Tell Julian we'll think about it, all right?
Iris...
I need to show you something.
- I forgot this place existed. - Yeah.
The original Wells used to call it his time vault.
I've been coming down here a lot lately.
I guess I've
become as obsessed with the future as he once was.
After Flashpoint happened, this article reappeared.
"Flash Missing...
Vanishes In Crisis." Julie Greer,
April 25, 2024.
The byline used to read "Iris West-Allen.
The future's changed.
So maybe I quit my job.
Yeah, that's what I'd hoped at first too,
or something,
but I...
Look, Iris, I'm sorry I didn't tell you this sooner.
When I threw the Philosopher's Stone into the Speed Force,
I accidentally ran to the future.
I saw Savitar murder you.
And I saw myself, and I--
I wasn't fast enough to save you.
Barry, no--I mean, we--
We destroyed the Stone. Savitar's gone, so...
Maybe not. I--
I don't know. I don't know. Maybe not.
Is that why you keep having nightmares?
You keep seeing me?
So what does this have to do with Plunder?
He was already in jail in the future,
so I don't know. I thought if I didn't catch him,
that I could stop the timeline from cementing.
I could prevent your death. I don't know.
Barry, you cannot stop protecting the city to save me.
Why? Um, why not?
I'm sorry. Uh, one robber goes free.
It's that versus your life.
Joe would want me to make the exact same choice, Iris.
He--
Iris.
- How long? - How long what?
How long until it happens?
This is not gonna happen.
Hey, look at me. This is not gonna happen.
Jay said that your death is just one possible future, okay?
So that gives us four months to figure out
how to stop Savitar.
I swear, on both my parents' lives,
I will protect you.
We can't do this alone, Barry.
Hey, guys, um...
Iris and I, um...
we have something we need to tell you.
So you're saying that four months from now,
- Savitar will... - Kill me.
Possi--possibly.
It's okay. Guys, I am okay. Really.
- How are you gonna tell Dad? - I'm not.
Iris, he needs to know.
I agree with Wallace. Joe needs to know.
No, guys, this news would blind him, okay?
We all saw how crazy he went when Wally was in danger.
Imagine if he knew that Savitar was trying to kill me.
He would go after Savitar himself.
Wally...
The future isn't set. There's still hope.
But, Barry, the future,
it's harder to change than you can imagine.
The future wants to happen. The way it was explained to me
was, imagine if you had a row of dominos, okay?
Now, those dominos are all set up, and it--it's--
Here.
So convenient--yeah-- uh, Barry, if you wou--
So imagine, okay,
domino--each domino is a moment in time.
One moment in time leads to the next,
so as one domino falls, it hits the next,
it hits the next, and the next, and the next, and so on,
leading to the inevitable conclusion, and that is...
The future.
And what happens if we alter certain events?
Well, you-- you could conceivably
change where you end up, but--
but, Barry, if you would--
So you could change the future,
but you'd have to be very careful
about which events...
you alter.
We need to figure out everything that happens
leading up to Iris's death.
Wait, when I saw the future, there was a news scroll on TV.
I mean, that could offer us some clues.
Absolutely. I think I can help with that.
Hang on, McFly.
About to vibe you back to the future.
- Can you pass me the multi-meter please? - Yeah.
- The multi-meter. - Yep.
- The multi-meter? - Yeah.
I'm better with the tools of the scribe.
There it is.
You sure your buddy Randolf back home didn't just
solve that cryptogram to get rid of you?
perhaps he did.
Look, I came to this Earth seeking redemption,but
I realize now, you're right.
Greatness isn't in the cards for me.
Okay.
So you failed. So nobody came to your opening.
Don't end it like this.
Greatness takes time...
and you know this.
If a string is in a knot, patience will untie it.
Patience can do lots of things.
Have you ever tried it?
All right.
All right, guys. You ready?
- Yeah. - Yeah, we're ready.
The machine's souped up and ready to go.
It's gonna be a hell of a vibe.
All you have to do is just sit back, relax--
or, well, try to relax--
and concentrate, really focus
on the exact date in the future that you traveled to.
Yep.
May 23, 2017.
Barry, whatever happens,
I am right here waiting for you, okay?
I know.
- Crank it. - Three, two, one.
What do you see?
An empty street.
A bus stop.
The me from Christmas just came out of the Speed Force.
In other legal news, the highly publicized trial...
He's watching the news report.
AKA Plunder, comes to a close.
Morillo was found guilty
of grand theft and aggravated assault...
These are the headlines, right?
Headlines. Yeah--you know what?
Call--call 'em out. I'll write 'em down.
"Music Meister gets six-figure book deal."
"Luigi's opens after murder."
"Joe West honored at City Hall."
Good for you, Joe.
"Killer"...
What does it say?
"Killer Frost still at large."
"S.T.A.R. Labs museum closes."
"City still recovering following gorilla attack."
Don't!
Savitar has Iris.
Don't do this.
Now finally, I am free of you.
Look, up on the roof.
Barry... I love you.
Hey, no, don't say that, all right?
- H.R. is here. - Me? Are you sure?
- Yeah, you weren't here before. - Future's changed since then.
You lose, Barry.
No!
Just get us out of here.
You had a rifle pointed at Savitar.
Somehow telling you about Iris's death,
it changed the future.
I was wrong, you were right. Your theory is correct then.
Guys, my future isn't the only one that we need to change.
No, the--these headlines, though,
they--they tell us what happens in the future--
where Caitlin becomes Killer Frost and Iris dies.
If we can change the headlines,
that means we can change the future.
That's right. Challenge accepted.
Dad's upstairs. We've been looking for you.
What happened?
Plunder escaped.
Morillo assaulted two guards on his way out of Iron Heights.
Any idea where he might strike next?
Well, we've got it narrowed down to 35 jewelry stores
and 48 hotels in Central City, so...
What about banks? Auction houses?
He was caught by The Flash,
robbing the Central City Museum earlier this year.
Central City Museum.
- That's where he is. - Where'd you get that?
- Isn't there a jewelry exhibit there right now? - Yeah.
Uh-huh, with diamonds-- big ones, so it makes sense.
Let's suit up.
I don't understand.
Come here.
I was a dick yesterday, Wally. It wasn't about you.
I was scared when you caught Plunder.
I didn't know what it meant for Iris's future.
You're ready,
far more ready than I was when I started.
What do you say?
- I'm in. - All right.
Plunder, my man. Where do you think you're going?
Right through you.
- You all right? - I'm good, dude.
You can have this one.
No, Wally. This one has to be you.
Why?
Because if you take down Plunder,
the news report that says that I captured him
in the future, it's wrong.
We can prove that we can alter the future
here and now.
So that's why you sent me out here.
Hey, I sent you out here because you're a hero.
Iris needs a hero right now, Wally.
They are running.
Wally, take your next left. The streets meet up
in about two miles. If you time it just right,
- you'll be able to blindside him. - Got it.
Kid Flash! Kid Flash!
Do you hear that? They're saying your name.
Today's top story,
Jared Morillo, aka Plunder, is back in police custody
after attempting to rob the Central City Museum.
Morillo was apprehended by a new speedster,
who goes by the name Kid Flash.
Well, that settles it.
I think you're officially Kid Flash now.
Yeah, it's growing on me.
And this rifle is growing on me.
Heat-seeking bullets are just the beginning
of what this bad boy can do.
How did you end up with Plunder's rifle?
Barry stole it for me. Right, Barr?
Oh, so you plundered Plunder?
I had to do something while Wally was cuffing him.
Thanks to you, we changed the future.
If we can change one of these events,
we can change 'em all.
Nothing is set in stone.
We'll see you guys tonight.
- Can't wait. - Yeah.
I called the local elementary school,
and gave the principal discounted tickets.
I figured, hey, you know, if the kids love it,
they'll tell their parents, and, well,
the rest writes itself.
You, Francisco... are brilliant.
Of course, science
is what will inspire these children--
not just The Flash.
Check it out.
Welcome to S.T.A.R. Labs.
My name is Francisco Ramon.
I wasn't always the esteemed engineer you see before you,
but after years of hard work and studying,
I joined S.T.A.R. Labs.
- I hope my love of science... - Should we go talk to him?
Will inspire some among you
to join the scientific community
as we strive to reach a new age for humanity.
Thank you.
You're very welcome.
Okay, the quiche is in the oven;
the beer and wine are in the fridge;
and the candles are on the table.
- Oh, my God. Oh, my God. - What?
I forgot the ice.
Instant party save.
Baby, you've never been sexier.
I know.
Hey, Iris.
How are you doing? For real, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine. - Because if you're not fine,
you can talk to me. You know that, right?
I know.
All right.
- You ready? - Yeah. - All right.
I got you guys a plant.
That's like a standard housewarming gift, right?
- Yes, perfect. - Not on my Earth.
On my Earth, we get reptiles.
I present to you McSnurtle...
the turtle. Careful, she bites.
- I--this is for me? - It's for the housewarming.
You two did really well. This place is "Noice."
Thank you. Mm, hi, Daddy.
Oh, my God, it's perfect.
Yeah, right?
What are we gonna call you?
Look, I--I got a pet. Who are you trying--
- Hello, hello. - Oh, hey.
Hi. I hope I'm not too late.
Right on time.
Good, good. This is a--it's for you.
Thank you.
So we all talked it over, and
welcome to the team.
You being serious?
- Yeah. - Thank you.
Yeah, it's so exciting. I mean, my last team,
they were all murdered by Savitar, so...
We need to work on your small talk skills.
Yeah, sure. Just wanted to be upfront.
- Come on in. - That's nice of you.
- You want a drink? - Uh, yeah, I'd love one.
Is this for me?
- Oh, yeah. - All right.
This place is incredible, Barr.
Thank you.
I have to admit, I miss you around the house.
- Yeah? - But Wally over there
keeps me plenty occupied.
Yeah, um, I already talked to Wally,
but I'm sorry about yesterday. You were right.
He's really important to this team.
He's a real hero, Joe.
Both of my sons are heroes.
Julian and I were talking about your battery problem
with your cuffs.
we decided we'd invest in an alternate accessory.
Voil¨¤.
Every time you go outside, solar energy will recharge it.
Guys,
this means so much to me. Thank you.
Of course.
Thank you.
Hey, guys.
I asked myself to say a few words, um, on this occasion.
A home, you know, it's more than bricks and mortar
and a turtle. It's a--it's a feeling.
It's a feeling of belonging, isn't it?
Of--of love, of course--
hope for the future.
I don't know
if I have ever met two people
who are more suited to one another than you two.
- To Barry and Iris. - Barry and Iris.
To Barry and Iris.
- To us. - To us.