My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I am
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day,
I'll find who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
That day is today.
What?
No Big Belly Burger?
It's one of the few perks
of living in this time.
We're out of cows
where I come from.
You don't care about that.
You have questions. Go ahead.
Not sure where to start...
Thawne.
That is your real name...
Eobard Thawne.
- Since the day I was born.
- And when was that?
136 years from now.
That's not what
you want to know.
Go ahead, Barry.
Ask it.
Why did you kill
my mother?
Because I hate you.
Not you now.
You years from now.
- In the future.
- In a future. Yes.
We're enemies, rivals,
opposites,
reverses of one another.
Why?
Wh-why were we enemies?
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't...
matter anymore.
What matters is that
neither of us was strong enough
to defeat the other.
Until I learned your secret.
I learned your name.
Barry Allen.
And finally, I knew how
to defeat you once and for all.
Travel back in time,
kill you as a child.
Wipe you
from the face of the earth.
But then you, future you,
that is, followed me back,
and we fought.
We both landed
some pretty solid shots.
And then you, future you, got
your younger self out of there.
I was so mad.
But then I thought...
what if you were
to suffer a tragedy?
What if you were to suffer
something so horrible,
so traumatic that your child
self could never recover?
Then you would not become
The Flash.
And so I stabbed your mother
in the heart,
and I was free.
Finally able to return
to a future without The Flash,
only to realize
that in traveling back
I'd lost my way home.
Lost my ability to harness
the speed force.
And without it,
I was stuck here.
Stranded in this time,
unable to return to my own.
And the only way back
was The Flash.
But The Flash was gone,
and so I created him.
Why train me?
Why help me save
so many people?
Because I needed you
to get fast.
Fast enough to rupture
the space-time barrier
and create
a stable wormhole
through which
I could return home.
Why would I
ever do that?
Because...
Barry Allen,
if you give me what I want,
I'm gonna give you
what you want.
You can go back
and save your mother.
You can prevent your father
from going to prison.
You can reunite
the Allen family.
No.
No, I don't
believe you.
I want to kill you
right now.
I know that rage.
I used to feel that rage
every time I looked upon you.
And now, somehow,
I know
what Joe and Henry feel
when they look on you
with pride.
With love.
No. No.
Don't you
ever say that to me!
I know you're upset,
but I'm giving you
a chance.
I'm giving you a chance to undo
all the evil I've done.
Don't you want that chance?
The rare opportunity to go
back in time and right a wrong
and save your mother's life...
Quite the paradox Harrison has
presented you with, Mr. Allen.
The chance to be
with someone you love?
Seems pretty cut and dry
to me.
At first blush, Dr. Snow,
it would appear so,
but this gift
has unparalleled risk.
Barry, the night
your mother died,
the night you saved yourself
from being killed,
that event altered the timeline
you were already on
and changed
the course of history.
So what you're saying is we're
living in a parallel universe?
Just like when
I time travelled before.
But he... he only changed
one day that time.
Exactly. Now imagine 15 years
of compounded experiences.
One different decision,
no matter how big or small,
impacts everything that follows.
Moments upon moments,
choices upon choices.
No relationships,
nothing would be as it is today,
and you'd never know
the difference
because you'd never
remember any of it.
So if I go back
and save my mom,
my dad doesn't go to prison.
I never live
with Joe and Iris.
You might never meet me.
Or Caitlin or Ronnie.
Truth is,
there's no real way
of knowing what
your life will be.
There's no choice here, Barry.
You have to do this.
You gotta change the past.
Joe?
So what...
What, that's it?
You think I should
just do it?
Yeah, I do.
Which means I will never
come to live with you, and...
you're okay with that?
Barry, you get the chance
to grow up with both parents.
You don't have to grow up
without a mother.
What about growing up
without a father?
You will have a father...
Your real father.
Wells has messed with our lives
long enough.
This is why you became
The Flash, Barry.
To put things right.
You saved a lot of
people's lives this past year.
Now it's time
to save yours.
Dad, look.
I know this sounds crazy.
I think
we're way past crazy, slugger.
Look, you're fast, I get it.
But turning back time...
No, I wouldn't be
turning time back.
I would be...
going back
to that night
to save her.
And what does Joe think
about all this?
He thinks
I should do it.
No.
You can't.
Dad...
I can make it so that night
will never have happened.
We'll be a family again.
We are a family.
Not like this.
Not without Mom.
Barry, there's a natural order
to things, okay?
Things happen the way they do.
We may not know why
at the time,
but there must always be
a reason.
Now, I believe that.
I've had to believe it.
I... I can save Mom.
At what cost?
You said time would change.
What if it changes you?
- I don't care.
- I do.
I am in awe
of the remarkable man
that you are becoming...
All the things you've achieved,
and not just as The Flash,
but you, Barry.
Your honesty.
Your heart.
You were always a hero.
And your mom would be
just as proud.
And if she had a say in this,
if she thought for one second
that you going back to save her
would mean you losing
what makes you so special,
she would never want that.
Barry, what I hope for you,
maybe the greatest thing that
a father can hope for his son
is that one day, you will become
a father yourself.
And then you will know...
How much I truly love you.
98.6. Normal.
I don't even know
what that word means anymore.
Me neither.
I know Barry
really appreciates you
coming back to help him
stop Wells.
That's not the only reason
I'm back, Cait.
I'm here now.
For good.
But I thought...
I thought too...
I thought too much
about what might happen if
the government tracked us down.
If we couldn't control
our powers and we hurt someone.
If we hurt you.
But I realized that although
sometimes I'm more than one man,
I'm not whole
unless I'm with you.
I love you, Cait.
- Are you sure?
- I am.
Once upon a time and a
Particle Accelerator or so ago,
you agreed to marry me.
Yes, I did.
What do you say
we do that?
Thought I might find you here.
I needed to get
out of the lab.
I thought this would be
a good place to think.
Oh, it is.
Trust me.
I've done a lot
of thinking up here.
When I wasn't having
clandestine meetings
with the mysterious
"streak."
Yeah, not mad
we lost that name.
Hey, I thought that
had pizzazz.
- No.
- Uh-uh.
So are you gonna do it?
It's just so... huge.
It's the biggest decision
of my life,
and if I'm wrong,
I can't undo it.
Why would you
want to?
I mean, you'd get to see
your mom again, your dad,
have a great career,
even get married.
Iris West-Allen, huh?
I never really thought of myself
as a hyphenator.
Must be a 2024 thing.
We don't know that
that's going to happen.
Do you think that because you
didn't live with us,
that's why things
are different there?
Growing up together and...
knowing so much
about each other...
it made it hard for me to admit
how I felt about you.
And I waited too long, and you
fell in love with Eddie.
But living with you
and Joe...
I've had a great life,
Iris.
Come here,
Barry.
What do you think
I should do?
I need someone to tell me.
I think...
that for once in your life,
Barry Allen,
you should stop thinking
about other people.
I think you should do
what's in your heart.
Do what you need to do
for yourself.
Ah!
Well, if it makes you
feel any better,
it took you a whole hour
longer to decide
than I thought it would.
So how does this work?
Your grand plan?
Well, it's really not
that grand at all, Barry.
In fact, it's rather simple.
We use
the Particle Accelerator.
The Particle Accelerator.
The last time that happened,
you caused an explosion
that hurt a lot of people.
This time, the accelerator
will operate exactly
the way it was designed to.
Except, instead of two particles
moving in opposite directions,
colliding at the speed of light
in the inner ring,
we're only going
to inject one particle
into the accelerator.
And I'm what
it collides with.
And if you can go fast enough,
Barry,
if you can hit that particle
with enough speed,
you will punch a hole right
though the fabric of reality.
And you will create a portal
connecting this time
to infinite times.
A wormhole.
Through which one might travel
back to the past, say,
to the night your mother died or
forward to the future, to, say,
my time.
You said if I run fast enough.
What happens if I don't?
If you don't achieve
the desired velocity barrier,
you'll die.
According to
Wells' calculations,
Barry super-speeds
inside the accelerator ring.
Once Barry
reaches optimum speed,
we then launch a hydrogen proton
into the accelerator.
Once the collision happens,
a wormhole forms,
opening a gateway
into time itself.
It's at that moment
I plan on shouting something
along the lines of "Eureka"
or possibly "Excelsior."
I'm uncommitted.
What do you think?
I mean, on the one hand,
it does make a kind of sense.
On the other hand,
why?
Why, why would you ever
consider doing this?
You know why.
So, for this to actually work,
how fast would Barry have to go?
By my estimates,
Mach Two at a minimum.
You've never gone that fast.
So what happens if Barry
doesn't reach that speed?
I mean, I'm imagining a bug
hitting a windshield.
How far off am I?
Not very far,
I'm afraid.
Let me worry about
how fast I have to go.
We're gonna need
something else too.
Really?
And what's that?
'Cause I don't know
about you guys,
but I'm not at all interested in
helping you get yourself killed.
I need you to build
a time machine.
Go on.
So, if Wells is as fast as you,
what's he need
a time machine for?
Apparently he lost his speed
when he killed my mom.
He gets it back sometimes
but only in spurts.
He can't fully
control it.
So I was right
about the wheelchair.
He was using it
to charge himself.
So after I open the wormhole,
he's gonna need the ship
to travel back
to the future.
He's been squirreling away
the parts.
Now we just need
to put it together.
Ronnie, I love you,
but this is a time machine,
not a bookcase from IKEA.
We got a problem.
These tiles...
They're made of tungsten.
Well, tungsten does have
the highest melting point
of any other element.
Yeah, but the dust
it generates is flammable.
The pressure exerted
from the wormhole...
Yeah. Yeah.
It could cause a hole to be
melted into the exterior.
It could explode.
Any ideas?
Let me ask Dr. Evil.
Which used to be
a name that made me smile.
Something on your mind,
Cisco?
No.
Yes.
How did you fit
your Reverse-Flash suit
into that little ring?
Is it some sort
of compressed micro tech?
Or actually, forget it.
I don't care.
Maybe a little.
Ronnie's right.
I should have accounted
for the temporal shearing.
Glad we're still good
for something.
I never underestimated
your contribution, Cisco.
Or Ronnie's.
As a matter of fact,
do you know how many times
I wished you were there with me
as I rebuilt the accelerator?
It would have been
a lot more fun.
Yeah?
Well, doesn't change the fact
that your nifty little
Time Sphere...
Is that what you're calling it?
Whatever it's called.
It's gonna blow.
Not if you cement the tiles
with a cobalt resin.
That'll prevent degradation
in conditions of extreme heat.
Okay. Fine.
We'll try that.
That's it? That's all?
Well, what do you
want me to say?
I don't know, Cisco.
I thought that of anyone, you'd
be a little more understanding
of my predicament.
I don't belong here.
These barbaric times.
It's like
living amongst the dead.
Is that what you told yourself?
When you killed me?
What?
What did you say?
It was an alternate timeline.
One that Barry reset.
But I never forgot it.
It just kept
coming back to me.
And I can still picture
the way you looked at me
when you called me a son
and you crushed my heart
with your fist.
Cisco...
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
It sucked.
Not for killing you.
I'm sure I had a good reason.
I'm sorry for the fact that
you're able to retain traces
of another timeline.
You're able to see through
the vibrations of the universe.
It means...
I wasn't sure
until just now.
Sure of what?
The night the Particle
Accelerator exploded...
You were affected too.
What are you talking about?
No.
I wasn't.
Don't be afraid, Cisco.
A great and honorable destiny
awaits you now.
I only hope that as you're
living your great adventure,
that you remember
who gave you that life.
And that it was given
out of love.
I'm sorry, but I'm told
this is the only station
with enough power
to run these calculations.
If we make the slightest error
creating the wormhole...
Say no more.
Joe told me to stick around
in case I was needed,
but it seems
I'm only in the way.
Everyone has
a contribution to make.
Perhaps you just haven't
discovered yours yet.
No, Dr. Wells made it
pretty clear when he told me
about the future.
I don't matter.
As far as history's concerned,
I don't save the day
or get the girl.
And you believed him?
He had a newspaper
from the year 2024.
And I have a mug that says
"World's Best Boss."
I doubt my teaching assistant
would testify
to its authenticity.
We're dealing with a lot
of big scientific ideas today.
But you, Mr. Thawne, might be
the most interesting thing here
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Me?
What are the odds that Dr. Wells
would travel back in time
and get stuck
in the exact same city
as his great-great-great-
great-grandfather?
Working in the same profession,
the same building?
And that part of his plan
to get home would mean
that he'd have to preserve
and protect your life.
That makes you this rare thing
that no scientist can plan for.
Which is?
Coincidence.
There is no science
to coincidence.
You, sir, are an anomaly.
A wild card, as it were.
You are the only person
in this whole story
who gets to choose
his own future.
At least, that's my opinion.
Wait, that can't be right.
Oh, dear.
- We have a problem.
- What?
The calculations.
There is a danger.
I know.
I'm ready to take the risk.
No, not just to you
but to everyone.
Wells didn't tell us everything.
Barry, even if you do reach
the right speed,
colliding
with the hydrogen particle,
there is a chance that explosion
could create a singularity.
What's a singularity?
It's a black hole.
We could destroy
Central City.
For starters.
If we create a singularity here
and then cannot control it,
we could be looking
at a global catastrophe.
So long and thanks
for all the fish.
Well, sure,
there's a bit of a risk.
I would hardly refer
to possibly causing
an extinction-level event as
"a bit of a risk."
Yeah, and your accelerator's
been about as reliable as the
beater I drove in high school.
Let me ask you a question.
How many meta-humans...
How many dangers...
Have we faced
this year together?
Or did you forget
that was me
fighting alongside
each and every one of you?
I have been planning this
for almost two decades.
It will work.
And how do we make sure
we don't open a black hole
in the middle
of Central City?
So, once the wormhole
stabilizes,
Barry will have 1 minute
and 52 seconds to alter the past
and return to this time.
If and when he does that,
you can close the wormhole,
and we can all live
happily ever after.
Almost two minutes.
More than enough time
to save Nora.
But not enough time
to stop you from going home?
Everything's a choice.
And what if I'm late?
You won't be.
I believe in you, Barry.
Always have.
So I guess the question is,
do your friends and family
believe in you as much as I do?
So, if I don't run fast enough
to collide with the particle,
then I'm dust,
and if I do run fast enough
but I'm not back here in time,
then a black hole will form,
swallow up the city
and possibly the world.
You're sure you still want to
look me in the eyes and tell me
this is for the best?
I'd be lying
if I told you I did.
Truth is, I don't...
I don't know what to think.
I thought
you were the sure one.
I...
was kind of banking on that
when I made my decision
the first time.
I was faking it.
Sometimes parents do that.
Most of the time,
parents do that.
Look, of course I'm scared.
But I didn't want you to not
help your mother
because you were worried
about me.
Well, I'll always worry
about you, Joe,
just like you'll always worry
about me.
Sorry,
but you can't stop that.
Do you think I can do this?
You think
I can save my mom?
I mean, do you think
I'm fast enough?
Yes.
I know you are.
You know, I've... I've dreamed
my whole life about...
saving her,
freeing my dad, and...
I never thought I'd have to lose
another parent to do that.
Barry...
Joe, it's true.
It's true.
I've always been
so focused on everything
that I lost that night,
but I gained so much too.
I was born with one father,
and that tragedy gave me...
another.
And I don't think
I can lose you.
You won't ever
lose me.
Ever, you hear me?
Ever.
Wow, slow news day?
If they only knew, right?
I thought you would be
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I was.
Then I got hungry,
so I went to Mama Chows.
For dim sum?
Your favorite.
And to remind myself
of something.
What?
A coincidence. A pretty big
coincidence, actually.
About a year and a half ago,
I had a date with this girl.
Katie Rogers.
She was a dancer.
We had plans to meet
at Mama Chows,
but she texted me.
She pulled a hamstring
and had to cancel.
Oh, those fragile dancers.
I was bummed 'cause I was
looking forward to it.
So I had dinner by myself,
and I was walking home
when I saw a mugger
running with a stolen backpack.
Your backpack.
And I arrested him.
That's how you and I met.
I remember.
Someone just told me how
powerful a coincidence can be,
and it made me realize how many
coincidences had to happen
for you and I to get together...
in this time.
We've all been so focused on
Barry's destiny,
I forgot that I have one too.
And it's you.
Iris West,
every moment of my life
led to meeting you.
Screw the future.
Is this actually binding?
My father made me become a rabbi
before he would send me to MIT.
This will be "legit,"
as the kids say.
No kids say that.
Let's not fight
on our wedding day.
♪ There is freedom within ♪
♪ There is freedom without ♪
If it's all right with everyone,
I'd like to skip all the Hebrew.
I've learned a lot
about merging one's life
with another this past year.
Yet, for all the incredible
advancements in science
we've all been party to,
the mystery that brings
two people together through love
is still the province of magic.
Mr. Ramon,
the rings please.
♪ When the world comes in ♪
♪ They come, they come ♪
♪ To build a wall between us ♪
♪ We know they won't win ♪
I owe you a real ring.
I don't need one.
I have everything
and everyone
that I could ever need
right here.
And...
if all the events
of the past year
have led us
to this moment,
it was worth it.
I love you, Ronnie.
I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Stop telling me
what to do.
♪ Don't dream it's over ♪
♪ Hey now, hey now ♪
♪ When the world comes in ♪
Congratulations.
♪ They come, they come ♪
Okay.
There are gonna be three yous
back there...
The you from the future
who saved younger you
from the Reverse-Flash
and now you you.
Remember, wait until future you
gets younger you out of there,
and then you can go
and save your mom.
Piece of cake.
May the Speed Force
be with you.
Good-bye, Dad.
Good-bye, Son.
Iris...
You don't have
to say anything.
I already know.
I hope whatever life you get,
it's enough for you.
That it makes
you happy.
You too.
Remember, Mr. Allen,
assuming you achieve the proper
velocity and open the wormhole,
you will only have
1 minute and 52 seconds
to save your mother
and return.
Or else...
I know.
Well...
you hold both our futures
in your hands now, Mr. Allen.
And I know you can do it.
Now...
Run...
Barry.
Run.
The accelerator's structural
integrity is holding.
What was that?
Is Barry okay?
Yeah.
He just passed Mach Two.
I was waiting for you
to bring Barry home.
Looks like he's going to be
staying with us for a while.
Barry, what you're seeing is
the Speed Force:
your past, you present,
your future
all at once.
So you need to focus
on where you want to go.
So think about...
that night.
Think about your mother.
Time for bed.
Good night, slugger.
Mom!
It's working.
Inject the hydrogen particle
now.
What's that?
What happened?
Barry... he's gone.
- Look.
- The wormhole.
And it's stable.
Start the clock.
Mom!
Barry!
Nora! Hold on!
Run, Barry, run!
Barry, no!
No, no, no!
Hey. It's okay.
It's okay. You're okay.
Please. My husband,
my son, are they...
They're okay.
They're both safe.
I promise.
Who are you?
I'm...
I'm The Flash.
I don't understand.
You look
just like my father.
This won't make
any sense,
but it's me, Mom.
It's Barry.
Barry?
Your Barry.
Oh, my beautiful boy.
I got a second chance
to come back here and...
Tell you that I'm okay.
Dad and I are
both okay.
And we love you, Mom.
I love you.
Oh, my sweet boy.
Bye. Good-bye.
Good-bye, Barry.
Mom.
I believe it's time to
say good-bye to Harrison Wells.
It's beautiful.
Rip Hunter would
be impressed.
He built
the first one of these.
Interesting man.
Now what the hell
is that?
That's my cue to leave.
Thank you, Cisco.
Don't ever come back.
30 seconds.
Home.
- Oh, my God.
- Barry.
We have to shut down
the wormhole quickly!
Caitlin!
You didn't save her.
Why?
You could have had
the life you wanted.
everything you ever wanted!
I already do.
Not for long.
Cut the internal generators.
Ten seconds, hurry.
Three, two, one.
Ronnie, are you okay?
Did you do it?
Yes, I turned them
all off.
They did it.
They cut the generator.
Just so we're clear,
after I kill you,
I'm going to kill them.
And then I'm going
to kill your father.
I always win, Flash.
Eddie! Oh, my...
Eddie!
What did you do?
No such thing
as a coincidence.
What's happening?
Cisco, help me.
Eddie's his ancestor.
If Eddie dies,
he'll never be born, and...
He's being erased
from existence.
No! No!
Eddie.
Eddie, no, no.
Stay with me, okay?
Stay.
He was wrong,
it turns out.
I'm a hero after all.
You are, Eddie.
You are my hero.
That's all
I ever wanted to be.
Your hero.
No!
I've controlled your life
for so long, Barry.
How will you get along
without me?
Guys, that's not good.
Professor, I shut down
the wormhole.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
You did close it,
but it seems to be reopening.
We got to go.
You okay?
Iris, we have to go.
I'm not leaving him.
We have to go now, honey.
I'm sorry.
So that's what
we didn't want to happen.
- What's it doing?
- Feeding.
A singularity won't stop, not
even after the earth is gone.
I'm afraid the accretion disc
has already assembled.
What?
The diffuse material
that's in orbital motion
around the singularity.
What does that mean?
We have to disrupt the motion.
Basically it's just like
the tornado, only upside down.
And bigger.
And scarier.
Barry, that event
has an energy level
of at least
6.7 Tera Electron Volts.
It cannot be stopped.
I have to try.
Oh, God.
Barry.
Move your head.