Damn, you're good.
Real good.
Maybe too good.
We did it.
We did it!
Oh, my.
Cisco Ramon, tonight you've got yourself
a hot date and a meta-human cure.
We're unstoppable.
Ooh, shrap...
We have to wait how long
before we can use the meta-human cure?
Not even that long.
- Cisco. - It's gonna go by like that.
Cisco.
- 29 days. - A month?
I know, right? Just one, teeny, tiny, month
until we stop Cicada's purge. You know,
historically speaking, this is way faster
than we've ever stopped a big bad so...
We can't wait that long.
If he finds another meta
or comes after us--we have to speed this up somehow.
We have to wait for the compound to fully synthesize
or it won't be able to effectively neutralize
the dark matter in a meta-human's pituitary gland.
Without any way to expedite the exotic evolution--
Barry, we're gonna have to wait.
I think we have to wait.
Unless...
you took it into the Speed Force.
What, you want him to go into
the Speed Force for a month and then, what,
come out the same day that he left?
Oh, no, no, I'm not saying you manipulate time.
I'm saying you manipulate dark matter.
So very simple. It's simple chemistry, right?
When you are synthesizing a compound, you use a--
commodity, uh, substrate, uh--
- A catalyst? - Catalyst, right.
And the most efficient catalyst you can use when synthesizing
a compound that negates dark matter
is superluminal particles.
- Tachyons? - Tr¨¨s bien.
Tachyons, and the place where tachyons are the most dense?
- Speed Force. - And voil¨¤.
That might actually work.
Yeah, it will. It'll be like nuking it
in a pan-dimensional microwave.
-Nice work. - I know.
So how much time would this save?
From 29 days down to 60 minutes.
Yeah, it's gonna be faster.
And also since Cicada has been quiet
since your last encounter,
maybe there's no time like the present.
- Do it. - All right.
I'll see you in an hour.
Nora, you need to stay here.
You don't want my help?
I just-- I got this one this time.
Are you sure that now is a good time to go?
I mean, I just mean, the city will be Flash-less,
and an hour is a long time to be without the Flash.
The city is not gonna be Flash-less. It'll have XS.
Yeah, but what about the time
you had to spend 24 hours in the Pipeline cell
and Weather Witch and Silver Ghost stole that A.R.G.U.S. car--
And you stopped them without me.
Eh, with what happened to Mom because of Cicada--
Iris is fine, and this is the key to stopping Cicada.
I gotta go.
If anything happens, just do what I've trained you to do:
slow down and think clearly.
- Yeah. - I trust you, you just gotta trust yourself.
You'll be fine.
60 minutes.
Nora, Cisco hasn't left for his date yet, has he?
Uh, I don't think so.
Great, we get another chance at this.
Well, it is-- that's why you don't do it.
- What's wrong? - Nothing.
Oh, God. Not the "Book of Ralph" again!
Yeah, buddy. You successfully completed
my 27 steps to getting over the love of your life.
Gypsy is in the past.
You have a new siren,
so now it's time for...
"The Art of Love."
Um, Caitlin?
I've gotta finish working on the device to inject the cure.
Also I have to inject the device for the cure.
I-- I-- I-- Iris?
Oh, no, this is all you, man.
I got an article I gotta write.
Let me know when Barry gets back.
Help me.
"Chapter one: Initial Planning."
Initial planning?
It's a first date, Sun Tzu, not an incursion.
Trust me, Grasshopper,
love is war, but, fine,
if you wanna skip to chapter six, "Know Your Terrain."
- We're meeting at Jitters. - Ah, familiar territory.
You are learning.
Uh, you know, he really should be going.
- I really should. - Hang on, hang on one second.
This one's really important.
Chapter thirteen, "Intelligence and Reconnaissance."
Wh-- you cyber-stalked Kamilla?
No, no, no, no, of course not.
That's her public profile.
But it did happen to have some info
on the types of guys that she might be into.
The types of guys that she's into?
Yes, and, unfortunately, you are nothing like them,
but, hey, if you don't wanna get a second date, be my guest.
Just don't come crying to me when everything inevitably
goes horribly, horribly wrong and you die alone.
No big deal.
See, now he's in my head.
Okay, no thank you.
I didn't take these.
- You saw nothing. - Nothing.
One Cicada on the bar for Ian?
- It's I-an. - Sorry, I-an.
Hey, Kamilla.
Cisco. Wow.
Sorry I'm late. I got held up at a meeting.
That's okay. I just got here.
If I'd had known, I would have dressed up more.
Oh, this old thing?
No, please, this is work clothes.
You have to wear a suit to your lab?
My lab?
When we met at the bar,
you were talking about DNA and genomes,
so I assumed you were some kind of scientist.
Right, I said that, scientist.
Yes. No. Well, I'm what you would call
a science businessman.
So, what, you make money off of other people's discoveries?
Well, somebody has to.
It's just a little joke, something I always say.
So, uh, what is the name of the company you work for?
It's called Ramon Industries.
It's named after yourself?
That's humble.
Maybe I should grab us a couple coffees.
Sure.
- Decaf Flash. - Decaf Flash, right, okay.
You're not the only one who does their research.
I know who you are, Iris West-Allen.
I know you work with the Flash and the other heroes.
You said you were gonna beat me,
but tonight, I'm gonna beat you,
all of you.
One Zoom and one decaf Flash.
That's the decaf. Men in this city...
Tell me about it.
Uh, I'm sorry, it's work. I have to go.
Uh, could we just have, like, a do-over, please?
It's Mom.
Get away from her.
She's not who you want.
No, she's not, but you are.
Then come and get us.
Caitlin!
Told ya.
Nora, Cisco hasn't left for his date yet, has he?
Uh, I don't think so.
Great, I get another chance at this.
We do.
- What's wrong? - Uh, nothing.
I just have to fix this. Okay.
Oh, God, not the...
"Book of Ralph."
- Again! - Yeah, buddy,
You have successfully completed my 27 steps
to getting over the love of your life.
Gypsy is in the past, you have a new siren,
so now it's time for the Art of Love.
Um, Caitlin?
I gotta go finish the device to inject the cure.
Also have to inject the device for the cure.
- I--I--I--Iris? - Oh, no, this is all you, man.
I got an article I gotta write.
Let me know when Barry gets back.
So not shway.
"Chapter one: Initial Planning."
- Uh, you can't leave. - What?
I mean, you just shouldn't go to your office,
- not right now. - Why?
Because Dad is gonna be back, like, any minute
and by the time that you get there,
you're just gonna have to turn around anyway.
Yeah, I know, but I need to get this article out tonight.
Yeah, but, I mean, you have your laptop with you, right?
So why don't you just write it here
in the lounge where it's safe?
Safe?
I mean cozy. It's cozy.
Um, yeah, I mean, yeah. I guess I could.
Great, I'll make you coffee.
- Ok. -OK
You end up dying alone.
Okay, see, now he's in my head.
No thank you, Ralph.
Dang it.
Last bottle.
One Cicada at the bar for Ian.
- It's I-an. - Sorry, I-an.
- Kamilla, hey. - Cisco, wow.
Sorry I'm late. I just came from the gym.
Ya gotta get your steps in, you know?
That's okay, I just got here.
You work out a lot?
You kidding me? I'm, like, a gym rat, you know.
I live there.
So what kind of workouts do you do?
What kind of workouts don't I do? I mean, like,
Pilates for the core,
plyometrics for the quads,
circuit training, I mean, pretty much anything
I can get my hands on, even my hands, you know.
I've been known to do some
you know, finger pushups every once in a while.
- What? - When we met at the bar,
you were talking about DNA and genomes, so--
So you thought maybe I wasn't your type?
I thought I had finally met a guy who was more concerned
with flexing his brain than his muscles.
Okay, um, maybe I should grab us a couple of coffees.
Sure, decaf Flash.
Decaf Flash, I was gonna ask you.
I know who you are, Elongated Man.
I know you work with the Flash and the other heroes.
Iris West-Allen told me you were gonna beat me.
But tonight,
I'm gonna beat you,
all of you.
- One Zoom and one decaf Flash. - Thanks.
- The men in this city. - Tell me about it.
That's the decaf. The men in this city...
Tell me about it.
Uh, I'm sorry, it's a gym emergency.
I have to go. Um, can we just have a do-over, please?
- Ralph. - Get Caitlin.
Okay.
Move!
Ralph?
Told ya.
Nora, Cisco hasn't left for his date yet, has he?
Uh, no, I'm pretty sure he hasn't.
Great, I'm gonna get another chance at this.
Yeah, we do.
What's wrong?
Nora?
Nothing. Come on, you can figure this out.
Not the "Book of Ralph" Again!
Yeah, buddy, you successfully completed my 27 steps
to getting over the love of your life.
Gypsy is in the past. You have a new siren,
so now it's time for "The Art of Love."
Um, Caitlin?
I gotta go work on the device to inject the cure.
Also I have to devise the cure.
I--I--I--Iris?
Ooh, nah, that's all you, man.
I gotta go write an article.
Let me know when Barry gets back.
Uh, no, you know what? Don't go.
Uh, why don't you write the article here?
Uh, I can make you coffee.
I mean, I know that there's coffee over there, but I--
I just think it's really important for the team leader
to stay here until Dad gets back
just in case something happens, okay?
Okay, lounge it is.
All right, "Chapter one: Initial Planning."
It's a first date, Sun Tzu, not an incursion.
Trust me, Grasshopper, love is war.
Yeah, and I couldn't agree more, so read these.
They'll help you, and you'll know what to do.
- Wait, wait, how-- - And if anything goes wrong,
just give us a call.
You and I are gonna stay here and have our own coffees
- in the lounge. - No, no, no.
There's brownies.
- Brownies? - Yes.
Ralph, did you cyber-stalk her?
You were talking about DNA and genomes.
I thought I'd finally met a guy who was more concerned
with flexing his brain than his muscles.
Ca va?
Yeah, yeah. Sorry, I just--
I'm having the most wicked d¨¦j¨¤ vu right now.
Is that right?
Why don't you want your mother to come here, hmm?
Because you time-travel.
- It's I-an. - Sorry, I-an.
Kamilla tha thrilla.
Cisco?
- Wow. - Sorry I'm late.
I just came from a photoshoot.
The things you do for the 'gram, am I right?
Hey, maybe next time you should be my photographer.
What do you think?
So you're a...
I'm an aspiring social media influencer.
This is my card. You can keep that.
When we met at the bar,
you were talking about DNA and genomes,
so I assumed you were some kind of scientist.
Really? When we met at the bar,
you were talking about DNA and genomes, so I--
You assumed I was some kind of scientist?
Yeah, exactly.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'm just having some d¨¦j¨¤ vu again.
Maybe I should grab us a couple of coffees?
Oh, yes. Yes, that'd be great.
Will you get me a Zoom, please?
Okay.
What?
Okay, here we go.
Thanks.
- One Zoom and one decaf Flash. - Thank you.
Something's wrong,
- and I think I have to go. - Right now?
No, right now.
Yep, gotta go. Um, I'd ask if we could have
a do-over, but, um,
something tells me I already have.
- The men in this city. - Tell me about it.
- Come on! - It's Sherloque.
What? I thought he was here with Caitlin.
- We gotta get Frost. - No, no, I got this.
You guys just stay here.
Gar?on, look out!
Told ya.
Cisco!
Why can't I fix this?
Why can't I go back any further?
- Nora? - Cisco hasn't left yet.
Great.
So we get another chance at this.
We do.
I'm fine, Sherloque.
I have to fix this.
Okay, you guys have to stay here.
Why?
Because dad put his trust in me that I would protect all of you
and I'm the only speedster here for the first time
and if something were to go wrong,
I don't know if I could fix it, in fact,
I'm pretty sure that I couldn't fix it, so just, for one hour, stay here.
I have to go finish--
No, no!
I got a date with--
Were you cyber-stalking Kamilla?
No, no, no, of course not.
This is her public profile.
You were talking about DNA and genomes,
so I thought I'd finally met a guy
who is more concerned with his brain than his muscles.
Kamilla.
Oh, I got some details on the kinds of guys she's into.
Wait, were you cyber-stalking her?
No, I'm not stalking her. It's her public profile.
Guys! I'm sorry, but you're just gonna have to stay here.
- I-an. - Sorry, I-an.
You have got to be kidding me.
You got the first one.
- I got the next one. - I think we all got one.
What did you get?
- It's Cecile. - Guys, um, just stay here.
Told ya.
Nora?
I was supposed to protect you,
but I can't. I don't know how to.
But my dad does.
I can't get into the Speed Force either?
You're reversing time, aren't you?
And I can't fix it.
So all of us die?
Sometimes, or just one of you.
Sometimes Cecile, but every time, there's at least one.
I thought I was having d¨¦j¨¤ vu.
I keep seeing my date with Kamilla again and again,
me failing miserably every time by using these.
I'm not having d¨¦j¨¤ vu.
I'm vibing the past hour over and over.
Yeah.
How many times has this happened?
- 52. - 52?
This is one of those fixed points the Legends theorized, isn't it?
There's no way to keep one of us from dying.
- We have to get Barry. - No, I tried that,
but there's something wrong with me.
I can't get into the Speed Force.
Well, then we'll just wait here until he gets back.
No, if we do that, Cicada will kill Cecile.
So just reverse time and go back to before he left.
No, I've tried that too, but I can't control it.
It doesn't matter what I try to do. Nothing works!
Believe it or not, this ain't the first time
I've died in a past timeline.
I once got a vibrating hand through the chest
courtesy of Eobard Thawne.
Well, more than once.
I actually kept vibing that moment until I realized
that it actually happened.
I guess I should have known the same thing was happening now, huh?
I keep trying my absolute hardest to change the outcome,
but I end up failing every time.
What if we can't fix this, Cisco?
Nora, sometimes we fail because
all we worry about is not failing.
I'm so worried about my first date since Cynthia
that I don't feel free to be myself around Kamilla,
and then I'll just end up screwing it up even more.
This--this intelligence and reconnaissance mess,
I don't need this. All I need is to be myself.
And I sure as hell don't need to dress up like Ozone
just to impress Kamilla.
Sorry, that is an outdated reference.
No, from the movie "Breakin'."
Yeah, I've seen "Electric Boogaloo" Too.
I've seen them both, like, a hundred times.
I know every move.
Wow, fangirl.
Wait.
Wait, that's it.
Every time I fail, I take notes in my journal
so I can do something different the next time.
We know every move.
So all you need to do is just tell us
everything you've done and how it went wrong.
So we can figure out how to make it right.
52 kidnappings, 52 combinations
leading to 52 deaths.
- None of them were Cicada's? - Exactly.
Yes, exactly.
Wait, does that mean you want to use Cicada's dagger against him
by having Nora reverse time?
That's exactly what I'm suggesting.
Yeah, but how are we gonna do that?
I mean, Nora can't control it when she reverses time.
She could control her abilities if we help her slow down.
Slowing it down.
If she can do that, we bring the fight to him.
And we all live through the night.
I like the sound of that.
Well, we have everything we need.
Looking for me? I know you did your research.
You know who I am, that I work for the Flash
and the other heroes.
I told you we were gonna beat you,
and tonight we will...
All of us.
Allez, now!
Told you.
No dark matter anywhere. Dwyer's gone, again.
Maybe after the ass kicking he just got,
he'll think twice before coming after us again.
And if he doesn't think twice, now you can make him.
Thanks for helping me slow it down.
Now that I've experienced a sense of control,
maybe next time, I can do it on my own.
Thank you for saving us, all of us.
I didn't save everything.
Maybe you can now?
No, no, that date is over.
There's no way Kamilla's still at Jitters.
Well, if she is still there,
there might be some stuff
in here that can help you smooth things over.
But, you can handle it. You're Cisco Ramon.
Come on, you gotta get a move on.
Okay.
- Giddyap, Romeo. - I'm moving.
Sherloque was right. One hour, it's cooked.
Something happen while I was gone?
Kid Flash on the bar for Steven?
- It's Stephan. - Sorry, Stephan.
- Kamilla, hey. - Cisco
I am so sorry I'm late. I had an emergency at work.
It's okay, I just got here.
So you're a scientist, right?
When we were at the bar,
you were talking about DNA and genomes, so...
I'm more of a tech nerd, actually,
but the project that we're working on now,
it gets very scientific.
You sound like you're really excited about it.
Oh, my God, I am. I'm so excited about it.
You have no idea, um.
I think we might have made a breakthrough recently,
a breakthrough that could change a lot of lives.
One Zoom and one decaf Flash.
I hope you don't mind, I called it in ahead of time.
It's the least I could do.
- That's the decaf. - How did you know what I like?
I had a feeling.
Not like most of the men in this city.
Tell me about it.
Listen, I know I screwed up royally
showing up late like this,
but it would make me very happy if--
Can we just have a do-over, please?
That sounds nice.
52 times?
53, if you include now.
That's a lot.
What was I supposed to do, let one of them die?
The thing is, Nora, there are consequences to time travel.
- Oh, I know. - No, you don't,
not like I do.
Let me show you something.
Imagine this coffee cup is the space/time continuum.
Whenever you go back in time, it breaks.
Now, you can try and reset the timeline,
try and fix it, but no matter how hard you try,
it's never gonna be exactly how it was.
It seems like things worked out this time,
but that's not always gonna be true,
and it's impossible to know how these changes are gonna unfold,
the ripples you'll cause, whose life you're gonna affect.
No one can do that.
No one?
No one.
We're not gods, Nora.
We've just been given extraordinary abilities.
Thawne, I need to know we're not making this worse.
Tell me you know what you're doing.
I am the only speedster who knows what he's doing!
Stick with the plan.
Follow my instructions and we'll defeat Cicada,
we'll destroy his dagger,
and then we will save your father.