Last season, on "The Flash."
Melt.
- Killer Frost... - Is gone.
It says there's still another cryogenic anomaly
in my DNA.
Killer Frost is still a part of you.
Hang on.
See, right there.
Killer Frost, she was part of you.
Even then.
How is that possible?
To the newest member of Team Flash.
We need to talk.
- Who are you? - I'm your daughter, Nora.
Sally's in a decaying orbit.
Okay, how do we stop something
that's going to send us back into the Stone Age?
Barry, you've got to destroy that satellite.
That satellite
it wasn't just me who took it down.
There was another speedster.
Okay, let's back up.
My name is Nora West-Allen,
the fastest woman alive.
When I'm from, 30 years from now,
I'm the guardian of Central City.
I'm a speedster, just like my dad.
People call me XS.
Every day, I hope to live up to the legacy of The Flash...
But I've still got a long way to go.
You're saying you're our daughter?
From the future?
Named Nora?
After your mother.
Anybody need a refill?
No? Just me?
Cisco Ramon,
always cutting the tension with a joke.
You know our names?
Of course. I know all of you.
You're Caitlin Snow, Ralph Dibny,
Papa Joe, Mama Cecile.
Little Auntie Jenna.
She's so cute.
And Uncle Wally.
Uh, and your nickname is XS?
Clearly not my doing.
No, uh, it's a nickname
that you gave me when I was a kid, Mom.
"Mom"?
You said I did everything in excess.
Guess I've always been like that.
Overdoing things, getting in way over my head.
Like, uh, recently.
This mistake that you made?
Big mistake.
Which was...
Helping you save the city
by destroying the STAR Labs satellite last night.
You were the other speedster?
I just couldn't stop myself
from getting involved.
But something happened when I did, because now,
I can't seem to go fast enough to open up the Speed Force.
Par--pardon me.
Are we talking about actual time travel here?
Do you just like, not pay any attention
when we have our briefings?
Y'all didn't teach him about the Legends?
Look, nobody said bubkes about time travel.
Come on, Ralph. You're scaring the baby.
Yeah, you're scaring the baby.
No, no, she's not scared.
She just said she's hungry.
She said that she's-- Joe!
I heard her!
I read her mind!
I might not be losing my powers!
Awesome.
I'm sorry.
I know how bizarre this must seem,
meeting your daughter from the future as an adult.
But really, this wasn't my plan at all,
but I'm kind of stuck here now,
and you're the only people who can help me.
So...anybody know what to do?
This is so, so weird.
Yeah, I mean, I can't believe that's our daughter up there.
- We have been lied to before. - Barry.
Yellow lightning like yours, purple lightning like mine?
I mean, it's-- it's got to be her.
We're meeting our daughter for the first time, Barry.
Yeah, well, look. If it is true,
Nora could say the wrong thing or step on the wrong butterfly
and screw up the whole timeline.
I mean, she could Marty McFly herself out of existence.
Mm, "Terminator 2," Yeah.
No, that's "Back to the"-- It doesn't matter.
Look, we just need to be responsible, all right?
I mean, I think we need to find a way to send her home, fast.
Barry, don't you think future us taught our daughter
how not to screw with the timeline?
Wow, this Speed Lab sure is archaic, huh?
La-la-la-la-la, you don't know--
you know what, um...
Sorry, just--no future talk, all right, please?
Right, I don't want to wreck the timeline.
All right, Nora.
This is gonna link us up with your biometrics.
And this little scrunchy doohicky
is gonna analyze your connection to the, um, uh--
The Speed Force.
The Speed Force. Thank you.
Great.
I'll be back in a...flash.
And what does it say?
A quick analysis of her DNA shows patterns
that are similar to both of yours.
I knew it. She's our daughter.
What about her being stuck here?
Everything's normal.
She definitely has Speed Force in her system.
She's just not going... fast enough
to, uh, open up a time portal, so.
How much champagne did you have at Joe and Cecile's?
This is the first opportunity I have
to process my breakup with Gypsy, okay?
How was I supposed to know
that your future daughter was gonna come show up
and crash my pity party?
How was I supposed to "Ancipitate" that?
Crap, I was supposed to meet Singh at CCPD an hour ago.
- Okay. - Hey, Wally, can you do me a favor?
Can you take the sample to the Legends
to see if they have any insight?
And maybe, worst comes to worst,
we can take her home on the Waverider?
- Yeah, I got it. - All right.
Okay, just-- I'll hurry back.
Keep an eye on her.
New ID, keys to the lab.
You are officially reinstated as our CSI tech, Allen.
Thanks, Captain.
Oh, one more thing.
We didn't fill your position while you were away,
so there are a few cases waiting for you in your lab.
Get to them fast as you can.
Welcome back, Allen.
"A few"?
What you working on?
- I don't-- - You are crazy behind.
Hey, so I thought you were gonna stay at STAR Labs,
with, um...with your...
Iris-- mom.
Your mom.
You know I'm a forensic scientist too?
CCU grad, just like you. 5.6 GPA.
I could help you get through this.
Oh, I don't know. I mean, it's--
So the fire marshal at this site says
crazing in the melted glass suggests a liquid accelerant.
Mm, any petroleum-based household product
could cause crazing.
Well, like floor wax, or shag rugs, even balloons.
Yeah, the glass melts under the surface,
like ice cream in the cracks of a waffle cone.
Oh, like when you get two scoops
of cookie dough ice cream with extra sprinkles
at the Mason Family Ice Cream Shop in...
Happy Harbor, Rhode Island.
My parents used to take me there when I was a kid.
It's my favorite dessert.
Mine too.
Hey, look, I'm sorry, um, you're obviously
good at forensics, but you shouldn't interfere.
I mean, people like us, we need to be responsible.
Right! Uh, timeline.
The timeline, yeah.
All available units,
M-0-3 in progress, 10th and Neely.
M-0-3, that's a meta attack.
Yeah, my suit's all torn up.
I don't have anything to--
Direct from Cisco's back closet.
One first-edition red emblem OG super suit.
Total fan favorite.
Thank you.
Uh, I'm-- I'm gonna handle this.
You just-- no, no, no.
Uh, you... stay.
- Okay? - Okay.
Seriously, please.
Now I'm gonna...
Going old-school today, Flash?
Yeah, it's a little tighter than I remember, though.
Hey, uh, you might want to do something.
Now it's my turn, Flash.
Gridlock? Schway!
- What are you doing? - No, no.
I just-- I just wanted--
Nice.
Oh, grife. You're mad at me.
No, Nora, we're not. We're just--
Please don't say "Disappointed."
That's so much worse.
I mean, I just didn't think it was a big deal.
It was only Gridlock.
Oh, Gridlock, huh?
Boy, the future's got some great names.
This lighting!
How did you know who he is?
Flash Museum.
Did you say...
- "Flash Museum"? - Yeah.
It has all the villains and battles in chronological order.
I've studied everything.
So you know this guy's real name?
Mr. Myles, the curator,
he scrubbed all the names for legal reasons.
But it really shouldn't matter.
I mean, Gridlock was a one-and-done.
You guys beat him in one try,
or at least... you were supposed to.
Ugh, now, because of me, he's on the run,
and the timeline's all messed up again, and I--
Nora, hey, look, look.
I've made way bigger mistakes than this time traveling.
We'll get this guy-- you don't need to worry about that--
but the longer you stay here, the more things might change.
We need to get you home.
But I can't go fast enough to get home.
What about the tachyon absorption enhancer?
The one that Thawne used to increase his speed?
Ooh, and if we charge it up,
we could uh, boost the Speed Force in her cells,
like some kind of, um...
thing that boosts Speed Force in cells.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. That's a good idea.
Let's--okay, finding Gridlock
and getting Nora home need to be our priorities.
No, no, no. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
- Wait. - Loud!
Okay, so--but this needs to be our priority.
Now, I realize that you're all way ahead of me
in this time-travel business, but guys,
I think I just discovered something.
So if--if Nora can time travel,
that means she can create new timelines, right?
New timelines means that parallel timelines can exist.
So, guys,
I think that a whole other universe could exist.
I know, I know, I know.
It sounds crazy, but think about it.
There could be an Earth where we're all bad guys,
or another Earth where there's no world hunger,
or--or another Earth where--
where they never made that last "Indiana Jones" Movie.
Think of the possibilities.
It's like some kind of a manyverse.
And everybody knows about the manyverse.
Multiverse, and so do you, Ralph.
Breacher? Gypsy? Harry?
What did you think we meant when we said
Harry was from Earth-2?
That he is from Earth "Also."
Oh, my God.
You guys really need to make, like, a welcome pamphlet,
or at least a Powerpoint or something.
Hey, Ralph, buddy?
Can we get off time travel, maybe, please?
Let's focus on finding Gridlock, all right?
Thank you.
I'm gonna go to CCPD,
see what I can dig up.
Okay, I'll stay with Nora.
- Let's just make sure- - I know.
Protect the timeline.
You thirsty?
Okay, latte for me, and a decaf Flash for you.
Dad's lightning bolt is way cooler than Lightning Lad's.
And do you think he's gonna be back soon?
Well, you know your dad.
Whenever there's a problem, he's gotta run off and fix it.
But, you know,
this gives us a chance to connect.
You're not worried about messing things up, like he is?
I--well, I just, I...
want to get to know you a little.
How about this?
I will ask you questions
about your life, and if I'm right,
you just blink twice.
I mean, blinking never broke the timeline, right?
Okay, yeah, I mean, if you really want to.
Yeah, I think it'll be really fun.
Okay, um, so let's see.
You are a reporter for a newspaper
that you can only read on Instagram.
Um, okay, you--you are a cop.
You're a--a CSI?
You're a CSI.
Just like your dad.
Okay, well, what about you and I?
Do we--do we, like, have dinner every Sunday?
Do we talk on the phone?
Do we still get coffee at Jitters?
Uh... Was that a blink?
Uh, no, I just-I have something in my eye.
You know, a coffee in my time at Jitters is $43 a cup.
That's one thing I really like about now.
2018 is way schway.
"Schway"? Oh.
Yeah, I guess it's a future thing.
Oh--oh, no. Oh, "Schway."
No, I know, I'm hip. I know what schway means.
Like, I'm schway, you're schway.
We're--we're schway, baby.
Stupid.
Do you think maybe Caitlin and Cisco need any help?
I can't believe I'm wearing the same tachyon enhancer
my dad used to meet Supergirl for the first time.
All set.
Wait, what happened to the second version?
The smaller one that was inside the emblem
of my dad's second suit?
Um, if he wore that one, he could harness tachyons
and share them with me.
Hey, fangirl, relax.
We know.
Did all these suits shrink?
And why does it smell so bad?
Because it's the one you used
when you swam against King Shark.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Flash!
Zoom wants you dead!
I know King Shark is technically a bad guy,
but you should see-just wait.
When he fights Grodd, it's-Um!
Spoiler alert.
We should get going, actually, let's--
Right.
Then this is goodbye.
From your guys' perspectives, at least.
I'll see you again in a minute and 27 seconds,
but when you see me again, I'll be a baby.
Get home safe, Nora.
I'm sorry
we didn't get to spend more time together.
Oh, it's fine, Mom.
We spend our whole lives together.
All right.
Did they already leave?
Yeah, why? What's up?
We have to stop them.
I'm sorry I was too late.
It took me a while to find where the Legends were.
Well, when they were.
But we got their Gideon
to scan Nora's blood sample.
- What'd she find? - Negative tachyons.
Negative tachyons?
So, what, instead of speeding you up, they slow you down?
Yeah.
Oh, damn, I was just joking.
That's a real thing?
Yeah, Ava and her team at the Time Bureau
have encountered them before, but no one knows
where they come from or how they're generated.
Like dark matter for the space time continuum.
Exactly, and they're saturating Nora's body
and keeping her from entering the Speed Force.
What about the Waverider? Can the Legends take her back?
If negative tachyons come anywhere near
the Rider's time drives,
uh, the reaction will vaporize the ship.
Well, there's got to be a way to get rid of them, right?
I mean, I don't know about getting rid of them,
but maybe we can offset
the tachyon absorption enhancer
to negate the reaction somehow.
- A new meta was last seen... - Hey, guys.
Jumping off a building in order to
evade capture after stealing jewels...
How did we miss this?
I guess this is a parting gift from DeVoe.
Without our STAR Labs satellite,
we've lost our eyes, our ears, our dark matter scanner,
our facial recognition-- I mean, we're always
gonna be one step behind these metas now.
I'll work on this.
Why don't you guys go help Ralph
with the Gridlock crime scene, okay?
I can come help.
Please, no, just--we just
can't let this get any worse, all right?
Just relax, okay?
How's your investigation going?
Uh, it just doesn't really add up.
I mean, if Eddie wanted to erase Thawne from existence,
why didn't he just have a vasectomy?
Right, uh, nobody's talking.
Probably because they're afraid
Gridlock will attack them.
Right, but maybe if I had Killer Frost at my side,
people would be a little more willing
to tell us what they know.
Ralph, Killer Frost has been gone
since the night that DeVoe took over your body.
Jeez Louise, no one tells me anything.
- Is she gone for good? - I hope not.
But I've tried everything I can think of
to get her to reappear.
You don't have any other leads?
Cisco vibed me back to when
Killer Frost and I were younger.
You've been a meta since you were a kid?
- I guess so. - How?
- I have no idea. - Did you see anything else?
- Just that my dad was there. - Well, that's something.
Except my dad's been dead for years.
But none of this matters right now.
We have much more pressing things to deal with.
Hey, come look at this.
I present Gridlock.
A mystery in three acts.
Please note the dark matter levels.
Act One, Gridlock attacks the cops before Barry shows up.
Okay, but these dark matter levels
are perfectly normal for a man of his size.
Until Act Two.
He gets lightning punched by Barry.
His dark matter levels increased.
Which brings us to our third and final act...
Gridlock hits back.
Even higher.
How--how is that possible?
It isn't, unless every time Gridlock got hit,
his cells absorbed the kinetic energy.
That would increase his dark matter quotient,
thereby increasing his powers.
If this is true, then whatever movement he's exposed to--
The stronger he's gonna get.
So, if Gridlock keeps moving, he becomes unstoppable.
So, figure it out yet?
Whatever these negative tachyons are,
it feels a lot more like science fiction
than actual science.
I wasn't asking about the science.
I was asking about the scientist.
You and Nora, you guys have such a strong connection.
I mean, it's... it's effortless.
So why are you so intent on sending her back?
I mean, what do you mean?
First of all, she can't stop talking about the future.
But--I mean, you know the danger that her being here
poses to the timeline.
Yeah, I do, but I also know you, Barry.
Look.
You're the guy that went back in time
- to borrow Snart before he died. - I know.
You're also the same guy that travelled to 2020
to figure out who Savitar was,
and 2015 to train with Wells.
You changed fate to save my life.
So, now that our daughter is here in front of us,
asking for our help, you expect me to believe
that you're worried about the timeline?
Nora shouldn't be here.
Look, I'm--
- I've always wanted a family. - I know.
You know, and when we got married,
I knew that one day, we'd decide to have a baby.
We would try, and you'd get pregnant.
I'd be there for the sonogram, I'd hear her first heartbeat,
and then she'd come.
And we'd take her home, see her first smile,
her first tooth, the first time I read to her.
Her first steps. The first time she ran.
But her being here now, don't you feel like
we missed all those firsts?
That we skipped all the good stuff?
Baby, we will still have all of those firsts.
Just not in that order.
But my whole life's been out of order.
These powers, time travel--
that's the reason my mom was killed,
why I grew up with my dad in prison.
They missed so many firsts. They missed our wedding.
I know.
I don't know, I just thought that when it was our turn to have a kid,
that life would let us have this one little thing
the normal way.
Just once.
But we lost that chance.
No, we're not losing anything by having her here now.
We're only gaining something extra, Barry.
And look, if we figure this out,
I mean, by the time we do have a baby,
we are gonna be the best parents ever.
- Maybe you're right. - I know I'm right.
You're gonna be there to put that quarter under her pillow,
and you're gonna be there
to drive her to her first day of school,
and you're gonna be there to cheer on her first run.
And we are gonna have all of those firsts.
I promise.
And think about it.
We have a kid who defied the laws of physics
to hang out with her parents.
I mean, that's pretty-- that's pretty schway.
Yeah, as eager as she is, you'd think that she's the one
that grew up with a parent in...
What's wrong?
Nothing. Um, nothing.
I'm--I'm gonna be right back.
Nora.
What happens to me in the future?
You said that you spend your whole life with your mom,
but you didn't say the same for me.
My poker face is that bad, huh?
I need to know.
How long?
You never come back.
How old were you when it happened?
I was born, um, a few years before you vanished,
but I don't have any memories of you.
So the wedding was...
Was pretty much the first time I met you.
I'd imagined so many different things to say to you.
Still can't believe I went with "Remember to say 'I do.'"
I guess things don't always go the way you plan them.
You're not stuck here, are you?
I found it in the museum archive.
Negative tachyons, harnessed on demand.
Really should work on that poker face, I guess.
This didn't have to be a secret.
Why did you keep this from us?
Because if you knew I could have gone home,
you would have sent me back
the second I walked into Grandpa's house.
I mean, it's like you said, Dad.
Speedsters have to be responsible.
But--but I'm not responsible, am I?
I'm...just selfish
and really, really bad at being a speedster.
Nora, you're not bad.
I mean, I can do some cool things, you know?
Sometimes, I run so fast, I reverse time a bit,
but I can't do the things you can.
I don't even know how to phase yet.
Guess there's only so much you can learn from a museum.
What about your mom?
Yeah, I--she's around, you know?
It's just, uh-- just me and her.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, I know.
I shouldn't have lied.
I just wanted to see you so badly
and spend a day with you.
Go for a run for the first time together.
I missed all your firsts.
I was so worried about screwing up your childhood
and screwing up our family, but...
I'm not even there.
Barry, we need you in the Cortex.
It's about Gridlock.
I-- - I'm fine.
you need to go fix my mess, and then I can go home.
I scanned the crime scene photos and got a match.
This is not Lang's first rodeo.
CCPD put out a warrant for him for carjacking.
He killed the whole crew inside.
And now he absorbs kinetic energy?
He only gets stronger if you punch him,
you shoot him, you throw him into traffic.
Which could only make the traffic worse.
God, I'd hate to be stuck in that gridlock.
Gridlock... Gridlock...
I came up with the name.
I am fortune's fool.
So how do we find this guy without Sally the satellite?
We don't need a satellite to hack a cell phone.
And if we want to find his cell phone, we'll find it...
By the airport?
Got it, 'cause he's on a plane that just took off.
Central City Air, flight number 5201.
Why would he get on a plane?
Because he's gonna crash it.
We are currently cruising at 34,000 feet.
We anticipate a smooth landing,
so sit back and enjoy...
Excuse me, sir.
If you could please fasten your seatbelt
until we reach cruising altitude
and the captain turns off the seatbelt sign.
Are you gonna buckle that thing in too?
Well, it must be something priceless to get its own seat.
Jewels, maybe.
The plane just lost an engine.
It's headed for downtown.
If Gridlock takes out the other engine,
the pilot won't be able to avoid the buildings.
Thousands of people will die.
Not if you phase the plane through the buildings.
I read about you doing the same thing
to a plane in the future when you were fighting Mob Rule.
Can you two do that?
A plane?
No-- I mean, no, I don't think so.
I mean, I think it's too big.
The three of us.
I mean, the three of us might be able to do it.
Well, I can't phase anything.
I can't even phase myself, let alone at G-Force.
Wait, G-For-- G-Force, that's it.
The plane is still ascending.
Once he blows up the other engine,
it's gonna slow down and point downwards
before it starts its descent.
That'll give us about ten seconds of zero Gs on the plane.
- Yeah. - And zero Gs means no kinetic energy,
means Gridlock has no powers.
Can you breach them onto the plane?
A plane goes way too fast.
I'd need to see it in person.
- Then go. - But I don't have a suit.
I actually have a backup.
I got more than just a list of metas from that museum.
Damn, Gina. I made that?
Uh, Ryan Choi, actually.
Oh, this is a supersuit.
- No offense. - None taken.
Guys, he just took out the other engine.
You can do this.
Don't drink and vibe. I feel like I'm gonna hurl.
It's slowing.
Guys, you've got ten seconds.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Okay, everybody stay calm, all right?
Just stay calm.
All right, come on.
Hey, take a wall, all right?
We got this.
Barry, hurry.
- It's not working. - What?
I can't do this.
All right, yes-- listen to me, just breathe.
Feel the floor beneath your feet.
Feel the rumble of the plane.
Feel the air.
Feel that wind on your face,
- and the lightning. - And the lightning.
Feel its electricity pumping through your veins,
traveling to every nerve in your body
like a shock you never want to end.
- You are no longer you now. - You're no longer you.
You're part of something greater.
Part of the Speed Force.
That's right.
All right, it's ours.
Now, let's do it.
Everybody hold on!
Hold on!
Are you okay?
Nice.
You phased.
For the first time!
Well, Gridlock's off to Iron Heights' meta wing.
Where he won't be moving from for a very long time.
Thanks to your help.
I'm glad we got to team up.
Me too.
Ladies and gentleman,
say hello to the tachyon absorption enhancer 2.5,
now complete with completely recalibrated
Time Bureau technology.
We haven't tested it yet, but it should counterbalance
the negative tachyons in Nora's cells.
Here you go, Billy Pilgrim.
Consider yourself unstuck in time.
So I can run home now?
Or...
maybe we hit pause on this thing.
You want Nora to stay?
Um, yeah, I thought getting her home was our priority.
No, it is, I just--
now, I'm thinking that maybe we should make sure
her powers are working correctly
before we send her home.
And what about the timeline?
It's risky, but I don't know.
I mean, Wally and I were talking about it.
Yeah, the Legends have a theory.
Uh, there are some historical events that are soft.
Basically, you change those,
it's not going to affect much else,
like catching Gridlock late.
And then, there are those that are fixed.
You mess with them, and all sorts of craziness starts to happen.
Like the night my mom died.
Changing that created Flashpoint.
It looks like Nora is gonna need a place to stay.
Uh, yes, and I'll stay in the lounge.
What lounge?
This lounge.
- Damn. - Dad.
- You found my spot. - You knew about this?
I've been napping in here since day one.
Uh, well, Nora was gonna stay here,
if that's all right with you.
Okay, well,
now I can get to know my granddaughter.
I'm sorry, you met Elvis?
Met him?
Uncle Wally fought the ghost of his twin brother.
I, uh--I went to a monastery,
and I was trying to find myself,
but I was really close.
Then, the Legends came, they swooped me up,
and life got even more crazy.
You want to go back, don't you?
I can't. I mean, I just got here.
I don't want to leave the team. I don't want to leave you.
Wally, everybody in this room loves you, especially me.
But you didn't finish what you set out to do,
and nobody's gonna get in your way.
So promise me, when you find what you're looking for,
come back, or you're gonna have
a very angry-looking dad in your zen garden.
Will you take care of him, XS?
You got it, Kid Flash.
You okay?
Yeah.
I thought I missed out on my chance to connect with Nora,
but now that she's staying, I get another shot.
If you could have seen her on that plane,
you'd know that you guys are already connected.
Really?
She was fearless, just like you.
- We have a daughter together. - Yeah.
We make a person.
In the end, everything works out.
We get our happy ending.
If Barry can go back in time,
why didn't he stop the Thinker from killing me?
Kidding, I'm kidding.
Guys, I'm kidding.
I realize that could have upset
the delicate balance of the universe.
Besides, if he did that, who knows?
He might have created a timeline where
I died in that particle accelerator explosion.
Wishful thinking.
Kidding. I'm glad you're here,
and I'm glad that we don't have to hold your hand
through the time travel thing; you're figuring it out.
Yeah, well, time travel's not the only mystery I solved.
While you guys were fighting Gridlock,
I was, uh, running this down.
- What's this? - An answer.
And a lot more questions.
It's my father's death certificate.
A friend at county helped me out with that.
The ME who signed off on it, Cameron Mahkent?
He doesn't exist.
So then, this death certificate...
Is a fake.
You should get some rest. You've had a long day.
Ooh, I'll try.
I'm just so excited. Like, literally.
Phasing excited all of the electron clouds in my body.
Well, if you're not tired,
two scoops of cookie dough ice cream sound good right now.
From Happy Harbor?
If that's okay with you.
It is, yeah.
Just, uh, bring me back some mint chip.
My name is Nora West Allen,
and I'm the fastest woman alive.
When I was a child, my father disappeared
in something impossible.
Then I grew up and became the impossible.
Now I'm trying to live up to the legacy he created
so that one day, I'll stop him from ever disappearing.
I'm XS.
How schway is that?
CCPD! Stay where you are.
Freeze, don't move.
Who the hell are you?
Wh--what do you want?
For all of you to die.