- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
- We've got Turtle
locked up in the Pipeline.
All we got to do
is use him to figure out
how to steal Zoom's speed.
- That might take longer
than we thought.
- Why's that?
- Because Turtle's dead.
- You need to figure out
what triggers your vibes.
- Sometimes it's
when I touch something
that belongs to a breacher;
sometimes it just happens.
- There's always a cause.
- We're gonna help you
save Jesse.
- I'm here.
- You want me to leave
everything I have here?
I mean, my life--
- You don't have
a life here anymore.
Zoom is too powerful.
- Close it.
Close it now.
- No!
- Augh!
- Jay's death
was not in vain.
We will meet Zoom again.
And the next time,
I will beat him,
whoever that monster is.
Whoo-hoo-hoo.
Uh, it didn't look this deep
on the map.
- That's 'cause maps are flat.
This is, like,
1,000 feet deep.
- Well, you want to get faster.
Maybe plummeting to your death
is the motivation you need.
- So to reach escape velocity,
you're gonna have
to go...
that fast.
- Well, that fast is impossible.
I can promise you that.
- Ah, "Nothing in life
is promised except death."
- Edgar Allan Poe?
- Kanye West.
- If it makes you feel
any better, Evel Knievel
cleared a line of cars
that was twice this long,
and he didn't even
have superpowers,
unless you count
that sweet-ass ride.
- Do you hear yourself?
- What?
Look,
you're gonna be fine.
I'm 80% sure of it.
- Okay.
- 76.
Like, a strong 72.
I can't stop, Caitlin, help.
- If you don't feel ready,
you probably shouldn't do it.
- Not helpful.
- Look,
Zoom's still out there.
And once I find a way
back to Earth-2,
I have to be faster than him.
And, I mean,
right now--I wasn't even
fast enough to save Jay.
I have to try.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- He's gonna make it.
No!
- Oh, damn.
"Why'd you have to bring
those drones along, Cisco?"
"Oh, I don't know."
You're welcome, everyone.
- Signed projects,
including releases
of solo albums.
Pop music
would never be the same
after Beyoncé left
Destiny's Child.
- Wait,
that doesn't make any sense.
They mean Senator Knowles?
[loud whoosh]
- Scooch.
- What?
So how'd it go?
- Well, he's not a red splat
on the side of a mountain.
- That's our new definition
of success?
- It's one of them.
- So, you didn't make
the canyon jump?
- No.
What else can we try?
- A bigger canyon?
Okay, fine, no more canyons.
- I know I crack this.
I've just been
going about it wrong.
I need to find my leg up.
Have we factored in drag?
Wells, can we rerun
the simulation?
- Let it go for now.
- Zoom's still out there.
He's terrorizing a whole world
full of people, your world.
You know,
I'm not doing this for fun.
- Barry, we've been
working on this all week.
You're tired,
we're tired.
- Yeah,
what we need is some downtime.
Downtime leads
to increased productivity,
ergo we have to have fun.
And the best way
to have fun
is for us to go out
to the club.
Am I right, Team Flash?
Let's get turnt!
No, but seriously,
we need a break.
- You know,
I think Cisco's right,
and if I'm saying
we need a break,
then you know it's serious.
- All right,
let's go out tonight.
- Oh, yeah.
Can I go?
- Over my dead body.
- Look, just 'cause you're stuck
in this lab all day
doesn't mean I should be too.
- Over my rotting corpse.
- Look, what happened to trying
new things, meeting new people?
You said I should start
a life here, right?
And Zoom's over there,
and we're over here,
so there's nothing
to worry about.
- There's always
something to worry about.
- Okay, well, you said Barry
and them are good people
and I should get to know them.
- I did.
- Yeah.
And you know they'll keep
me safe no matter what.
Look, I have a life
to live, Dad,
and whole world to explore.
Please?
- Fine.
But if you're gonna go,
you should take protection.
- Oh, Dad,
I don't need--I don't know
what you thought
I was gonna be doing,
but I...
Oh, right.
I mean, is it necessary?
It's kind of, you know...
- Or I could always build you
an inescapable daughter cube.
- Funny.
You know I'd
get out though, right?
All right, fine.
I'll do it.
Thank you.
[electronic music playing]
♪ ♪
[electronic beeping]
- Oh, God, sorry.
It keeps doing that.
My dad made me wear it.
- Don't worry about it.
It's all good.
- I'm really glad
you came, Jesse,
even though this place
is less than ideal.
- Hey, toast?
To Jay.
- I wonder what Jay would say
if he was here right now.
- "What's a Kamikaze?"
And then you'd spend
ten minutes explaining it.
- And he'd say, "Just kidding.
We have those on Earth-2."
- Yeah, well,
we don't have those, so...
- Eh-eh, I'm sorry,
Miss Underage.
None of us plan on getting
murdered by your father tonight.
- Oh, whatever, he's all talk.
- Mm-hmm.
- Yo, guys, what's up?
- Hey.
- Glad you could make it.
What's up, Wally?
- Hey,
interesting choice of venue.
The tic-tac-toe theme is cool.
- Barry picked it.
- Cisco picked it.
- I--
- For real?
- Yeah, I picked it.
I don't go out much.
It had four stars on Yelp, so...
- Okay, fair enough.
- So who's this?
- This is Wally.
He's my...
foster,
or step--adopted...
My new--this is--
he's my new friend.
This is Jesse.
[electronic beeping]
- Oh, hi.
- Hey.
So, Jesse,
are you new in town?
- Yeah, you could say that.
- Yeah, me too.
Are you from far away?
- Like you wouldn't believe.
[electronic beeping]
Oh, you know what?
Would you just excuse me?
I just need to go powder
my...watch.
- Mm-hmm.
- Hey, so I know
I'm practically your brother,
and I'm, like, half Jay's size,
but you want to dance?
- Sure.
- Come on, let's go.
♪ ♪
- Stupid watch.
All right, buddy,
you have beeped your last beep.
♪ ♪
- Something else rising also,
some dark instinct
about what I would do
to the person
who had taken you,
the things I would do.
[upbeat electronic music
playing]
♪ ♪
- So how's Wally doing?
- Yeah, he's good; he's just
diving into his schoolwork.
- Good.
- Yeah.
I'm glad.
- Oh, God.
- [laughs]
- Promise me
if we ever do get married,
you will not do that dance
at our wedding.
- Oh, I can promise you that.
I mean, not the wedding,
the dancing.
What?
- I don't know;
I just think it's weird
that were married in the future
and on Earth-2.
- I wonder what our married
doppelgangers are doing tonight.
- Probably Earth-2's equivalent
of "Netflix and chill."
[laughter]
- Sounds nice.
I mean, for them.
[intense whooshing]
[people screaming]
- It was The Flash!
- My wallet's gone.
- Someone took my purse.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- [gasping]
Who the hell are you?
- Okay, I got it.
Thanks, man.
Hey.
- Hey, excuse me.
What happened last night?
I know you didn't rob
these people.
- No, I was bored.
Thought I'd have some fun.
- Well, look, whoever did this,
they got everyone
within a ten-block radius
in under six minutes.
You couldn't catch them?
- No, this speedster's
faster than me, I guess.
- Unbelievable.
Hey, babe.
- Hey, so I spoke to that girl
over there.
She snapped a photo
of the red blur.
Look familiar?
- This is not good.
- I know, it looks exactly
like the photo
I took of you last year.
Don't worry,
we'll figure it out.
We always do.
- Hey.
- Oh, it's work.
I've got to go.
Keep me posted, okay?
- Joe, I don't want people
thinking The Flash
is a petty thief.
- Well, we need to get
to work squashing those rumors
before they spread.
- Here it is, people: evidence
that The Flash has gone rogue.
- Couldn't it be the speedster
in the helmet?
- The photo speaks for itself.
No helmet glare, confirming that
this is The Scarlet Speedster.
We're gonna expose him
as a fraud.
McKay, I want you
at the police department
getting any interview you can.
- Okay, on it.
- Williams,
eyewitness encounters.
The people of this city
need to know
what it feels like
to be robbed by a hero.
West, I want you to do a piece
on it from your perspective.
You were there last night.
You've seen him in action.
- Okay, but why would The Flash
need to make off
with a couple of hundred bucks
when he's saved so many lives?
I mean,
he is actually a hero.
- Iris, you're a smart woman.
You can't be that naive.
We live in a city
full of meta-humans
who continually do
whatever they want,
The Flash included.
Write it up,
his journey
from streak to freak,
due on my desk tomorrow.
- So...fun night?
Before all the chaos
broke loose?
- Then I would do anything
to get you back,
including killing a man.
- Tell me I'm not hearing
this right.
- No, that's true.
Zoom had you.
Zoom needed
The Flash's speed.
And it was him or you.
And I was not going
to lose you.
- You know,
you were my hero.
My dad,
the brilliant scientist
who could accomplish anything
he put his mind to.
He taught me I could never
dream too big.
But now...
now you're a killer,
and I barely recognize
you at all.
- Jesse--
- No, no, no.
Don't--
don't worry.
I'm not going far.
- I mean, where did this
speedster even come from?
- I don't know, man.
All I know is that blur
made 60 smackeroos off of me.
Ridiculous.
- Maybe it's another one
of Zoom's henchmen somehow?
- The breaches are closed.
- The only other way to become
a speedster
is from a particle accelerator
explosion.
- Okay,
but then why only
make yourself known now?
You see what I'm saying?
We'd have had to seen them
in action before.
- I'm not saying
it makes sense; I'm just saying
that's the only other way
to become a speedster.
- Actually,
there's another way.
It's called Velocity-9.
- Ooh, that's a sexy-ass name.
What is it?
- It's a speed drug.
Jay took it when you were
on Earth-2
to save the city
from a meta-human.
- What?
How could you not tell me this?
- I promised Jay I wouldn't.
- Jay, what do you--why?
- Because Jay knew
how dangerous this drug is.
I should know, Barry; Snow and I
worked on it together.
- Guys, I have been busting
my butt out there,
pushing myself to the limit,
trying to get better,
trying to be faster,
and you're telling me
that there's been something
this whole time
that could've helped me?
This could've helped me
take down Zoom.
It could have helped
me save Earth-2 Joe, save Jay.
- Jay was sick.
The drug that he took
to regain his speed
was also causing
cellular degeneration.
It was killing him.
I tried to help,
I tried to find a cure,
but in all my experiments,
the effects were just temporary.
The V-9 is deadly.
- Why not tell me this?
Why keep me in the dark?
- Caitlin.
Where am I?
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Are you okay?
- Did you vibe?
- Uh...
[electronic beeping]
Meta-human.
Yeah, social media app
for the win.
Bad Flash is back.
Bad Flash...what?
No.
I'm losing my touch over here.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
He's coming up
on Fifth and Everett.
You can use the alley
to cut him off.
♪ ♪
- A lady speedster?
It only took us two years,
but we finally got one,
a lady speedster.
Hey, here's a question
for you, purely scientific,
was she good-looking?
- You know, I was a little busy
getting my ass handed to me,
so I didn't really notice.
- Right, right, right,
but, you know,
next time, for science?
- Okay, yeah, next time
she punches me in the face,
I'll be sure to get her number.
- There you go.
- But the question remains,
who is she?
- I have no idea.
- We could run her through
the facial recognition.
- She had a mask on.
- What was her suit like?
- Hey.
- Hey, it's a valid question.
- It is, actually.
How was her suit constructed?
- It was good.
It was very good.
It was like mine.
It was made by somebody
who understands the needs
of a speedster.
- So that would be someone
with access to tech and a lab.
- Oh, no.
I'm having a very bad thought.
When I designed V-9,
I was having trouble formatting
the extracellular matrix,
so I called a colleague of mine
at Mercury Labs
for some assistance,
Eliza Harmon.
- She knows how to make
this speed drug?
- No, I followed the protocols
of information
compartmentalization.
I only gave her three
of the eight components
necessary for V-9's structure.
- Okay, so she didn't have
the full recipe.
- Unless she reverse engineered
her own V-9.
- Eliza's a genius,
but that's way
out of character for her.
- Well, it's worth
taking a look.
- I'll go see her.
- Hey, I'm coming too.
- Great.
I'm gonna go train.
- Knock-knock.
- Am I hallucinating,
or is that disgraced
ex-Mercury employee
Caitlin Snow?
- Eliza Harmon,
burning the midnight oil.
Don't you ever take a break?
- Well, you know what they say,
these thiocyanate ions
won't bond themselves.
[laughter]
Hi.
- Hi.
Who is your handsome friend?
- Detective Joe West, ma'am.
- Detective?
What brings you
around these parts?
- Well, that's a funny story.
- You know how there's
a speedster that's been
wreaking havoc on the city?
- Yeah, I heard
The Flash went nuts.
Fame will do it to you.
I guess some people can't handle
the limelight, right?
- Well, we happen to know
it was someone else.
That's why we're here
looking into this.
- Wow, how very "Law & Order"
of you, Caitlin.
- Do you remember that formula
that you were helping me with
a few months ago?
- Yeah, vaguely.
- We think that
it was somehow involved.
- How?
What did you have me working on?
- It's classified,
but let's just say it was
some kind of enhancement,
and we're afraid
that my research was stolen.
- Not from this lab.
Okay, between you and me,
the place is pretty vulnerable.
Ever since that break-in
a few months ago,
some of us think McGee
hasn't sufficiently
stepped up security,
but I kept my research on lock
and destroyed the originals
when it was given back to you.
But hey, you're free to look
around my lab if you want.
- I don't think
that'll be necessary.
- Sorry.
I wish I could be more help.
- It's okay.
It's actually kind of a relief.
Will you call me if
you hear anything, though?
- Of course.
That's what friends are for.
- Thank you.
So what do you think?
- For now,
we take her at her word.
[thunder booming gently]
- West, how's
your article coming?
- Um, great.
I have a source
who knows for a fact
that this speedster
is not The Flash
but an imposter.
- Ah, who's your source?
- I am not at liberty to say.
- Well, if you can't
tell me your source,
I'm running the original story.
- Wait, wait, wait.
You're right;
what's one unnamed source
compared to dozens
of eyewitnesses?
Honestly, I'm just--
I'm having a hard time
wrapping my head around
your vision for the story.
Something isn't adding up.
How about we talk
about it some more?
Grab some coffee?
What you say?
- Coffee? Right now?
- Yeah, yeah.
I mean, a little caffeine
never hurt anybody, right?
- Sure.
- I'm so tired.
- Oh, well, you've been
pushing yourself too hard.
- No, not hard enough.
I'm sick of always being
passed over
for the grant,
for the promotion.
I'm underpaid
and understaffed
and six months behind
on my research.
That's why I started
all of this.
- Your problem is you're
too much of a perfectionist.
You don't have to be.
There's beauty in chaos.
- I don't have time for chaos.
This was supposed
to fix things,
and it ended up making it worse.
- Oh, silly girl.
You know it makes
you feel better
to blow off some steam.
- You will say anything
for a fix.
It's your fault
we're hooked.
- It's Caitlin's fault;
if she didn't want us
to find out
what she was working on,
she shouldn't have made
it so damn easy.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- There's not enough
for both of us.
We--we need to save it
for an emergency.
- You take it now; worry
about getting more later.
You'll thank me.
♪ ♪
I know what's
best for us
and where to get more.
- Whatcha doing?
- Training.
- Training?
Allen,
don't be stupid.
I know you took
the V-9, Allen.
- No I haven't.
- Oh, no?
- No.
I took it,
but I haven't taken it yet.
- Good.
- Tell me why I shouldn't.
- Figure it out.
- If the game
is already rigged,
why can't I level
the playing field?
I mean,
if everybody else is cheating,
how can--
I want to be fast enough
to stop Zoom
and any speedster
that tries to hurt my friends.
Shouldn't I use everything
in my power to do that?
- You want to take
a shortcut; is that right?
You want to take a shortcut?
Remember this.
You lose a chunk
of your humanity
every time you compromise
your values.
- [laughs]
Sorry, that's really good
coming from you.
- So don't be like me.
Be better.
Be like Jay.
[glass shattering]
- Are you okay?
- Oh, yeah, I'm fine.
- Hey, any luck
locating our speedster
since Eliza checked out?
- I'm still working on it,
but...
[electrical zapping]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Hey!
- [laughs]
Time to have some fun.
- Hey! Cisco!
Hey, Joe!
Hey, she's got me
in the Pipeline!
[glass shattering]
- What do you want?
- Where's the V-9, Caity?
I need a fix.
- Eliza, is that you?
- Oh,
Eliza's not here right now.
My name is Trajectory.
- Oh, why do the crazy ones
always name themselves?
- Look, Eliza, Velocity-9
is very dangerous, okay?
It made a friend
of mine very sick,
and he already had
the speed force in him.
Look, your cellular system--
- Enough!
You are boring me to death.
Hand over the V.
- I'm a physician.
I took an oath.
I can't give you anything
that will hurt you.
- Right,
so either hand over the V,
or the cat guy gets it.
- Oh!
- Hey, move, now.
- Look, all the flasks are gone.
There's nothing left.
- Hey, I was really hoping
you wouldn't make me do
one of those "I have
to kill you each one by one
until you give me what I want."
Oh, well.
- Wait.
Wait.
You want V-9?
We'll make it for you.
- Dad, you can't.
- We have all the ingredients.
- I'm not a patient person,
so better move fast.
- ♪ Hey, baby ♪
♪ I know we wasn't ready yet ♪
- Ah, latte for me,
and a Flash for you.
Wow, this guy even gets a drink
named after him.
- Yes, he does; he's saved
a lot of people's lives.
They just want
to show their appreciation.
- A little too much,
if you ask me.
- Why can't you see
what everyone else sees?
- A few years back,
I won the Dornfeld Award
for Investigative Reporting
for my story on corruption
in the mayor's office.
I investigated a man
that everyone loved.
The mayor was young,
telegenic, a former war hero.
He was voted in with
overwhelming popular support.
It was...
[chuckles]
But--but I knew that his
campaign was bought and paid for
by the mob.
- Okay, but not everyone
is a corrupt mayor.
- But I saw him for
what everyone else
was too blind to see.
Everyone wants a hero.
- Yeah, but in this case,
The Flash actually is one.
- Iris, Iris, it's our job
to ensure that people,
even heroes,
are held accountable
for their actions.
[chuckles]
- [chuckles]
- So I'm guessing
on your list
of dating pros and cons,
being anti-Flash
is a major dealbreaker.
- Dating pros and...
did you think that this...
- Oh, what?
No, no.
No, forget what I said.
I get it.
You just wanted to talk
about the story some more...
To stall.
[chuckles]
Right,
because you're trying to get out
of writing this article
altogether.
- Scott, wait,
please don't leave.
I'm sorry, I didn't know
that this was...
- Why would you?
Excuse me.
- It's what you wanted.
Now let her go.
- How do I know
the two of you
didn't lace this with a sedative
to put me on my ass?
- We wouldn't do that.
- You can never
be too safe, right?
- No!
- Thanks for the fix, Snow.
- Get Barry.
- Are you okay?
- Well, good job
on the cell, Cisco.
- Jesse.
- What happened?
- Turn her on her side.
- Eliza shot her up with V-9.
- She's going into shock.
It's too pure.
- Stay with me, Jesse.
Stay with me.
- What do we do?
- We've got to get
the V-9 out of her system.
- She needs a blood transfusion.
The new blood will flush
the drug out of her system.
- What blood type is she?
- PZ negative.
- Yeah, that's not a thing
on this Earth, man.
- I'm a match.
- Jesse.
- Hey.
- What happened?
- We--you're fine.
You're--you're gonna be fine.
We got the drug
out of your system.
- Oh.
Looks like you
saved the day again.
- Look, honey,
I know that this isn't enough.
I promise you, though,
I'm going to spend
the rest of my life
making it up to you for the--
for that terrible thing
that I did.
- Yeah?
- Yes.
- And how many
more terrible things
are you gonna do to protect me?
- What does that mean?
- I mean,
everything that you do
and everything
that you have done for me,
it's so dark,
and--and you don't even see it.
I mean, you didn't even
hesitate out there.
- Of course not.
I'm not going
to lose you, Jesse.
- Okay, but you just gave
that crazy speedster
everything she wanted
without even blinking,
without even thinking
what other lives
could be at stake.
- It is my job
to keep you safe,
to protect you;
that's my job.
That's all that matters.
- Well, maybe it shouldn't be.
- Caitlin, I know she was
your friend and all,
but homegirl has gone
cuckoo bird.
- Now she's out there
with more V-9.
- What she doesn't know is,
I put in micro tracker
in the drug.
- Hmm, that's a brilliant idea.
- You can run,
but you can't hide.
- I'm the one
to blame for all this,
so I need to help fix it.
- There's plenty of blame
to go around, Snow.
What's her location?
- Central City bridge.
- Why is she running
back and forth?
- Villains gonna vill.
- She's creating friction,
and at that vibration
and speed...
- What?
- Complete chaos.
She could destroy
that whole bridge.
- And everyone on it.
[all screaming]
[people screaming]
- Guys, this bridge
is coming down.
- Barry, there's about 200
people on that bridge right now.
- You're ruining all my fun.
- Trajectory's too far away.
You won't get to her running
across the river.
- I will if I jump.
- Barry, to make that jump,
you'll need to go Mach 3.3,
but only for a second.
- Okay.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Yeah, buddy!
- It's over, Eliza.
- It is never over.
- Wait, hey!
Stop doing this to yourself.
You don't actually
want to hurt anyone.
- You don't know
anything about me.
- No, I know you're not
a bad person.
This is the V-9
in your system.
I also know what it feels
like to want to be the best.
It makes you feel like
there's not enough time
to accomplish things
the right way,
but it's a cop-out.
And this is killing you.
Look at yourself, Eliza.
You're not well.
- [gasping]
- Let us help you, please.
- That is all the help I need.
How does it feel to know
that I am faster
than you will ever be?
See you around.
- The lightning,
it's turning blue.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [screaming]
- Your article was well-written.
- Thank you.
You know,
it's a lot easier to write
when it's the truth.
Not every hero is a fraud.
It's okay to believe in them.
- So I've been told.
- And sometimes,
even great journalists,
smart and brilliant journalists,
can misread situations.
And sometimes
they can be caught off guard.
Look,
about the other night,
it--it just surprised me.
But once the surprise
went away, I, uh...
Not a dealbreaker.
- Noted.
- Okay.
- Hey, have you seen Jesse?
- No.
- Hey, Dad.
It's me.
Listen, your job
over the years
has been to shield me
from harm.
But now it's my turn to go out
into this new world
on my own, no shield,
and discover
what this Earth can offer.
You know, you are
the best teacher I've ever had,
but I don't know
what more you can teach me.
I love you.
Please,
don't come looking for me.
[beep]
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- So Eliza just evaporated
from running too fast?
- Looks like cellular
degeneration, same as Jay's.
- Jay warned us V-9
was dangerous.
At least now we know why.
- You find Jesse?
- She went out.
- Barry, what is it?
- It's just
right before Eliza disappeared,
her lightning,
it turned blue.
- Right.
What if it's
a side effect of the V-9?
- Yeah, but Jay took Velocity-9,
and his lightning
didn't turn blue.
- About how fast was he running?
- Not as fast as Eliza.
- All right, so what if V-9 is
what turns your lightning blue?
I mean, that would explain why
Zoom is so much faster than me.
- If that's true, then
that means he's sick, right?
- He's dying.
That's why he wants
your speed.
He's dying,
and he needs a cure.
- Same as Jay.
- No.
- Jay? No.
See, he died right
in front of us.
Zoom killed him right
- Cisco, we've seen a speedster
be in two places at once before.
- Then I guess there's
one way to find out.
- I guess now
would be a good time
to tell you all
I've been vibing Zoom.
- What?
You...
for how long?
- It started when we closed
the last breach.
And every time
it's happened,
I've been near that thing.
- [sighs]
[glass shattering]
- We need to know.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, no.
No, no...
- Cisco,
what did you see?
[mournful music]
- I saw Jay.
He's Zoom.
♪ ♪
- Barry!
- [screaming]
- Greg, move your head.