- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at s.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down
the man who killed my mother,
but in doing so I opened up
our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the flash.
Previously on "the flash"...
- Welcome to earth-2.
- I met your doppelganger.
She's a cold-hearted
ice queen
named killer frost.
- The name is vibe.
Reverb.
- My brothers and sisters,
I've brought us
to this new world,
ours for the taking!
[Shouting]
Whose world is this?
[All chanting]
Our world! Our world! Our world!
Our world, our world!
[Gunfire and zapping]
[Dramatic music]
¶ ¶
- reloading!
- Ah!
[Groans]
- David!
- [Groaning]
- Back door!
Captain's down.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
[Thudding]
[Tires screech]
- Down, down!
Down, get down!
[Whooshing]
[Gunfire, screaming stops]
- Some people are calling
it the metapocalypse,
the days when central city
was overrun by an army
with powers beyond
imagination.
But in these dark times,
we must never forget
our own strength,
our own power to fight back.
[Keys clatter]
That it is only
in the blackest of nights
that we can truly
see the light...
And know for sure
we are not alone.
We are never...Ever...
Alone.
- We usually take these guys
down one at a time,
not 100 at a time.
- And yet, you don't
seem overwhelmed.
- I know we can do it.
- Guys.
You have to come see this.
- Cisco, what are you...
Caitlin?
- [Sighs]
She's in shock.
A little...
Dehydrated and malnourished,
but I think
she'll be fine.
- I'm okay.
- What happened?
How did you get away?
- He...
Let me go.
I didn't think he would;
I thought it was a trap.
But...
He told me you were dead.
- I'm not.
I'm right here.
We're all here,
together.
Snow.
- Jay's not here.
- You're safe.
- He's gonna overrun the city.
You can't stop him.
- Yes, we can.
Listen to me,
he's not going to succeed.
We've got this.
This is our earth.
- You don't know that.
You don't know
what he is capable of.
- I know from
being in the speed force
that the universe
is with us, not zoom.
And if the universe is with us,
how could we possibly lose?
Right, guys?
- Yeah,
yeah, right.
- You've been through a lot.
You should get some rest,
come on.
- You were in
the speed force?
- I...When you were gone.
It's hard to explain, but we
tried to get my powers back
and when the dark matter
lightning...
- Okay,
I'm gonna say it.
Um, we don't think he's being
just a little too--
- overconfident?
Yeah, maybe it was
his time in the speed force.
I mean, he's acting like he's
invincible now or something.
- Yeah, like nothing fazes
him anymore, which isn't--
- realistic, no.
Somebody needs to talk to him
before letting his guard down
gets him hurt or worse.
- He did bring me
out of my coma.
That's bound to make someone
a little overly chipper.
- Well, like I said,
somebody needs to talk to him.
- Amazing job, anupam.
This is exactly the kind of
groundbreaking thinking
I built this company for.
Well done.
[Foreboding music]
¶ ¶
[sonic wail]
[Dramatic music pounds]
¶ ¶
[overlapping chatter]
- Everyone, evacuate!
Now!
[Women screaming]
Hurry!
[Screaming, objects crashing]
- Hey.
- She's out
like a light, huh?
- Yeah.
Jay really did
a number on her.
- It's not like he
exactly used kid gloves
on the rest of us.
- She'll be okay.
She just needs time.
And for us to
finally bring zoom down.
Which we will.
- Yeah, because
the universe is with us, right?
Listen, man...
[Dramatic music pounds]
[Birds chirping]
[Eerie music]
¶ ¶
- cisco?
Hey.
You okay?
You just vibe?
- Yeah.
- What'd you see?
- I saw a bird.
Like, a dead bird.
[Alert beeping]
- Mercury labs.
- It's under attack.
- All right.
[People shouting]
[Boom]
¶ ¶
- thank you, Mr. Allen.
I'm not stupid.
- [Small laugh]
- Boom.
- So how did you know?
- Your real identity?
- Yeah.
- Come on, Barry,
I'm a scientist.
We're paid to be
perceptive.
And you're always a little
too well informed
when things go pear-shaped
in this city.
But I don't believe
we've ever met before.
Dr. Christina McGee.
- Doctor Henry Allen.
I'm Barry's father.
- Okay, now that
the cat's out of the bag,
did you happen to see
who it was
that cause your building
to collapse?
- I didn't see anything.
It happened so fast.
- Maybe the security cameras
caught something?
- Can we access them?
- Mercury labs does have a
crash-survivable memory unit.
- A what?
- Virtually
a black box for buildings.
It will have stored
all the security footage
right up until
the building collapsed.
- Okay, great,
I'll go find it.
This wasn't some
random meta-human.
Whenever Mercury labs
has been targeted
in the past there's always
been a specific reason.
- Yeah, someone's
after something.
- Yes, and that someone
is probably zoom.
- There may be
one more possibility.
A few months ago,
i saw Harrison Wells
running out
of my facility.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I'm certain it was him.
Is there any way he could
have anything to do with this?
- A few months ago?
Sure.
Now?
No.
- Yeah, there are a few
more things that we could
catch you up on, Dr. McGee.
- Hey, my purse!
[Engine revs]
- That ain't yours, punk.
- Big mistake.
You picked a bad time
to play hero.
[Dramatic music builds]
¶ ¶
[groaning]
- Dad?
- Wally.
What the hell
were you doing?
- That guy just jacked
a bunch of people
so I had to
go after him.
- You could have
got yourself killed!
- I'm not just gonna let
these guys get away with this.
I have to do something.
- Wally, these are not
just guys!
These are meta-humans!
Leaves this to the cops
and the flash.
- The flash can't
be everywhere at once.
I--i have to
do what I can to help.
I have to show him
i was worth being saved.
- Wally...
You are...Worth it.
- Really?
Am I?
'Cause last time I checked,
I'm the guy who avoided
his dying mother
for weeks.
I'm the guy who shamed
a bunch of other guys
and illegally took
their cars from them.
I'm the guy who caused the flash
to lose his powers and start
this whole damn "metapocalypse"
in the first place.
- Wally--
- last time I checked,
I've a whole lot
to make up for.
That's what
i intend to do.
[Somber music]
¶ ¶
- damn it.
- Snow.
- Oh.
I didn't know
you were here.
- What you doing?
- Uh--Jesse asked me
to run some tests
to see if her genetic structure
had changed.
- Why did you ask Dr. snow...
To run tests on you again?
- Because I got hit
with a dark matter, okay?
I mean, that must have
affected me somehow.
[Pensive music]
¶ ¶
- you're not a meta-human.
What you are
is a young woman
with a genius-level IQ
that we could use
in our fight against
this new wave of meta-humans.
- Okay.
All right, fine.
- Fine.
[Dramatic sting]
- [Gasps]
- Snow?
You all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
[Whooshing]
- Is this it?
- That's the one.
- All right, great.
Dad, Dr. McGee, cisco.
Why don't you guys
crack this open,
see what you can find?
- Sure.
- We'll go see what kind
of meta-human powers
can take down a building
like that and how to stop it.
- Great.
- Sounds like fun.
- All right, I'm gonna go see
if Joe needs any help
in the streets.
Everybody cool here?
Should be
a piece of cake, right?
- Hey, slugger!
- Hey.
- Can I talk to you
for a minute?
- Yeah, sure.
What's up?
- Well, I know
you said that
what happened to you
in the speed force
changed the way
you see things,
but you seem very optimistic,
you know, with a lot
of meta-humans running around
tearing up the city.
What, did you see
the future in there?
- [Laughs]
No--um--
not this time.
No--i--look--
what I was shown
in the speed force
didn't just
change my mind,
it changed me.
I don't know--
what you're seeing as optimism
is, for the first time,
I'm just not afraid anymore.
- Great, that's--
but...
You know you still
have to be careful, right?
- What do you mean?
- Well...
- I don't--why are
you trying to
take something from me
that I fought so hard to get to?
- Barry!
- I--you--you don't know
everything that
I've been through, dad.
You haven't been here
long enough to know.
I didn't mean--
I'm sorry.
I don't know
why I said that.
- I think I do.
Hadn't been around.
Teach you how to drive
or take you to look at colleges.
But I've done everything
in my power
to know who you are.
Barry, I don't want to
take anything from you.
I believe in you.
This isn't about my
not believing in you.
- I know that.
And I'm fine.
Okay?
Thank you,
thank you very much
for worrying about me.
I love you.
But I'm fine.
[Alert beeping]
Come on.
What is that?
- It's ccpd.
- Zoom.
- Barry.
Don't do it.
[Whoosh]
¶ ¶
- you know, I never saw
the crime photos
of my mother's murder.
Well, I guess
i didn't need to.
I have a ringside seat
while you got whisked away.
Too delicate, I suppose.
[Foreboding music]
Not just a hologram after all,
are you, flash?
Interesting.
- I know you didn't
call me up here just to banter.
Let's finish this.
Right now.
- Actually, I did.
I called you up here to
tell you you can't keep running
from one meta
to the next.
Around and around,
like a dog
chasing its tail.
- I'll do whatever
it takes to stop you.
- If only that
were good enough.
'Cause here's the thing.
I know you.
I know you, I know
what's holding you back.
You and me...
We're really just
the same person.
- [Scoffs]
Yeah, you keep
saying that,
but it's not gonna
make it true.
- You'll see.
We are.
Same tragic background.
Same reason for running.
Same desire to be the fastest,
to be the best.
The difference?
You think your anger
is dirty somehow.
You want to be
seen as pure, the hero.
Doesn't it get
exhausting?
exhausting, Barry!
It was exhausting
playing Jay, believe me.
- I'm not pretending.
[Electricity crackles]
[Rumbling]
- Now if it were me,
I'd let that building tumble
without a second thought.
But you,
you'll never let
that happen, will you?
That's why I'm
gonna beat you, Barry.
Because you always
have to be the hero.
And while you're
playing the good little boy...
[Dramatic music builds]
I'll be busy winning.
- We can't let zoom
destroy another building.
We need to
take him down.
Now.
- How do you propose
we do that
with an army of meta-humans
laying waste to central city?
We couldn't stop zoom
on my earth.
What makes us different?
- We're a team.
We start with the meta-humans,
they're his armor.
We take them down first,
then zoom's more vulnerable.
- Barry,
we don't even know
how many of his
minions there are.
- There could be hundreds,
a thousand.
- And all of them, they're all
working with different powers.
- It could take weeks
to track them all down.
- Guys,
we don't have weeks.
So what we
need do to is
come up with a way
to stop them all at once.
- Again:
How?
- Cisco,
your goggles,
your camera,
they didn't work
on earth-2, right?
- Yeah, it was a whole
different frequency.
- And the way you
took down the time wraiths,
that was
based on frequency.
Hartley's entire shtick...
- I think I'm smelling
what you're stepping in.
- Yeah.
- So basically,
we create some
vibrational tech
that can take down
the earth-2 metas.
- Basically.
- Oh, I gotcha.
- Me too.
- I'll help.
- Okay.
- I'll let you know
if I hear anything from ccpn.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- You guys...
We got this.
[Subtle uplifting music]
¶ ¶
- barr, can i
talk to you for a second?
- Yeah.
[Eerie music]
¶ ¶
[thumping]
[dramatic music oscillates]
- Birds.
Why?
It's like a Hitchcock
movie in my head.
- What's up?
- Man, it's Wally.
- Is he okay?
- Not really.
Earlier, he thought
it would be a good idea
if he used himself
as bait against
a meta-human psycho.
Thought he could
do things
the way the flash would.
- Joe, I mean, he--
he did tell me that
he wasn't gonna waste the
opportunity the flash gave him.
I don't know if
you can stop him.
- I'm gonna have to or
he's gonna get himself killed.
Look, he ain't you, Barry.
He can't just go mach 50--
- mach 50 isn't a real thing.
- The point is
thinking you're invincible
isn't any kind of armor.
Wally's already at a higher risk
than I'm comfortable with,
and him throwing caution to the
wind on top of all that?
No.
We got to
keep him safe.
So...In the flash,
talk to him.
Again.
- Yeah, I'll talk to him.
I'll try, I promise.
- Yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
- Thank you.
[Somber music]
¶ ¶
- I thought
throwing things was
Harry's preferred method
of dealing with stress.
- That is how
frustrated I am right now.
I'm--just running
out of ideas as to how
to make this work.
Where's Barry?
I need a taste of that
"walking on sunshine" thing
he's got going
on right now.
- [Gasps]
No...No!
[Whimpers]
- Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's me, okay?
Breathe.
You're okay, all right?
You're shaking.
- I--i thought I saw him--
zoom--
I thought I saw him
right there.
- It's just me,
okay?
Look at me,
he's not here.
He's not here.
- I see him everywhere.
- Look, you literally
just escaped a psychopath
who kidnapped you, all right,
so I think it's normal
for you to have
a severe reaction
like this.
- This is so much
worse than that.
I--I'm afraid
all the time.
I don't think I can
ever move forward.
- You will.
- When?
Jay took everything
from me.
My confidence, my trust,
my sanity.
I don't think I'll
ever be whole again.
- Of course you will.
I promise.
[Indistinct radio chatter]
- Stealing is illegal,
you know.
Detective west
tells me that you've been
fighting zoom's army
on your own.
- Yeah.
I want to help.
- I admire
what you're trying to do,
but the best way to help
is to just
leave this to the police.
- Like you did.
- I do have powers, Wally.
It is a little different.
This isn't your fight.
It's mine.
- No,
it's all of ours.
This is my city
too now.
It's up to all of us
to protect it.
[Sentimental music]
- Barry, we got
a major meta-human alert
at 5th and main--
get there.
- 5th and main.
Got it.
We'll continue this later.
[Whoosh]
[Epic music]
¶ ¶
- [sighs]
Why is it always
so difficult to choose?
- Barry, what it is?
- It's--
Laurel Lance.
[Dramatic music swells]
¶ ¶
- Laurel.
- [Chuckles]
Laurel Lance is dead.
On this earth, anyway.
Poor black canary.
Bye-bye, birdy.
- Earth-2 Laurel.
- You knew her
doppelganger?
- We didn't just
know her, we loved her.
- So...
What do I call you?
- You can call me
black siren.
Zoom mentioned that
you might be showing up.
- If he told you
what I can do,
you should look
more afraid.
- And so should you.
- Tell me,
why did you
take down Mercury labs?
- Because I like to
watch things crumble and fall.
Guess what.
You're next, red.
[Sonic wail]
[Dramatic music]
¶ ¶
- [groans]
- You okay, Barry?
- [Sighs]
Look.
Anything over 200 decibels
will kill a human.
- [Groaning]
- Was that too loud?
Perhaps we should
quiet things down a bit.
- [Grunting]
[Blows landing]
[Groaning]
- [Groans]
- You know,
the sad thing is,
I think zoom's actually
afraid of you.
And I didn't think that
he feared anything.
[Chuckles]
And you, you're
hardly worth the chills.
How many metas did he send
to try and kill you?
Well, it's too bad.
He should have
just sent me
because that way,
you would have
already been--
[tires screeching]
- Get in.
[Heroic music swells]
¶ ¶
[engine revving]
- thought you might
need a lift.
- Yeah.
Thanks.
- You're welcome.
- Why do so many villains
that we go against
use sound as a weapon?
- What?
- [Laughs] Nothing.
You're gonna be fine.
- Thanks.
- So Wally just drove on up
into the thick of it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Must have been some
conversation you two had,
seeing as though he did
literally the opposite
of what we wanted.
- This I can hear.
- It's not funny.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm in
no laughing mood.
- Look, Joe, I tried.
I told you I would try, right?
I--
Wally's a determined kid.
- Yeah, determined
to get himself killed.
- Or determined to
help people.
And be glad,
or you know,
I would not be
standing here right now.
- Well, he was
lucky tonight.
I don't want to see
the day when he isn't.
- We've got more than
luck on our side, Joe.
- You know you're
not invincible, right?
- Yes, of course,
i know this.
[Sighs]
Joe's being
overprotective,
but I get it.
- Yeah, but it's like
you think that
nothing can touch you.
Like nothing bad
can get in your way.
That's not true
for any of us.
- What are you saying?
- Look,
I know that you had an
experience in the speed force.
And I'm happy that you think
we're gonna win the day.
But I think a little fear
can be a healthy thing.
It helps you determine
which risks are worth taking.
I think that's
something for both
you and Wally
to take to heart.
[Somber music]
¶ ¶
- I met your
little red friend tonight.
Aren't you going
to ask me if I killed him?
- You didn't.
You're good
but not that good.
- And yet I seem to be
the only one
of your top lieutenants
still standing.
- Like I said,
you're good.
So why don't you go
knock down a few more buildings?
Like I ordered.
- What's the point?
- The point is so that
it seems random.
That way the flash
and his merry band won't
realize what I'm up to
till it's too late.
- What are you up to?
- No good.
[Foreboding music]
- Ow.
- Sorry.
- Ow!
- There we go.
- Are you kidding me
with this?
- Hey, at least it works.
- Tremendous.
- What is it exactly?
- It's just a small
source of joy,
but more importantly, it's how
we're gonna stop zoom's army.
- By giving them all
electroshock therapy?
dimensional shock therapy.
- This is where I play stupid
and you explain science.
- Okay.
Fair enough.
So all matter vibrates at
its own unique frequency, right?
You disrupt that frequency,
you disrupt the matter.
- Like how an opera singer
shatters glass with her voice.
- Exactly.
So we found out that
all earth-2 people
vibrate at their own,
more erratic frequency.
- Higher frequency.
- Different frequency.
- Higher.
- Higher frequency than we do.
- Right.
- So I ran this all
past hartley, right?
And he postulated that
we could create a sort of
dimensional tuning fork--
voilà--
- okay, you didn't
do it yourself.
- Just let me
have this one, okay?
- Have it, have it.
- Thank you.
So if you run around
the city
fast enough to create a
refracting field,
the device can send out
a pulse
that'll bounce off of it,
split apart,
and collide with itself
over and over.
- Amplifying it to an erratic
frequency on the earth-2...
- Higher. Higher frequency.
- Higher frequency
on the earth-2 spectrum.
- And when that pulse
hits anyone from earth-2--
- it'll disrupt
their nervous system.
- Earth-2 metas
go night-night.
- Even zoom?
- Even zoom.
- Harry and Jesse
are from earth-2.
How do we keep the
pulse from hurting them?
- Oh, detective,
i didn't know you cared.
- Yes you did.
- Uh, we designed
these headphones
to protect us
from the pulse.
- Beats by Wells.
- [Laughs]
[Alert beeping]
- Cisco, it's your
meta-human alert app.
- That's the high-rise
development on the West Side.
- Hundreds of people
live there.
- Ramon, we're up.
Let's go.
Set that pulse off right now.
Allen, you need to start
generating that refracting field
right now.
- But black siren can take down
this building at any point.
Wha--all those people, Wells.
- How many more people
are gonna die while we wait?
- Guys, which is it?
- I think I just got
the worst idea of all time.
[Ominous music]
¶ ¶
- I don't think I've taken down
so many buildings at once.
- Maybe you're not as powerful
as you think!
[Dramatic music]
¶ ¶
- what are you two
doing here?
- Why should you
have all the fun?
[Dramatic music]
- I thought you two
were dead.
- Zoom thinks that too.
And we'd like to
keep it that way.
- For now.
- You think you two
can pull one over on zoom?
Well, enjoy being dead.
- I told you.
- Give her a chance.
- What chance?
- She's not ready.
- Excuse me.
Do you know
what I'm capable of doing?
- Try it, and I'll
shatter your entire
nervous system
without breaking a sweat.
- Wow, you really think
you can take on zoom.
- We can.
You don't even know
how powerful you are.
With a single call,
you can take down a building.
I'd call that impressive.
But why...Stop...
There?
Why serve a master
when you can be a master,
when you can be a God?
We...Could be gods.
[Dramatic music swells]
- All right!
- All right.
We're synced up with
whatever
the heck that thing is.
- Finally something
we're both baffled by.
- I'm kidding.
That, my friend,
is a 75ktsb 40,000-watt
reverberating sound amplifier
designed to single out
the operating frequency
of every single earth-2 being
on this planet--
which, went contained
and magnified
by the flash
creating a sound pressure wall
around the city,
will render all of us
earth-2 beings unconscious.
Hence...
The safety precautions.
- I'm baffled by it.
- [Laughs]
Are we ready?
- Yes, we are.
- All right.
[Device activating]
- Here...We...
Go.
¶ ¶
- if I were interested
in forming an alliance
with you two,
what's your plan?
Exactly?
- We ambush zoom
at ccpd.
With our three powers
combined,
he'll be no match
for us.
- Hmm.
Well, I like
the sound of that.
- Great.
Then let's go.
- There's just
one more thing.
Reverb...Catch.
You know,
all doppelgangers--
they're mirror images
of themselves.
But you two,
you didn't know that, did you?
- Reverb is left-handed.
- Well, I just--
i just happened to--
catch it with my right--
run!
[Dramatic music]
¶ ¶
- oh, no.
What are we
gonna do?
- I don't think that
there's anything you can do.
- What the what?
- I don't know.
- Well, do it again!
- [Panting]
- Cisco...
[Alert beeps]
- We're a go.
[Frequency amplifying]
- There's nothing
on this earth
that can stop us!
[Frequency wailing]
- It's working.
- [Groans]
- Yaaaahh!
- Dad?
Dad, it hurts.
[Whimpering]
No--no--stop--
- it's okay.
- No...
- It's okay, honey.
[Dramatic music flourishing]
¶ ¶
- turn it off!
Turn it off, it worked!
[Sound stops]
- It's okay, it's okay,
we'll take care of him.
It's okay, Jesse.
He's gonna be okay.
- Barry.
We did it.
Bring them all in.
- Copy that.
I'm on clean up.
[Inaudible]
- What's that?
I can't--i can't hear you
through the double-paned
soundproof glass.
It's--it's kind of hard
to make out what you're saying.
- So should we tell Sara
and captain Lance about her?
- No, I've seen
what interacting with
your family's doppelgangers
can do.
It's not even Laurel.
- No.
It's just a poor imitation.
Speaking of,
that was a pretty good
killer frost
you did back there.
- Guess I was in
the right head space
to play a cold,
vicious killer.
- How you doing,
are you okay?
- No.
But I think
I'm gonna be.
Being out there
with you guys,
fighting meta-humans,
saving people...
It's the first time
i felt
normal in a long time.
- Come here.
- This is a group hug moment.
- Yeah.
- It is.
[Peaceful music]
¶ ¶
- so all of zoom's
meta-humans
are locked up
in iron heights?
- Most of them.
Some are somewhere else.
- I don't want to know.
- No you don't.
- And zoom?
[Whoosh]
- The metas we spoke to
said zoom
created a breach
and escaped.
- And how did he
do that again?
- Who knows,
but he's back on earth-2 now.
- Earth-2?
That something else
i don't want to know about?
Both: No.
- All right.
Well, flash, thanks.
The man who saved
central city once again.
- No, we're all
just part of the same team.
- Speaking of teams,
where the hell is Allen?
- Ooh--sorry, man,
sorry--hey.
Heard my name.
Uh, what's up?
- Good, well, you've got
about 100 meta criminal cases
to get through, so I would get
to cracking if I were you.
- I will get
right on that.
- Captain.
[Snickers] Well done.
- Thanks.
Listen, uh,
I've been thinking
about Wally some more.
- Are you gonna
talk to him again?
- No, I'm not.
- Why not?
- Because he's your son,
Joe.
- I know he's my son.
- I--look--what I mean is
he's got your values.
He's got your inner drive
to help people do what's right.
We're supposed to think
we're something we're not
until we become that thing.
That's the path
that Wally's on.
I'm not gonna stop him
from being the hero
that he's gonna become.
I really don't think
you should either.
[Subtle uplifting music]
- I can't wait till you have
kids and they torture you.
I'ma laugh in your face.
- [Laughs]
All right, gramps.
- Poppa.
- What?
- My grandkids are
gonna call me "poppa".
- [Laughs]
All right.
- ¶ Ah ah ¶
¶ when I was young ¶
- what in the world?
What is this?
- Blame iris.
- Okay.
I just figured that since Henry
is officially back for good,
we should celebrate.
And since zoom is gone
and the city is quiet right now.
- Oh, I appreciate it,
iris.
Thank you.
Hi, Tina.
- Hello, Henry.
- Jesse.
- Hi.
- Good to see you.
- Good to see you too.
You look...Great.
- Thank you.
- I hope you don't mind
that I invited Dr. McGee.
- Seems like
somebody's glad you did.
- Mm-hmm.
So I guess
you are invincible.
- Told you.
- [Chuckles]
- The speed force
is with us.
Since I'm
feeling extra invincible
lately,
what do you say
you and I
give this a shot?
- Yeah, I would like that.
¶ ¶
- so is it true?
You saved
the flash's life?
- Oh, I mean, I was
just in the right place
at the right time.
- Proud of you, Wally.
You did good.
- Thanks, dad.
- [Laughs]
- What?
- I'm just--
I'm proud of you too.
- Soup's on.
- Hey!
Taking out a city
full of monsters
makes a man hungry.
- First,
a toast.
To family.
All: To family.
- That's my kind of toast,
short and sweet.
Let's eat.
- [Laughs]
[Dramatic music oscillates]
- Oh.
You guys.
Great.
[Overlapping screams]
Earth-2.
[Epic music]
¶ ¶
[dramatic music oscillates]
- Cisco?
What--what is it?
What'd you see?
- What do you mean "see"?
- Cisco gets visions.
- I don't understand.
- What cisco?
- Earth-2
splitting in half.
Straight down to the poles.
Tell me I didn't just
vibe the future.
Please tell me
i did not
just see
the end of the world!
[Foreboding music pounds]
¶ ¶
- our story continues,
flash.
- Henry!
- Oh, my God.
[Dramatic violin music]
¶ ¶
- dad?
Dad?
- It's poetic, returning
to your childhood home.
- Jay.
Don't do this.
I'm begging you.
I'm begging you!
Take me.
Kill me!
- No!
- You still won't believe me
that you and I are the same.
- Come on.
- Barry, look at me, son.
- So I'm gonna have to
make you believe me.
- Whatever happens
you have made me
the happiest father...
- Dad--
- this time, you're gonna
watch your parent die
just like I did.
- No, no!
- And this
is what's gonna make you
just like me!
- Your mother and I love--
- Jay!
- [Groans]
- No!
[Epic music flourishes]
- Greg,
move your head.