My God, Orlin.
You scared the living daylights out of me.
Did anyone follow you?
Of course not.
It's been weeks since you fought the Flash at the hospital.
If anyone knew you were here,
you would have found out by now.
I got you some groceries
and some Meloxicam for your injuries.
I don't need it.
Good to hear.
- How's Grace? - Nothing's changed.
She's stable. CCPD hasn't left
and they're not leaving any time soon.
- Well, I need to see her, Doc. - That's not possible.
Don't tell me what's possible.
You're angry. Good.
For all the pain your family has suffered
at the hands of those metas, you should be.
But right now there isn't anything you can do for Grace,
so put that anger towards something else.
I have a friend who feels the same way
about meta-humans as we do,
and he wants to help you finish what you've started.
Orlin?
It's time to get back to work.
This is it. The only thing between us
and our big score is one reinforced concrete wall.
Don't hurt yourself, Bork. - Can't hurt Bork.
But Bork can hurt you.
That should do it.
The hell?
You're one, too.
I don't know what's crazier, how big this guy is
or the number of incised wounds on his body.
Well, and the depressed skull fracture points to impact
with hardened surface,
but cause of death is definitely repeated stabbings.
Yeah, looks like someone was really angry.
Look at these wounds.
Doesn't it look like they have the same depth and diameter
as the ones on Gridlock's body?
Yeah, and like Block's and Raelene Sharp's.
Yeah.
Iris just got a tip.
Another meta-human was murdered in her apartment, same COD.
- Dad, these aren't one offs. - No.
Cicada's back and he's on a killing spree.
Okay, well, there's got to be a lead in one of these attacks
that can help us track him. We'll get the team on it.
Killer Frost, seriously? I can't take it anymore.
Uh, Caitlin, is everything-
Alter-ego confab.
Seen enough episodes of "Sister, Sister"
to recognize a sibling spat when I see one.
So, I'm trying to help Cisco with his meta-human cure,
but every time I start working on it,
Killer Frost takes over and messes with my equations.
Like this.
She changed all my heterozygotes into asterisks.
Oh, I thought those were just tiny snowflakes.
So she's not on board?
No, and I don't exactly know why.
- Can't you just ask her? - Oh, I've tried.
But every time we start talking about it,
she starts singing Barney's "I Love You" song.
- Ooh, that's cold. - Yeah.
What about Cisco? Is he having any luck?
Not yet.
He went to the Tannhauser off-sites so he could concentrate.
He says it's quiet there.
Yeah. Quiet like a tomb.
So I think if I can isolate the genetic marker
that bonds human DNA to dark matter,
I can reverse engineer the process
and unravel it to create a cure.
- That's great. - Yeah, except I need meta-DNA
that hasn't fully bonded with dark matter yet.
Of course, because as we all know
with genetic modification we-- Why?
Because that's the only time when I can identify
where the marker is in the genome.
Okay, so you need DNA from a meta-human who was created recently?
Yeah, ideally in the last eight months,
but everyone I can think of has been killed by Cicada.
Right.
So where the heck do we look?
The lone decrypted entry from the journal of Nora West Allen:
"The timeline is malleable."
Why that's the only one that translated?
And why is she interested in the timeline,
and maybe more important,
why is she hiding this interest?
Sherloque, we need you in the cortex.
But of course.
Kira May, Dwayne Geist, Carl Bork.
All three metas who were killed by Cicada last night.
So Cicada's killed almost as many people
in the last 12 hours as he has in the last eight months?
And it doesn't look like he's slowing down anytime soon.
Well, we need to stop him before he hurts anyone else.
Sherloque, do you have any ideas on what to do about that?
Not at the moment,
but any time I run into a road block in an investigation,
I do what I always do.
I just pursue a different avenue.
We'll find him. Something will bring him to us.
Something like--
Satellites picking up dark matter flare. It's him.
Something like that.
Suit up. We don't have a lot of time.
Not without precautions. For Killer Frost.
She doesn't need a weapon. Killer Frost is the weapon.
Powers or no powers, I will mess you up.
Negate this!
Hold on. Help!
We need Caitlin.
We need to get her to a hospital.
Here, come with me.
Oh God.
No!
Nora. Hey, Nora, Nora?
Okay, Nora-- Nora?
Nora?
Well?
Cicada caused an axial burst fracture
in her L3, L4, and L5 vertebrae.
He also severely displaced her fourth thoracic vertebrae.
It's not good.
But her speed healing is going to kick in, right?
Right?
Cicada's cut flooded her body with dark matter.
It's affecting her powers.
Her speed healing should kick in...
for now.
I'll keep monitoring her progress.
- Barry. - It's okay, she'll heal.
It'll be all right.
Nora?
Oh, what happened?
Honey, um...
Oh, why does it hurt to breathe?
It's gonna hurt for a little bit.
Why?
I can't move my legs.
Um, why can't I move my legs?
- Mom, I can't move my legs. - Nora.
Mom? Mom, why can't I move my legs?
Nora, look.
You can't move your legs because...
Cicada broke your back.
What? So I'm paralyzed?
- What, forever? - No, no, not forever.
Well, for how long then?
We don't know.
Mom...
Hey, I got here as fast as I could.
Joe's still in Tibet.
I left him a message to get back ASAP.
Hey, it's all right. He should stay with Wally.
Oh, my God.
- How is she? - It's not good.
I'm so sorry, Barry.
Hey, I don't care how we do it.
- We need to stop Dwyer now. - Well, I agree.
All right, Well, I'm gonna call Cisco.
We should get him back here.
No, no, no, he-he should finish the cure he's working on.
His time is better spent there.
- Sherloque. - Oui?
Earn your money. How do we track this guy?
Well, I think the first thing we should do
is concentrate on the victims. Look for a connection.
Take a look here for example. This man, Geist,
has a spider tattoo on his neck,
generally indicating he was caught in some form of web.
What kind of web? A prison web, perhaps.
And Kira May-She was wearing clothes.
Of course she was wearing clothes, Giraffe.
No, she was wearing clothes that are two sizes too large.
Two sizes too large. Recent rapid weight loss.
It's a common side effect of solitary confinement.
Right. And Carl Borg--
And Carl Borg, this report says he had a droopy eyelid
which is nerve paralysis,
common side effect of consuming too much Borat.
Or as it's known on this earth, Bruno.
More commonly known as prison wine.
Prison wine.
All three of these meta-humans were former criminals.
Look at this.
It's a meta-human arrest log from 2018.
Look at the first three names.
These were his victims.
He's killing in the order of this list.
This list has addresses, employment information.
It's got license plate numbers. This is everything
Cicada needs to find them.
Where would he even get this?
I think there's only one place, right?
There's a killer still at large in our city.
People are afraid of being out in the streets.
I'm getting 100 phone calls a day about this guy.
I want neighborhoods re-canvassed.
I want evidence re-examined. Jonesy!
Take your unit and paper the city with Dwyer's photo.
I want this guy. Let's go get him!
Allen?
We need to talk... in private.
All right.
What the hell is this?
That's how Dwyer's getting his victims.
This is from our database of meta-humans?
Well, it doesn't prove he got it from CCPD.
Doesn't it?
He could have broken into another precinct
or hacked into the CCPD database.
David Dwyer is a machinist. He's not a hacker.
Somebody gave this to him. Somebody here!
Okay, Barry, maybe we should go ahead
and let Captain Singh look into this on his own.
Yeah, I think that's a good idea.
Thank you, David.
Hey, Barry. Barry.
Barry, where are you going?
I don't know, Cecile,
but I gotta do something
before Dwyer kills all the people on that list.
What if we use it, too?
- What? - The list.
Three years ago, Joe asked me to help get meta-humans
transferred out of the city.
Yeah, I remember. You told him not to do it.
Yeah, well, that was before I knew what I know now.
Besides, those metas were active prisoners.
These metas, they've already served their time.
Look, even if we got 'em out of town, it wouldn't matter.
Cicada's gonna track them down eventually.
They need new names, new identities.
We don't have the resources to do that.
No, we do not.
But the Feds do.
They give this kind of protection to regular humans all the time.
It is about time they start offering it to meta-humans, too.
I am going to go call in every favor I have ever banked
and I am going to make this thing happen,
and in the meantime,
you need to go get them somewhere safe.
- All right. - Okay.
So, can you try wiggling your toes?
I can't.
Again?
Anything?
I don't feel anything.
Okay, well, Cicada's dark matter has left your system,
so you should be healing soon.
I mean, since my last scan,
your spinal axons have grown five millimeters.
That's something, right?
It's progress.
Maybe not quite the speed we were hoping for,
but it's something.
I'm going to go run a few more tests.
Don't give up, okay?
Growth is growth.
Normal axon growth rate
reaches five millimeters a day in a large nerve.
With speed healing,
mine should be over 100.
How do you know that?
I took neuro-regeneration in my fifth grade STEM class.
I took fractions in fifth grade.
What if I don't heal, Mom?
What if I never get better?
Can I just be left alone for a little bit, please?
Yeah. Okay.
I respect your right to protest the cure, Frosty,
but even for me, that is excessive.
Well, maybe Caitlin will get the hint now.
Snow and Frost are having creative differences.
I'll get Caitlin.
No, I-I need you, actually.
We need to get all those metas to a safe house
before Cicada finds them.
Oh, and you think they're going to listen to me?
50-50 on that.
I haven't quite lived up to my name.
But I do know where we should start.
Doesn't look like anyone's been here in months.
Maybe the rumors about Amunet skipping town are true.
We're not here for Amunet.
We're here for her pet snake.
And the thing about snakes is,
they're always lurking in some dark corner.
Hello, Norvock.
Frost, thank God it's you.
Those are Cicada's targets,
but we need your help rounding everyone up
so we can get them to safety.
Because they're not going to trust a bunch of masks?
They will if you tell them it's for their own good.
Some of these guys are bad news.
You sure they're worth saving?
Are you? Cicada's not going to stop
until every meta in this city is dead.
Is that how you want to end up?
Damn. What did he do to you?
We've arranged for everyone to enter
a witness protection program.
Federal agents will lead you out of the city to safety tonight.
All right.
I'm in, but only if I'm the first one on that transport.
Nice of you to look out for your fellow metas.
I look out for me and me alone.
Then let's get to rounding up.
Yup.
- David. - If this is about that list...
It is, but it's not what you think.
I need your help.
With what?
I'm having those metas moved to federal protection,
which is where you come in.
What do you need?
Road blocks, tonight, from Linsin to Webber Avenue.
I know, David, I know,
but I can't risk any incoming traffic
during the scheduled transfer.
I'll make it happen.
Thank you.
Officer Jones.
You all right?
Never better.
I'm tired of waiting.
This Cicada, he wants to kill us?
I say we kill him first.
You can't. We're your only chance.
So you keep saying.
Look, if you're too dumb to recognize the truth,
then you can go, but you're on your own.
I'm not going to watch anybody else be broken by this maniac.
He's telling the truth.
I saw Cicada kill Carl Bork.
Bork's dead?
His dagger took away our powers.
I ran, Bork fought.
That's why I'm here and he's not.
So, yeah, leave if you want,
but I'm gonna listen to these guys
and stay alive.
That was quite the speech back there.
Almost seemed like you actually wanted
to save those meta-humans.
No, you know me better than that.
No, I don't think I do.
I used to be a good guy, you know?
I worked at the Central City Zoo, watching the reptile cage.
We were open the night the particle accelerator blew up.
After the blast shattered all the cages,
I had to pull an elapid snake off a kid.
Then that dark matter hit.
What happened to the kid?
He's fine.
But what do I get, huh? A snake in my head?
And a psycho killer that wants me dead?
That was the last time I put anyone else before myself.
You know, it's almost like a small part of me feels
sorry for that guy.
Why? He's only out for himself.
Come on, he's clearly terrified.
I know what that's like.
You're going to tell me that you've never felt fear like that?
- No, why? - Really?
Not even a little bit worried about Caitlin making the cure?
Is that everyone?
Everyone except Shawna Baez.
A meta that calls herself Peek-A-Boo?
Anyone know where she'll be?
Try the Sundollar on Eighth.
All right.
Bar's not open yet. Not even for you, Flash.
Shawna. I need you to come with me.
I didn't do anything this time.
I know. You're not in trouble.
All right, you're in danger.
I want to take you some place safe.
Like your science prison? Sorry.
Shawna? Please.
Somebody is trying to kill you.
Someone's always trying to kill me.
See ya around, Flash.
What did you do to me?
Shawna, run.
Who the hell is that?
Take this, press the button.
When a breach opens, jump into it.
Go!
Come on, come on...
Make this thing work.
They're all terrified. I can feel it.
Maybe now they believe us.
Hey, we're almost through this.
We are going to get all of these people to safety.
Even if we do, Cicada's not going to stop killing.
- Not until-- - Until he's dead.
- I didn't say that. - You didn't have to.
The anger that I feel from you says it all.
How am I supposed to feel? He almost killed Nora.
Barry, I understand, I do.
That man hurt your child.
But this anger that you're feeling,
I have felt it before...
from Cicada.
Honey, if you let it, this rage will consume you,
the same way it's already consumed him.
Wait, I have felt this anger from someone before.
At CCPD. Oh, my God, Barry,
I think I know who leaked the list.
Then let's go get him.
No, no, no, you-- you stay here.
You get these metas to the drop.
I can handle the rest.
Ah, well, look. Neurological delight.
Why, you'll be back on these feet
and chasing Cicada in no time.
I hope so.
Yes. In the meantime, maybe you can help me do the same.
Oh, I already told the team everything I know
about the Flash museum.
Flash museum, right.
Do you think that I could look at the archives
from that Flash museum?
After all, I have made a career
out of noticing things that other people miss.
Maybe it's not a problem to bring those archives
for me to look at?
ah, I guess so.
Or maybe it's easier for me to go there?
You want me to bring you to the future?
It's a great suggestion.
Is it even possible for a non-speedster
to go into the commodity-- What'd you call it? The, um...
- The Speed Force? - Speed Force. Right.
Uh, I'm not sure.
Right.
Well, perhaps that's a question for someone with more experience.
Sherloque.
Can I talk to you for a second?
Excusez-moi.
- That's my daughter in there. - Yes, so?
And I'm going to do whatever it takes to protect her.
Even from people who I thought were her friends.
So I'm gonna need you to tell me right now
why you're investigating Nora.
Invest--no, no. Quoi?
No one's investigating Nora.
Quoi? No one's investigating Nora.
Maybe I'm investigating Nora a little bit.
Why?
You think, what, Nora is hiding something?
No, um...
How can I say this?
Sometimes when you're a detective,
you see a story and you follow it.
And there's different tracks.
You follow down the track.
With Nora, I am following down this track.
Do you know how many stories I've chased
that went absolutely nowhere?
So many that I stopped chasing them for a while
instead of doing what I should have done,
something you suggested, actually,
which is going down a different track.
That track is the wrong one.
Careful with your little monocle.
Learn to take notes like everyone else.
Nora!
Oh, my goodness.
What do you want, Ralph?
I know it's none of my business
why you're afraid of a cure,
but for what it's worth, I'm a meta,
and I'm all for it.
And after talking with most of those people out there...
So are some of them.
Oh, yeah, I can see that.
I just don't understand why.
It might save their lives.
It's not that simple for me.
Why not?
Because, just like Norvock didn't ask for his snake,
Caity didn't ask for me.
So if one day she wakes up scared of being a meta-human
and decides to take that cure,
her powers don't just disappear.
I do too.
That's what I'm really afraid of.
'Cause if I'm gone who's going to protect her?
It's witching hour.
I get why you're scared, but...
you need to know that when DeVoe made you disappear,
all Caitlin talked about was getting you back.
So maybe as much as you want to protect her,
Caitlin wants to protect you, too.
I went after three of them tonight and they weren't there.
Did you tip them off?
No, I swear.
After what that Spencer woman did to me with her meta-tech,
I want them all gone.
- Then what happened? - The D.A.
She figured out you're targeting everyone
on the list I gave you.
The contact of mine with the Feds says they're being picked up
and put into protective custody.
Tonight.
Where?
Boys and girls, your ride's here.
What the hell?
Everybody get back!
Thank you, Flash,
for bringing them all to me.
The chopper's not going to be able to land.
Take everybody out the back and get them on it somehow.
Come on.
No, he's mine.
All right, we're out of the dampening field.
Shawna, can you help?
Every meta for themselves.
What now?
I don't suppose you can run up my arm, can you?
Ralph, what are you planning to do?
Remember, Baby Giraffe,
they took a leap of faith with you.
That's why I'm going to take a leap for them, Shirley.
All right, everybody. Straight line, single file,
tuck your arms in.
- Keep this thing steady. - Roger that.
Stand there!
Tuck your arms.
You can't win this fight.
I bet I can.
We haven't been formally introduced.
They call me Killer Frost. Let me show you why.
Killer Frost, duck!
- You saved me. - You saved them first.
Nice work.
Let's get out of here for real!
Give him hell, Flash!
Okay, you see, the metas are on the move. Bravo.
Something's wrong with Barry.
What?
I've never seen these kind of readings from Barry's suit.
He's channeling over 2.86 billion joules of energy.
That's a combined equivalent of--of almost three lightning bolts.
Cicada's powers allow him to sustain injury
but not that much.
Barry. Barry.
He's not going to stop.
You're never gonna hurt my daughter again!
Dad!
No.
Oh, I'm sorry. I let him get away.
No, you brought me back.
Alright, the Feds have processed Norvock
and the other metas, giving them new identities,
so everybody's safe.
Satellite hasn't registered any unaccounted for dark matter
so, wherever Dwyer is, his dagger's not in use.
Psh, after the beating Barry gave him,
ain't no way he's using that dagger anytime soon.
What? He got what he deserved.
Oh, no, I think we appreciate your groove.
Also I think that Killer Frost and the Flash combination is
enough to maybe have Dwyer
not want to show his face around here any time soon.
Dad, are you okay?
I'm good.
What matters is that you're okay.
How's it feel to be up and running again?
Super frickin' schway.
Uh, wanna know what's not super frickin' schway?
Cicada knowing exactly when and where
our secret transport was taking place.
Mm. Inside job, right?
Cicada clearly has a inside man, only--
Only what kind of cop would help Cicada kill innocent people?
One that's going to have to answer to D.A. Cecile Horton.
Captain, you wanted to see me?
Come on in.
Officer Jones,
this was printed off of your hard drive.
Copy of the list of metas that Cicada's been pursuing.
Funny thing, it is the same list that we know you accessed
on your home computer just this week.
Care to tell me why you decided to aid and abet a murderer?
No, that's not--you don't know what you're talking about.
Really?
A woman used meta-human tech to take control of your mind.
She made you do things that you were certain
you would never do.
And that frightened you, didn't it?
It frightened you and it made you angry,
and you went ahead and you embraced that anger
and you let it drive your every move.
Betrayal. Revenge.
Escape.
The metas in this city have no respect for human life.
They don't deserve to breathe our air.
You swore an oath to protect the citizens of this city.
Every one of them.
Get him out of my sight.
You know, your instincts have always been sharp.
But knowing he was going to try to escape?
Could have swore you were reading Jonesy's mind.
It's a funny thing, yeah.
Since Jenna was born, I've been
a lot more in touch with my feelings.
When Joe gets back,
the two of you will be a force to be reckoned with.
Oh, we already are.
Killer Frost, you shouldn't have.
It's the closest you're getting to an apology from me, so...
Well, maybe that's why I can hear you
without the M.A.D. 2.0.
Or maybe it's because you've stopped hating me.
I didn't hate you.
I thought you were being stupid.
There's a difference.
Hey, you know I'd never take that cure, right?
Even if it means sharing a body with me
until you get old and grey?
Of course.
You're a part of me that I never want to lose.
I promise, I will do everything I can to protect you.
Right back at you, Caity.
Now, don't get all soft on me,
but I got you a little something.
Check the cooler.
Hey, Frosty. Oh, Caitlin.
Is that a ball of ice with blood inside of it?
I think Killer Frost took it from Cicada.
Ralph, this isn't just blood.
This is a DNA sample from a recently created meta-human.
- So Killer Frost came around. - Yeah.
She did.
Ugh, I said don't get soft.
Begin handwriting analysis.
As I suspected, the journal of Nora West Allen
contains two different types of handwriting.
So...
There is a mastermind behind the scenes.
The only question is...
who?
Okay, 47 tacos is officially my limit.
I think that's anyone's limit, honey.
A healing speedster's gotta eat.
Healed, Dad. I'm fine.
I promise.
Hey, uh, dinner again tomorrow night?
- Yeah. - Yeah, Nora? Um...
I just...
just want you to know how much we love you.
See? She's back to her old self.
And so are you.
No, I'm not.
In fact, I don't think I'll ever be the same.
All of this has made me realize that, I don't know,
I just--I never knew I was capable of even caring
for someone as much as I care about Nora.
I did.
I've never met anyone with a bigger heart than you, Barry.
So it's no surprise to me that you are a fantastic father.
Just like you're a fantastic husband.
Cicada's a father, too.
What if the key to defeating him is appealing to his heart?
- How do we do that? - By saving his child.
We need to wake up Grace.