- This season on "the flash"...
- Who are you?
- My name is Jay garrick.
Where I came from,
I was a speedster like you.
Before I arrived on your earth,
I was in a fight
with a man named zoom.
He will do whatever it takes
to ensure
he's the only speedster
in any world.
- Never forget:
I am the fastest man alive.
- I get these feelings
sometimes, these vibes.
- Cisco, what did you see?
- I saw Jay. He's zoom.
- Who's the man
in the iron mask?
- You wouldn't believe me
if I told you.
- What do you say
you and I give this a shot?
- Yeah, I would like that.
- I've always
measured my success
by counting the number
of victims I've had.
But now I think I'm going
to start counting
the number of earths
i conquer instead.
- Earth-2 is splitting in half.
Tell me I did not just see
the end of the world.
- Dad? No. No!
- This is what's gonna make you
just like me.
- Jay?
No!
- No!
Dad?
Dad? Hey!
Hey!
Hey, look at me.
Look at me.
Dad.
Don't leave.
Not again.
Dad!
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
It's all right.
No.
Dad.
no, dad.
- I told you family
was a weakness.
you feel the anger,
don't you, flash?
And now...
The two of us are the same.
- No! No!
- There you go, flash!
Use your anger,
just like I did.
- I got you, zolomon!
- Go on, Barry.
Embrace your anger.
End me!
let me do it for you.
so close, Barry.
- Another time remnant.
- You see, Barry,
there could be two of you.
You just have to be willing
to kill yourself.
Yeah.
You're almost ready.
- and comfort us today
with the word of your promise
as we return our brother
to the earth,
and leave us with the hope
that, one day, we'll meet again.
- um...
My father's...
I can't do this right now.
- it's okay, Barry.
- Henry Allen.
Henry suffered two
great losses in his life.
He lost his wife, Nora,
and he lost Barry.
He suffered guilt,
embarrassment,
ridicule, shame,
and everything that comes
with being blamed for a crime
he didn't commit.
Henry Allen was proof
that love can get you
through the darkest of days,
and that love will keep him
alive in all of our hearts.
- I'm gonna find him, dad.
I promise you I'm gonna take
from him what he took from you.
- hey.
- I thought maybe
you should eat something.
- I'm not hungry.
Thank you, though.
- Yeah.
Barry, um...
I had no idea that
you were the flash.
What you did for me,
all the things that
you've done for everyone,
this whole city...
And now this
with your dad and zoom.
I'm so sorry.
- Thanks, Wally.
- If there's anything
you need,
you just say the word.
- All right.
guys,
zoom's still out there.
We need to come up with a plan.
- The man can crack open
breaches to earth-2.
I mean, if he can do that,
what else can he do
that we don't know about?
- Right after he killed
his time remnant,
he told me I was "almost ready."
- Almost ready for what?
- I don't know.
- Yep. Classic psychopath.
Why can't they ever just say
what they want to do?
We also have to figure out
why I keep vibing earth-2
being ripped to shreds.
- Seriously.
- It's like I'm watching
"transformers" in 4-d,
but, like,
ten times more realistic
and with much better acting.
- Look, if you can vibe
the future,
we need to stop zoom
before that happens.
- I'm gonna get some air,
all right?
- I got it.
- When I was in the speed force,
I felt like
I'd finally come to grips
with her death,
with not saving her
when I went back.
And then the moment...
Where I'm finally
at the place I can move on,
my father's taken from me.
How am I ever supposed
to find peace with that?
- I don't know, Barry,
but you're gonna have
to find a way to do that,
or it's gonna tear you apart.
- I just miss him
so much already.
zoom.
- Barry, no!
- Bad time, flash?
Thought I'd give you
some time to mourn.
- This ends now.
- Not yet.
There's always more to take,
Barry.
- You're gonna
stay away from them.
- Well, that's
completely up to you.
- What?
- When we first met,
I told you that zoom
needed to be the best.
You just didn't realize
i was talking about myself.
- Is that what this is about?
- A race, Barry,
between you and me...
To see who's the fastest.
You win: This is over,
and you get to be the hero.
- I'm not racing you.
- Then your father won't be
the only person you love
that I'll take from you.
Think about it, flash.
All I want to know is
who's the fastest man alive
on either world.
I'll be waiting.
- so zoom wants to race you?
- He's obsessed
with being the best.
- Why would we trust him?
- He just wants to race.
You know,
it actually makes sense
in a completely-off-your-rocker
sort of way.
- That can't be
everything he wants.
- It isn't.
This magnetar
that's being developed
by Mercury labs--
turns out,
it can act as a pulsar.
- Whoa.
- What is a pulsar?
- It's a power amplifier
with a highly magnetized,
dense rotating core
that can be
easily weaponized.
- Nah, that's not
dangerous at all.
- That's what happens
to earth-2.
What happens in my vibes
is because of this machine.
- That thing is powerful enough
to destroy a planet?
- A lot more than just a planet,
if it has
the right power source.
- Like what?
- Like me.
That's why he wants to race.
He wants to siphon
the energy I create when I run.
- He wants to siphon the energy
off both of you.
- When Jay captured me,
he said that he used
to measure his success
by counting the number
of victims he had,
but now he was gonna measure it
by counting the number
of earths he conquered instead.
- He doesn't want
to just destroy earth-2;
he wants to take out every
other planet in the multiverse.
- How many are there?
- Infinite.
- Yeah, well, he can do that?
- If he can create a breach
to earth-2 all on his own...
- He can get to all of 'em.
- One pulse
to destroy them all.
- I guess I don't have a choice.
I have to race him.
and I have to win.
- bare.
Don't race him.
- It's not that easy.
- Yes, it is.
You just say no.
We find another way
to stop him,
together, like we always do.
- And do what, Joe?
Just sit around and wait for him
to kill somebody else?
Wally? Iris? You?
No. No way.
- He needs you, bare.
He needs your speed again
to get what he wants.
We have the advantage here.
- All I have to do
is beat him, Joe.
That saves the multiverse,
this whole city,
all of you.
I won't let
another person I love die
when I can prevent it.
- This...
Isn't just about
racing zoom, is it?
You want to kill this guy.
- Of course I want
to kill him, Joe.
I want to do a hell of
a lot more than just kill him.
I want him to suffer
for everything that he's done.
And he's going to.
- Come on, bare.
Think about
what you're saying.
- I have to be willing
to do whatever it takes.
I'm sorry, but I'm racing him,
whether you want me to or not.
- And I can't
talk you out of it?
- Not this time.
- Then I'm sorry too.
wha...
what are you doing?
Why did you put me in here?
- Because you're
too angry right now.
You can't race him like that.
Without a plan, you're--
you'll lose.
- Keeping me in here
is gonna get everyone killed.
I'm the only one that can
stop him; You know that.
- You race zoom on his terms,
you'll lose.
- This is not
your decision to make!
- It is this time.
- No.
- We all made it together.
- What?
All of you?
- Bro, I went back and forth.
I was, like,
a good 60/40 at first.
- Ramon.
- Yeah, yeah,
we all made the decision.
- Come on.
- Allen.
Allen.
This is for your own good.
- Don't do this.
Guys, come on.
Iris?
Cisco, come on, man.
You have to let me--
you have to let me stop him!
You have to let me...
- did we make
the right call here?
- Yeah, we did.
- You okay, Joe?
- Yeah, that was just
a little harder
than I anticipated.
- Yeah, locking up Barry...
That was the easy part.
Now, using our plan
to take down zoom
without Barry,
that's gonna be
the hard part,
but it's gonna be
a lot easier
once we know
where he is, Ramon.
- Chill, man.
I'm working on it.
- Work harder.
- Got it.
He's at the industrial park
on leawood.
Give me that.
- Yep.
- Mm.
- That is some serious
nerd love right there.
- Snow.
Look, everybody here
would understand
if you don't want
to go through with this.
- Jay may be a monster,
but there's a human
inside of him somewhere.
I've gotten
to that part of him before.
I know I can do it again.
I want to stop him, Harry,
for good.
- Ramon.
- So let's go over
the plan again.
- Okay, Caitlin
will distract Jay
so that you and Harry
can hit him with the boot.
Cisco's gonna open the breach,
and we're gonna
put him through it.
- I'll disarm the magnetar.
- Destroy the magnetar...
- Save the multiverse.
- One more thing.
We need to agree.
We all made
this decision together,
so if anything goes wrong,
we stick with it.
- Let's load up.
- hey.
- Hey.
- What's the matter?
- You know,
I've just been thinking.
You know, what's--what's next?
- What's next?
We stop zoom.
- Right.
Right, I guess--
I don't know, I mean--
after that.
- I don't know. Haven't
really given it much thought.
- Yeah, no--
no, I know you haven't.
Guess I've just--I've been
thinking about it a lot lately.
You know, I see the way you are
with everyone here--
Caitlin and cisco,
Iris and Joe,
Barry,
especially Barry.
You care about
these people a lot.
You know, but--
but my friends?
They're all back home
on our earth.
I guess what
I'm trying to say is,
you know,
when this is all over,
I'm gonna go back home
to live my life.
But if you need to stay here
so that you can live yours
again, I get that.
I understand.
It's okay, because--
- i--
- no, dad.
Seeing you happy,
that is all I've ever
wanted for you.
- okay. In position.
- Copy that.
We got you.
- Okay.
Snow, you ready?
- As ready as I can be.
- cisco.
Cisco, you good?
- Define "good."
- Ramon.
You're gonna be great.
Snow.
When you're ready.
- Okay.
- You got this.
- Here we go.
Jay?
- Caitlin.
- Jay!
- How did you find me?
- Doctor McGee said the magnetar
was stolen from her labs.
I knew that it had to be you,
so I tracked you here.
I tracked you here, Jay.
No one else knows.
- I told you, if you left me--
- that if I betrayed you,
you'd show me no mercy,
i know.
But I just want
to explain why I did that.
Please, Jay.
- Talk.
- Good job, girl.
Now draw him towards you.
- I made a mistake.
I am so sorry
that I abandoned you.
But you have to understand,
what you said to me--
that there was
a dark side of me--
that I was more like
killer frost than I knew--
I didn't want to accept that.
I tried to lock the darkness
inside of me.
But you knew that that was
already a part of me now.
And you're
the only one who did.
And now, I'm ready to accept
who I really am.
- Cisco, get ready.
- I am so sorry
that I hurt you.
But now I want to be the one
that only you know.
Please, Jay.
Let me try.
- one more step.
- I knew you'd eventually
come around, Caitlin.
but it's too late.
- Now, Ramon!
- damn it.
- Tranq him!
Tranq him!
- Gun is jammed!
- dad!
- did you see my dad?
- No, the vibe keeps changing.
It's like my brain
is channel surfing or something.
- They must be on the move.
That's why the vibe's in flux.
Keep trying.
Hey, did you turn off
the magnetar?
- No, there's no messing
with that thing.
Whatever he did to it--
we try and touch it,
we try and move it--
this planet's done for.
- Iris.
What's wrong?
- Zoom took dad.
- What? How?
- We tried to stop zoom by
pushing him through the breach,
but he took Joe with him.
- Well, where's Barry?
Did he go after him?
- He's not with us.
He's in a cell in the intake.
- Wait, you--you tried
to stop zoom alone?
- Long story.
- Well, we have to get him back.
- Wally, before zoom took dad,
we all agreed
that if we got him
off this earth,
we would close
the breaches for good,
and we would never
open them again,
under any circumstances.
- Why--why would you do that?
No. No way,
that's not gonna happen.
- He made us all agree to it.
- Well, guess what.
I didn't agree to that.
- Wally--
- Iris, I already
lost my mom.
If dad...
I--
- I will say,
if anything, Barry sure has an
ample number of fathers to kill.
- If you're gonna kill me,
kill me.
It doesn't matter.
You're not racing anybody.
- Come on, Joe.
You know Barry better than that.
You raised him.
He'll say yes
if he thinks he can save you.
- Not this time.
I made sure of it.
Who is that?
- It would just confuse you.
- Try me.
- I got my speed
the same way Barry did.
When I got struck by the
dark matter and electricity,
I became zoom,
the fastest man alive.
Wasn't long before I had
this earth on its knees.
But it wasn't enough.
I wanted more.
I wanted to be faster.
So I created a speed drug.
- Velocity-9.
- It made me faster
than I ever thought possible,
fast enough to break
the dimensional barrier,
fast enough
to run to other universes,
other earths.
And then, one day,
on one of those other earths,
I discovered him.
- He's another speedster?
- Yeah, you could say that.
That was right about the time
i discovered something else too.
All that v-9 I'd been injecting
into my system
had a little side effect.
- It was killing you.
- I searched for a cure.
I tried everything.
I even tried to manipulate
the speed force,
but let me tell you,
the speed force does not like
its rules being broken.
Now it's been sending its
enforcers after me ever since.
- So you brought him here
to steal his speed.
- I tried, but it wouldn't take.
But then the skies parted,
and I saw Barry,
and then I stole his speed.
I won.
I beat the rules
of the speed force.
- Why keep him here?
- Trophy.
And a little idea I had for fun.
You see, I got so tired
of being the villain,
so I decided
to be the hero too.
I even borrowed his name,
Jay garrick.
You know what's gonna be
great, detective?
After I beat Barry in the race
and prove that I'm the fastest
man alive on any earth,
he's gonna rot in a cage
just like the one
Jay's in now.
And then I'll have a flash
from two worlds
to keep me company.
- Look.
Everyone's gonna freak
when they find out I did this,
but I don't care.
We need your help, Barry.
- Uh, hey, guys,
Barry's not...
In his cell anymore.
- Wally!
- What? I wasn't just gonna
stand here and let this happen.
- You let him take Joe?
What the hell were you thinking?
- Allen, there was
nothing we could do.
- You could've let me race him!
- Allen!
You're not racing zoom!
- What are you gonna do?
Are you gonna tranq me again?
- Don't tempt me.
- Look, I know you guys made
a pact to keep zoom on earth-2,
but you did that
without me and Wally.
All right?
You don't get to do that!
- Barry, look at yourself
right now; You're not okay.
- Cisco, my dad was just killed
in front of me!
Do you have any idea
how that feels?
- Watching someone you love die?
Yes, I do.
- Cait--
- look, Barry.
I know how cold and angry
and distant that can make you.
But when this happened to me,
you were the one
who kept me in check.
You told me to stop
and take a breath,
and that's all
we're telling you to do now.
- I'm telling you
I'm good.
- Really?
You're good?
Because it seems to me you
want to do more than stop zoom.
It seems to me you want revenge.
If that's why you're doing this,
Allen, you will lose.
- Look, you guys.
I--you may not think
i can do this.
You may think I'm too angry.
But we're running out of time!
I have to beat him,
and I'm going to,
whether I have your help or not.
So which one is it?
So how does this work?
- It's the same way
we took Iris
into the speed force.
Harry does
his best Frankenstein,
you hold my hand,
and I vibe you there.
- All right, let's do it.
I'll do it.
Say when and where.
I'll be there.
- Cisco's learned how to bring
people into his vibes.
- There's one condition.
You bring Joe back.
But if he's harmed in any way,
it's off.
- I'll bring him,
and I won't release him
until after we race.
Deal?
- Deal.
- I tell you,
Jay might be crazy-pants,
but he can pick a venue.
- Brought the whole crew
with you, huh?
Can't say I blame you.
- Dad.
- Wally!
- It's gonna be
one hell of a show.
- Let him go.
- After we race.
- Cut the crap. We know you plan
to power up the magnetar
so you can destroy
the multiverse.
- Bravo.
You figured it out...
Almost.
I don't want
to destroy all of it.
This earth is at the center
of the multiverse.
It's the access point to every
other earth in existence.
One trans-dimensional shockwave,
and...Poof.
- Leaving just our earth.
How generous of you.
- Need to have some place
to hang my cowl.
You might want
to say your good-byes.
- don't worry.
I'm gonna save your dad.
- No.
You're gonna save our dad.
- Get back to s.T.A.R. Labs.
It's safer.
- We're not going anywhere.
We got eyes and ears right here.
- Either he goes,
or we all die together.
- we believe in you.
- wait.
Barry,
kick his ass.
- what are the rules?
- One lap around
the inside of this loop
will produce about
1 gigawatt of energy,
and I need 500-plus
to power the magnetar
enough to do the job.
Once it's full, I win,
because there is
no stopping it.
- So all I have to do
to beat you
is stop you before that happens.
- Yep.
It's that simple.
But if, at any point, you decide
you don't want to race anymore,
dear old dad number two
is a dead man,
as well as
your little fan club.
- They're not my fan club.
They're the reason
that I'm running,
why I'm gonna beat you.
Let's see what
you're made of, flash.
- just say when, zoom.
- Run, Barry.
Run!
- he's powering up the magnetar.
- come on, Barry.
Catch up.
- which one's Barry?
- Both of them.
He made a...
Both: Time remnant.
- go, all right?
Go!
I'll explain later, Joe.
- a remnant?
Stole my trick, flash.
But you're too late.
Bye-bye, multiverse.
- No!
- what's the time remnant doing?
- He's creating his own pulse.
- Why would he do that?
- Because...
If that's out of phase,
it'll counteract that one.
- Wait, his body
can't handle that.
- Then what's gonna happen?
- He'll die.
- ahh!
ahh!
You're a hero, Barry.
You couldn't kill me before.
You won't kill me now.
- I don't have to.
- Ahh!
- okay, so you ran back in time
and made a copy of yourself?
- Well, uh, basically.
Yeah.
- It's called a time remnant.
- It's not something
that I can do every day,
but I needed a way
to draw the time wraiths
out of the speed force,
hoping they'd be more upset
at what zoom had done
than they'd be with me.
- Is that what I look like
when they start
talking about science?
- Pretty much.
- Don't worry, Wally.
It'll get easier to understand.
- Well, how does that
even work?
- Same way zoom did it.
I ran back in time
moments before I left.
It's the only way I can be
in two places at once.
- Okay, so the time remnant,
it's still you?
- Yeah.
- But he died.
- Uh...
He was willing to sacrifice
himself for all of us.
- That's how much he loved us.
- You know what? We'll just--
we'll forget about it.
Barry, I'm glad you're okay.
- You know what?
In battle,
choose your weapon wisely.
All right?
Some people choose a gun.
I choose a Phillips-head
screwdriver.
- Oh, oh, I'm sorry.
You're so particular.
- Ramon, can you just please--
have you ever worked
with a tool before?
- I'm working with one now.
- Are you ready?
One,
two,
and...
- Ugh.
I don't know
what's more annoying,
being in that thing
or listening to you two
arguing about it.
- um...
You're--
- I'm Jay garrick,
the real Jay garrick.
what?
- I'm sorry. I--I'm sorry.
- bare.
- He looks just like him.
He looks just like my dad, Joe.
I can't believe this.
My dad told me.
He told me this.
He said
his mom's maiden name
was garrick.
I just never thought that
that meant--
- Barry, Barry.
- I never thought it meant--
- Barry, he doesn't know that.
He doesn't know
that he's your dad's
doppelganger, okay?
You want me to tell him
that you had to leave?
- No. No.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
I just need a minute.
I'll be all right.
- that's smart.
- Because of--
yeah, and there it is.
- Genius.
- So the reason
you didn't have your powers
is because there
was a dampener in the mask.
You see?
- I don't want
to see this thing ever again.
- So your powers are back.
- I see Jay--
excuse me--hunter--
stole your color scheme too.
- He took a lot
of things that were mine,
except for that.
That's, um--
that's all him.
- He said it was his father's
from the war.
- Ironically,
on my--on our earth--
this helmet stood for hope.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Well, maybe I can continue
that sentiment,
take something from him,
for a change,
make it my own.
- it suits you.
- Thank you,
all of you,
for saving me from zoom,
especially you, flash.
- You're welcome,
flash.
- now all I have to do
is find my way home.
- And where's that?
- I think you would call it
earth-3.
- Uh-huh.
Well, I can get you to earth-2.
- My daughter and I can help you
with the rest.
- We can?
- Yes, we can.
We're going home.
okay.
snow.
You're a tremendous scientist,
but...
You're an even better person.
- Don't make me cry, Harry.
I've done enough of that
already.
- Detective Joe west...
- Harry.
- You have great kids.
You take care of them.
- Same to you.
You take care
of that beautiful girl.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey.
- I'm a better man than I was
when I got here,
and that's 'cause of you.
- I'm not the same either.
- Hey, don't be surprised
if I project myself
over to earth-2
every once in a while,
you know,
just to throw your stuff
across the office.
- I'll miss you too,
cisco.
- So I guess I can't text you
from another earth, huh?
- I guess not.
- That's too bad.
Thank you guys, seriously,
for saving our home.
- Mm-hmm.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- can't stop thinking
about my dad's doppelganger.
Seeing him,
knowing that he's out there,
that should've made it easier.
It doesn't.
It just made me miss him
even more.
- I can't even imagine
how hard that must have been.
- We just won.
We just beat zoom.
Why does it feel
like I just lost?
- because you've lost a lot
in your life, Barry,
more than most.
But...
Maybe you and me
seeing where
this thing goes,
maybe that can give you
something for a change.
- That's all I've ever wanted
to hear you say.
And I wish that
i was in a place
where I could try that
with you.
But I feel so hollowed out
inside right now.
I feel more broken
than I've ever felt in my life.
If I'm ever gonna be
worth anything to you,
I need to fix
what's wrong with me.
I need to find some--
some peace.
- Barry, listen to me.
You waited for me
for years.
You let me get to a place
where this was possible.
So I am telling you
I am gonna do
the same thing for you.
Wherever you need to go,
whatever you need to do,
do it.
And when you get back,
I'll be here.
- okay.
- I love you, Barry.
- I love you too.
And I always will.
that's why I'm so sorry.
But I have to do this.
- Barry!
- Mom!
No!
No.
you're not gonna kill her
this time.
You're not gonna kill her
ever again.
- no.
- I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Okay?
You're safe.
You're safe now.
- Greg, move your head.