Perfect.
What are you doing to me?
Not the results we'd hoped for.
Your labs confirm what we saw on the ultrasound.
You're in end-stage liver disease.
But I always took my medicine.
I know.
You're the most compliant patient I have.
But autoimmune hepatitis can progress
even with treatment.
You need a liver transplant.
We talked about that before, remember?
But you're gonna have a fantastic team of surgeons
working their tails off to get you fixed up.
We're gonna get you admitted.
Do you have any questions?
Someone has to die
so I can live?
I want to pray,
but I can't pray for someone else to die.
Ooh, hold the door!
Thank you! I'm late enough already.
What happened to you?
Oh, not much.
Just slept through my alarm, stubbed my toe,
then got a parking ticket and a flat tire.
You have a 50-year-old relic, and you don't use Triple A?
I drive a 44-year-old car,
and it takes longer to wait for help
than it is to put the spare on myself.
I'm surprised you know how to use it.
Because I'm a woman?
Because you're a millennial.
I'm also an engineer who used to work for a car company.
A computer company. You built software.
For self-driving cars.
So Sony is a car company
because they built stereos for cars...
My point is I obviously know how to change a tire
faster than any tow truck driver or you.
Okay. No need to be hostile.
I'm just trying to make conversation.
Have a nice day.
What do you got?
He almost drowned in the triathlon.
We restarted his heart, but he's obtunded,
and breathing's labored.
He was in the triathlon?
Agonal respiration with accessory muscle use.
His sats are dropping.
- It's Cort Graham. - Eight liters oxygen.
Are we supposed to know who that is?
Cancer survivor and endurance athlete.
Also heads a big cancer charity.
Left lung has focal consolidation
and fluid collection.
- I need a chest tube. - On it.
If he's an experienced swimmer,
something must've made him pass out.
Could be a heart attack. Stroke.
- Head trauma? - From swimming?
I did a sprint tri once.
The swim was like a roller derby in water.
Damn it. Pyxis won't open.
I tried to put in my code, but nothing happens.
Well, figure it out. We need the chest tube.
I'm going to go in with a 10 blade.
That won't release enough fluid.
I know.
Come on!
He's cyanotic.
Ugh! Come on, open!
Get out of the way.
Don't just stand there. Get the tube.
Sorry. Sorry.
What's going on? Why didn't it open?
I don't know.
The power's on, but our computers are down.
All of them? The whole hospital?
Looks that way.
We'll need to temporarily close the clinic, ER,
and divert new patients.
Good news is,
the ORs are isolated from the network,
so we won't be able to share imaging
on external monitors,
but the MRI and radiology machines are still functional.
Well, great.
Let's postpone all elective procedures,
keep the most urgent cases on the board.
Got it.
You call the cops?
San Jose Police and the FBI
and the Cyber Attack insurance carrier.
What's the ransom?
Two million.
Well, we have the data backed up.
Got it covered.
We got a problem.
If it's only one problem,
it'll make me extraordinarily happy.
No, it won't.
They actually hacked into the network
over three months ago.
Took their time to not only
encrypt our servers
but our on-site and cloud-based backups.
Don't we have backups, data?
Actually, we have three,
which get rotated out every 30 days,
which means the oldest backup we have
was synched four days after the bastards broke in.
We have no data?
Technically, we still have data.
We just can't access it
without their encryption key.
Okay.
You can't pay the ransom.
You don't negotiate with terrorists.
What I can't do is
pay an exorbitant amount of money to an insurance company
and then not use them.
They gave us 24 hours to get the Bitcoin.
If I can find a mistake in their encryption software,
I might be able to get our data back.
Of course, I'll also have to retrace the attack chain
to find the exact door they came in.
Otherwise, we might as well toss
every computer we have in the recycle...bin.
If you're trying to convince me to not pay the ransom,
you maybe shouldn't have said that last part.
I realized that as I was saying it.
You've got 24 hours.
The surgery shouldn't be a problem,
but finding a liver will be.
Her MELD score puts her first up
on our list, which still leaves her competing
against every patient in the region.
No procurement coordinator is gonna discriminate
against a patient with Down Syndrome,
but they are gonna give a patient
with shorter life expectancy a low priority.
She also lives alone
and doesn't have any family to help with recovery.
She's worked so hard to be independent,
and now it's gonna be held against her?
It sucks, but it's not unfair.
I'm not giving up.
You don't have to worry about the list
if you can find a living donor.
Look for one who's already volunteered to give a kidney.
Get help. With the network down,
everything's gonna take longer,
and she doesn't have much time.
I couldn't have gotten kicked.
Wasn't even close to the pack.
I thought swim was your strongest section.
Usually, but I let my ego get the best of me.
I went out way too fast
and got dropped at the first turn.
Well, I'm impressed you're even out there.
I can barely finish a 5K.
I used to be the same way, too.
Cancer actually made me a better runner.
That can't be true.
The chemo you had reduces lung capacity,
and how could losing a leg make you a faster runner?
Well, once you get past a mile, it's not about speed.
It's about pain
and how much you're willing to push through.
And my threshold definitely increased
after chemo and rehab.
And seeing the hope I give survivors
every single time that I cross the finish line,
that doesn't hurt either.
His cancer could be back.
The odds of sarcoma reoccurrence are very high.
It could be lots of things.
It could be a virus or bacteria.
More likely cancer.
Overtraining can weaken the immune system.
I'm a motivational speaker,
so literally a professional optimist.
I can handle the truth.
Dr. Murphy is probably right,
but we'll do a full blood panel and chest CT to be sure.
The good news is, it's clearly an underfunded startup.
Their website's garbage,
and the ransom's only half your cyber policy limit.
Underfunded? Startup? Website?
Where do I start?
Despite what you see on TV,
these attacks don't come from lone wolves.
It's a global business.
With websites and customer service call centers.
Our IT Director thinks
that we might be able to decrypt the data.
Even if he could do that, which is impossible,
it wouldn't do any good
unless he can also retrace the entire attack chain.
She explained that.
She also said that she might be able to do both.
I'm sure your IT Director's excellent.
I'm also sure
that this is outside her area of expertise.
The only way to retrieve your data is to pay the fee.
Now, I'm sure I can negotiate it down
to a few hundred grand.
From two million?
Well, they're amateurs.
I'm not.
Thought I had a perfect match,
but she's in Shanghai on business.
How long's a flight from...
11 hours, but I couldn't talk her into it.
She's about to close the most important deal of her life.
Who talked to John Raponi?
Retired firefighter, peak physical condition.
I did.
He was at a bar at 3:00 p.m.
Doesn't give me high hopes
that his liver will be in perfect condition.
Mmm, not ideal, but not disqualifying.
Rachel Trainor is a better option.
She's local, preschool teacher,
and an extremely devout Christian.
What makes you think her faith helps us?
I'm a devout Christian, and I'm not sure
I'd be a live liver donor for a family member,
much less a stranger.
Well, you may be devout, but you're also selfish.
Um, we all are,
relatively speaking.
So what makes you think Rachel isn't?
Her Instagram.
I mean, you'd be surprised by how much you can learn
from what people "like,"
and Rachel likes everything she sees.
Like, literally everything.
We rescheduled the chemo appointments we could,
but there's still three that need their infusions today.
We're doing our best to modify the regimens.
Okay. Check and see if they got second opinions
from other oncologists.
- And if so, then maybe we can use those records. - Okay.
And keep me posted.
Yes.
What the hell?
You said I had 24 hours.
God, you're gonna give me a heart attack.
I authorized a negotiation. I didn't authorize a payment.
You don't trust me?
It's not about trust. It's about
weighing the costs of a delay.
Well, then you should know your costs just went up.
They sent us a Signal text.
What's a bot worm?
It's what happens when you listen to an insurance rep
instead of your own Head of IT.
They were insulted by the offer,
so they doubled the ransom and activated malware.
If we don't pay, they're gonna delete our data
and destroy all of our MRI, CT, and X-ray machines.
They obviously just figured out what the policy limit is,
which means they didn't do their research
and are now improvising.
They're playing catch-up.
Can we still get them down to a few hundred K?
No. That was before they had the policy information.
Now we'll end up somewhere between
their initial and current demands.
This is just a piece of paper
and a check to you, isn't it?
I'm sorry, you're upset because your insurance rep
wants to promptly pay a claim?
The frequency of these attacks is skyrocketing
because insurance companies make it so easy to collect.
I'd quibble with the analysis but accept the compliment.
It's just a matter of time before these bastards kill someone.
I agree, but do you have a solution or just a lecture?
Give me the time I asked for
to decrypt the data and restore the network.
- Not gonna be able to restore... - How do you even know that?
Because I've never seen it done.
- It would take a thousand years - I'm not running
- a brute force with some... - to run all the possible sequences.
Stop, stop, stop, stop!
Enough.
Your solutions aren't mutually exclusive.
You keep negotiating,
and you do whatever you do to get the network back online.
We have some good news.
Your cancer hasn't returned.
You have a fungal infection
that is causing a bleed in your left lung.
- That's great. - No, it's not.
The best treatment is surgical excision
of the infected lobe,
but we can't do that because of scarring
from the Bleomycin you were treated with
during chemotherapy.
They always do this good cop, bad cop thing?
I'm sorry.
Dr. Murphy just has a more direct bedside manner.
That's good. I like direct.
You can't climb an obstacle until you're facing it head-on.
We're gonna start you on an anti-fungal drug.
If surgery's the best,
that's what I want.
The chemo was over 10 years ago.
Bleomycin weakens the lungs permanently.
For most people.
I climbed five of the Seven Summits
with these lungs.
It's my decision.
I want the surgery.
I'm sorry, but sometimes
a positive attitude just isn't enough.
We may have to try you on several different drugs
before we see some improvement,
so you're gonna have to be patient.
It's not one of my strengths.
Me neither.
But we're gonna get through this together.
Turkey, avocado, and Swiss on wheat bread with mayonnaise.
It's your favorite.
I don't have time.
Low blood sugar can decrease
your ability to concentrate.
I've had five energy drinks and three granola bars.
Okay.
I have an interesting patient.
He said he thought cancer made him stronger,
- but that is obviously not true...  - Shaun!
Would you walk in on Glassman while he's doing brain surgery,
offer him a sandwich,
and start telling him about your day?
That's different.
Of course.
Because his job's important and mine's not.
Do you have any idea
how insulting it is to hear you demean what I do,
just like every man I've worked under and over my whole career?
You...
You don't respect me.
You can't bring sandwiches into an OR.
I have to go.
King me.
We have a problem.
Am I too sick for the transplant?
No.
But you are.
Your bloodwork indicates
nonalcoholic fatty liver disease.
It's a minor case which should be manageable with diet,
but it means you can't be a liver donor.
Wouldn't a fatty liver be better than nothing?
It wouldn't be safe for either of you.
There has to be another way.
We can't give up.
We're not giving up, but...
Thank you for trying to help me.
I'm sorry you are sick, too.
Your kidney is fine.
Would you be willing to donate it?
Uh, of course.
But how does that help Jamie?
You might be able to save two lives with one kidney.
What's going on?
Blood oxygen level dropping. He's hypoxic.
The anti-fungal regiment isn't working, but don't worry.
There are other drugs we can try.
I want the surgery. Please.
I'll take the risk, whatever it is.
Not a risk. It's a guarantee.
Increase voriconazole by 320 milligrams
and add Amphotericin at 24 milligrams.
We may need to intubate you.
Stop! Stop.
I would survive the surgery.
- No, you...  - Yes.
I would.
Because I never had the drug.
Because I never had cancer.
So, how'd he lose his leg?
Drunken motorcycle accident when he was 22.
It's good news.
Now we can give him the surgery he needs.
No way. He needs to find new doctors,
and we need to figure out a way to alert the charity.
He faked cancer so he could steal money,
date models, and get his face on a Wheaties box.
He didn't steal the money.
He gave it all to charity.
I don't care what he did with it after he lied
and cheated thousands of people to get it.
He should be in prison, not our OR.
Can we even do that? Refuse to treat him?
We refuse to treat noncompliant patients all the time.
What's going on?
I mean, he's obviously not the first patient
who's lied to you.
He didn't just hide how much he smokes or drinks.
He weaponized people's empathy,
and he kept pushing his lie
until he was some sort of national hero.
How does that not piss you off?
It does.
But I can be pissed off and professional.
Get him prepped for surgery.
A multi-organ chain.
We need to find someone
who wants to give a kidney to their loved one
but isn't a match, but is a match to Jamie.
And the loved one has to be a match to Rachel.
We have to match blood and tissue types,
as well as organ size,
and kidneys and livers have different test requirements.
And we need another donor willing to do a surgery
that's more painful and dangerous
than the one they already signed up for.
Twice the challenge.
To save twice as many lives.
Park and I will start calling hospitals.
Asher, back to social-media stalking.
Jordan, check local news reports
and any other corner of the Internet you can scour.
Stay back
or you're gonna contaminate my clean room.
I found an error.
Not theirs. Ours.
The serial numbers on the server didn't match up.
Turns out one of my techs spilled coffee on a server,
didn't want to tell me,
so he switched it out three days before the hack.
His screw-up might just save our ass.
So it's not encrypted?
No, but it is corrupted from the coffee and dust and dirt.
I found it under a pile of junk in the recycling bin.
But if my patient pulls through,
I'll be able to restore the network
without having to pay the hackers a dime.
That's great.
The insurance guy came to an agreement
with the hackers, didn't he?
Actually, he negotiated them down
below the original ransom amount.
I didn't authorize it yet.
You have till 9:00 a.m. to get us back online.
Okay.
We will get one more chest CT,
and then we will insert
the central venous line and the arterial line
to finalize your surgical prep.
You must think I'm a sociopath, but...
Don't even bother.
It's not like I planned this all out.
It just happened.
You just forgot
the drunk driving on a motorcycle detail
while you raked in cash and collected famous friends?
I went back to school
and got my MBA in nonprofit finance.
My first interview after graduation
was with this small cancer charity.
And for some reason,
the woman assumed I lost my leg to cancer.
And I didn't correct her.
It was a weak
stupid moment.
It wasn't just a moment.
It was years.
Where I was raising money,
helping thousands of cancer survivors.
And I knew if the truth came out,
that would all end.
I have helped
far more people over the last 10 years
than I have hurt.
You're scheduled for surgery first thing in the morning.
Hey, what's going on?
Don't you have a thoracotomy to prep for?
Yeah, I just needed a break.
I'm fine.
"I'm fine" is a pretty reliable indicator
that someone is not fine.
I suck at this.
I completely froze, could've killed the patient.
I always freeze. Lim knows it.
I feel like an impostor because...
I am.
It's a stressful job.
Patient's being a jerk?
Get used to it.
Chief of Surgery doesn't appreciate you?
Earn her respect.
If you want to be a successful surgeon,
you got to develop thicker skin.
My skin's not...
Suck it up and get back to work.
I did it!
If I had a mic, I'd drop it!
I fixed the server.
It's still missing the last 96 days of records,
but it's totally malware free,
which means we can restore the network with...
with three hours to spare.
And the, uh, the bot worm, the thing on the imaging?
How did you get rid of that?
I didn't, but I don't have to
because I went through every line of code,
and there's no sign of a worm.
They were obviously bluffing.
Obviously? It's not obvious to me.
No, the cyber insurance rep was right.
These guys are amateurs,
and the level of skill it would take
to cause an offline machine to self-destruct,
they would have to be like the Sidney Crosby of hackers,
and they're beer league at best.
Are you sure?
Totally.
95%.
Okay, well...
You have three hours to get to 100.
It's not going to work.
I already tried.
Why would the hack affect the microwave?
It's a smart microwave.
Apparently not.
Why are you so angry about Cort's lies?
You told me before, when the truth can't help someone,
you should lie.
I was talking about small white lies.
Cort's lies are huge.
When does a lie stop being white and start being huge?
The amount of good Cort did was proportional to the size of his lies.
Looks like you got what you wanted.
I just got off the phone with a reporter.
She wanted a comment on her soon-to-be
front page expose on Cort Graham.
Because her source is an employee in my department.
- I mean, I didn't... - You're off the case.
And you're lucky I can't prove it was you,
or you'd be out of a job.
What?
- Crap. - It's okay.
I got someone.
I called an old buddy who runs the infirmary
at the state pen in Arizona.
He put me in touch with an ex-inmate,
just paroled on compassionate release for kidney failure.
He's a match for Rachel.
His daughter's a match for Jamie.
They're on their way here with a police escort.
ETA 20 minutes.
The chain is closed. We did it!
Not to be a buzzkill, but...
An ex-inmate?
What'd he do?
He killed someone?
It was a complicated case over 20 years ago.
- He's paid his... - I can't do this.
You're not doing it for him. You're doing it for Jamie,
who's an innocent and deserving woman the system failed.
I understand.
But you want to put my kidney in a murderer's body.
He's a person who did something wrong a long time ago.
It's more than just wrong.
I'm not going to risk my life
to help someone who took another's.
Please take this IV out of my arm.
Now!
I get it.
I wouldn't want to save a murderer's life either.
But you should understand what Dr. Park means by "complicated."
Chris was abused as a child sexually, physically.
You don't want to know the horrors.
Once he got strong enough, he put a stop to it.
With a bullet.
But the prosecutor and the jury didn't see a brutalized kid.
They just saw a thug.
So they put him away for life for fighting back.
All finished. You're free to go.
That man shot someone in a robbery.
If the lie saves a life, it's fine by me.
And it saves two lives,
so I definitely think we can let it slide.
I think I've actually solved a huge problem,
but Glassman wants me to be 100% sure,
and I can't be.
I need your advice.
If I'm wrong,
all the imaging machines in the entire hospital will self-destruct.
Tens of millions of dollars' worth of damage.
But if I'm right, I'd save the whole hospital
and prevent some really bad people
from getting almost $2 million.
And I'm almost sure I'm right.
I'm never 100% sure
a surgery is going to cure the patient.
There's always a chance something could go wrong,
but I still do the surgery.
But you get the patient's permission first.
And in my case, Glassman is kind of the patient,
and he hasn't given me permission.
In fact, he told me not to.
Oh, then I wouldn't do the surgery.
But this isn't actually surgery.
I don't know what you want me to say.
It's all right, sorry.
I'll just figure it out on my own.
Lea...
I wouldn't bring Dr. Glassman a sandwich in the OR
because you can't eat in the OR.
I knew that because I know about surgery.
I don't know about computers.
Neither does Dr. Glassman.
But you do.
You always know how to fix things.
I respect you.
I would've thought you would respect me enough
to at least ask me the question to hear me out
before kicking me off the case and threatening to fire me.
I did hear you out, when you sat right there
and said you wanted to blow the whistle on a patient,
and then that's exactly what happened.
- What am I supposed to think? - You're supposed to trust me.
I thought we were friends.
Is that why you went over my head
to tell my boss about my diagnosis?
- Is that what this is about? - No.
I'm capable of separating my personal feelings
from my professional decisions.
Excuse me.
Yeah, what is it?
Sorry. Cort just coded.
We had to do CPR. and manual cardiac massage.
Dr. Murphy didn't want to start the lobectomy with...
I'll assist Dr. Murphy.
You coming or not?
BGM: Lift you up by Ruelle
♪ There's some things you can't explain ♪
♪ Is It chance or is it fate? ♪
♪ You're past the point where this could break ♪
♪ Not much more that You can take ♪
♪ Is there any medicine? ♪
♪ It hurts too much to mend ♪
♪ When You can't hold on any longer ♪
♪ I will lift you up ♪
♪ And when you feel the storm getting stronger ♪
♪ I won't let you give up ♪
♪ When there's pain, there's healing too ♪
♪ Ooh, I'll be there for you ♪
♪ I will lift you up ♪
♪ Ooh, I will lift you up ♪
Spread the ribs more with Finochietto Retractor.
Would you really fire Dr. Browne?
If I find evidence she did it, I will.
Shingle the ribs.
But you and Claire are friends.
Professional responsibilities come before friendships.
It wasn't Dr. Browne.
It was me.
I called the reporter.
Why?
People suffered real tragedies,
and he used their pain to enrich himself.
But
why confess?
You're the kind of person I aspire to be.
So is Dr. Browne.
If you two lost trust in each other,
it would do a lot of damage to this department,
to what makes it so special.
I didn't want to be responsible for that.
Scrub out.
Stapler.
Transecting the bronchial branches.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop!
Please tell me
you haven't made the transfer yet.
No. But I'm authorizing it.
Turn your computer on.
Your employee ID is your temp password.
Who knows their employee ID number?
I remotely rebooted every authorized user.
Totally.
100%.
Successfully.
Imaging's unscathed.
No malware. No worm. No nothing.
Bastards were obviously bluffing,
just like I told you.
You gambled your entire imaging department on a hunch?
Do you have any idea how reckless that was?
Thank you.
Appreciate all you've done.
That decision was not yours to make.
If you ever usurp my authority again,
I'm going to fire you right on the spot.
- I'm sorry, but... I - Will you just...
- just saved the whole hospital... - Will you shush for a second?
Wait for the compliment.
Thank you.
Well done.
You're welcome.
If I ever have another poker night, you're invited.
You'll need to take all three of these
every morning and before bedtime.
Call me if you need anything.
Thank you for not giving up on me.
You can't just leave.
I've never been fired before,
but I'm pretty sure that's how it works.
I'll talk to Lim.
Convince her to give you a second chance.
I do not think she'll do that.
She was willing to fire you,
- and she likes you a lot more than her. - Shaun...
It's okay.
I've enjoyed working with you both.
Thank you.
if there is anything I can do, don't hesitate to call.
I'll miss you.
But I don't want to hug you.
Surgery went well.
You'll be back to competition in a couple months.
Was it you?
I can't claim credit for that good deed.
Not a terribly convincing denial.
If I cared about convincing you, I'd try harder.
I knew this day would eventually come.
And I expected I'd feel vulnerable,
exposed.
And I do.
But I also didn't expect that, you know, I'd feel
relieved.
It's a little like getting back in the water the first time
without my prosthetic.
I had to awkwardly hop to the water,
people staring at me.
But once I got in, I...
I felt a little bit lighter.
BGM: Falls (Reprise) by ODESZA, Sasha Sloan (feat. Sasha Sloan)
♪ Ever feel like you can't breathe ♪
♪ Does the water feel too deep ♪
♪ Lie awake 'cause you can't sleep without it ♪
Livy.
♪ Ever feel like you're alone ♪
♪ When You're lost, but you're already home ♪
You weren't gonna say goodbye?
♪ Lie awake 'cause you can't dream without it ♪
Uncle Marcus, I can't.
Not now.
I'm sorry I let you down.
You didn't let me down.
You confused me.
I know you're not the whistleblower.
- It wasn't Dr. Browne. - I know.
It was me.
You?
Why?
Exposing that guy was the right thing to do.
Patient privacy is an important obligation,
but it's not our only one.
I knew there'd be no proof, so no one was gonna get fired.
Never expected Lim to blame Browne.
But I know that's not why you destroyed your whole career here.
How can I help you if you don't...
- I don't want your help. - Livy.
I never wanted to be a doctor.
But every time I tried to tell my parents,
my professors, you,
you'd just push me and encourage me until I backed down.
I knew if I got myself fired,
there was no way that you could pep-talk me back
into a career that I don't want.
♪ Ever feel like it's too much ♪
I don't want to be important or successful.
I just want to be myself.
But I don't even know who that is.
♪ Yeah, I swear I know what it's like ♪
The only way to find out is if I burn the bridges behind me.
♪ Maybe You don't know it, but it gets better ♪
♪ It's gonna be all right
I know exactly who you are.
♪ I'm never gonna leave your side ♪
You are a resilient, amazing young woman.
♪ Everybody falls down, all the way down ♪
And I can't wait to see what else you become.
♪ You gotta get up, gotta get up ♪
I'll be rooting for you.
♪ Gonna make it through this time
♪ Everybody falls down, all the way down ♪
♪ You just gotta hold on tight ♪
♪ You gotta get up, gotta get up ♪
♪ Gonna make it through this time ♪
♪ Gonna make it through ♪
I know I'm the last person you want to see right now,
so I brought a bribe.
I was wrong to accuse you,
not only because you didn't do it
but because I was holding against you
the very thing that makes you such an awesome doctor.
You care.
When you meet a patient,
you don't just see muscles, bones, and organs.
You see a human being
with all of their strengths and flaws.
And you should never lose that,
even if it does make the job harder.
And most importantly,
you're a good friend.
You got salted caramel in that bag?
And an insane amount of hot fudge.
♪ Everybody Falls Down, all the way down ♪
♪ You just gotta hold on tight ♪
♪ You gotta get up, gotta get up ♪
♪ Gonna make it through this time ♪
♪ Gonna make it through ♪
♪ You gotta get up, gotta get up ♪
♪ Gonna make it through this time ♪