Previously on "The Good Doctor"...
Can we just hold each other for a little bit?
Deal with your crap
before this is who you really become.
I'm sorry for making you meet me after hours like this.
I'm always available for my patients.
Come on in.
Your dad's been diagnosed with pancreatic cancer.
You're not like other people.
You're like a spoiled, little baby.
Shaun?
You okay?
We have to be at the airport at 7:00 a.m.
I think when you're taking the first flight out of Casper,
you don't need to be there 90 minutes early.
Or maybe you do.
You want to talk about last night?
I think we should.
Why?
Because you were in a pretty bad place,
which is totally understanda...
I feel better now.
Thank you.
I'm glad I could help you.
But I also think
we shouldn't tell anyone I stayed here all night.
People might get the wrong idea.
Okay.
We slept together.
Did you use protection?
N-no. We did not have sex. We just slept.
Together.
Held each other.
I was upset, and Lea comforted me.
Lying in bed with her,
it felt...
Different than it does with Carly.
Well, maybe that's why you invited Lea
instead of Carly in the first place?
Lea and I are just friends.
Yeah, she's made that very clear.
Sometimes you learn more about someone
by what they do than what they say.
Of course, who the hell knows what she wants.
But more importantly, what do you want?
I don't know.
Well, you better figure it out soon.
Sex or no sex, the wheels are in motion.
And someone's about to get run over.
They had Mallomars.
Let's roll.
Respiratory tech to 3 East.
Shaun, y-you're back already?
Why wouldn't I be? I like being here.
Shaun.
I'm really sorry to hear about your father.
How are you doing?
He died.
And the seat was very uncomfortable on the flight,
so I couldn't sleep.
And they only had the salty peanuts
and not the pretzels I like.
Yeah. Life sucks.
We need a doctor!
We were mountain biking.
She fell down a rocky slide.
Her leg...
We'll need an X-ray and an MRI.
Let's also get you something stronger
- than this ice pack for the pain. - N-no.
Uh, they gave me Vicodin when I had my wisdom teeth pulled.
I was sick for two days.
We have other painkillers...
Really, I'm fine.
Look, I made it through childbirth without drugs.
I can make it through this.
That hurts less than childbirth?
Tender and bloated.
We should get you admitted, get an X-ray.
That's all right. All I need are laxatives.
Intestinal blockage could be fatal if we don't treat it.
Please.
I'm unemployed, and I don't have insurance right now.
How about this...
We skip the X-ray, give you the meds.
But in exchange, you agree to stay here
till you've had a bowel movement,
and we have peace of mind.
Deal.
Shaun, you're back.
Hello, Carly. It's good to see you. I missed you.
Morgan and I have a patient
with a comminuted leg fracture.
We need a rush on a C.B.C. and coagulation panel.
Shaun, I'm sorry about your Dad.
Why didn't you return any of my calls or texts?
I was very busy.
You had time to text me.
I wasn't sure what to say.
Shaun, I know that you don't always understand people's feelings.
But a part of you had to understand
that ignoring me would be hurtful.
I'm not sure what to say now.
My patient is getting an MRI.
I need to get back to them.
Are you going to take the samples?
PTSD.
It's an interesting topic.
Just organizing some notes for a potential case report.
Nice. Look forward to reading it.
I started seeing a therapist.
Good.
I hope you find it helpful.
She thinks I, uh... I might have PTSD.
Sounds a bit excessive.
You've definitely dealt with some childhood trauma.
You think she's right?
I think doctors make the worst patients.
The best patients are the ones who ask a lot of questions.
And keep an open mind.
We gave him the laxatives,
and right away, he tried to leave.
Ended up passing out and vomiting.
I'm fine. I can take care of this at home.
We need to get him to Radiology.
We need an abdominal CT stat.
No. You can't keep me...
Can't keep me against my will.
Wherever you need to be, it can wait.
You need help now.
What are you transporting?
Painful constipation, nervous agitation,
refusing scans...
You're obviously packing drugs.
The balloons have either created a complete obstruction
or one of them burst.
Please, I just want to go home.
Luca, we're doctors, not cops.
He definitely sounds like a cop.
We won't call the police, I promise.
Whatever is wrong, let us help you.
How's Carly?
She wasn't upset about you ghosting her
while you were with Lea in Wyoming?
She said it was hurtful.
You got off easy.
Is this your weird way of breaking up with Carly to get with Lea?
I don't want to break up with Carly.
But you do want to get with Lea.
I didn't say that.
Not out loud.
And you're making a big mistake.
Carly's smart. Pretty.
And the fact that she's willing to deal with all your stuff
means you should be thanking whatever God you pray to
that you ever met her.
While Lea is... Well, a flake.
She's not a flake.
She showed up on your doorstep
without even giving you a heads-up
that she was coming back to San Jose.
Then she needed to move out, but then she moves in.
Not to mention the whole
"Let's get drunk on tequila and I'll teach you how to kiss,
but I just want to be friends" nonsense.
She's...not a flake.
There is traumatic avulsion of the ligaments.
She's going to need surgery.
We hammer a long rod through the medullary canal
to hold the two ends of the break together.
It's a broken leg.
Can't you just put a cast on it or something?
Obviously, you'll be asleep. You won't feel anything.
I lied.
About the vicodin making me sick.
My husband doesn't know.
I'm an opioid addict.
I've been clean for 10 years,
but one dose could send me right back.
Do whatever you need to do to fix my leg,
but you can't use any narcotics.
Not even an epidural?
Strongest thing she'll let us give her is Tylenol.
Ketamine? What about Ketamine?
It's non-narcotic and can create a dissociative effect.
It's mind altering and potentially addictive.
Hypnosis has been shown to be effective.
Only when used in conjunction with narcotics.
Studies say playing the patient's favorite music
can help manage pain in certain surgeries.
Yeah, we hammer a nine-inch rod
through her tibia,
but she's okay because she's listening
to the soundtrack from Hamilton.
I said "Certain surgeries."
Okay. That's the answer.
Music?
A different surgery.
Some other way of putting her leg back together.
An external fixation.
We put two pins through the proximal tibia.
Another two in the distal end of the bone beyond the fractures.
Healing will take much longer,
and there's an increased risk
of infection and permanent deformity and...
And small pins are much less painful than a huge nail.
I'll get her prepped.
I got laid off.
I needed money, and this was just a one-time thing.
But it was a mistake. It was a stupid mistake.
This works best if you don't talk.
Our plan is to attach a metal frame with pins into your leg.
It'll stabilize the fractures,
and we can do it without narcotic anesthesia.
I know she's worried about an allergic reaction,
but aren't there any other drugs you can use?
Given your wife's medical history,
this is the best strategy.
Don't worry, sweetie.
Remember... I'm strong like Wonder Woman.
There's over 50 latex balloons
lodged near the ileocecal junction.
They'll need to be surgically removed.
And we need to alert San Jose Vice/Narcotics.
No.
The only reason he agreed to treatment
is because we promised we wouldn't do that.
I didn't promise that. Neither did Dr. Melendez.
We don't call the police
on overdose victims or addicts.
He's got probably two kilos
of what I'm sure is heroin in his gut.
He's not an addict. He's a dealer.
I know you feel for this guy.
But hospital policy is clear.
Take a few more of those deep breaths for us.
Just two more to go.
Kerry, we need you to somehow keep your leg still.
BGM: Claire de Lune by Royal Philharmonic Orchestra
B.P. is 190/110.
Push I.V. beta blockers.
- Wait, no! - No, they're not narcotics.
We just need to give you something to reduce the pressure.
Back to 150/80.
- Kerry, how are we doing? - Better.
We'll get this last one in, and you'll be good to go.
No. You promised me.
Yeah. You value honesty and morality over all else.
If you leave this hospital now, you will die.
I'll take my chances.
You know what'll happen when one those balloons bursts?
You'll start feeling weak, get cold.
Soon you'll have secretions filling your lungs and airway.
You'll try to scream for help, but nothing will come out.
Can you get the release paperwork?
I'll be back in a few minutes.
Luca, I understand where you're coming from.
You're a doctor.
Last job I had, I was a busboy.
I grew up in a trailer.
A bunch of 'em, actually.
My mother wasn't the type to save for a rainy day.
But we never gave up.
Even when you think you're alone, you're not.
I want to help you.
You just have to give me a little more time.
One hour.
If I can't figure out how to treat you
and keep you out of jail, you can walk out the door.
One hour.
And then I'm gone.
You'll have some discomfort for the next few weeks,
but all you need right now is rest, and you should be able...
Mommy!
Oh, my gosh, that's so cool.
Everyone says their spouse is the strongest person they know.
But I have actual proof now.
Told you.
Wonder Woman.
This is absurd.
If this was a tumor, we'd take it out and toss it.
This time, it just happens to be drugs.
Yeah, because cancer is not a felony.
You can't just toss out the drugs with the medical waste.
He's not a gangster or a hardened criminal.
He's just... he's just a scared guy trying to survive.
You're assuming anything he's told you is true.
And even if it is,
not everyone who needs money becomes a drug mule.
You can't imagine what it's like
to grow up in that kind of poverty.
Shouldn't you be judging this guy the harshest?
You made it out just fine without breaking the law.
That's not exactly true.
My mother used to go on these trips.
I would come home from school, and she'd be gone.
Sometimes hours, sometimes days.
I didn't have any money.
So when I needed supplies and food from the store,
I would sneak them away in a backpack.
One day, the bag broke
and all of the soup and oatmeal that I had stolen
fell out right in front of a security guard.
And she looked at me,
at my face, at my clothes,
and then she helped me pick them up
and let me go with a warning.
If she hadn't given me a break,
I wouldn't be standing here, as a doctor,
discussing this with you.
Maybe there's a way to save Luca
without ruining his life or breaking policy.
Shaun.
You need the elevator. Use the elevator.
What am I doing wrong?
I never know where I stand with you.
One minute, we're sharing
deep, personal fears with each other,
and the next, you're running away
because you can't stand to touch me.
Be honest...
Is there anything going on with Lea
that you're not telling me?
Say something, Shaun.
It's different.
I...
like you, Carly.
When I'm around you,
I want to be impressive to you.
I don't feel like I have to impress Lea like I do you.
We will have to keep whatever medical waste
we collect during your surgery in the lab for testing.
But we will discharge you
before the pathology report comes back.
At which point we'll be obligated to alert the police.
How do I know you're not gonna call the cops
right after you put me to sleep?
You'd be a moron not to trust Dr. Browne at this point.
She's gone way beyond the call to save your ass.
Okay.
Say thank you.
Thank you.
Dr. Murphy.
How about you head home for the night?
We still need to monitor Kerry.
And it's easier for me to avoid Carly here
than it is for me to avoid Lea at home.
Okay, I'm only gonna respond to the first objection.
You've had a long week,
and it's important you get some rest.
Morgan will take point.
How did you know your wife was the right woman for you?
Personal advice?
I thought that was Dr. Glassman's domain.
Dr. Glassman is divorced.
He seems happy with his marriage now,
but I have no way of knowing for sure.
You're better than him.
For this.
I knew I wanted to be with Isabel the first time we spoke.
Freshman-year biology class.
And I have not wavered in that resolve in the 27 years since.
But...
How did you know?
It was a feeling I had in the pit of my stomach
every time I was around her.
I felt...
Nervous?
Excited.
It's a cliche,
but my heart sped up every time I saw her.
Still does.
Not quite in the same way, but...
Now, if you don't mind, I need to get home to that woman.
Hey, you.
How was the first day back?
Confusing.
Problem with a patient or Carly?
If you don't want to talk about it, we can just hang.
Let's just hang.
Copy that. Commencing a hang.
Sh... Shaun?
What's up?
This will just take a few seconds.
Hello?
It didn't work.
Kerry's leg is swelling up.
I think she has compartment syndrome.
You need to get back here.
We'll have to do the surgery we've been trying to avoid.
We'll first have to make multiple incisions to relieve the pressure
and then replace the external frame with an internal nail.
If we don't act soon,
you could be facing an amputation.
Okay.
You'll need to be sedated.
No. Look, I can take it.
Kerry, you had a blood-pressure spike
during the fixation procedure.
Without anesthesia,
you could have a hypertensive crisis,
a risk of stroke, or heart attack.
Post-op, we can help you manage the dosing.
And if you relapse, we have counselors that...
No.
I remember waking up all those mornings cold and alone,
wondering if I could ever be happy again,
if I deserved to be happy.
Any amount of pain is better than losing everything again.
My husband, my daughter...
How long can you keep secrets from the people you love
before they stop being the people you love?
Every relationship has secrets.
This, it doesn't have to be one of them.
Drug addiction is a disease.
You have nothing to be ashamed of.
It happens because of the choices you make.
When you have lost everything,
but you still manage to find someone
who makes you want to get up and live another day,
you do whatever you can to hold on to them,
even if it means
burying a piece of yourself in the process.
If we can't convince her to change her mind,
maybe her husband can.
Impracticality isn't cause
for breaking doctor-patient confidentiality.
This isn't impractical.
It's irrational and barbaric.
We're not permitted to reveal any secrets to the husband.
But we can tell him that.
Last one.
What's wrong?
It's too adherent to the intestinal wall.
Could use Potts Scissors to dissect it free.
Let's give it a try. Nurse?
Your idea. Only fair you do the honors.
Check it for perforations.
It's intact.
Vitals are stable.
Take the specimen container to the lab.
Dr. Browne, you're leading closure.
There's been some complications.
We need to perform an additional surgery.
What do you need to do?
I can't tell you.
I'm unable to go into further detail.
It would violate your wife's confidentiality.
Confidentiality?
Haven't you been telling me everything?
Again, I'm unable to go into further detail.
What's going on?
Why can't the doctors talk to me?
Kerry, obviously, there's something going on
you don't want me to know.
Are you dying?
No. No. It's...
It's nothing like that.
Then what?
Whatever it is, I want to be able to help.
Please.
I'm an opioid addict.
I've been clean for a decade, but...
That's why I never take painkillers.
And that's why I can't let them use anesthesia.
Why didn't you ever tell me?
You don't know the kind of person that I was.
Who the drugs turned me into.
I tried quitting so many times,
but it never stuck.
Until you.
Meeting you saved me.
But...
if I relapse, I know I'll drive you away.
How could you ever think I'll stop loving you?
The woman who knows the lyrics
to every Boyz II Men song?
The woman who rushes home
to watch those stupid home-makeover shows live.
The woman I'm raising our daughter with.
The woman who will steal from you,
the woman who will lie to you,
- who will hurt you... - No.
the woman you won't be able to trust.
No.
Just do what the doctors tell you.
Take the meds.
I will be there for you.
No matter what happens.
I love you.
And I know you mean that.
But I'm not as strong as you think I am.
Baby. I just can't.
I'm so sorry.
We'll start prepping you for surgery.
I like your laugh. I like your smile.
I don't usually look at eyes,
but I think yours are pretty.
I like your breasts.
You can keep going if you want to.
I like spending time with you.
I like that you are kind.
I like that you are patient.
I like that you're my girlfriend.
Are you going to break up with me?
No, I am not planning on breaking up with you.
We had a fight.
Couples fight.
But...
I'm worried, Shaun.
I'm flattered that you want to impress me,
but that is not worth anything
if you feel like you can't talk to me.
You're right.
I have to tell you. Everything.
I got very upset in Wyoming.
Lea came in to comfort me
and we hugged and laid down on the bed,
and we fell asleep hugging.
That's everything that happened.
We struggled with lying together for weeks.
And you...
Did it in one night with Lea?
Yes.
But sh... she's a close friend,
and she wanted to be there for me.
Please, just stop talking.
Shaun, I-I just... I need some space.
I can't be around you right now.
Shaun?
I wanted to be honest.
Carly said she wanted me to talk to her.
Lea said not to tell what happened. Lea was right.
Uh, take a breath. Sit down.
I can't. I have surgery in a few minutes
and I can't focus and...
and I feel sick, and is everyone going to leave me?
What? What? What are you talking about?
My dad didn't want me.
My mom chose him over me.
Carly now hates me.
- Shaun. Shaun. - Lea will get tired of me.
- Shaun. - You'll get sick of me.
- I do everything wrong. - What?
- Shaun, Shaun, look at me for a second. - Everyone will go away!
- I make people upset! - Hey, hey, Shaun!
Oh, my God, Shaun!
I make them angry! I make them hate me!
Shaun, look at me, look at me, look at me right here.
Right here. Look at me here.
Don't ever say that about yourself.
Don't ever say that!
You hear me?
You're gonna get through this.
You're gonna go to surgery, and you're gonna get this done.
- How? - How?
Because you're an extraordinary doctor.
That's how.
And that's what you do. That's what you do.
I could not be more proud of you.
You hear that?
And I could never get sick of you.
You're not getting rid of me, pal, okay?
I'm right here.
Right... right here.
Okay? I got you.
I'm going to be late to surgery.
Can you let me go now?
Yeah, okay.
- Okay. - Okay.
Numbing cream applied.
Are you ready?
We were able to remove all the balloons.
So you should be out of here in 24 hours.
It'll likely take another 48 hours
to get the contents tested.
The lab's very busy.
I know I've been a pain in the ass.
I've just gotten used to people screwing me over.
You're the first person that's made me feel,
I don't know, seen.
Maybe one day, I'll find a way to pay it forward, right?
Reamer's in the intramedullary canal.
This will make space for inserting the nail.
You're doing great, Kerry.
Inserting into canal.
Here comes the nail. You ready?
- B.P.'s spiking. - Push beta blockers.
Hang in there.
220/170.
She's having a tachyarrhythmia.
Screw it. We have to push the fentanyl.
- Nurse, help Dr. Murphy. - No.
It's helping distract her.
You sure, Dr. Murphy?
Yes. Please hurry.
It was a good day.
It must be very gratifying, saving lives.
Yeah, I think I might've done a little more than that today.
I... I think I might have changed one.
Last time we met,
you mentioned that your mother
would frequently berate you when you were young.
What kind of things would she say?
Do we have to get into that right now?
Can't I just have a good day?
You know, enjoy feeling okay for once?
Claire, I believe you've fallen into destructive patterns
precisely to avoid confronting your feelings about your mother,
her death.
Feelings that need to be confronted if you hope to get better.
Cardiac care nurse to E.R.
They're reviewing the security video.
Someone faked a seizure, staff responded,
and another person broke into the storage locker.
Do you think Luca...
The only thing missing was his specimen.
Is someone questioning him?
Luca's gone.
What will the police do?
Nothing.
All we have is a fake name and the knowledge
that someone stole some balloons with unknown content.
BGM: Circles by Wildes
♪ If I weigh in ♪
♪ You'll give me a reason to say it ♪
She definitely is a Wonder Woman.
You were right the first time.
She's totally irrational.
Needlessly endangered her life.
But I understand why.
♪ To these motions ♪
♪ Scattered with our words never spoken ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
♪ Mm-mm-mm ♪
♪ All the circles that we move in ♪
My mother used to say I'd end up like her...
Putting my faith in the wrong people,
getting taken advantage of.
That no one would ever truly love me except her.
There are worse qualities in this world
than trying to see the best in people.
If you're a good person,
every now and again, you're gonna feel like an idiot.
Today you were wrong.
And I am still grateful that I work with you.
♪ Dreadful silence ♪
Thank you.
♪ Waiting for the moment to break it ♪
♪ I've been slipping ♪
♪ But I think that I'm gonna make it ♪
Have you had enough space yet?
♪ I lost you in the smoke ♪
♪ And I've tried patience ♪
♪ But we've just overgrown ♪
Shaun, do you remember the first time we met?
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
I was checking on a biopsy
to see if the tumor margins were in the artery walls.
Yeah.
And you said if I didn't do it right then,
you would toss a rock through my window.
Yes.
I thought it was cute how much you cared.
And when you started working in Path, I realized,
"This guy may be the most genuine person I have ever known."
You told me the truth.
That is a good thing.
That's why I like you.
That's why I don't want to lose what we have.
You hurt me.
And I worry something like that could happen again.
♪ That we move in ♪
♪ Remind me of the love... ♪
I want to be with you, Shaun.
But I don't know how this works
if you're still living with Lea.
♪ Then why are we still suffering? ♪
You...
want me not to live with Lea?
I know that's a lot to ask.
And if it's too much...
I understand.
♪ I thought love was true ♪
♪ But loneliness won, too ♪
You don't have to answer right away.
♪ Love's been runnin' out ♪
♪ Maybe I'll find solitude without you ♪
Take some time.
♪ All the circles that we move in ♪
♪ Remind me of the love we've wasted ♪
♪ If we're searching for the same thing ♪
Okay.
Okay?
I want to be with you.
I love you, Carly.