m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0
m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60
m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1
Last season on "The Flash"...
Iris isn't Iris-- the real Iris, my wife,
she is somewhere else, probably in danger.
Barry!
You targeted me from the very beginning.
- I saw everything. - As for the other Wellses,
they're as much a part of you as yourself.
You mean I'm gonna keep hearing them?
- Yeah. - I did this.
I killed the Speed Force.
I need your help to build an Artificial Speed Force.
I need my speed back if I'm gonna save Iris.
This whole time when you looked at me,
you saw this other person.
For six years, I've been in my own personal hell.
You let me rot in here while you took everything I created.
Stay out of my way, Flash.
I will be resuming my position as CEO.
My husband, Joseph, he worked tirelessly to try to find me,
only to be murdered moments after we were reunited.
Eva McCulloch has never faced us head-on.
That's about to change.
We're gonna find her, beat her,
and get back everyone.
Yeah, you're right for now, my sister, but what if?
What if the entire universe is just some kind of...
cosmic neural network?
Then what you gonna say?
Oh, okay.
Okay, okay.
You know the drill, Chester P.
Been prepping this for weeks.
Okay, now, that is...
that is not good.
Where's Eva?
Satellites have her at 2nd and Walczak.
Make that 3rd and Certo.
You doing okay?
I know the Cryo Pod keeps your residual speed forces stasis,
but waking up can be pretty disorienting.
Call Joe. Tell him I'm heading downtown.
But, Flash, you only have 1% of your speed left.
Then I better hurry.
Eva's coordinates slowed down.
- Maybe she stopped moving? - No.
She's going up.
Why do you keep interrupting my mission, Flash?
I told you,
we're on the same side.
If we're on the same side, then give me back my wife!
My fractal photons move at the speed of light.
You never had a chance.
I don't want to hurt you.
But I'm cleansing the world of Black Hole's influence,
so you either die,
or you stand down.
Flash, are you okay?
Flash?
Okay, I picked up Eva at a warehouse on 199th Street.
Suspected hideout of...
Rosa Dillon and Sam Scudder,
AKA...
- Top and Mirror Master. - Yeah.
Mirror, no!
You just killed the man I loved.
He never told you what he really was?
'Cause Sam Scudder wasn't a man.
He was my creation.
My first.
Flash?
Did you make it? Did you stop Eva?
Well, that was the best takeout world tour yet.
Coq Au Vin from Paris, sashimi from the Arctic...
The Kansas State Fair funnel cake was Clark's recommendation.
I just wish I didn't have to go back to work already.
Is anybody still here?
Allegra went home for the day.
And Kamilla,
she is...
Missing.
I've missed you so much.
No, this isn't right.
This isn't right.
Barry?
God. I'm still here.
Eva hit nine more spots last night.
I missed her every time.
How much speed do you have left?
A few days.
Maybe a few hours.
Eva's targeting Black Hole tech, right?
So why go after Scudder and Dillon?
They were working for Black Hole.
I found this in Scudder's remains.
I'm guessing they've been on Carver's payroll
since breaking out of Iron Heights last year.
And when they got in Eva's way,
she moved them off the chessboard?
Well... they are not the only ones.
The whole city thinks that Sue killed Carver.
She and Ralph are staying way off the grid.
And Caitlin and Cisco are still gone, too.
And Iris.
I should get back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
If we're gonna stop Eva and fix this,
I need the Artificial Speed Force up and running.
Well, we may not know
where Scudder moved the Black Hole tech,
but I bet you Dillon does.
I'm gonna go in,
see if I can get her to talk to me.
Actually, Captain...
I am.
Right. When you were a prosecutor,
you put Dillon in Iron Heights.
And now I'm her defense attorney that's gonna keep her out
and get her to tell me where that tech is.
That's my girl.
Connecting Fusion Sphere.
Fusion Sphere connected.
- Activate. - Uh...activated.
Oh, it's working.
Now we just have to find a fuel source to put in it.
And then, we can power the Artificial Speed Force.
Exactly.
What?
One of the sphere plates doesn't look fully magnetized.
Whoa! You can't touch that.
If you touch the Fusion Sphere while it's activated,
the Fusion Sphere thinks you're the fuel source.
Yes. And fuse my atoms,
which would lead to a complete molecular degeneration.
Sorry. I'm just trying to get your speed back.
Don't hurt yourself trying to do it.
I'd never want you to do that.
- Allen. - What?
- Can you get this guy a coffee? Wake him up? - Yes. Let's--
Hey, come on. Let's get a coffee.
Whoa, can I use that cappuccino maker
you guys have in the lounge?
- Knock yourself out. - Yes!
All right.
What? What?
Well, it's nice to see you, too.
So it turns out we cracked the fuel problem
for this A.S.F. of yours.
Pas facile non. Not easy, not great.
But so much fun, huh?
I love all the brainstorming.
Plus, we got all the Wellses back together again.
So I expect I need no introduction,
but, yes, it is I, master of stage and screen,
Harrison Orson Wells.
- Okay, you're new. - Nash, as I know you know,
when our worlds died in Crisis,
particles from our brainwaves were drawn to you like...
Like a moth drawn to a cosmic flame.
Whatever happened to show, don't tell? H.R.?
- Oh, nice catch. - I love this part.
So there are multiversal particles
inside you right now, Nash, made of synaptic energy.
Now, we take those particles
and you put them in the Fusion Sphere,
theoretically, they could power the A.S.F....
forever.
Forever.
Not only would Allen get his speed back,
but I'd be rid of you lot forever.
No, you'd be gone, too,
I mean, because of the whole organic receptor thing. Oof.
- What? - What's he talking about?
Multiversal particles are just--they're very volatile.
Right? And there's no way they'll stay in that sphere
long enough to be charged unless...
unless we have an organic receptor.
The organic receptor...
is me.
For the Flash to run again, Nash Wells must die.
No.
- What? - No way!
- Nash, you're our organic receptor.
You're the only one that can contain us
inside the Fusion Sphere.
By dying?
- By dying, Harry? - Yes.
- How stupid do you think I am? - Come on.
I have a life here now.
I have people that I actually don't hate.
I'm not gonna give all that up so Barry Allen can run fast!
Nash, you're the only one of us that can help Allen.
And I will, Harry, by figuring out another way
to save Allen that doesn't mean I have to commit suicide!
- Nash! - Where he's going?
Bozos!
Didn't see that coming.
And scene.
What the hell?
Maybe I can message Kamilla.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
My wife died in the particle accelerator explosion!
You're not...
even...
human.
You do not control me anymore, Joseph.
She killed Sam right in front of me.
If you tell me
where you and Scudder were moving that tech,
I can use that information to strike a deal for you
with the state and...
catch Sam's killer.
I wish I knew, but Sam made all the deals.
That's funny.
Your IHP file says that you were running
a psychotropic drug ring out of the Meta-Wing.
You were flush with cash, and
It's just that you felt so sad
when you were remembering that time.
It's almost as--
almost as if you were deliberately projecting
a fake emotion at me,
but why would you do that?
Why would you do that unless you already knew
that I was an empath?
How would I know that?
I'm not psychic. I just cause vertigo.
What else can you do inside people's minds, Rosa?
Let me show you.
I feel so empty.
What did you do to me?
What did you do to me? What did you do to me?
I found a little kernel of doubt inside of you
and spun, spun, spun it
into a full-blown crisis of confidence...
like a top.
Scudder's ditzy girlfriend?
It was all an act.
I was always the brains.
He was just the pretty face.
Then Sam cut a deal with Black Hole.
We got rich, but we were in over our heads.
So, when I heard Eva McCulloch wanted him dead...
You sold him out to her.
And in return,
Eva gave me a cause to believe in.
She delegated her next mission to me.
And what I've cooked up for her
is gonna blow this city away.
If you are planning something
that will put people in danger--
What?
The Flash is gonna stop me?
He can barely run.
You know, when I first got my powers,
I was an empath, too.
And look what I've grown into.
Who knows what you would've become
if only you weren't so...
afraid?
Guess we'll never know.
Thought you could use a pick-me-up.
Thank you.
"Organic Receptors in Nuclear Physics."
- Yeah. Yeah. - What's an organic receptor?
Ah, no. I'm just, uh...
This is--I'm just helping Barry
get his speed back, or I'm trying to, anyway.
Well, it's nice to see you care about someone
other than me for a change.
Well, you're...
You're the answer.
Multiversal particles
oscillate at certain frequencies of light.
Allegra can control electromagnetic wavelengths.
So she can push the particles out of you
- and into the Fusion Sphere. - Right.
Charging a fuel source for the A.S.F.
And we take all that kinetic energy,
and we just transfer it to the track ring above us--
giving Flash his groove back.
- Uh, just--just one thing. - What?
Aren't multiverse particles a little too chaotic
to be contained in a Fusion Sphere?
Yes, normally they would be, but Allegra can use her powers
to contain the particles inside the Fusion Sphere
from a safe distance.
Hey, thanks for looking out for me,
but if Nash says it's gonna work, I trust him.
Okay.
All right, then.
- Ready? - Yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
The Fusion Sphere is....
- ready for particle insertion. - Okay.
- Good? - Yeah.
Guys...
something's not right.
What's happening?
The charge is dropping.
I can't hold it much longer.
A-Allen?
- Barry, you okay? - Please be okay.
Please be okay.
Hello.
Qu'est ce qui se passe?
What are you all doing?
Uh, since when do you speak French?
- Since always, no? - Why is he talking funny?
I think when the particles left the Fusion Sphere,
they transferred to Barry Allen.
So all the brainwaves of all the Wellses who've ever lived...
Are inside monsieur Allen's mind.
Allow me, introduce myself.
I'm Sherloque Wells,
master detective, at your service.
I'm Chester. Chester P. Runk.
- Chester. - Yeah.
- There's a Sherlock Wells? - Sherloque.
Yes, there's a Sherlock Wells.
- Sherloque. - -loque.
- lock. - Sherlock.
- loque. - lock.
- loque. - loque.
Good. Good. No great.
Vite, mes Ami.
We face a mystery stranger
than the King Tut Killer
of Earth-66.
- The Many Minds of Barry Allen. - Oh, man.
All of them ended up inside Barry?
It looks like, but, listen, let's not panic.
Between the three of us and a master detective,
we can figure out how to fix Barry Allen.
You guys talking about B.A.?
He's so fast!
- What just happened to him? - I think another set
of Wells particles just took over his mind.
H.R. Wells. How you guys doing?
Yeah, so this is simple--we just get all the Wellses
out of B.A. Into the Futon Sphere.
It's a--Stop. It's a Fusion Sphere.
Can you stop drumming?
Can you stop drum--okay.
The drumming is so annoying--
Do you hear the drums?
They are coming.
It is I,
Wells the Grey.
- Oh, Wells the Grey. - There's a wizard Wells?
This is all my fault.
Oh, my God. Do you know Gandalf?
Barry trusted me to help him, and I screwed up.
No, it's not...
it's not your fault.
Look, here's what we'll do.
Um, just blast him again,
and we'll push the particles back into me.
Uh-uh. No way. I'll just make it worse.
No, you won't make it worse.
All we got to do is figure out a way to contain
the particles once they leave Allen's body, like a magnet--
Guys? Guys?
What are you?
Can't figure it out?
Did you lose your dissertation?
- You're a copy of me. - No. I'm no fractal anomaly.
I am a product of your broken mind.
- That's impossible. - No, it's not.
You pushed your mind to find Singh until it broke...
Forever.
Leave me alone.
There's no escaping this, Iris.
How long have you been trying to get out?
Weeks? Months?
You are weak in every universe--
an insignificant speck,
a victim.
Okay. Okay.
Don't worry. I'm gonna use the Mobile Gideon
to diagnose him.
So, Gideon, what's wrong with Barry?
An abundance of multiversal particles
inside his mind are causing his cerebral cortex to overload.
Yeah, all those brainwaves at once?
It's like when Grodd was trapped in his mind,
but to an infinite degree.
Only Barry Allen's speed healing is keeping him alive now.
Gideon, what happens when his speed runs out?
If the particles remain inside his brain,
Barry Allen will instantly die.
Barry is going to die because of what I did to him.
No. No. I should've trusted my gut.
Look, I knew we needed something else
to keep the sphere intact.
Yeah. That was supposed to be my stupid powers.
No, they're not stupid.
The particles always needed something stronger,
like some sort of...
I don't know, some sort of organic receptor.
That's what you were researching in your office.
You let me think I was the only solution,
when this whole time, there was another way?
- No, it's not that simple-- - Yes, it is.
- You lied! - Yes! I lied!
Because I'm the organic receptor.
And I'm not ready to die yet.
Okay, look, Barry wouldn't let anyone die
for the Artificial Speed Force.
Yeah, so why lie about it?
Because I was scared.
I get it.
I thought you had changed.
- Chuck-- - It's Chester P., actually, but--
I need a way to aim the particles
after I push them out of Barry.
Like a particle magnet?
I can build that.
Oh, I mean, I can try.
Lead the way.
What the hell?
Harry--
Look at these brainwave ratings.
Allen's cerebellum is burning up.
Harry, if you want the kid to survive,
- then maybe you better relax-- - I'm fine!
I'm fine. Do not touch me.
What happened to the J.V. Squad?
Why are you moping around here instead of helping them?
Oh, they don't want my help. Right?
Frankly, I don't blame them.
- Garcia found out the truth? - Yeah.
You know what Cisco said after Crisis?
He said, "An infinite number of Harrison Wells,
and we're stuck with the one who killed the Multiverse."
And every day I ask myself, why?
Why am I the one left standing?
So who should've gotten the slot?
One of us bozos?
You're not bozos. I only called you that because
I find the Wells very annoying-- present company excluded.
But you know what you are?
You're a daily reminder
that even though we may all look the same,
we're not the same...
because you're all good men.
And I'm...
I'm not.
So you're a selfish jerk.
You think that I wasn't?
That we all weren't?
Hell, when I met this team, I was working for Zoom.
H.R. Lied.
Sherloque...
kept secrets.
We all came here broken men.
Thanks to Team Flash,
eventually we learned to be better.
That's why I believe in you, Nash.
There's a good man in there somewhere.
You just need to dig him up, let him breathe.
You're not real. You're not real.
- No, I'm not crazy. - Yeah, you are.
And there's only two options in this place--
survival...
Or madness.
No.
This is not neural dissonance.
I'm not seeing you because I'm--
I'm crazy and broken.
This is something else...
someone else.
Keep trying to break me down...
because I am not afraid of the woman that I am today.
But you are...
Eva.
You want me distracted.
I must be getting close...
to finding my way out of here.
You can push yourself until you break,
and you will never escape this world.
I'm sorry, Iris,
but if you can't accept my conditions either,
you might never see your husband again.
Wow. You actually came back.
I'm a defense attorney, Rosa.
I can handle a few mind games.
I'm here to get you a deal.
Am I supposed to be intimidated by you now?
The woman who's afraid of her own powers?
Maybe you're right, okay? Maybe--maybe I am afraid.
When I first got these abilities,
I was so excited.
But then when my powers-- they started to grow
and change,
and I...
I bottled them up because I was afraid.
I was afraid I was gonna become someone like you.
Are you trying to rile me up?
No, Rosa.
I'm trying to remind myself
of all of that fear
that I have locked down
deep inside...
so that I can put it all into you.
My heart...is...racing!
You want to go back to prison?
Or do you want to tell me what you're planning?
Hey. What's wrong?
There's a supersonic jet about to leave
a secret Black Hole site in the Badlands,
and it is loaded with all of Carver's remaining tech.
But that's not the only thing it's carrying.
Rosa Dillon planted a bomb on board.
If it blows over this city, hundreds of people will die.
And the Flash isn't fast enough to stop it.
Okay. Okay. Here, put this on.
Once Allegra pushes the particles outside of Barry,
these ionic circuits will catch them, put them back into you.
- Smart, Runk. - That's brilliant.
Thanks.
Listen, when this is over,
I'll find a way to make this up to you.
This is a pretty good start.
- Ready? - Yeah.
It's working. Keep going.
Barry?
Are you...Barry?
Yeah. It's really me.
All right, let's celebrate later,
because we still have a supersonic jet
about to explode over the city.
I still can't stop it.
The plane's only three minutes out.
We need a plan.
No.
We need the Flash.
Nash!
- That'll kill you. - I know.
But I'm the organic receptor that we need.
You're getting your speed back.
We'll find another way.
What other way, Allen?
- There's no time. - Nash.
You don't have to do this just to prove a point.
I'm not doing it to prove a point.
I'm doing it because I won't watch you die.
I won't let any of you die.
Don't! Don't! Don't!
No, no, no, no, no. If you touch him, we'll lose you, too.
Nash, please.
I can't let anyone else die for me.
I've already lost so many people.
Do you know what I feel right now, Allen?
Pride.
Honor.
It's been so long since I felt those things.
And it's not just me.
The Council feels it, too.
And we've made our decision.
We're doing this, Allen.
Is it charging?
Yeah, the Fusion Sphere is charging.
How can I be the Flash without a Wells on this team?
You've always been the Flash.
You always will be...
with or without me.
Hey, B.A.
How's it going?
You're so fast.
No, no, no. B.A., don't be upset.
This is not goodbye. It's just...
till our next communion.
Not great, hmm?
Our current situation, huh? But...
it will be.
Allen...
you know, when I came to your stupid Earth...
With its good burgers...
lost, angry, blah, blah, blah,
and you showed me...
how to be a better person.
And I'll always be grateful for our friendship.
Now...
Run.
Barry...
run.
We're at 80%.
You got this.
After I'm gone...
look out for one another.
A.R.G.U.S. Was waiting for the jet when it landed.
They seized all the Black Hole tech on board.
All thanks to the Flash.
So Nash died a hero.
And I...
I never really got to know him.
Look, I know after tonight that none of us will...
ever be the same.
But we all heard what Nash said.
He was so happy to have you in his life.
Thanks, Chester.
Y-you can call me Chuck.
I need to tell the rest of the team.
I'll call Carla, make sure Caitlin knows.
Cisco's gonna want to come back from his trip.
Harry was like a father to him.
When they were all in my mind, I could...
I could feel their spirits.
I could feel how much they loved me.
They gave themselves up for me.
How am I supposed to live with that?
Uh, I think that's the point.
You know, they put themselves in the A.S.F.
so you could live...
and thrive.
And now, whenever you run,
it'll kind of be like they'll be running with you.
Right?
You know, Nash wasn't
the only one who rose to the occasion today.
I wouldn't be here if it wasn't for you guys.
So...
what now, Flash?
We go save Iris and our friends.
We get everybody back.
Eva, what was that? Are you okay?
Eva?
Help!
Someone help me!
I died.
Everything I thought was a lie.
I'm the mirror duplicate.