My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
By something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
But secretly,
I use my speed to fight crime
And find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
The night we trapped
the Reverse-Flash
In the force field,
there's no reason
That the containment system
should have failed.
- I've been having these dreams.
- What happens in the dream?
Dr. Wells is the Reverse-Flash,
And he kills me.
If this is Dr. Wells,
Then who have we been working
for this whole time?
A completely different person.
Oh, my god.
What the frack?
"Flash missing.
Vanishes in crisis."
"after an epic street battle
with the Reverse-Flash,
"our city's
very own scarlet speedster
Disappeared in an explosion
of light."
Barry, look at the date.
April 25th, 2024.
Guys, when I fought
the Reverse-Flash at christmas,
He said that we'd be fighting
for centuries.
Wait, you can't really think
that this is from...
The future.
That would means Dr. Wells,
or whoever he is, is also...
From the future.
I have to say,
I'm really digging
The brighter red suit.
And the white
on the symbol?
That's dope.
Wait a second.
Suppose we now change
the color on your suit.
Will it be because we got
the idea from this picture?
That would mean
we're living in a causal nexus.
This... wow.
This is so trippy.
Like, Marty and the Polaroid
trippy.
Not as trippy as the name
on the byline.
Iris West-Allen?
Mazel Tov?
Hebrew.
Ancient language
of the Jewish people.
Uh-uh.
What the hell was that?
Is someone here?
Hello?
Good evening,
Barry Allen.
Uh...
H-Hi.
- You know who I am?
- Of course.
Barry Allen,
Director of Central City Police,
CSI division.
Director?
I guess
you get a promotion.
Also known as The Flash.
Founding member of...
What are you?
I am Gideon,
An interactive
artificial consciousness.
Ai.
Sick.
You know Dr. Wells?
Yes.
Do you know who he really is?
I don't understand the question.
I...I mean,
what is he doing here?
W-why did he come here?
To kill you.
Wells is in the building.
What?
How do you know that?
I put a tracker
on his wheelchair.
Which, if we're wrong about him
and he is paralyzed,
I'm going to hell
for that one.
He's in the cortex.
Ask questions fast.
Why did he kill Nora Allen?
Because he was angry.
About what?
That you escaped.
He's on B level.
He's coming this way.
What does he want from me?
For you to be the Flash.
Maybe that's why wells let
The Particle Accelerator
Explode,
So that you could become
the Flash.
Why?
I mean, for what reason?
Guys, we got to go.
He's almost here.
- Hurry.
- All right.
Wait a second.
Wait.
What if Hal over there tells
Wells that we were in here?
That would be bad.
If I can get into
its operating system,
Maybe I can disable
its memory core.
Gideon, can you show us where
your operating system is?
Certainly.
Yeah.
Nope.
That's not gonna happen.
Guys, he's in
the corridor.
Gideon, could you just,
like,
Not tell him that we were here?
Of course.
I will accept any command
given to me by you.
- Barry.
- Come on.
- We got to get out of here.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Why would you accept
my commands?
Because you created me.
Good evening, Gideon.
Good evening, Dr. Wells.
Is everything all right?
Everything is fine.
Eddie.
- Thank you.
- What's the emergency?
Oh, no emergency.
I just wanted to,
you know, talk to you...
Thanks.
Without Iris around
Or Barry around
Or Cisco around
or Caitlin around.
So, in other words,
you want to talk to me alone.
What is it?
Right.
Um, so listen.
With everything going on...
Investigating Wells
and finding out about Barry...
Eddie, you cannot tell Iris
about Barry.
This isn't about Barry.
I know the timing
might seem off, you know,
With everything
that's going on,
But I want to propose to iris,
And I'd like your blessing.
No.
Come again?
You do not have my blessing.
That's Barry.
We got to go.
Joe, I only asked
as a courtesy,
Out of respect.
I don't need your permission.
Really?
For three very smart people,
That was really stupid.
What if wells had caught you
in that...
- Time vault.
- Thank you.
Okay, I know we've seen
a lot this past year,
But time travel?
I did it.
- Or I will do it, I mean.
- Excuse me?
One of the two speedsters
in Barry's house
The night his mother died
was Barry.
I mean, The Flash.
He was there.
Which means that one day
in the future,
Barry will travel back in time
to that night.
Okay.
Actually, I wasn't talking
about that.
I kind of already
time traveled.
- By accident.
- What?
I was running to
try and stop a Tsunami
From hitting the city...
When was that?
A few weeks ago.
Right before you started
getting those dreams.
Oh, you mean the ones
where Wells uses
His super-speeding hand
to shred apart my heart?
- Those?
- Yes, right.
So, what if they're not dreams?
What else could they be?
Memories.
I'm not following.
All right, what if, that day,
Cisco found out
That Wells is the Reverse-Flash,
and then Wells killed him?
But when I ran back a day,
I changed the timeline
so that event never happened.
If it never happened,
how can Cisco remember it?
I don't know.
I think the important thing is,
he does.
Guys, I think
I've got a really bad idea.
Dad, it's been three weeks.
You barely eat or sleep.
You should probably go home
at some point.
- Hey, baby.
- Hi.
I'll go home when Barry does.
Oh, my god.
Help!
My son's coding.
They said he was stable.
Barry.
- Oh, my god.
- I need the room.
Just go.
I need the room.
How can he be seizing?
He has no heart rhythm.
- Starting compressions.
- Epi push. Epi.
They can't save him.
But I can.
I know who you are.
You're that scientist
that Barry's obsessed with,
The one who blew a hole
in the city.
Harrison Wells,
and interestingly enough,
My facility is the very place
I would like to take him.
You're out of your mind.
I'm not gonna try and
convince you with promises.
But, detective,
give me a chance.
I think we already know
what you're capable of, doctor.
You hurt a lot of people
that night.
So those doctors in there,
they're good enough?
The best in the city,
best in the country.
Look at them.
They have no clue
what's going on.
They're baffled,
and the reason for that is
What's happening
inside Barry is a mystery,
And they don't have
the tools to solve it.
- But you do?
- That's right.
Millions of people
Used to look at my lab,
and what did they see?
They saw the future.
Well, let me take
that technology,
Let me take that know-how
into ensuring
That your son
actually does have a future.
Detective.
Let me save him.
- Hand me the paddles.
- Starting compressions.
Then save him.
Charge.
200. Pads.
Joe?
Joe, are you listening?
Yeah.
We... we have to access
Cisco's memories somehow.
Somewhere in his subconscious
is the key.
The key to what now?
Getting my dad out of prison.
And how are we going to do that?
We're gonna get Wells to confess
to killing my mom.
So, this will allow Cisco
to see into his dream?
I got the idea
from a journal article
On Lucid dream therapy.
They think it can be used
to help people
Suffering from post-traumatic
stress disorder.
Traumatized, stressed?
Check and check.
The theory is that
it will allow people
To objectively enter
their dreams
And face their fears.
Still working on
the talking part.
And you're sure this thing
isn't gonna, you know,
Mess with my brain?
Oh, the amount of electricity
required
To trigger Lucid dreaming
is harmless.
Probably.
Who's going to be
Lucid dreaming?
Um...
With all of the meta-humans
in Central City,
People have been seeing
some strange things...
Things that
they don't understand.
And it's really just
a matter of time
Before psychological issues
develop.
And Lucid dreaming will help
the doctors
Better understand their fears.
Intriguing.
Of course, you still need to
guide the patient
From the outside, right?
Direct them to
specific aspects of the dream.
We're still working
on a communications interface.
When we dream,
The middle brain lights up
with electrical activity,
Whereas the higher brain
remains dormant.
Once we find a way to make
both parts of the brain active,
Then it's just a matter of
finding the frequency
That will stimulate
the language center.
Then the dreamer could speak.
He could describe his dream.
- Exactly.
- Or her dream.
It could be used for anyone.
Right, it's not gender specific.
I would try a frequency of
45 hertz to start.
Thank you, Dr. Wells.
Well, you never cease to
impress me, Caitlin.
- Allen.
- Hey.
The owens case.
I'm still waiting
on the fiber evidence
And the ballistics report.
Are you on vacation
or something?
- No, I'm so sorry, I've just...
I've been distracted
by another case.
Which is no excuse,
I just...
Okay, just get me the reports
when you can.
There's... there's no rush.
All right.
Uh, Captain?
Is everything okay?
Yeah, since Rob and I
have been planning the,
You know, wedding,
between the florist
And the hundreds of kinds
of cake filling
And who can sit next to who...
Never get married, Allen.
Right.
- Oh.
- Iris.
- Barry.
- Hey.
Are you okay?
Yeah. No. Yes.
That was...
That was just really weird.
Captain Singh was
nice to me.
Oh, well, he's in a good mood.
He's about to get married.
Lucky him.
Yeah, I know, it's...
Oh, hey,
can I talk to you in private?
It's... it's kind of work-related.
Okay, yeah,
now's not a great time.
- I'm sorry, I've got...
- Hi, beautiful.
Hi.
Barry, can I grab you
for a second?
Absolutely.
Yeah.
Okay, well, can you call me
when you're done?
It's... it's really important.
Yeah.
What's up?
Oh.
O-okay.
W-what did she say?
Or, wait, you still have it, so,
duh, you haven't asked her yet.
Or you did ask her,
and she said...
- I was gonna propose tonight.
- All right.
But I went to joe
to ask for his blessing.
- He said no.
- He did? He...
- Repeatedly.
- Uh, weird.
I need you to talk to him,
find out why.
Uh, Eddie...
Look, I know me
asking you like this,
It's a little awkward.
Yeah.
But you know how heartbroken
she's gonna be
If she finds out
that Joe's not on board.
Yeah.
Yeah, all right.
Yeah, I'll talk to him, man.
Oh, thanks.
I appreciate it so much.
- Yeah.
- And so will
The future
Mrs. Thawne.
Iris Thawne.
Sounds pretty good, huh?
I have a feeling
she's gonna want to hyphenate.
Okay, can we go over this
one more time?
Yeah, you put the glasses on,
fall asleep, and start dreaming.
Not that hard.
Yeah, except I'm pretty sure
I die in this dream.
If I go back into it,
am I gonna die in real life?
I mean, what are
we talking about here?
Is this inception
or dreamscape?
Here.
Drink this.
- What, am I five?
- Just drink it.
Okay, I'll drink it.
You're gonna be fine, Cisco.
Mm.
Okay.
The glasses are emitting
a Low-Level Delta Wave
Which should help you
fall asleep.
Okay.
I got to warn you, though,
Usually it takes me
a long time.
I mean...
I'm not saying I'm, like...
An insomniac or any...
Ah, so that's how you get him
to shut up.
He's entering rem.
It's working.
Cisco.
Can you hear me?
You're dreaming, bud.
Okay, I will take Dr. West
to jitters
So you do whatever it is
you want to do.
Whoa.
Guys, this is mad freaky.
Okay, um, where are you?
Um, in the cortex.
I mean, I know I'm just dreaming
that I'm in the cortex,
But it feels so real.
What is dream you doing?
Caitlin just left.
I asked her to
take Wells to jitters.
Why... why do you want Wells
out of the lab?
I think he might have
tampered with my work.
I need to check.
Okay.
Okay, I'm walking to the bunker.
Oh, man, I love this shirt.
I thought the dryer ate it.
Focus, Cisco.
Okay, okay.
All right.
Now I'm running tests
on the containment system.
This data...
It doesn't make any sense.
All the supercapacitors...
They were all still
fully charged.
There's absolutely no reason
that the man in yellow
Should have escaped.
Oh, my god.
It was just a hologram.
He tricked us.
Hello, Cisco.
Oh, god, Wells is here.
Cisco, it's just a dream.
He can't hurt you.
You better be right
about that.
My name is Eobard Thawne.
Eobard Thawne.
Thawne?
Like Eddie Thawne?
You killed Nora Allen.
It was never my intention.
Nora?
What about my mom?
- He's confessing.
- Cisco?
He... he didn't want to kill her.
It was you, Barry.
He was trying to
kill you.
Guys, he's losing
higher brain function.
Cisco, you're gonna be okay.
It's just a dream.
You're gonna be okay.
I have grown quite fond of you,
Cisco.
His hand...
It's vibrating.
- He's gonna have a stroke.
- Get him out of there!
In many ways,
You've shown me
what it's like...
- Help me.
- Caitlin.
Help me, please!
To have a son.
Help me!
Aah!
You're okay.
It was just a dream.
Oh, god.
It felt so real.
- Barry?
- My mom.
That's why it's my fault.
Hello?
Where are you?
Barry.
Barry, are you there?
Dr. Wells.
Yeah.
It's... sorry, yeah.
It's... it's a bad connection
right now.
Where have you been?
Uh, we're...
Why? What's going on?
A fire.
A huge fire just erupted.
A fire?
Where?
New Brighton.
Bradford tower high-rise.
I know that building.
That's where Captain Singh's
fiance works.
On my way.
Now move it!
Go!
Get those hoses up.
Move!
And tell dispatch we need
As many tankers
as this city has.
- What floor?
- 21st.
My god.
That's where Rob works.
Please hurry.
Over here!
Dr. Wells, the sprinklers...
They're not working.
I see that.
Just get everyone
out of there, Barry.
No, I can't.
I can't save them all.
Dr. Wells, please, what do I do?
You create a vacuum.
Rotate your arms
at super-speed.
That'll create a wind funnel
That will suck the air
right out of the room.
It's making it worse!
Barry, listen to me.
You need to move
your arms faster.
I believe in you, Barry.
Rob.
I'm okay.
It's okay.
I thought I lost you.
Medic!
Mr. Allen.
Tonight, at the fire,
I saw hesitation.
I saw you doubting yourself.
Why is that?
I don't know.
Uh, I guess I was afraid
I couldn't save everyone.
Right.
But if there is anything
that I have learned
In our time together, Barry,
It is that the only thing
standing in the way of you
Achieving every goal
that you set for yourself
Is you.
There is no limit
to how strong you will get
Or how fast you will go.
Everything that you need,
You already have.
Thank you, Dr. Wells.
You know,
I couldn't have done
any of this without you.
I feel the same way about you.
It's so strange.
I mean, I look at him now,
And I know that he killed my mom
and he sent my dad to jail,
But, I mean,
sometimes he's just so kind
In the moment,
I actually like him.
But you never did.
- No.
Well, at least now
we know how to trap him.
In Cisco's dream,
he confessed to everything.
If we can just recreate
those conditions,
He'll do it again.
Man, Barr.
Taking down bad guys,
pulling confessions.
I'm the cop.
I'm the one that's supposed
to be doing this.
Look, if we're gonna get him
to confess,
It has to be with someone
that he truly trusts,
Someone that he'll genuinely
let his guard down with.
He thinks of Cisco as a son.
Well, then we need to do
a better job protecting him
Than I did protecting you.
I'm not sure
what that means.
Barry,
this is all because of me.
No.
I never should've let Wells
take you from that hospital.
None of this would've
ever happened.
If you hadn't let him take me,
I would be dead, for sure.
But even then,
I knew something wasn't right.
Everything in my gut
was telling me not to trust him,
But I did,
Because I was so desperate
to see you okay.
Joe, this isn't your fault.
It's not your fault.
Look, every bad thing
that has happened to us...
All of it...
It was him.
And now he's gonna pay for it.
So, Wells set up a fake showdown
With a fake opponent
who was never really there?
He figured if we saw
both of them together
It would prove that he wasn't
the man in yellow.
This all just keeps getting
crazier and crazier.
I just talked to Dr. Wells.
He's attending
a lecture downtown,
Won't be back until 5:00.
All right, Cisco,
you know when he gets here
You need to be working
on the trap
So he sees you set off
the hologram.
Hold on,
isn't that, in your dream,
When everything went all...
Kali Ma.
Temple of doom.
Yeah, that definitely happened.
But this time,
I'm ready for him.
I originally designed
the force field
To keep a speedster
from getting out.
But I've reversed it.
Now it won't let one in.
Back up.
Barry, are you okay?
Ah.
It works.
Okay,
as long as I'm inside,
Wells won't be able
to get near me.
And I will be in the cortex
Watching and recording
everything that happens.
And as soon as we get
the confession we need
To free my dad,
I'm moving in.
So what do I do?
Wells also threatened iris,
So if something
goes wrong here,
We need you to keep an eye
on her
Until wells is neutralized.
I'll always keep iris safe,
Joe.
- What?
- Come here.
So, um, Eddie told me
what happened,
That you kiboshed
his proposal.
That was supposed to be
between him and me.
I so agree with that.
And I... and I know that we have
a lot going on right now,
And I should definitely be
the last person
Pleading Eddie's case,
but I don't get it, Joe.
Why did you say no?
Because if Eddie
proposes to Iris,
She's gonna get caught up
in the moment and the romance,
And she's gonna say yes.
What's wrong with that?
Again, I don't know
why I'm saying this.
Because one day
she's gonna wake up and realize
She married the wrong guy.
But she'll stay anyway
because she made a promise.
I don't want
that kind of life for her.
Or him.
She's got feelings for you,
Barry.
She may not know how to deal
with those feelings right now,
But I know her.
They're there.
Always have been.
You know that, too.
Speaking of,
Iris just sent me a 911 text.
I'll be right back.
Like I said.
- Hey.
- Hi.
What's going on?
Look, Barry, I know
it's not a good time.
I mean, lately, it never seems
to be a good time,
But I need you to listen to me
right now.
Like... like, really
listen to me.
Of course.
Yeah.
Whatever you need to tell me,
I'm listening.
Okay, I mean,
I know this is gonna sound
Really crazy at first,
but...
Everything strange that's been
going on in Central City,
It all goes back to
that night.
The night that the particle
accelerator exploded.
I have gone through
every bit of information
That I've collected
since I started my blog...
Every tip, every rumor,
every strange sighting.
Nothing predates the explosion.
Whatever was released
into the atmosphere that night,
I think
it changed people...
Caused them to have powers.
And I think that
S.T.A.R. Labs knew about it.
I think the burning man
worked there,
And I think that that's how
the Flash got his powers too.
- Uh...
- So what do you think?
I...
I don't know.
I mean, it's... it's interesting.
Yeah, it's interesting.
It's... there's... there's just...
A big hole
in your theory.
Um, you know...
I was affected by whatever was
released by the explosion,
And I don't have any powers.
- Obviously.
- Right, yeah.
Look, I mean, I know that it's...
It's really mind-blowing.
I mean, I haven't even talked to
Eddie about it yet, but...
Yeah, you and Eddie...
How are...
Everything's okay
with you and Eddie?
Uh, sure.
Sure.
Yeah, we're great.
Why?
Uh, I...
Yeah, okay, look.
I'm gonna... let me read over
all of this stuff,
And we'll definitely
talk about it later.
I promise.
Just... I mean, this is crazy.
Yeah, okay, just let me
just go through it,
And we'll talk later,
all right?
Okay.
Hey, Barry.
It's Iris.
I don't know if you can hear me,
but I hope you can,
Because I really, really
need you to wake up.
Like, the other day,
Detective pretty boy
came into jitters,
And he asked me out,
and I actually said yes.
See, I do dumb things like that
when you're not around.
And the house is really
quiet without you.
I know that the reason
that you came to live with us
Was awful.
But Barry,
You made it a home again.
You made us a family again.
We need you.
I need you.
Hello, Dr. Wells.
How was your lecture?
Oh, boring, tedious.
Platitudinous?
Couldn't have said it better
myself.
Um, where...
Where's Cisco?
Uh, he is in the bunker.
He thinks he finally figured out
what went wrong at christmas.
You know, when we were trying
to catch the Reverse-Flash?
Yes, I remember that night.
Well, did he say
what he's found?
Nope,
just that it was important.
Hmm.
Good for Cisco.
Um... Okay.
Well, maybe
I'll wheel on down there,
See what he's got.
Okay.
Here he comes.
Hello, Cisco.
You've been busy.
You really are
incredibly clever, Cisco.
I've always said it.
You're him.
The Reverse-Flash.
Joe was right this whole time,
wasn't he?
Good ol' Joe.
Joe West had his doubts
all along.
Even from that first night
in the hospital,
Joe knew
something wasn't right.
Cops... as inconvenient now
As they will be
in a hundred years.
Come on, Cisco.
We need a confession.
You killed Barry's mother.
I want to know why.
It was never my intention
to kill Nora.
But from my perspective,
She was already dead.
It just happened sooner
than it was supposed to.
No.
That's not an admission.
Oops.
You're not gonna get away
with this.
I'm not gonna get away
with it?
Oh, you're smart.
You're smart, Cisco.
But you're not that smart.
Cisco!
No!
He didn't confess.
Cisco, are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm never ever gonna sleep
ever again,
But, yeah, I'm okay.
He's dead.
He didn't confess.
Joe, this was it.
My dad's gonna be in prison
forever.
Barry, I'm sorry.
Hey, uh...
Whoa.
What the hell?
I told you this before.
I am always
one step ahead... Flash.
Allow me
to reintroduce to you
Mr. Hannibal Bates
And his incredible ability
to transform
Into any person he touches.
I knew that ability
would come in handy.
I did not expect it
to come in handy this soon.
You used him!
Like you used all of us!
Well, he served a purpose.
Didn't take much convincing.
Just the simple promise
of his freedom.
You ruined my life!
All our lives!
We stood by you
after everything that happened.
I can see how this must be
difficult for you to understand,
But trust me,
Your lives now
are so much better
Because of what
I have done for you.
You don't have to
hide anymore.
We know you're not
Harrison Wells.
Just tell us who you are.
A confession
will get you nowhere.
You've seen who I am.
You know what I can do.
You want to kill me, go ahead.
I'm not gonna fight you.
But just tell the police
what you did.
Get my dad out of prison.
I don't want to kill you, Barry.
I need you.
And...
I also did not anticipate,
As difficult as the past
15 years have been for me,
How much I would come
to love working with you.
With all of you.
And yet, that does not change
what needs to happen.
Then face me now!
Oh, we will face each other
again.
I promise you.
Soon.
Very, very soon.
He's in the time vault!
Barry!
It was all a set-up.
We thought we set
a trap for him,
But he set a trap for us.
Oh, my god.
Iris.
We have to find Iris.
- Why?
- Wells.
He's been watching
all of us.
He has surveillance footage
set up everywhere.
Our homes, my lab
at the police station,
Central City picture news.
Cisco, call me
when you have a location.
I am very much enjoying
this stroll.
We needed a good stroll.
Yeah.
Actually, though, would you mind
if we park here for a second?
Um...
Oh, it's my dad.
Could you call him back later?
Sure.
What's going on?
Iris, this week,
when I was arrested
And it looked bad,
You never wavered.
You never lost faith in me.
Impossible.
And even though we've been
through some rough times,
I've never lost faith in us.
Iris West.
Eddie?
Eddie!
Bad timing, Detective.
Stop!
Leave him alone!
Iris, no!
I know who you are.
You killed Barry's mom.
But you don't have to hurt
anyone else.
Hey, Iris.
It's okay.
It's me.
He took him.
The man in yellow,
he took Eddie.
I promise I will find him,
okay?
What is happening?
Listen to me.
You go home.
Don't say anything to anyone.
I swear to you, I will
bring him back, all right?
Wait, stop.
Barry?
You might as well take
that mask off.
I know it's you, Wells.
Or whoever you really are.
Well, allow to
to introduce myself.
My name is Eobard.
Eobard Thawne.
I don't understand.
Why do you have my name?
Why?
Well, 'cause we're family,
Eddie.
Funny, I haven't seen you
at any reunions or weddings.
That is funny.
And the reason for that
Is because as far as
those guest lists are concerned,
I haven't been born yet.
So that's why you didn't kill me
that night at S.T.A.R. Labs?
This whole thing...
It's been about me?
Not a chance.
You, my friend,
Are simply my insurance.
You look so young.
And I could kill you
Right now so easy.
What I wouldn't have given...
All those times before
to have had you like this.
So...
Helpless.
But fate,
It's tricky, isn't it?
I come here to destroy you...
And then to get home,
I have to be the one
Who creates you.
But I will say,
It's been an education...
Watching you grow up
all these years.
Science fairs
and soccer games.
No hint, no sign,
No trace of the man
you will be one day
For whom I have
nothing but hate.
And to be clear,
Nothing is forgiven.
There will be a reckoning.
I promise you, Barry Allen,
That you will die.
Greg, move your head.