Last season, on "The Flash"...
What's happening to me?
I wasn't the only one affected, was I?
We've been searching for other meta-humans,
like yourself.
Don't be afraid, Cisco.
You were affected, too.
Once upon a time, you agreed to marry me.
Yes, I did.
What do you say we do that?
Harrison Wells is the Reverse-Flash.
You killed my mother!
Why?
We're enemies, rivals, opposites,
reverses of one another.
Just tell the police what you did.
Get my dad out of prison!
You could go back and save your mother.
A wormhole, opening the gateway
into time itself.
I always win, Flash!
Eddie!
Eddie's his ancestor. If Eddie dies,
he'll never be born.
He's being erased from existence.
The singularity won't stop,
not even after the Earth is gone.
We have to disrupt the motion.
It cannot be stopped!
I have to try.
- He's coming back around!
- Yeah, to die!
I swear one of these days I will kill you!
I was late again, wasn't I?
Right on time.
Whoo!
Two down at the same time?
Superhero double play, baby!
- Didn't do it alone.
- You're never alone, Barry.
Neither are you, Mrs. Raymond.
Thank you for not doing that
when I was inside you.
It happened one time. Let it go.
Snart and Rory.
You're gonna put a cop
like me out of a job.
Just trying to help.
You do more than help, Barry.
You give the people of this city hope.
You're the hero, Barry.
Congratulations, everyone.
A spectacular victory.
A milestone, if you will.
Mr. Allen, I believe there's
nothing left I can teach you.
I believe...
that you're ready to do
all of this on your own.
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident made me the impossible,
and I became the Flash.
I used my powers to find the man
responsible for my mother's death.
I thought I would finally
get justice for my family,
but I failed.
It's been six months
since the Singularity.
I'm on my own now.
Decided it's better that way.
Keeps the people I care about safe.
There's only one thing I can do now.
I run.
Synced & corrected by oykubuyuk
WEB-DL resync by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com
How's it going?
Hey. Uh, good.
How you doing?
Good.
So, the victim. His name is Al Rothstein.
He's a welder here at the nuclear plant.
Co-worker found him this morning.
So, what do you got?
Petechiae on his face and
the whites of his eyes,
and this bruising around his neck...
So he was strangled.
By someone very strong and very large.
Or something?
This wasn't Grodd.
Oh, thank God.
Look,
I'll let you know
when I find more.
So this Flash Day thing.
I'm hoping you're planning
on making an appearance.
Ah... I haven't decided.
Bar, I heard the Mayor's trying
to give you the key to the city.
Yeah, I don't need an award.
You love getting awards.
Like all those science trophies
you got in high school?
Those I deserved.
I'll let you know what I find, all right?
All right.
Flash Day is almost here.
A special downtown rally
to honor the man who saved Central City.
It's been six months since
the Flash saved Central City
from the freak black hole
that erupted in the sky.
Joe, where are we at with
the murder at the nuclear plant?
Barry's still analyzing the evidence,
but there was definitely something weird.
Yeah, which is why I let you have
that Anti-Meta-Human Task Force.
Speaking of which, where's
your scientific advisor?
Ho, ho, ho!
Fear the beard!
It's a very distinguished look... Sir.
- What is all this, Mr. Ramon?
- Oh, this right here?
This is a little something I'm working on.
I'm cooking it up for Joe
and the task force to
take down meta-humans.
I'm think I'm going to call it The Boot.
Oh, here are the receipts.
Oh, Captain, one more thing.
You are not getting a badge, Mr. Ramon.
He's really stingy with
those badges, isn't he?
Yeah, cops are funny that way.
So you really think
you can get this to work?
Don't have me caught out on
the streets with my pants down.
Yes, once I finish the Boot,
CCPD will totally have what it
needs to take down a meta-human.
Especially now that Barry
has decided to go all
Lone Wolf McQuade and
fight crime by himself.
I know, right? Have you spoken to him?
Not really. Haven't even heard from Caitlin
since she started work at Mercury Labs.
- Hey Cisco. Hi, Dad.
- Hey, baby.
Hey, I was wondering if you'd
talked to Barry about the rally.
We was just saying.
I'm sorry, but, I can't believe
they're gonna give the
Flash the key to the city.
Although technically,
as members of Team Flash,
we should all be getting keys.
Well, you know Barry.
The more we try to convince
him to do something,
the less he's gonna want to do it.
Yeah, but he should go.
Someone should try and get through to him.
Maybe his best friend.
Joe, believe me, I've tried.
I meant her.
Bye, baby.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
You know, if you ever decided
that you didn't want to be the Flash,
you have a good future being a contractor.
Thanks.
Yeah, I'm just trying to put it all back
exactly how it was before the...
You know.
Seems like a lot of local businesses
are being rebuilt at night.
In secret.
I was thinking about writing
an article about it for the paper.
Don't. Please.
Look, people have heard the stories.
They've read the articles.
They've maybe even seen the
red streak racing past them.
But they've never seen the Flash, Barry.
So that's why you're here?
You came to talk me into
going to the rally?
'Cause I'm... I'm not gonna go.
People just want to thank the
man who saved Central City.
Well, they can't, 'cause that's not me.
You should know that, better than anyone.
Central City believes in the Flash.
So do I.
Brilliant!
He's contained the Singularity
by adding to its angular momentum!
Barry, it's stabilizing.
Keep doing what you're doing!
I'm not sure how much longer I can.
Cisco! Now what?
We have to merge the inner
and outer event horizons.
How do we do that?
By separating in the eye of it.
The amount of energy from
the fissure should do the trick.
It's our only hope, Ronald.
Ronnie, no! It's too dangerous.
What if you can't escape the inrush?
Cait, we have to try.
Ronnie... Professor...
No!
Ronald... Ronald...
I'm so sorry.
Are we expecting trouble?
Cops always expect trouble.
In this city, I expect
super evil flying monsters.
That's a solid expectation.
Well, I'll be.
Good morning, Central City!
A year ago, our world changed.
Our city became ground zero for...
some pretty weird stuff.
We got a new breed of criminal:
Men and women who defied not only our laws,
but physics and reason.
But we got something else, too.
We got the Flash!
Our wounds run deep,
and I know many of you are afraid
of what threats tomorrow may bring.
But the Flash doesn't just protect us,
he restores hope where it was lost.
That's why I'm honored to present the key
to the man who saved
Central City: The Flash!
Flash. Flash.
The doors to Central City
will forever be open for you, Flash.
Look out!
You all right?
I got this, all right?
The man who saved Central City,
hate to rain on your parade.
Oof!
Cisco!
- The Boot!
- Right!
Locked and loaded. Go!
Booted!
Cisco, you said this
thing would take him down.
He's not going down.
He went up.
Run! Run!
- What are you doing?
- I'm throwing, you're shooting.
That's Al Rothstein.
The body we found at the nuclear plant,
he's alive!
According to the coroners office,
Al Rothstein's body was in
the morgue all night,
so we can scratch off "zombie attack."
Rothstein have a twin brother?
Nope. Only child.
And get this, the night
the accelerator exploded,
Rothstein was on his
honeymoon, in Hawaii.
So we're looking for
a guy who's really strong,
can grow twice his size,
and just happens to look
exactly like the guy he murdered?
I would think this meta was really cool
if everything about him didn't
just terrify me to my core.
Is that what happened to you?
You looked really spooked
there for a minute.
- Uh...
- I actually see
the guy that I can ask about it right now.
Call you back, okay? Hey.
So, the hospital next to
the Flash Day rally,
The x-ray and CT machines
all failed at once.
Was that because of you?
I did not do anything
that would cause that.
I'm 92% sure.
I'm going to go make that 100. Excuse me.
You okay?
- We need to talk.
- Okay.
Barry can't do this alone anymore.
That's his plan
and I don't know how to talk him out of it.
At this point, I'm just trying
not to push him farther away.
Well, maybe Barry has been so successful
at pushing you, me and everyone else away
because we keep letting him.
Let's not let him.
What do you suggest?
Well, "if you keep
getting 'no' for an answer,
stop asking questions."
I say that. You quoting me to me?
What can I say? You are a very smart man.
So this is what it looks
like inside Mercury Labs.
Security here is way better
than it was at S.T.A.R. Labs,
what with people walking in and out
of the Cortex all the time.
- Hi Cisco.
- Sweet Sarek.
Is that a 6K proton splicer?
Yes, it is.
Dr. McGee insists on having
all the latest technology.
Wow.
You deserve it.
I spotted you, at the rally today,
and I'm guessing you saw what happened.
Cisco, I can't come back.
Okay, check this out:
we found this on a victim
at the nuclear power plant,
but the badge shows
absolutely nothing at all,
which is so weird.
What's also weird is that at the
same time that meta-human grew,
all the x-ray machines within a
mile radius just went belly-up.
- Cisco.
- Just... if you could just...
See if the badge was
tampered with or something.
I mean, if it's broken, or...
Whatever.
It'll really help.
Mr. Allen.
Barry Allen?
- Yeah.
- I'm Greg Turk.
I'm an attorney at Weathersby and Stone.
I don't usually make house
calls, but I've been trying
to get in touch with you
for several months.
Yes. Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
I've just...
I've been really busy with police work.
We need to talk about S.T.A.R. Labs.
As you know, Harrison Wells
left the property to you
as part of his living trust.
Yeah, which I did not ask him to do,
but I've been keeping the place up.
Well, It's going to take more
than cleaning the floors
to retain it, I'm afraid.
The facility and the real
estate are scheduled to go
into receivership at the
end of this week unless...
you watch this.
What is this?
A video message drafted by Dr. Wells.
What's on it? Have you seen it?
No. He was very specific.
It was only to be watched by you.
The device will send me a notification
after you've viewed it.
And at that point, I'll have
everything ready to execute.
I'm not going to watch that.
Well, that's up to you, Mr. Allen.
I'm only here to represent
Harrison Wells' final request.
Good day.
What are you guys doing here?
- Working.
- So, Caitlin was right.
Yes, all humans contain
small amounts of radiation
due to contact with cell
phones, microwaves,
televisions, et cetera.
Our bodies are natural conductors.
I think our meta's been
sucking up all the radiation
around him and using it to power himself.
Which is why the x-ray
machines at the hospital
failed the day of the rally.
So if we want to find him,
we gotta look for places without radiation.
All right, guys, I don't want
any of you here right now.
Tough. You need your partners.
You need your friends.
Barry, everyone in this
room cares about you,
but we also care about this city.
We all want to make a difference,
and that means fighting meta-humans,
and that means working with the Flash.
You can't deny us that.
Not anymore. Got him.
There's a three block dead zone
near a hazardous waste reclamation plant.
It should be blooming with rads,
and right now it's at zero.
That's where you'll find your atom smasher.
Because he absorbs atomic power,
and he, well, smashes.
Come here.
That's a great name. Welcome to the team.
- Thank you.
- Great, guys, thank you.
You can go now, all right?
Barry, you need to let Cisco and Stein
figure out a way to stop this guy.
No, I don't.
Barry left his comm system behind.
We can't talk to him.
He's on his own.
Well, this is a curve ball.
I thought I was going to
have to come looking for you.
I'm not gonna let you hurt anyone else.
- I'm only here to hurt you, buddy.
- Yeah?
Then why'd you kill Albert Rothstein?
And why do you look like him?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
- Try me.
- I'm about to.
Is there really no way of knowing
what's going on in there?
I'm looking for the security cameras.
Booyah.
My turn.
- Dad.
- Maybe I can make it there.
No, you won't, and what are you
gonna do when you get there?
The Boot didn't work on him.
Alarm!
- Believe me, we're all alarmed.
- No, the alarm system.
You've tapped into the
surveillance cameras, correct?
Correct!
"Come on, feel the noize."
He said you were some kind of big hero,
but you don't seem worthy
of him, or this city.
Professor Stein, you are a genius.
I believe that's already
been well established.
No, thank you.
Iris says mac and cheese is your favorite.
I'm not hungry.
It's been six months, Barry.
You gotta eat, son.
It's a good move,
being angry all the time.
I get it.
You miss your mom and dad, and you want
to show them that you're strong.
Being mad makes it easier.
Tougher thing to do
would be to let yourself feel.
It's okay to be sad. You can be sad, Barry.
Your parents will understand
if you're not strong all the time.
That is why I'm here.
It's okay, son. I got you.
You're good. I got you.
Where is everyone?
I figured you wouldn't want an
audience when you came to.
Yeah, thanks.
Iris is right.
You're not gonna do this anymore.
For the last six months I've
given you your space
to work all this out, come back to us.
But today proved that you'd
rather just get yourself killed.
It's better than getting my friends killed.
You want me to tell you
that it wasn't your fault?
I can't. It was. Guess what?
You weren't the only person
making decisions that day.
All of the rest of us were there too.
Eddie and Ronnie,
they chose to help you stop Wells,
and stop that...
- Singularity.
- Singularity thing.
It's on all of us, Barry.
So stop with this hogging
all the blame and regret.
We gotta live with it. Move on.
What do I do now?
Well, I know that you've been
rebuilding Central City at night.
It's just bricks and paint.
Maybe you should start trying to rebuild...
things that really matter.
What are you doing here?
Sorry, I should've called or something.
I just... I wanted to see you.
It's been a while.
Yeah, Cisco said that he saw you
at the Flash Day celebration.
I was surprised.
You, better than anyone,
know I wasn't the hero that day.
- Of course you were.
- No.
Cait, Ronnie died saving me.
And I should've saved him,
and I'm... I'm so sorry.
Barry, I know that you
did everything you could.
It wasn't your fault.
I don't blame you for Ronnie's death.
I blame myself.
Why?
When Ronnie first became Firestorm,
he asked me to leave Central City,
and go somewhere that we
could have a normal life.
And I said no.
I couldn't leave S.T.A.R.
Labs, Dr. Wells... you.
If I had gone with him,
Ronnie would still be alive.
Being at S.T.A.R. Labs just
made me think of that
every single day.
Here.
Oh, you carry a handkerchief now?
What are you, 80?
- What's that?
- Ah, it's uh...
Apparently, in case of his death,
Wells had some kind of a living will.
And you haven't watched it yet?
No. No, I've...
been too afraid.
What if we watched it together?
All right.
Hello, Barry.
If you're watching this,
that means something
has gone horribly wrong.
I'm dead and the last 15
years have been for nothing.
Bummer. 15 years.
You know, when I realize
that in all those years
helping raise you,
we were never truly enemies, Barry.
I'm not the thing you hate.
And so, I want to give you
the thing that you want most.
It won't matter.
You'll never be truly
happy, Barry Allen, trust me.
I know you.
Now...
Erase everything I said up to this point.
Give the following message to the police.
My name is Harrison Wells.
Being of sound mind and body,
I freely confess to the
murder of Nora Allen.
In her home, on the
night of March 18th,
in the year 2000.
I attacked Nora Allen
in her dining room.
- Oh, my God.
- I stabbed her in the chest
- with a large butcher knife...
- He confessed.
From the drawer to the
left of the sink in the kitchen.
This is it.
This is what I need to free my dad.
Hey, Joe. Yeah, hey.
Can you have everybody
meet me at S.T.A.R. Labs?
Yeah. All right, thanks.
Yeah. All right, bye.
I'll drive.
Okay.
You think the video's enough?
Well, sure.
- What's she saying?
- Hold on.
Wells gave all the right details.
It's not a done deal yet,
but the D.A. says it looks good.
Yeah, I'm here.
Is it good news?
- I think so.
- Henry's coming home?
Okay, well...
that still leaves Atom
Smasher to deal with.
Last time you faced him,
it did not go well.
No, it did not.
I clearly can't stop him by myself.
So how are we gonna beat him?
Well, ever since I was
shown a drained radiation tag,
which I haven't been
able to stop thinking about.
- Thank you, Cisco.
- You're welcome, Caitlin.
If this guy likes radiation so much,
I say we give it to him.
Showtime.
What's up?
I see you got my message.
That light was perfect bait.
What made you think of that?
I don't know, I think I saw
it in a comic book somewhere.
You want me?
You're gonna have to catch me.
It's working, dude.
Rothstein's following you.
I must say, he's quite
agile for a man his size.
Run, Barry, run.
Come on.
Didn't think I could catch you, huh?
No, I knew you could.
Now, Cisco!
The amount of radiation
about to flood that room...
Atom Smasher won't be
able to absorb it all.
The radiation's been cleared.
It's safe for you to go in.
I'm sorry.
I couldn't let you hurt anyone else.
Why?
Why did you want to kill me?
He promised he'd take me home...
if I killed you.
Who?
Who promised you that?
Zoom.
Let's get out of here.
I'll race you.
You will lose.
Welcome home!
Gather round, everyone, please.
Looking at all of you,
thinking how far we've all come,
and remembering those
who are no longer with us,
I'm reminded of a Hebrew word
used during times of graduation.
Kadima. It means, "Forward."
Forward.
- Forward.
- Well said.
- Thank you.
- You good?
- Ah, yeah.
Stuff goes to your head after
being away from it for 14 years.
I bet. All right, well, look.
I was thinking, what if, in the morning,
the two of us started looking
for an apartment for both of us,
and Iris has actually been
doing some research on
how to get your medical license back
so you could start your practice up again,
or, if you wanted, come work
with us at S.T.A.R. Labs.
I don't know. I mean...
- What's wrong? You okay?
- Yeah, it's a party.
Come on, we can talk
about all this tomorrow.
- Talk about what?
- Barry...
Are you not planning on sticking around?
Okay.
Okay, do you think...
Can you be all that you are becoming...
With me here?
You're the only family that I have left.
Well, that's not really true, is it?
Don't you have another family in this room?
They need your help too, Barry.
When you need me, I will be here,
but right now, Central City
doesn't need you
to be Henry Allen's son.
It needs you to be the Flash.
My kid.
The superhero.
I have to go.
I need you to tell me that it's okay.
Yeah.
Your dad get off okay?
Yeah, I just dropped him at the station.
You good?
I don't know, I...
Just feels like every
time I win, I still lose.
Well...
It's not bad.
No, it's not bad.
It's pretty cool. It's real cool, come on!
- Ho ho!
- Hey, guess what?
I added a little upgrade to your suit.
It's just like the one from
the future newspaper
Gideon showed us.
I was thinking, you know,
you shouldn't fear the
future anymore, right?
No, and it'll be here faster than we think.
Well, see, I like it. The
lightning definitely pops
more against the white.
And S.T.A.R. Labs is now safer than ever.
Increased security and surveillance.
Re-coded, double firewalled,
electronic lock sets.
Nothing is getting through
here without us knowing.
So people can't just waltz
in and out of here.
Exactly.
For real? Stay where you are.
Who are you?
You don't know me, but
I know you... Barry Allen.
Take one more step, it'll be
the last step you take.
The man asked you a question.
Who the hell are you?
My name is Jay Garrick,
and your world is in danger.
Synced & corrected by oykubuyuk
WEB-DL resync by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com