My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
In an attempt to stop the evil speedster Savitar,
I was accidentally thrust into the future,
and I saw him murder the woman that I love.
But I won't let that happen.
I'm gonna do everything in my power to change the future,
and I'm the only one fast enough to keep her alive.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
It's definitely a meta.
I think this is someone new.
I'm Cisco, by the way. You must be Gypsy.
- So this good-bye, then? - For now.
Caitlin, you do not want to do this.
Time for me to own who I really am.
You're one of the strongest people I've ever known.
You can win this fight.
- Jesse! - No, no.
- What's wrong? - Grodd.
He's got my dad.
He has him in Gorilla City.
It's been two weeks since he disappeared.
I mean, no one's seen or heard from him since.
Slow down. Just start from the beginning.
Okay, why did your dad go to Gorilla City?
Wait, can we slow down even further?
What the hell is a Gorilla City?
Okay, so...
There are sentient, highly intelligent
evolved gorillas in Earth-2.
And they all live in a city deep in the heart of Africa.
We sent Grodd there
when he went after Fay Wray here.
Grodd's there?
Why on Earth, any Earth,
would your father want to go there?
I mean, we received a mathematical cryptogram
at our S.T.A.R. Labs.
It was highly complex.
It took a week to decode it, but my dad and I did.
What did it say?
It was an invitation
from the gorillas to my dad.
Why Harry?
They wanted to meet him.
So he mounted an expedition with ten other people,
and they went into the jungle.
But they failed multiple check-ins,
and a search party went in after them.
But all they found were the bodies...
all of them beaten to death.
But no one's seen my dad.
- I mean, is he-- - No.
No, he's alive. They--
they went to a lot of trouble to get him there.
They need him for something.
We're gonna figure out what that is.
There you guys are.
I've been looking all over for you.
Are we going for coffee or what?
Dad!
Yes, that's how you say good morning, people--
with hugs. Hi!
Jesse, that's not who you think it is.
This is H.R.
You met him briefly before you left last time.
At your service, madame.
He's Harry's replacement.
Some would say improvement.
This is Harry's daughter.
- Yeah. - He's been kidnapped.
He... I didn't know. I'm so s...
- I thought... - Sorry about that.
I'm sorry, too.
I'm sorry I took the smile from your face.
What are you thinking about?
The future.
This headline from the future:
the city's still recovering from a gorilla attack.
So you're thinking this headline
and Harry being taken are tied together.
I mean, it can't be a coincidence, right?
Harry getting lured to Gorilla City?
Grodd must be planning something.
Seems like he's planning to come back to this Earth.
And not alone, by the sound of it.
If we rescue Harry, then maybe that stops
whatever Grodd's planning here,
and maybe that changes the future.
Which would change my future.
So we save Harry, we save Iris.
But you're not sure.
No, but...
I'm going either way.
Harry's my friend. I'm not gonna just abandon him.
I'm going back to Earth-2.
And I suppose you'll want somebody to come with you
who's gonna open those breaches for you?
We had so much fun last time.
Fun-ish. I'm in.
I'm gonna come too.
I have a special connection with Grodd.
Maybe we can use that to get through to him.
- Yes, okay. - Great, yeah, I'm coming too.
No. I'm sorry, Jesse, no.
Look, I didn't come here for you to take all the risk.
I'm going to help.
Your dad would kill me if I let you come along.
I'm a Speedster now, okay?
I can take care of myself.
I know, which is exactly why I need you to stay here.
I mean, this city needs protecting while we're gone.
Besides, maybe you can teach Wally a thing or two.
Wait, what is he talking about?
So you're-- you're a Speedster now.
Yeah, we're both Speedsters now.
Great, yeah, that's, uh...
that's awesome.
I, um-- I thought she'd be more excited than that.
Hey, Julian, would youaybe able to cover for me
at work for the next few days?
Few days? Why?
I-- I just, um, have a thing--
we're-- it's just--
it's Flash stuff.
Such as?
A friends of ours is lost on a parallel Earth,
and we're gonna go get him back.
- A parallel Earth? - Yeah.
This is the-- this is the multiverse.
I'm fascinated.
And do you often travel to other Earths?
No, I-- well, when I have to.
Look, Julian, will you just tell Singh that,
I don't know, I'm under the weather or something?
It's-- you know, it is kind of what we do on Team Flash.
We cover for each other.
What does Caitlin think of all this multiverse hopping?
- Does she approve? - She's coming with me.
- You're letting her go? - It's her choice.
Allen, it's not a wise move, surely.
She can barely control her cold powers as is.
- I mean-- - We might need her for Grodd.
Grodd? Gr--
Telepathic gorilla?
- Yeah. - Where-- where are you going?
Are you going to Planet of the Apes?
No, it's just a city of them, okay?
Will you cover for me?
Are you going to Planet of the Apes?
I'm not going to Planet of the Apes, okay?
Calm down. Will you cover for me?
I got you. Yeah, of course.
Okay, thank you. See you in a few days.
All right, now.
- And make sure Wally doesn't-- - I won't.
Because, you know, sometimes he can be a little--
- Barry-- - You know,
if given the opportunity--
Barry, I am very good at bossing my little brother around, okay?
- Don't worry. - All right.
Just please don't do anything stupid.
You mean like voluntarily going to a city of super apes?
I'm being serious. Rescue Harry.
But other than that, you-- you don't have to do this for me.
Everything I do is for you.
Good.
Y'all know Wally can hear you, right?
Sorry, Wally.
Be safe.
You see anything hinky, you run.
Listen to me. I don't need to tell you that.
- I promise. - All right.
Detective.
Indiana Jones much?
Cisco, my friend, this is not my first expedition,
and believe me, this is the perfect attire.
Wait, Julian, what's going on?
I thought you were gonna cover for me.
I spoke to Captain Singh.
He thinks we're at a morphology conference up in Bludhaven.
So if it's all the same to you...
You don't have to come, Julian.
You don't even know Harry.
A chance to travel to another dimension--
I mean, I wasn't gonna miss that.
We're not going sightseeing.
Neither am I.
Well, damn.
All right, Jesse, Wally,
you make sure this city's safe while I'm gone, all right?
We will.
Hey, Barry.
If you--if you see my dad, just tell him--
You'll see him real soon, Jesse.
Speedster's honor.
- All right, let's do this. - Okay.
Earth-2, here we come.
How was that?
Bloody brilliant.
Well, we made it.
Welcome to the jungle, baby.
Earth-2 Africa.
Not hot.
Guess global warming's not really a thing here.
But bugs are.
Someone please help me out.
How exactly does saving someone on this Earth
prevent an attack on ours?
If Grodd is planning to attack,
he's gonna need to open a breach to our Earth,
and the only one over here that can open one is--
- Harrison Wells. - Harrison Wells, yeah.
So if we save him from Grodd,
then he can't get to our Earth,
the attack never happens, we change the future,
and we're one step closer to saving Iris.
You want to go for a run?
Yeah, yeah. Maybe later.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Look, I know I haven't been great at keeping in touch.
It's just everything's been so crazy
trying to train with Barry and shadowing him,
and I just haven't had that much time for other things.
Yeah, or other people.
That is not what I meant.
No, look, I--I get it. Trust me.
It's not easy being a hero, is it?
No, but I love every minute of it.
Great.
Are you sure you're okay?
- Because... - Yeah.
I'm just worried about my dad.
I hope we didn't interrupt you two.
Nope. Nothing to interrupt.
Aren't you--
you aren't happy she's back?
I am. I just wish she felt the same.
Ever since she got here, she's been acting so weird with me.
I--I don't know if it's because I have powers
or if it's just me.
Wally, she's probably still just upset
because her father's missing, right?
Yeah, it's hard to focus on other things
when something like that is weighing you down.
Yeah, Wally. She'll be fine.
Just give her some time,
and then, you know, lock it down.
- Lock it down, hmm? - Yeah.
What, you think I didn't notice
that your Facebook profile still says "Single"?
What? I mean, technically, I'm still single.
What was it?
Ugh, robbery in progress at O'Sullivan Bank.
You two go.
Come on, let's go.
- Didn't hear the news, huh? - What news?
That you don't mess with Kid Flash.
We got to get back to our friends.
They're expecting us.
Yeah, they picked some real winners.
I know, which is more than I can say for you two.
Be right back.
Sorry, I-- I had to stretch my legs.
Hey, guys, come out.
It's--it's nothing to see here, guys.
It's just a couple fools getting their asses handed to 'em.
Thank you.
Oh, my gosh, thank you.
Want some water?
I'm okay, thanks.
It's important to stay hydrated on a parallel Earth.
So weird being back here on this alternate universe.
This is where I met my doppelganger,
the evil one.
Killer Frost.
She's the one I'm always afraid of becoming.
And where is she now?
Dead.
That's not gonna happen to you, Caitlin.
I'm glad you came with us, Julian.
You're a nice addition to the team.
Yeah, well,
I live for danger.
We're close, guys.
Do you hear that?
This is it.
It's a trap.
Welcome, Caitlin.
Knew you'd come...
Flash.
You guys all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Yeah, me too.
I've lost my gun, but I'm all right.
Well, looks like you're gonna have to phase us out of here.
I don't know. Something's holding me back.
Can you open a breach?
No dice.
I don't think it's the cell. I...
Grodd must be dampening our powers somehow.
Okay.
Harry?
You're all right.
Wells. Hey!
You got to help us get out of here
before the gorillas come back.
Hello, Flash.
- Grodd. - What?
That's Grodd the gorilla?
He's talking through Wells?
- That's a--a thing? - Yeah.
Yeah, sort of trips you out at first, but trust me,
you get used to it.
Grodd, let him go.
This is between you and me.
Not yet.
- I need him. - For what?
Why'd you lure him here?
For you.
Need your help.
Help? Got a funny way of asking for it.
You sent me here!
Remember?
To live in this hell!
Where I am forced to serve
under the rule of Solovar.
Who's Solovar?
Leader of Gorilla Kind.
Ruler of Gorilla City.
And now...
he wants to rule the humans.
He will bring war to your Earth.
- Why? - He has seen many conflicts
between gorillas and humans.
He is afraid the humans will attack,
but now that you're here,
he will bring the fight to you.
So you lured us here to stop him?
As trespassers...
you will be sent to the arena
and executed.
What? How about a signpost at the front?
"All trespassers will be executed."
That wouldn't be the worst idea, would it?
Will be Solovar's great honor
to kill you...
himself.
But, Flash...
if he were to be defeated,
the other gorillas would see his weakness
and would no longer follow him.
Well, I'm not gonna kill anyone,
not even a gorilla.
Kill or be killed!
This is the only law Gorilla Kind understands.
How do you benefit from this, Grodd?
Solovar falls.
I take his place.
I rule the gorillas,
and I promise to keep them in Gorilla City.
How do we know we can trust you?
Because...
even though you sent me away,
your Earth is still my home.
And there are those among you
I will never forget.
Kill Solovar,
and Central City will be spared.
Fail, and see your home
turned to ash.
Hey, Jesse, you got a sec?
Did I do something wrong?
I don't-- I don't think so.
Okay, then why are you being so cold with me?
Jesse, come on, you can talk to me.
I know that this is about more than just your dad.
Look, I guess...
I guess I thought one day we'd figure out a way to be together.
You know, but now that you have your powers, it's...
It's like I never hear from you.
Jesse, if--if you would,
I want you to stay.
- I can't. - Why?
Because of your dad?
Because Barry is going to find him.
Look, you don't know that, okay?
You don't.
When I first got my power,
you were so lost not having yours.
You know, and I thought maybe part of the reason
why you liked me was...
'cause you were attracted to the speed and not me.
I know, I know, okay?
But I saw you out there today...
being Kid Flash.
Okay, and you were complete, Wally.
You were scary complete.
I could have all the speed in the world.
I'm not complete without you.
Stay.
Barry, do you really think you could kill this Solovar?
Do you think you could take a life?
It is as I feared.
The humans court war with Gorilla Kind.
Why did you not tell me, Grodd,
more humans had entered the city?
I was about to inform you, Solovar.
Why? Why are you here?
To study us like animals?
- Make us your pets? - No, no.
I'm--I...
We came here in peace.
We entered your city by mistake.
Uh, we mean you no harm.
Please...
just let me and my friends go, and I promise,
we'll never come back here again.
My brethren have seen you.
Your fate is sealed.
You will all die by my hand...
in the arena...
so that all will know that Solovar's justice
is wise and swift.
All right, I'll make you a deal.
I'll fight you in the arena-- just me.
But if I beat you, you let my friends go,
and you leave us alone for good.
I accept.
Humans and their arrogance.
First you will suffer.
Then I will grant you each...
a horrible death.
Speedster versus super gorilla.
Best worst video game ever.
Do you really think that Barry can beat Solovar?
Well, he'd better, for all of our sakes.
It's starting.
After you die,
your friends will follow you into the black.
- We'll see. - Okay, Barry.
I got a plan for you.
It's all about the speed punches.
Speed punches. Come on, Barry.
Change of plan, Barry.
It's all about the running away.
What aboutbo lightning throw?
Yes, Barry, lightning throw!
Worth a shot!
That's oh for two.
Come on, Barry, get up.
All my days, this is quite the reversal of our fortune.
Reversal...
Barry, it's time to pull a reverse Flash.
Do it!
He did it!
He actually did it.
He bloody well did it.
I won't kill him!
I won't!
I know you all fear humans!
You think we want war with Gorilla Kind!
We don't!
We're not all murderers and killers!
We only want peace!
Which is why I'm sparing your leader!
We call it mercy!
Take him out.
what happened?
Congratulations.
You won.
What about Harry?
He's still catatonic.
- Flash. - I won.
Solovar promised to let us go.
No.
No? What do you...
I don't understand.
Solovar's words mean nothing now.
You never had any intentions of letting us go, did you?
I told you I needed you.
I could not defeat Solovar in combat,
but you could.
You did, and now I am the ruler of Gorilla City,
and all the gorillas will follow me.
Solovar never wanted to attack Central City.
You do.
You took my home away from me,
and now I will take it back!
The gorillas saw what you did, Flash.
They saw you defeat Solovar,
and now they are afraid of humans
and will do anything I order,
and I will order them to invade your Earth,
and your city will burn.
You were planning this the whole time.
Yes.
Father taught me well.
Always think ahead.
And I had plenty of time to think in cages built by you
and then by Solovar.
Then why don't you just kill us?
Since we already did your damn dirty work for you.
Still need you.
I'm not doing anything for you.
Not you, Flash.
You.
Me?
You will open the breach to First Earth.
My army will cross that breach,
and all the humans in Central City
will burn before Gorilla Kind!
Grodd, you are smart,
maybe smarter than all of us,
smart enough to know that you cannot do this.
Intelligence and violence,
they're opposites from each other.
What you want to do, it's not logical,
not for someone as wise as you are.
You forget, Flash,
I am an animal.
I am a gorilla.
Kill or be killed!
I'm gonna get out of this cell, and I'm gonna stop you.
No, you won't.
You will die.
- Snow? - You okay?
I...
I have a headache, I guess.
And I think-- i--is that me? I smell.
That counts as okay.
Jesse, my daughter. Where's--
She's fine. She's on Earth-1.
She's totally fine.
Barry?
Cisco.
You guys all came for me?
A city of evil genius apes.
Sounded like fun.
Well, I don't deserve it, but...
thank you, Snow; thank you, Barry,
Cisco...
Indiana.
It's Julian Albert, thank you.
And I came along for--
I live for danger.
Looks like you came to the right place.
I still can't phase through the bars.
We have to find a way out of here so we can stop him.
You keep saying that, but what if we can't get out?
What if we're stuck here? What if this is the way--
Well, we can't think like that.
While there's life, there's hope.
And if there isn't life?
What is that supposed to mean?
Grodd needs me to open the breach so he can attack Earth-1.
What if I wasn't alive to do that?
You planning on dying?
Only if you kill me.
Look, this is something we have to consider.
Right now, I can't think of any other way to stop them.
They'd have no other way of getting to Central City.
He's right.
Cisco's death would change the newspaper headline in the future.
- Headline? - It's a long story.
But it would also make another one come true,
the one about Killer Frost.
You want me to kill you?
Think about it.
Grodd doesn't know you have cold powers.
- You might be able to use them. - Cold powers?
She-- you have cold powers?
I knew it. I knew that you and I
did not get Barry out of that mirror.
Wait, now. Caitlin. If you kill someone,
there's no going back.
You'll be Killer Frost for the rest of your life.
Now, I did not come all this way to see that happen.
Did you come here because you "Live for danger"
or to protect me?
I just don't want to see you become something you're not.
Okay, Cisco.
I'm not gonna kill you, and neither is anyone else, okay?
So let's come up with the next best plan
that doesn't involve murdering one of our friends.
No, Cisco's right.
It's the only way.
One of us has to die.
What you doing up there?
Just, uh, hanging out.
What're you-- what're you thinking about?
Wally. He wants me to stay here with him.
Yeah, he does.
Guy is no dummy. Congratulations.
Oh, that's great. Love...
Nothing like young love.
Yeah, I just-- I don't--
I don't know if it's the right thing.
Why?
He's on his own journey.
Besides, my dad just got captured by gorillas.
And if-- if he does come back,
how could I ever tell him I'm leaving?
Well, 'cause you're human.
That's--that's how.
That's what we do. Look, my point is this.
When it comes to love, you got to go for it.
You know? Everything else be damned.
'Cause if you don't,
you're gonna end up being the kind of person
that lives the rest of their life with regret.
I mean, I know that telling your dad that, you know, you're--
you're switching Earths,
that's gonna be a difficult conversation to have,
but one that you've to go for
if you want to be happy.
But that's, you know, just my opinion.
What do I know?
I'm just a handsomer guy than your dad
with a song in his heart.
Good luck, Jesse.
He started coughing... violently.
And then he clutched his side and keeled over.
The injury...
it must have ruptured one of his kidneys.
He went into shock.
His heart stopped.
I couldn't resuscitate him.
Cold.
He's dead.
He was of no use to me anyway.
He's gone, Barry.
Grodd is gone.
Come on, mate.
Yo, it worked!
It worked.
Allen, Allen, you all right, mate?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
I didn't freeze you too much, did I?
No. I'm good.
Well, then...
let's get the hell out of here.
Yeah.
Go!
- All right. - Hallelujah.
Let's go.
All right.
We should be far enough out
that you should be able to use your powers.
We need a breach open right now.
Guys, we got to go before they realize we're gone!
It's too late for that.
- Run! - Run!
Open a breach!
Time to warp out of this madhouse.
All right, go.
Hey, gang, who wants to take their mind off their troubles
with a "Sure to take your mind off your troubles" Game of charades?
I'll go first.
Okay, ah, let's see.
Movie--I mean...
one word.
Dad!
- You okay? - Good, yeah.
I'm sorry you guys missed it.
I ain't.
Word of advice:
don't volunteer for these things.
Nothing ever tries to rip you limb from limb
if you don't volunteer.
I'm fine. I'm so fine, thanks--
thanks to our friends,
our good friends.
You're welcome, Harry.
I--I think--
I just forgot how handsome you were.
Oh, I forgot.
He's-- you're still here.
Yeah. Still here.
I guess we have your tactical and technical genius
to thank for getting us out of that fix.
No, no, nah.
- Nah? - Nah.
You were completely right about him.
He's a total fraud. He's not even a scientist.
And I'm sure you couldn't even remember an ATM code if you tried.
All those-- all those numbers.
It's only four digits. Why is he still here?
Because we couldn't do it without him.
I thank you, Francisco.
Fran-- Francisco?
Don't ask.
Yo, so what actually happened?
You fight some really super-smart apes, or what?
Yeah. Yeah, we did.
And they were smart, but today, at least,
we were a bit smarter.
How's he doing?
He's gonna be okay.
He's got some cuts and bruises,
but Caitlin said he just needs food and a little sleep.
Okay.
Hey, I'm...
I'm sorry for being an epic basket case lately.
My, um...my dad was kidnapped once,
and it turns your world.
You turn my world, Wally.
Look, I--I need you to be honest about something.
Of course.
When my dad wakes up, if I tell him that I love him
and I'll always be his daughter
but that I want to move to Earth-1,
what would you think about--
That's what I think of that.
I'm glad we think alike.
I see you're--
you took my love advice.
You know, when it comes to scientific advice,
mine is sometimes specious,
but when it comes to affairs of the heart,
well, I consider myself a genius.
Okay, yeah, we're gonna go now.
Okay, great.
Congratulations. I'm happy for you.
Invite me to the wedding.
He's gonna be so pissed.
Caitlin.
Wait.
Listen, if I overstepped,
then I apologize.
Just, after drinks the other night--
You were willing to risk your life for me?
I've been doing a lot of silly things recently.
I thought adding one more to the list wouldn't do any harm.
I like you, Julian.
I do.
And I like that you like me.
But I'm also afraid of my powers--
and not what they could do to me,
but what they could do to anyone who gets close to me.
Caitlin, I'm not afraid.
You should be.
Fear me, Julian.
It's not a threat, just...
good advice.
Okay, fine.
I'll fear you.
You know what really helps me when I'm scared?
What?
Just a good fillet steak...
bit of b¨¦arnaise on the side,
mashed potatoes--
does the trick ever time.
- Really? - I promise.
I think we should find a local steak house
and be terrified together.
Sure. Together it is.
Well...
- We did it. - You did it.
No, uh, we all did it.
We changed the future without changing who we are.
If we can keep doing this,
we can stop Savitar.
Wherever he is, however he's gonna come at us,
I can stop him.
I know it now.
- How do you do that? - Do what?
Stay positive in the face of overwhelming odds.
Because I plan on living a long life with you,
and nothing's gonna take that away from me.
Good.
So does that mean no more nightmares?
You're finally gonna get some sleep tonight?
Well... that last part is entirely up to you.
Like I told Flash,
always think ahead.
Now you will open the breaches
and very soon,
Central City will fall before Grodd.