My name is Barry Allen
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother
killed by something impossible.
My father went to
prison for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist...
but secretly, I use my speed to
fight crime and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find who killed my
mother and get justice for my father.
I am the Flash.
Previously on The Flash:
If you ever need anything,
I will race over in a heartbeat.
Same. Well, as
fast as I can run.
Advanced Technology
Operating Mechanism, A.T.O.M.
- What are you gonna use that for?
- To protect people.
You think Dr. Wells
killed Barry's mom?
I don't know yet, but I do
know that Wells keeps secrets.
The way that he
described running...
feeling the wind
and the power...
it's like he was
talking from experience.
Harrison Wells is
the Reverse-Flash.
Eddie, we need your help.
Pedal to the metal.
We got a 10-31 in progress.
Shiny Diamond, 18th and Olive.
- That's a few blocks from here. - Has
every crook in Central City gone crazy?
This is the third attempted robbery
tonight. Barry, we got another one.
Hello.
- Eighteenth and Olive.
- Got it.
- Who's this?
- Oh.
Indecent exposure. Powell Park.
That ain't something
you should be showing people.
They're getting away, guys.
- They're not getting away.
- Get these bozos up ahead first.
Then we'll worry about the
idiots at the Shiny Diamond.
- All right.
- Gonna run out of room, though.
I'll take care of that.
What do you think
he meant by that?
Oh, that's what he meant.
- I think we lost them.
- Oh, no, you didn't.
And by the way,
you're under arrest.
We need to go. Now. Come on.
Uh-uh. Freeze.
You guys missing these?
On the ground. On the ground.
So, uh, I'm just curious...
but, um, have you guys
have not heard of me, or what?
Nice work, detective.
- Good night, Dr. Kang.
- Good night.
No. What...? Aah!
No!
Victim's name is Lindsay Kang.
Engineering professor at
Hudson University.
Just got tenure.
Hey, so her whole body is covered
in these puncture wounds...
you see on her face.
Bites marks, maybe.
Whatever it was, she must
have gone into anaphylaxis.
- Damn.
- Yeah.
The blood sample should tell us
everything. I'll run tests back at my lab.
They can do it faster
at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Well, yeah, but I
mean, it's just...
It's just what?
It's kind of weird
being there right now.
Barry, you know we have to
play it cool with Wells.
- If he finds out we suspect him...
- I know. I get it.
I just think that we should
tell Cisco and Caitlin.
They could help us.
The more people who know, the more chance
Wells is gonna find out we're onto him.
What if one of them
slips up or panics?
- Or what if...?
- What?
What if they're not on our side?
No, absolutely not. They're not
involved in whatever he's planning.
I mean, Wells is their boss, their mentor.
They've been with him for a long time.
I've seen plenty of people make
the wrong choice for loyalty.
Please, do not include them
until we can be sure.
All right.
- Death by apitoxin.
- Honeybee venom.
Bees. Why did it
have to be bees?
Y'all, I don't do bees.
Ain't nobody got time for bees.
When a honeybee stings...
the stingers are torn from
their abdomen and they die.
There were no stingers in the
body and no dead bees in the car.
A honeybee can only deposit 0.1 milligrams
of apitoxin when it releases its stinger.
Yet Ms. Kang was found with enough venom
in her system to kill a herd of elephants.
It appears not only is a metahuman
controlling these bees...
but also increasing their toxicity. Bees
communicate by releasing pheromones.
Maybe this meta is controlling
them through secretion?
Anyone wanna join me
in getting a beekeeper suit?
- I'm pretty sure I can outrun a bee.
- Just don't run into a lake.
The bees will wait for you to come
up for air. Then they'll sting you.
Discovery Channel. Turns out
there's a lot to discover.
Felicity, what are
you doing here?
Can you guys come
outside for a sec?
What exactly are we waiting for,
Ms. Smoak?
Up there.
Is that a bird?
It's a plane.
It's my boyfriend.
Hi. I'm Ray.
So he seems a
little tall for you.
Barry Allen, are you jealous?
No, no. I'm not jealous.
I just... I really wish you would
have called before flying in.
- Oh, no. He flew. I drove.
- I'm serious.
All right? Now is
not the best time.
Why? What's going on?
- Ah. My ears popped, so that's something.
- You're lucky you didn't break your neck.
What is it with billionaires
being superheroes?
So have you picked a name yet?
I'm kind of partial
to the Atom. Shhew.
Are you married to that, or...?
Your A.T.O.M. suit.
Quite the technological
achievement, Mr. Palmer.
- I'm impressed.
- And he is never impressed.
Well, thank you. But I can't
quite seem to keep it up.
He means the suit.
Yeah, I mean the suit.
I can attest that everything else works fine.
There's nothing we need to fix in that area.
- The sex is great.
- God, there's two of them.
I know from Felicity that you have been
very helpful with Barry and the Flash suit.
And I was hoping to get
another set of eyes on my...
- Problem?
- ...problem.
- Any friend of the Arrow's is
the friend of... - Hell, yes.
Uh, guys, we kind of have a lot
going on already.
There's a metahuman killer that
can control a whole swarm of bees.
Cool.
I mean awful.
I'm sure Caitlin and I will
provide ample support, Barry.
And I will be happy
to sit this one out.
You...?
Ray, why don't you stay here
and work on your suit...
while Barry and I run
to Jitters for some java?
Sounds like a plan.
- Coffee?
- Sure.
- Hey, detective.
- Iris.
What are you doing here?
I am following up on my story
about crime in Central City.
Or lack thereof.
Could someone be working
with the Flash?
No, of course not.
You caught a flasher, armed
robbers in a getaway car...
and two jewelry
thieves last night.
I'm just that good.
What is going on
with you lately?
You've been acting really weird
and withdrawn.
If I didn't know any better, I'd
think you were hiding something.
Iris, I'm not hiding
anything from you.
- Do you ever go to work?
- Oh, you're funny.
Okay, I can't keep lying to Iris
about the Flash.
- You have to. - It's really
starting to affect our relationship.
We haven't had sex in two weeks.
- Which you didn't wanna know about.
- Keeping her in the dark keeps her safe.
I don't agree.
- Well, I'm her father.
- And I'm her boyfriend.
When does my vote
outweigh yours?
When you become her husband.
You know I left Starling City to
get away from the mood and brood.
- But it looks like it followed me here.
- I know. I'm sorry.
It's like I said before,
now is not the best time.
Barry, I have been through
enough with you...
to know when you're
holding something back.
Is this because I told Ray your secret?
Because he is trustworthy, Barry.
- He wants to help people, like you.
- Yeah, I know.
That's not what I'm
worried about. It's just...
I really don't wanna put
anyone else in danger.
In danger of what?
- Barry, hey.
- Eddie, hey. Uh, you remember Felicity.
- Of course.
- Hey.
- Great to see you.
- Yeah.
What is wrong with you? Is everyone
in Central City in a bad mood?
I thought Central City
was supposed to be the fun one.
It's just, um...
- it's not...
- Felicity knows.
- Wow.
- Yeah.
So everyone but Iris.
It feels that way.
- How do you lie to everyone you care about?
- For starters, don't think of it as lying.
Think of it as protecting her
from getting hurt.
- With a fib. - But Iris can
tell I'm hiding something.
And it's putting this
distance between us.
I have an idea. Why don't
we all go to dinner tonight?
A little wine and dine
is sure to bridge the gap.
- Come on, we all had fun last time.
- Sure. Why not?
Barry Allen, fifth wheel.
I can't make my 3:00 meeting. Also,
confirm my reservation for tonight.
Last time, they couldn't find it,
and that was unacceptable. Thanks.
You see that bad man over there?
Tell your sisters it's time.
So you put solid oxide
fuel cells into the belt?
Yeah, that's the only place
to hide the hardware.
Hmm. Well, they should be generating
enough energy to power the suit.
It could be the operating temperature.
I mean, you're essentially...
Overheating the
system. I figured.
But if we insulate them
with a ceramic compound...
We may improve the
operating efficiency.
You really are
quite clever, Cisco.
Some would say I'm the Reverse.
You're incredibly clever, Cisco.
How do you turn this thing on?
- Cisco? You okay?
- Yeah.
I haven't been getting
enough sleep, so...
Cisco, we need you up here.
- Killer bees are at it again.
- Get ahold of Barry.
- Another bee attack. Folston Tech.
- I'll see where Joe is.
"Bee" careful.
- For real?
- Bad pun, sorry. Just don't die.
- I'm too late.
- Where are the bees?
I don't know. There's
no sign of them.
I found them.
Uh, how do I get out of here?
Take the northeast crossways. The
quickest way out of the building.
Guys, they're everywhere.
I'm surrounded.
Barry!
Barf)'-
He's going into cardiac arrest.
Barry, stay with me.
Cisco, Barry doesn't
have a pulse.
- Step away from him.
- What? Why?
We need to jump-start his heart.
There's a defibrillator in the suit.
- Charge it to 360 joules.
- Charging in three, two, one.
Hit him again, 400 joules.
Charging in three, two, one.
Barry.
Joe.
Oh, thank God.
That is it for the defibrillator.
It is completely fried.
- You're lucky to be alive, Mr. Allen.
- I was very specific that you not die.
- Yeah, it's a pretty big thing for her.
- Cisco, what happened out there?
I followed your
directions exactly.
I'm sorry. I led
you the wrong way.
The schematics that we had,
they, um, weren't up to date.
They weren't up to date? What do you
mean? That's never happened before.
And what? You think Cisco
was trying to get you killed?
No. Why would he do that?
That doesn't make any sense.
I know. That's why I was joking.
Barry, it's ourjob to protect
you, and today we failed.
But that will just serve as a warning for
all of us to be more vigilant in the future.
Good news. The apitoxin is out of your
body. Your levels are back to normal.
Terrific.
Ray, Felicity,
we're gonna be late for dinner.
- Are you sure that's wise, Barry?
- You just died.
- Maybe you should order in tonight.
- Yeah. We could totally cancel.
I'm fine. Alive.
Hungry. All right?
Let's go.
- That was weird. - Yeah,
why didn't we get invited to dinner?
Oh. Thank you.
Hey, guys.
- Wow, Iris, check you out.
- Hi, Felicity.
Hello.
- Oh, hey.
- Guys, this is Ray Palmer.
- Hi. Nice to meet you.
- Lovely to meet you.
- Nice to meet you.
Mr. Palmer, your table is ready.
- Great. Shall we?
- Yes.
Hey, how did he get a reservation
here? We've been trying for months.
I don't know.
Here's your table, sir.
I thought it'd be nice if it was quiet,
so I bought out the entire restaurant.
- Too much?
- Just a tad, sweetie.
Joe.
Oh, Cisco. Hey.
You just saved me a trip to S.T.A.R Labs.
I got some info on our second victim.
Name is Bill Carlisle.
He was recently hired at Folston Tech
to beef up their robotics division.
Robotics?
That's just like
the first victim.
Wow. That is weird.
That's not why you stopped by.
No, I wanted to talk
to you about Barry.
Okay.
Is there something
going on with him?
- Something he's not telling us?
- What do you mean?
He hasn't really
been himself lately.
Not that I'm aware of.
It's like something
is just really bothering him.
I think he's got his mind trained
on catching the bad guys, Cisco.
And he's probably worried
about when the Reverse-Flash...
is gonna show his face again.
Oh, I'm not like
the Flash at all.
Some would say I'm the Reverse.
- Hey, you okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah. No, I'm fine. It's just
I got this crazy headache.
Thank you for the
file and the talk.
- So how did you two meet?
- Work.
I bought the company
where Felicity was employed...
so she was forced to join me
at Palmer Tech.
It's not as creepy as it sounds.
So you two work
closely together.
Interesting.
I guess you guys share all your
thoughts and feelings and...
Yeah, I share everything
with Felicity.
It's nice that you guys have
that level of communication.
Oh, well, no, not
"every" everything.
I mean, sometimes it's
good to just shut up, heh.
I get that. Some things
are better left unspoken.
Really?
I don't find that to be true.
Oh, thank God. It's
the food. Food's here.
Our first course on
the tasting menu...
is a quail-egg
frittata. Bon appétit.
Barry, I gotta admit, I envy you
spending so much time at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Harrison Wells is like
a personal hero of mine.
It's amazing just actually being
in the same room with him.
Yeah.
- I'll be right back. Just excuse me.
- Okay.
Well, I...
um, heh...
have to pee.
You've been acting strange ever
since Ray and I got to Central City.
What is going on?
Don't say it's a bad time. Oliver
might join the League of Assassins...
Laurel is Black Canary, and Thea is training
with Malcolm, so I know about bad times.
Okay.
Joe and I found out...
that Wells isn't
who he says he is.
He...
He is the man that
killed my mother.
- Oh, my God. But he's been helping you.
- Get faster, stronger. I know.
- Why?
- I don't know.
I don't know anything anymore,
especially who I can and can't trust.
So you think Cisco and Caitlin
are helping him?
That's impossible.
- Is it?
- They were trying to save you today.
- They did save you.
- Wells has also saved me many times.
I thought that Wells
was a great man.
And I was so wrong about him.
What if I'm wrong
about everything else too?
Hey, guys.
Uh, things are getting a little
intense in here.
Please, can't we just have
a nice evening?
Okay, so it's my fault that
we're not having a nice evening?
I am your girlfriend.
Who you live with. I shouldn't
have to beg you to talk to me.
If I could talk to you about
this, I would, believe me.
But I can't.
- You know what? I am not
hungry anymore. - Iris.
When you are ready to act like we are
two people who love each other, call me.
I'll be at my dad's.
Thank you for
dinner. I gotta go.
Uh, emergency at S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Go.
- Sorry.
Well, only 17 more
courses to go.
Containment breach,
foreign object detected.
Did I get it?
I think I got it.
Where is he?
Thank you.
Let's see what makes this bee
so poisonous. Ugh.
You saved my life.
That is one odd-looking bee.
That's because it
isn't a bee at all.
It's a robot.
No way.
Unbelievable.
This bot's got a 360-degree
vision system.
I mean, we're talking
multiple microcameras...
all coming from various
angles at the same time.
- Which means... - It can see
all around the room at once.
- That is amazing.
- Amazing.
Disturbing.
It's next-gen hardware
that's nowhere near the market.
- So we're not dealing with a metahuman.
- It's just a mad scientist.
Cisco, you said Bill Carlisle
was a robotics engineer.
Let's cross-reference his
previous employers with Kang's.
Allow me. Mama's been away from
the keyboard for far too long.
Okay.
They both worked
at Mercury Labs.
Let's call Joe. I think it's time
we paid a visit to an old friend.
Twice in one year, Harrison.
You really are vying for
comeback scientist of the year.
- Always a pleasure, Christina.
- To what do I owe this visit?
Did you find my tachyon prototype, or are
you here to blackmail me for another one?
- Do you have another one?
- We came here for information.
Bill Carlisle and Lindsay Kang.
Former employees
who were recently murdered.
My God. I wasn't aware.
Stung to death by robotic bees.
- You're looking for Brie Larvan.
- Brie Larvan?
A quite brilliant roboticist...
who once developed miniature
mechanical bees for agricultural use.
Kang and Carlisle warned me that Brie was
weaponizing the bees for military use...
so I terminated her.
Well, it seems that you would be
on her hit list too, doctor.
You've got to let
us keep you safe.
I'm all too familiar with your
inability to protect things, Harrison.
I can take care of myself.
Good day, gentlemen.
Thank you.
Hey.
Okay, so we found our queen bee.
Brie Larvan. She's a roboticist.
Joe is running a trace on her
location. So far, nothing.
- Good.
- Where is Ray?
He's working on his
suit with Cisco.
I like Ray. He seems like
he's a really good guy.
He is a good guy.
Just like Cisco
and Caitlin. Girl.
Is that why you called me here?
You're in a tricky situation, but that's
when you need your friends to have your back.
- And how can they if you won't
let them? - It's not that simple.
What if Joe is right and I
tell them and it backfires?
Wells isn't just their boss, Felicity.
He is their mentor, their hero.
My hero.
Look, it...
I don't know what to do.
When I first met Oliver...
before I knew he was
the Arrow, he would...
He would ask me
to do weird things for him.
Like decrypt a bullet-ridden
computer or hack some company.
And when I would ask him why...
he would come up
with these ridiculous excuses.
And I always knew he was lying,
but I would help him anyway.
- You know why?
- Mm.
Because I knew Oliver was a
good person with a good heart.
Cisco and Caitlin...
they're no different.
H9)'-
So you're really
staying here tonight?
Tonight, tomorrow night,
the night after that.
Do you think that Eddie's
cheating on me?
No. Eddie's not
that kind of guy.
Well, I don't know what else
he could be hiding from me.
Iris...
Remember when we were kids...
and Joe would come
home from work...
with that blank
expression on his face?
Hmm. Yeah. The Earth-to-Joe
look. How could I forget?
I never understood that look until
I started working for the C.C.P.D.
Showing up at crime scenes
and seeing someone murdered...
it can be ugly work.
And I'm lucky.
I get to hide behind the science
of it and just stay in my lab.
But Eddie, he's out there...
every day, in the darkness.
And I just... I think that maybe
if he doesn't wanna talk to you...
about his work, it's probably because
he wants to keep you in the light.
What?
Just surprised.
You going out of your way like this
to help me see Eddie's point of view.
I mean...
Eddie makes you happy.
And all I ever want
is for you to be happy, Iris.
Welcome home.
Ha, ha. It's so fun to watch
grown men play with their toys.
You're so lucky. Ray is
so nice and smart and hot.
Yeah, it's kind of like I'm
dating Barry but in Oliver's body.
- A sentence you will never repeat to
anyone. - Your secret's safe with me.
It must have reactivated.
If it's controlled wirelessly...
I can trace its signal and figure
out where it's trying to go.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, boy.
- What?
- The swarm is headed for Mercury Labs.
Brie Larvan's going after Tina.
Hello, Dr. McGee.
You gonna open the window,
or should I buzz myself in?
How do we stop them?
She's gotta be remotely piloting
those bees from somewhere.
We need to stop
this bug-eyed glasses woman.
And her mini bandits.
Bug-Eyed Bandit.
She's in an
abandoned greenhouse.
Barry, take out Brie.
It's the only way to stop these.
- What about Dr. McGee? - The
defibrillator in your suit is broken.
You cannot risk going
near Mercury Labs.
The bees can't
penetrate my suit.
I'll go.
Whoa. We haven't tested out
the new power system yet.
We'll do it now.
- I'm following you.
- I'm driving.
And I'm kissing you.
- Dr. Wells...
- Mr. Palmer will protect Tina.
Go.
You fired me,
destroyed years of my research.
You took everything from me.
What you were doing was wrong.
You wanted to harm people,
not help them.
I did what I had to do.
You mean ruin my life? Sure.
Now I'm doing what I have to do.
- Found her.
- Felicity, can you jam their frequency?
I already tried, but I might be able
to redirect them onto a new target.
- Ray, get ready for incoming.
- We have the technology.
It's over, Brie.
I know you're trying to kill Dr.
McGee. You think that she betrayed you.
I can imagine how that feels.
You think you understand
the sting of betrayal?
I'll show you what
it means to be stung.
Barf)'-
Barry, I hacked into the bees'
frequency. I'm controlling them.
I'm the queen of this hive.
Oh, she's good. She's
like my nemesis.
I've never had a nemesis before.
I kind of like it.
- Okay, Cisco. Now what?
- Ray, get to the ocean.
If the bots follow you into
water, their electronics will fry.
Got it.
Wait, but so will my suit.
Cisco, I'm fried.
I'm losing propulsion control.
Can you see the van?
- Yeah.
- We'll catch you.
- You Will?
- We Will?
We Will.
All right.
Keep it steady.
Unh. Whew.
The Atom lives.
- Argh.
- Oh.
Let's work on some softer gloves
for next time, okay?
Sorry.
Oh, you wanna bring it?
It's been brought.
Rude.
Felicity, right now would be
a good time to do something.
Stay away from Barry Allen.
- Felicity!
- Got it.
Boom. Drop the mike.
It's metaphorical, of course,
because I don't have a real mike.
Brie's restrained. Call C.C.P.D.
- Some kind of team you have here.
- It helps to have friends in your corner.
- That was like...
- This guy's a stunt driver.
Are you okay?
Cisco!
Come on, please.
Wake up.
Cisco has been stung.
He's going into shock.
I'm on my way.
Come on, stay with me.
Hold on, back up.
I'm gonna try something.
Cisco.
Either my fear of bees is over,
or it just got a lot worse.
Thank God you're okay.
I've never had anybody
take a bee for me.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome, bro.
Cisco...
you're a hero, man.
- Dr. McGee.
- May I come in?
Yeah, of course. What
can I do for you?
I wanted to apologize.
I should have listened to you
when you warned me about Brie.
Perhaps next time I will take the
C.C.P.D.'s offer of protection.
After we lost your
tachyon prototype...
I can understand why you
were hesitant to trust us.
Thank you.
Can I ask you something?
I couldn't help but
notice some tension...
between you and Dr. Wells.
That's all in the past.
Do you mind if I ask what
happened between you two?
I ask myself that same question
all the time.
Fifteen years ago, Harrison
and I were thick as thieves.
We were promising young
scientists in Starling City.
He was such a kind man.
Then everything changed
after Tess died.
They were gonna get married.
I understand how grief can affect
someone, but this was more than that.
It was like after that day...
Harrison Wells became
a completely different person.
Good day.
Bye.
Doctor.
How's Cisco?
Happy to be alive.
And sad that Ray is leaving.
It was a really brave thing
he did, risking his life.
- Selfless.
- Yeah, definitely was.
And another end to another
exciting adventure in Central City.
- Ah. Yes. Thank you.
- Ray, thank you for all your help.
And I hope you figure out
the problem with your suit.
- I have.
- Oh.
All this time, I've been looking
at the power source the wrong way.
I kept thinking we
needed to go bigger.
But the solution, as always,
is simply to go smaller.
Oh. Great.
- You okay?
- Mm-hm.
I'm gonna be. Thank
you for your advice.
Oh, I won't even
charge you the 5 cents.
Bye, Felicity.
Bye, Barry.
H9)'-
What's up?
I, um...
I spoke to Barry last night.
Oh, yeah?
He was trying to help me understand
why you've been so off lately.
Why you might be having trouble
connecting with me.
Really?
What did he say?
It was a good explanation.
Valid.
But the truth is,
it doesn't matter.
Because when you love someone,
you tell them everything.
So if you love me, Eddie, you'll
tell me what is going on with you.
_Or__ Or what?
You know what.
All right, all right.
Who's ready for some...
karaoke?
We are not going
to karaoke, are we?
No. Um...
This is everything we know
about my mother's murder...
and the Reverse-Flash.
I've been gathering information
on him for a long time.
And this is everything we know
about Dr. Wells.
I don't understand.
What do Dr. Wells and the Reverse-Flash
have to do with each other?
Um...
They're the same person.
That's impossible.
Look, Caitlin, it took me a
long time to believe it too...
but it's him.
Dr. Wells is a speedster?
- He's paralyzed.
- Is he, though?
And why would he
kill Barry's mother?
It doesn't make any sense.
Cisco? Say something.
I've been having these dreams.
Mostly at night
but sometimes during the day.
But they don't really feel
like dreams. They...
They feel real.
What happens in the dream?
Dr. Wells is the Reverse-Flash.
And he kills me.