That's the chess player?
She looks like Ann-Margret.
Let's hope the Russians like redheads.
In the words of Thomas Huxley,
"The chessboard is the world,
the pieces are
the phenomena of the Universe,
the rules of the game are
what we call the laws of Nature,
and the player on the other side
is hidden from us."
Ladies and gentlemen,
dear comrades,
please welcome,
Thank you.
And maybe she takes with check.
He takes back.
But then she takes his rook.
So what? He's got h5.
Yes, that's a nasty pin.
And, she's done.
Elizabeth Harmon plays pawn to Queen four.
Borgov plays pawn to Queen four.
Harmon plays pawn to Queen Bishop four.
The Queen's Gambit.
Borgov declines,
moves pawn to King four.
The Albin Counter Gambit--
Knight to G6.
Go!
Knight to G6!
Let's play.