My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other
meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
You're just letting us go?
Just remember
who it was made sure
you didn't
get thrown on that plane.
I call it the Wizard's Wand.
Captain Singh mentioned there
may be positions available
on your anti-meta-human
task force.
- Why do you want to do this?
- Mark Mardon killed my dad.
James Jesse, Your Honor,
AKA... the Trickster.
You're going to prison
either way, James.
You stay away from me and
you stay away from my father.
If he finds out
that he might have a son
that grew up
without knowing him,
it would crush him.
Jesse's my daughter
and Zoom has her.
[electricity crackling]
You're next.
[electronic music]
♪
[groans]
[gasping]
Go ahead. Kill me.
But... my daughter...
is innocent.
Please...
Let...
Jesse...
live...
[gasping]
Go on.
Say something!
[suspenseful music]
Merry Christmas.
[sleigh bells jingling]
[jazzy Christmas music]
♪
- Whoo.
- [laughs]
I had to fight some
old lady for the last one.
They didn't have
any Green Arrow dolls.
Don't know why you'd want
a toy of that crazy man.
I can't figure out
what to get Barry.
I was thinking
you could give him this.
Oh, that's nice.
But I kind of want to get him
something more meaningful.
I mean, it's been a strange,
emotional 12 months.
Yeah, you don't have to tell me.
Oh, I know, babe.
I miss Eddie too.
How about you get Barry
a really nice watch?
Like Grandpa Ben gave to you.
That ain't a bad idea.
You know, my dad only
gave me this watch
because I was always late.
- You?
- Yeah.
He always gave a gift
with a not-so-hidden message,
like this watch or the time
he bought me free weights
because he said
I was too skinny.
I told him, "When I have a son,
I'm only giving him
fun presents."
This thing barely works.
Don't know why I still wear it.
[tapping on watch]
Because it's from family.
You sure you're all right?
Yeah, yeah. I promise.
You know, we should really be
more professional.
You do realize
you initiated that.
Yes, and I'm fully prepared
to reprimand myself then.
I'm just saying, you know,
anyone could walk in,
like, Joe or Captain...
Yo.
But I have, like,
a 4:00 to 12:00, but...
- I'll see you later.
- Yeah, all right.
- I'll see you for Christmas.
- Yeah, okay. Bye.
I'm so happy for you. Truly.
Thank you.
It means a lot to me
that you like her.
[sighs] I don't know.
Wells, um, he left me
that message where he said
that I'd never really be happy.
And for a while I really started
to believe him,
but, now... I... I don't know.
Maybe there is a way to...
Are you okay? What's wrong?
[crying] I'm so sorry.
I can't keep this
in anymore, Barry.
I know I was so mad
at you and Dad
for not telling me that
you were The Flash,
but when I found out about this,
I didn't know what to do.
What? What's going on?
When Francine came back,
my Dad told me not to trust her
and he was right.
I didn't know how much.
When my mother left us,
she was pregnant.
She had a son.
Joe's son. My brother.
[dramatic music]
What's his name?
Wally.
Wally West.
When I found out,
I told her to leave
and never come back
and to never tell my dad,
but Barry, I feel...
I feel like this
is hollowing me out.
Every time I look at Dad,
I feel like I'm hurting him.
I don't...
I don't know what to do.
I think you know
what you have to do.
I can't. It's gonna kill him.
No, it won't.
You don't have to do this alone.
We can tell him together.
Thank you.
Yeah.
♪
Hey, look. Snow.
Maybe it'll be
a white Christmas.
That'd be nice.
I was thinking
that if we could inject
an unstable neutrino burst
into the individual breaches,
it might cause them
to seal on their own.
And stop Zoom
from travelling back and forth
between our worlds.
At least then we wouldn't
have to worry about him
sending any more meta-humans
over for Barry to fight.
- It means a lot.
- What does?
You looking after Barry.
He's been through a lot
the last few weeks.
Barry's not the only person
here I want to keep safe.
Oh, dear Lord,
just kiss already.
- Oh, the thirst is real.
- Is everything all right?
Yeah, I keep checking,
but all is quiet
on the meta-human front.
Hey, you think Zoom decided
to take Christmas off?
What's Christmas?
Oh, well,
it's this holiday we have
where we cut down trees
and sing songs
to celebrate the birth
of a baby 2,000 years ago,
and then the Romans killed him
so we give each other gifts...
That's your explanation?
- I know what Christmas is.
- Oh, right, of course.
Um, you know, Joe
and Barry and Iris
are having people over
for Christmas Eve,
and they said we could
invite whoever we want.
- Who... who do you want?
- You.
I want to invite you, I mean.
This is so painful.
Have you guys seen Harry?
Uh, no, I have not.
I told him to rest.
He's just as stubborn
as all the rest of
my male patients in this place.
I'm gonna
leave you two alone, okay?
I'm gonna go find Harry.
Holy Hannah!
- Hi.
- Everything okay?
- Sure.
Why wouldn't it be?
[chuckles] Why wouldn't it be?
[wind howling]
Man, it's really coming down.
The news didn't
say anything about snow.
Maybe it's a Christmas miracle.
[wind howling]
[glass shatters]
Let it snow.
We got a code... Aah!
[alarms blaring]
Knock, knock.
[dramatic music]
So.
Early parole. You interested?
Don't mean to be a noodge,
but the exit is upstairs.
Just need one more thing.
- _
- [door clanks]
♪
You got to be kidding me.
It's beginning to look
a lot like Christmas.
[evil laughter]
Please tell me
this is not happening...
It's official, Santa hates us.
This sudden blizzard
took out cameras
and the security system.
I mean, thank God
nobody was killed,
but there's no trace
of Mardon, Jesse, or Snart.
Speaking of which,
with Mardon back on the scene...
Yeah?
Patty might not be
thinking so clearly.
What do you mean?
What does Mardon
have to do with Patty?
[dramatic music]
We should have expected this.
♪
The unexpected drop
in barometric pressure
had to mean
Mardon was back in town.
Patty...
Jesse was on full
communication lock down,
but that doesn't mean Mardon
and Snart weren't in contact.
Patty, Joe told me about Mardon.
[scoffs] I can't talk
to you about this.
Hey, Patty, it's okay.
♪
Got it.
Look, Barry, you're a
really sweet guy,
but you have no idea what's
really going on in this city.
I mean, you don't even
know that Harrison Wells...
I'm sorry, I don't have time
to bring you up to speed.
That's ironic.
Patty, Patty,
look I care about you a lot.
I don't want to see you
do anything reckless.
I'm a cop.
Going after criminals
is in my job description.
It's not reckless.
And powers or not, Mardon's
gonna answer for what he's done.
Patty...
♪ Deck the halls ♪
♪ With body parts
from a girl named Holly ♪
♪ Fa la la la la, la la la la ♪
I don't remember those
being the lyrics.
I am tremendously creative.
That I can tell you.
You'd better be.
I didn't break you out...
I didn't break
either of you out,
because I was looking to make
some new friends.
That is not the holiday
spirit, Marky-Mark.
Christmas is a time
for togetherness.
And what says togetherness
more than mass graves?
- Hmm?
- So why did you break us out?
Well, I owed you one,
and this guy, he's just crazy.
It's a compliment.
And we all want the same thing.
- Fashion advice?
- To see The Flash dead.
Well, that was more of a
New Years resolution,
but, hey, I'm flexible.
That hasn't gone so well
for anyone in this room.
What makes you think
you can stop him this time?
Three against one.
Plus, the one
isn't quite what he was.
See, another speedster
dressed all in black
nearly took him out
a few weeks ago.
He's vulnerable. He's weak.
It's a mistake
to underestimate him.
With my power,
his... flair, and your smarts,
we can put him
in the ground for good.
- Tell me your plan.
- Tell me you're in.
- I'm thinking about it.
- What's the matter?
A few months in the clink
make you soft, did it, Snart?
- [gun whines]
- [whooshes]
- You wanna dance?
- Boys, boys, boys!
Play nice! Mellow out, Mardon.
Don't have a snit, Snart.
Here's an idea.
We all go out, have a few
drinks, kill some carolers.
We'll all feel better.
All right.
So what's it gonna be, Snart?
[laughs] Oh, yeah.
The Weather Wizard,
Captain Cold, and the Trickster.
There's three of them
and one of you.
I do not like those odds.
And I'm gonna be no help
without my speed, so...
Oh, oh, light bulb up here.
I have an idea.
Most weather phenomena
are marked, no pun intended,
by the change of electric charge
and pressure in the atmosphere.
We could just
map out those fluctuations...
To pinpoint his location.
Right, it would just be
a matter of removing all...
The electricity
from his immediate surroundings.
Both: Attracting it to one spot.
The same way
a lightning rod does.
Only instead of a lightning rod,
we could use...
A wand?
Have we already had
this conversation?
- Kind of.
- What does that mean?
All right, so the last time
Mardon attacked,
he, um, generated a tidal wave
that destroyed
all of Central City.
So why are you not all
sleeping with the fishes?
Earth-2 has "The Godfather"?
Every Earth
has "The Godfather," Vito.
So I ran back through time.
One day into the past
and I got a do-over
and I stopped Mardon
before he could hurt anyone.
You shouldn't have
messed with the timeline.
That's what
the other Wells said.
So the good news is,
in that timeline,
you created The Wand
and it worked.
So you just got to do it again.
For the first time.
- Yeah, no pressure.
- I can give you a hand.
- Best of both worlds?
- I like that.
You good, Harry?
Yeah, why wouldn't I be?
Holiday blues?
It can't be easy knowing Zoom
still has his daughter.
Yeah, all right,
look, I'll be right back.
I have something
I have to deal with.
Hey.
[chuckles]
Okay, the last time
the two of you
were looking at me like that,
it was when you both
took my convertible
on a joy ride
and wrapped it around
that big oak tree
on Fairmont Drive.
Dad, um...
All right, Joe, we have
something we need to tell you.
No, um...
I have something
that I need to tell you.
It's about Francine.
[clears throat]
When she left us...
she was pregnant.
[melancholy music]
♪
Did she have the baby?
Yes.
His name is Wally.
Wally West.
Short for Wallace.
That's what we were gonna
name you if you were a boy.
I only found out
a couple weeks ago.
Dad, I am so sorry
that I didn't tell you sooner.
That's why she reached out to us
after all these years.
She wanted us to know before...
Before she died.
And I thought Francine
was running out of surprises.
♪
I got to get to work.
Dad, listen... Dad.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Just let me sit with it.
♪
Do you think that
he's gonna be okay?
I do, yeah, I think...
It's just a lot to take in.
He just needs a little time
to process it.
Ho, ho, ho.
Mmm. Cocoa isn't cocoa without
the mini marshmallows.
And you're out. I checked.
- [whooshes]
- Are you out of your mind?
Breaking into my home?
Careful. I made an upgrade
to the cold gun.
If I release my grip
from the handle,
the core goes critical.
You might make it,
she won't.
[tense music]
♪
Read your article on the
disappearing middle class.
Strong point of view.
Nice prose style.
Yeah, well, who needs a Pulitzer
when you have a homicidal
maniac's seal of approval.
Didn't Barry tell you?
I had a rough childhood.
Everyone in this room
had a rough childhood.
- Get over it.
- Why are you here, Snart?
I got the Noel spirit,
wanted to give you a gift.
Mardon broke Jesse
and me out to kill you.
Jesse's on board, of course.
He's shaking with excitement.
Me, I'm gonna pass.
Why? You grow a conscience?
Mardon wants revenge.
Jesse wants chaos.
I'm just not invested
like they are.
You mean there's no money
in it for you?
I was never much
for non-profit work.
If you're not in with them,
then tell me where they are.
Nah, consider me more
of a secret Santa.
Besides, you and your friends
love to solve a good mystery.
[scoffs]
You are full of it, Snart.
I think my friends and I
saved your sister's life
and you can't stand
owing me a marker.
I hate to break it to you,
but that... that right there
is called honor.
Go on, make your pitch.
I can see you're dying to.
Help me stop them.
Sorry, I'm not interested
in being a hero.
[scoffs]
Well, you're doing
a pretty lousy job
of being a villain this week.
Merry Christmas, Barry.
Hey.
I was just thinking
about a big drug bust
that me and Singh
made about ten years ago.
Afterward,
we went for a steak lunch
to treat ourselves
for a job well done
and while we were ordering,
I got this feeling in my chest.
Like my heart
was being squeezed.
I knew something wasn't right.
So I called your school
and the nurse said to me that
she was just about to call me.
Iris was on her way
to the hospital.
When her appendix burst.
And I knew it.
I could feel it, right here.
I knew my kid needed me.
So if I have that feeling
as a parent,
why didn't I feel it
from my son?
Joe, it's not your fault that
you didn't know about him.
Yeah, it was.
When Francine left rehab
that last time,
I should've looked for her.
I'm a cop. I could've found her.
Brought her back here.
Tried again. Tried harder.
You were protecting Iris.
I've been telling
myself that for 20 years.
A 20-year lie,
but I wasn't protecting her,
I was protecting myself.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
I couldn't...
I hated not being able
to help Francine.
So it was easier
for her to be dead.
Out of my life.
Out of our lives.
But it wasn't for Iris.
I was being selfish.
And that poor boy
paid the price.
Joe...
He never had a father...
to read to him at night,
show him to throw a football,
to make him feel safe.
And loved.
Who taught him
how to be a man, Barry?
"Him."
I can't even say his name.
What have I done?
Joe, look,
you have been there for me
every day since I met you.
You have.
You would have done
the exact same thing for him
if you could have, I know it.
I'm sorry.
Where's your partner, Spivot?
I don't know,
I'm not his babysitter.
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm not sure where Joe is.
♪ Flash-y the red-nosed
speedster ♪
♪ Had a very shiny suit ♪
♪ And if you ever saw him ♪
♪ You might even want to puke ♪
[gags]
Merry Christmas, kiddie-winks.
I'm back!
Get TARU down here now.
I want to know
how he's doing this.
Citizens, you know,
the holidays can be a time
for gentle reflection
on the year past.
Our ups and downs,
our triumphs and heartaches,
but don't forget,
it can also be a time
for disemboweling our enemies.
We don't have
a Trickster on Earth-2.
He's one of a kind.
My stocking won't be
completely stuffed
until it's filled to the brim
with bloody Flash parts.
So what do you say, speed freak?
You wanna roast chestnuts?
I want all tactical units
on high alert.
Get in touch
with other precincts,
I want watch commanders
coordinating deployment.
Spivot, I need you to...
Spivot!
Are there any clues as to
where he is based on the video?
None that I can see.
Guys, there's a reflection
of something in his cornea, see?
- What is that?
- Not sure.
That's Mr. Jiggle Wiggle.
- Come again?
- It's a doll.
A stuffed children's toy.
I gave one to my daughter
when she was six.
Mr. Jiggle Wiggle was
manufactured by Okamura Toys...
Yahtzee!
Okamura once had a shipping
facility in Central City
that shut down four years ago;
it's been abandoned ever since.
What if Weather Wizard's there?
The wand's not finished.
The Trickster is.
[tense music]
♪
[whooshes]
What are you doing here?
Same thing as you.
Trying to catch a murderer.
♪ Dreidel, dreidel, dreidel ♪
♪ I made it out of clay ♪
We can't let Christmas hog
all the holiday fun!
Happy Hanukkah!
♪ Dreidel, dreidel, dreidel ♪
I made you out of C-4!
[laughs]
Put that in your pipe
and smoke it!
[repeating] ♪ Oh, dreidel,
dreidel, dreidel ♪
I'm afraid we
are definitely looking at
closed casket funerals.
There's nowhere for me
to run us to!
- So what should we do?
- Hold me.
- I'm seeing someone.
- Me too. Don't let go.
[dust whooshing]
[dramatic music]
♪
Detective.
It was all just a trap for you.
Mardon and Jesse
aren't even here.
- They're still on the loose.
- How did you know to come here?
Because there was a reflection
in Jesse's eye
of Mr. Jiggle Wiggle.
And that's the thing
that my dad...
It doesn't even matter.
That's why you came here alone
without any backup?
Because of your father?
You don't know
anything about me.
I know
that you're being reckless.
And I'm sure
the people in your life
care enough about you to not
want to see you get hurt.
Except Mardon
didn't kill my father.
I did.
See, he had a little shoe shop,
and we didn't have any money,
so I worked there after school.
Except one day
I decided not to show up,
because I was being stupid
and silly with my friends.
I didn't even call to tell him
that I was ditching.
So he brought
the deposits to the bank,
not me.
He was shot and killed
by Mardon, not me.
That's why you became a cop.
Joined the meta-human
task force.
It'll be legal
when I kill Mardon.
I have made my whole life about
getting justice for my father,
even if it meant
I didn't have a life
and now I met
a really great guy,
and that doesn't even
feel real to me
and I'm scared he's gonna
find out how angry I am.
I don't even know why
I'm telling you this.
Sometimes it's just easier
to say things
to someone with no face.
Thank you for saving me.
You know, even if you get
this guy that wronged you,
it doesn't always
make things better.
It has to be better than this.
Patty, it's me. Again.
I'd really love to talk.
I'm worried about you.
Anyway, just give me a call when
you get a chance, all right?
Thank you. Bye.
- Barry.
- Yeah?
How's it look?
Wow, eerily familiar.
How's Patty?
She is, um,
hiding a lot of pain
behind her smile.
They say couples start
to resemble each other
after a little while.
The thing is, I mean, she only
opened up to Flash, not me.
So even if I could got her
on the phone,
I don't know what to say.
Well, it's been my experience
that just being around you
can be a big help.
Thank you.
I want an iPhone,
an iPad, and an iTouch.
Ho, ho, ho, dial it back,
Mr. Greedy.
Those are a little out
of Santa's price range.
How about this?
Now remember,
don't open it until tomorrow.
It's a surprise.
[laughing]
[tense music]
[whooshes]
Have you decided?
- I need more time.
- Don't we all.
- Decide.
- I need more time.
Maybe if I go up there
and kill
a few of your new friends...
- No!
- One more day.
I'll tell your daughter
you said, "Hello."
[whooshing]
- What's that? Is that Mardon?
- That's definitely him.
Atmospheric pressure
just dropped 200 hectopascals.
- Where?
- Central City Square.
The tree lighting ceremony.
There's thousands
of people there.
[dramatic music]
♪
[whooshes]
Oh, glad to see you.
Maybe you can help me.
Help get back to a jail cell?
- It'll be my pleasure, Mark.
- No.
No, see, I'm trying to decide
if I should kill
everybody down there
with a deadly hail storm,
or... little trickier,
with acid rain,
what do you think?
Ah, let me think, um...
How about neither?
You see this wand here?
Guess what?
[wind rushing]
Um... guys? He's flying.
He can fly?
Since when can he fly?
Well, he's using his
powers to alter the air pressure
around him to create
pockets of updraft that can...
No, he can fly.
- Barry, get him.
- Yeah.
[whooshing]
[tense music]
♪
[helicopter blades whirs]
[electric crackling]
- [groans]
- [overlapping screams]
You didn't really think
I'd let you hurt
all these people, did you?
No, of course not,
but bet you're gonna let me
hurt you.
[wheels skidding]
Feliz Navidad!
Time for a real
war on Christmas.
What is this?
That is a box with a bomb in it.
Yup, I've handed out
about 100 of them today.
It feels so good to give.
You see, right now,
there are 100 random children
who've each taken home a box
just like that one
and are shoving it
under their Christmas tree.
There's no way
for you to to all of them,
even if you knew where to look.
Oh, no, Please don't do this.
What? Me? Kill 100 families?
No, that's up to you.
I'm happy just
to take your life.
So this is how it's gonna be.
You are gonna stand there
and let me end you.
Very publicly
and very painfully
and I'll let everybody live,
but if I see even
a little flicker
of electricity on you...
the casket makers in this town
are gonna have
a very merry Christmas.
So, Flash...
what's it gonna be?
Huh?
[tense music]
♪
There you go.
[chuckles]
♪
- [shouts]
- [groans]
- They're gonna kill Barry!
- Unless we find those bombs.
- Cisco?
- Jay, there's no way.
There is a way.
To find 100
randomly-placed bombs?
We don't have to find 100.
We just have to find one.
And then we get rid of them all.
- How?
- A breach.
That's right.
We sent Grodd away.
We can do the same to these
bombs, all of them.
Do you have a drone
in your workshop?
- Yeah.
- Does it fly?
- Good.
I'm taking it.
You're not getting it back.
I'll warm up the van.
[laughing]
♪
[wand crackling]
I'm cross-referencing
credit card statements with
toll road usage and families
with children under ten.
Hold up...
Make a U-turn. Two streets back.
- [tires screech]
- [engine revs]
[knock on door]
Your toys. Give them to me.
Mom!
[groans]
Flash, you all right?
You don't look so good.
I know...
I'll give you a jolt.
[groans]
[electricity crackles]
Oh!
[rapid beeping]
Harry, what is the plan?
One of the 52 breaches opened
by the singularity
is 1/4 mile
directly above the city.
We are gonna use your drone
to put this bomb
into that breach.
Okay, how does that work?
One down, 99 to blow.
Basic physics, Ramon. Magnetism.
Magnetism. Magnets of opposite
poles attract one another.
Help me out, Garrick.
If we can change
the dimensional frequency
of this bomb
and get it through that breach...
It'll drag all the rest of
the bombs right along with it.
I'll drive. Okay, hold on.
[sighs] I'm done.
He's all yours.
[coughs] Oh, God...
[chuckles]
To think this city worships you!
But, when I kill The Flash,
they'll realize I'm the man
who saved Central City!
[dramatic music]
[rattling, crashing]
[laughing]
It's working.
- Was that you?
- No! Gut him!
All right, I'm gutting already.
Barry, the bombs are gone.
[electricity crackles]
Uh-oh...
[whooshes]
[grunts]
[panting]
[victorious music]
♪
How do you like
the magnets, bitch?
[police sirens wailing]
Detective, it's taken care of.
They can't hurt anyone else.
[energy surges]
[groaning]
What are you doing?
- What are you doing?
- This is for my father.
No, no, no, Detective!
Detective, no.
You can't do this.
He killed my father
for a couple hundred dollars.
What was so important that my
father had to lose his life?
Mardon will get
what he deserves.
- He deserves to die!
- Not like this!
You don't have it
in you, pretty lady.
I've been asking myself that
for the last four years,
and now I know.
No, Patty!
You pull that trigger,
your life ends too.
You will go to prison.
Everything and everyone that
you could have had in your life
will be taken from you.
Again.
Mardon can't take anything else
from you unless you let him.
♪
I didn't know your father, but
I know he wouldn't want this.
Not over him.
Please. Please.
[dramatic music]
Mark Mardon,
you're under arrest.
[handcuffs click]
That was beautiful. [sobs]
- Barry, hey.
- Hey.
Everyone's heading over
to our place for Christmas.
You okay?
Yeah, no,
nothing a little meta-human
regenerative healing
capabilities won't cure.
How'd it go with Francine?
It was good.
It was really good, actually.
I mean, I spent so long
lying about her being dead
that I started
to believe it myself.
But the truth is, those feelings
were always there.
That anger, that regret,
the guilt...
I just didn't realize how much
I needed to forgive her.
And now...
there's room for another West.
Did you meet him?
No. He still doesn't know.
That'll come.
- Wow. You have a son.
- I know, right?
It's crazy.
- Speaking of which, take this.
- What?
No, no, no, no,
I can't take that.
I've always said that one day
I would give this to my son...
[poignant music]
♪
And now I have.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas. Thank you.
[chuckling] Love you.
- I love you too.
- See you at the house.
Yeah.
[exhales deeply]
I know that you're not him...
But he's not here
and I have to say this for me.
In that video message,
you said that...
that I would never
really be happy...
And I've been trying...
I've been trying really hard.
[breathes deeply]
After what Joe said,
and helping Patty,
I realize that
you're still in my heart.
How much I hate you
for what you've done.
I don't want to hate you
anymore, I can't.
Can't hate you anymore.
I forgive you.
♪
You need me for something?
No, no, I'm good.
You know, you should come over
for Christmas tonight.
You shouldn't be alone.
It's a nice offer.
I can't celebrate
without my daughter.
All right.
♪
[bouncy Christmas music]
♪ I saw you comin' down
my chimney ♪
- ♪ I saw you, Santa ♪
- [chuckles]
- Strong enough?
- We'll see.
♪
I'll be right back.
- Hey.
- Oh!
What do you have there?
- Mistletoe.
- What's mistletoe?
Oh, um,
it's a hemiparasitic plant
from the genus
Santalaceae family
in North America, I think.
Caitlin, I'm kidding.
We have mistletoe on Earth-2.
Right, of course.
Um, we also have this
tradition over there.
♪
We have that tradition here too.
- Aww.
- Finally.
- [knock at door]
- Oh, let me get that.
- Eggnog, please?
- Yeah.
Hi, I'm so glad
you could make it.
Aw, thank you for having me.
Merry Christmas.
This is for you.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Hey.
- Hi.
I've been really
worried about you.
- I've been calling.
- I know...
and I'm really sorry.
I just have been dealing
with something by myself,
but I want to tell you about it.
I think that I'm ready to.
Someone reminded me
of what's important,
so if you want to hear, I
would like to share it with you.
That would be
the best gift I could get.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
I don't know.
This is a really sweet sweater.
I hope it's as
sweet as this one.
It's matching.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Detective Spivot.
- Hi!
- What brings you here?
- Merry Christmas.
Well, uh, I'm...
Barry's girlfriend.
- About time.
- Cheers.
- [knock at door]
- Are we expecting anybody else?
- Not that I know of.
- Maybe Harry changed his mind.
♪
Hi, I'm Wally.
I'm Francine's son.
♪
I'm... I'm... I'm Joe.
This is Iris.
- Hi.
♪
Uh, I just wanted to...
I don't know.
I guess now's a bad time.
You've got company, so...
No. No, no, no. Come in.
♪
[eerie music]
Time's up, Wells.
What's it gonna be?
I know what you're doing.
I know why you keep sending
villain after villain
from our Earth to this one.
You want Barry to get faster.
You want him to get stronger.
You want him to become more
powerful, more full of...
speed force.
[dramatic music]
♪
You're fattening him up
like a Christmas goose.
The more power he has,
the more I can take
and you're going to help me.
Let me see her first.
[crackling and thudding]
Daddy?
[sobs]
Are you okay? Did he hurt you?
Please help me.
Don't let him
take me back there.
- I won't...
- [whooshes]
Now decide.
In return
for your daughter's life...
I'll do it.
♪
I'll help you steal
The Flash's speed.
Sync and corrections by explosiveskull
WEB-DL resync by kinglouisxx
www.addic7ed.com