- My name is barry allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother
Killed by something impossible.
- Run, barry, run!
- My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
But secretly, I use my speed
To fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
- Mom!
- And get justice for my father.
I am the flash.
Previously on the flash...
You killed my mother. Why?
- If you want to know that,
you're gonna have to catch me.
Not fast enough, flash.
- I love you, iris.
I couldn't lie to you anymore.
I'm sorry.
My name is barry allen.
I am not the fastest man alive.
That title belongs to the man
who killed my mother.
But not for long.
- That was too close.
- He told me to make it hard.
- Pretty sure he didn't tell you
to make him dead.
- Remember,
this is just supposed to be
A training exercise
to improve barry's speed.
- Cisco, you gonna bring it
or what?
- Bring it.
- Why isn't he running away?
Barry, run away.
- Very impressive, mr. Allen.
Your reaction to stimuli
At super-speed
continues to improve.
- It's still not enough.
- It will be.
You keep working like you are,
you stay focused like you are,
And you will be ready
the next time
Your man
in the yellow suit comes around.
- I think
you mean the reverse-flash.
What? He said it, not me.
And he's right.
Yellow suit, red lightning,
and evil...
The reverse of barry.
- Meh.
- Actually, I kind of like it.
- All right, I'm still ready
for another round.
How many more drones
do you have left?
- Two.
And they've got lasers.
No.
- Told you it would break.
- And the shrink says I'm crazy.
What is this place?
- Customs warehouse.
Imported cars from europe,
all worth a fortune.
- Question.
How do you suggest you and I
Drive all these cars
out of here?
- We're not.
We're not stealing anything.
- What are you talking about?
- Our entrance set off
the silent alarms.
The cops will be arriving
in 2 minutes and 14 seconds.
- Bring them.
- That's not for the cops,
as we discussed.
He'll be here.
- You do hear that, right?
- He's not coming.
We're leaving.
- This better make sense
real fast, buddy.
- It will. Let's go.
- You promised me I'd get
to do my thing.
- I always keep my promises.
Seat belt.
- Are you sure
nothing's missing?
- That's what the supervisor
said.
I can check again.
- Bar.
- Hey.
Well, the breakage
indicates that the door somehow
Had zero viscoelasticity
when it hit the ground.
- What does that mean
to normal people?
- Sorry. Uh...
The steel shattered like glass.
It was frozen, joe.
- Snart.
- He's back.
- I thought snart
was some world-class thief.
All these expensive cars...
He didn't take any of them?
It doesn't make sense.
- Eddie, put out an apb
on snart.
- Got it.
- Snart wasn't here
to steal anything.
- He was setting a trap.
- For me.
And by me, I mean...
- yeah, I know who you meant.
- God, you're beautiful.
- Mick.
- This is a joke.
How do you know this flash
didn't skip town, hmm?
Maybe that's
why he didn't show up.
Or maybe he's dead.
Or maybe someone
smarter than you iced him.
- He's not dead,
and he didn't leave town.
- You will tell me
what we're stealing this time.
We are partners, after all.
- This is what we came for.
- That's worth money?
- It's called fire & ice, an
abstract modern-day masterpiece
Said to represent
the dichotomy of being.
- It represents to me
That people with lots
of money buy dumb stuff.
- Osgood and rachel rathaway,
One of the richest couples
in central city,
Paid 25 million for it in paris.
They're flying home with it
today.
- Mm.
- Captain cold is back?
- For a non-metahuman,
Leonard snart is proving
to be quite the nemesis.
- He still has the cold gun,
The one he stole from us,
the one I built.
- Well,
what does he want this time?
- The flash.
If snart wants a fight
with the flash,
Then I'll give him one.
- Well...
You don't think I should?
- I didn't say that.
But, barry,
As fast as you are, you
cannot be everywhere at once.
And it becomes then a question
of priorities.
Now, in the last month,
You have made a commitment
to increasing your speed,
Enhancing your reflexes,
and it's working.
You're finally getting faster.
- Okay, but what am I supposed
to do, just ignore snart?
- The last time you had a fight
with snart, a train derailed.
You were lucky to get
all those people to safety.
And if you don't give
him that fight...
- He may just back off,
and there'll be no casualties.
- Look, barry, cisco
and I will work with joe
And the police
and devise a way to catch cold.
Yes, I said it, cisco.
As soon as it came
out of my mouth, I heard it.
- Yeah, we can definitely
come up with ways
To neutralize snart.
- Listen, barry.
Whether or not you go
after snart, that's your choice.
We here, we will do
whatever we can to support you.
But after this past christmas,
After the events
with the reverse-flash...
I just think he poses
a greater threat to all of us.
- Okay.
- T-minus three days
and counting...
Till the big move in.
You know,
I've never had a roommate.
But it did occur to me
that if we ever get in a fight,
I can't just storm away
and go home,
Because home will be with you.
- Are you predicting
many arguments?
- Have you met me?
- I remember the night we met.
I stopped a mugger
who stole your bag.
- My hero.
- Hey.
- Eddie, you know where joe is?
- Uh... I think he's upstairs
in your lab.
- Okay, thanks.
- No second thoughts
about moving in together?
- None.
- Joe, hey.
- Hey. I'm glad you're back.
I've been going
over snart's file.
- Thanks.
Yeah, I need to talk to you.
As csi, my work
on this case is done.
And as the flash,
I don't think
I can focus on snart right now.
- You mind telling me
what brought about this change
Of heart?
- This man in yellow,
the man that killed my mom,
Is still out there.
I have to be ready
to face him,
Which means amping up my speed.
It's a question of priorities.
- Your mom's killer
Isn't the only reason
you've been doing this.
You told me that if you
could use your powers
To save someone from a burning
building, you would.
- Look, dr. Wells and s.T.A.R.
Labs are gonna work with you.
Cisco thinks he has a way
To protect the police
against snart's cold gun.
- Barry, I can understand
if you're scared.
We talked about this.
- Of course I'm scared, joe.
This guy could run
into the precinct
And kill everyone
in here in seconds.
He threatened iris.
I won't let him hurt
the most important people
In my life again.
If that means devoting
every second
I have outside this place
to getting faster
And to stopping him,
then that's what I'm gonna do.
I'm sorry.
I've made up my mind.
- Aw. Mcsnurtle the turtle.
How you been?
When did you stop
sleeping with this?
It was your favorite.
- He was.
But if I remember correctly,
You took him away from me after
I broke your duke ellington:
Live at the blue note vinyl.
- Oh, yeah.
- Mm.
- You can have him back now.
- Oh, gee, thanks.
Oh, dad.
- I'm going to miss you, baby.
- Dad, I'm only
ten minutes away.
- I know.
Don't you worry about me.
I'll be fine, just like always.
- Hey.
- You came to help her pack?
- Oh, no. No, no, no.
Iris said that she had
something for me.
- Oh, um...
I found this in my closet.
- I haven't seen this in years.
- Well, the nerd survival kit
is still intact.
- Wow.
- I thought
those might be worth something.
I am so late for work.
I promise I will clean this
up when I get back, okay?
- Bye.
- Bye, yeah.
- Okay.
You mind telling me what's
going on with you and iris?
- Nothing.
- Hmm.
That's funny, because I have
these two things called eyes,
And it doesn't look like you
two are fine.
- I told iris.
- You told iris
you're the flash?
- No, no, no, no.
I'm sorry.
No.
I told her
how I felt about her.
- Oh, god.
- Mm-hmm.
- What did she say?
- Well, I mean, she's still
moving in with eddie, isn't she?
I just want to pretend
like it never even happened.
I mean, that's what
we're both doing, so...
- Well, not saying how you feel
is what got you in this mess
In the first place.
Speaking of which,
We both know she's not gonna
clean this mess up anytime soon.
- Nope.
Sure.
- Uh, excuse me.
If I could have
everybody's attention, please.
- You have our attention,
mr. Ramon.
- Okay, check it.
So dr. Wells and I,
We took your ballistic shields
and...
And we lined them with a pretty
sweet compacted heating ribbon
Designed to repel
temperature attacks,
Especially
those reaching absolute zero,
Like captain cold's gun.
- And that's supposed
to keep us from getting
Turned into popsicles?
- Um, yeah.
Yeah, they will.
- How are we supposed to trust
anything from s.T.A.R. Labs
After you nuked the city?
- You're right.
You're right,
you shouldn't trust us.
What happened a year ago...
that was our fault.
And we can't change the past,
as much as we wish we could.
But tomorrow
is a different story.
Tomorrow's a different thing.
We just want the chance
to make things better.
Observe.
- Dummies are one thing.
My officers are another.
- You seem pleased
with yourself, doctor.
- Well, I'm just happy to help
the police catch snart, joe.
- Barry might be able
to help too.
- I think cisco's heat shields
are more than up to the task.
And, joe, if barry
feels he's gonna endanger lives
By taking on snart
and, conversely, feels
He's gonna
save lives by training
To take on the man in yellow...
That's ultimately his call.
- You know what makes
barry so special?
He wants to help everyone
he can, however he can.
Always has.
Until now.
- I guess it's just a question
of priorities then.
- You know, barry
said the exact same thing to me.
And I thought,
"doesn't sound like him."
I guess because
it sounds like you.
Hey.
- Sorry,
didn't mean to scare you.
- No, it's okay.
I was just kind of focused.
- Gotcha.
What's firestorm?
- It's one of the last things
Ronnie said to me before he...
Flew away.
My dead fiance can fly.
I haven't broke that
to my parents yet.
You doing okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
No, I just...
I told iris
how I felt about her.
- Bold choice.
- I knew where we stood before.
We were best friends.
And... I don't know.
Now I just don't know
What's normal for us anymore.
- Before I met ronnie,
I knew exactly what was going
to happen every day of my life.
It was predictable.
I like predictable.
But when ronnie
and I started dating,
Everything started to change.
He made me try indian food
and scuba diving.
At first it was scary.
But then it was better.
Things weren't really normal
with you pining after iris
And her being totally unaware.
Whatever happens next,
it will be better.
- Wait, caitlin.
Scuba.
- What about it?
- Self-contained
underwater breathing apparatus,
It's an acronym.
- What if firestorm
isn't a word?
Fusion ignition research
experiment and science
Of transmutation originating rna
and molecular structures.
It's 800 pages.
There's a lot
of stuff in there,
But it mostly
focuses on transmutation,
Which is the process of altering
the structure of an element
By unzipping the atoms...
- And rebuilding it to create
an entirely new element.
- Well, the article
was co-written by jason rush,
Who's a grad student
here at hudson university.
So if anybody knows
what happened to ronnie...
- Maybe he does.
- Maybe.
- Thanks.
- Pleasant flight,
mrs. Rathaway?
- Yes, quite.
Thank you.
- Careful, please.
It's worth a fortune.
- Welcome home, mr. Rathaway.
- Thank you, ethan.
- Sir, your son hartley...
he called again.
- We don't have
a son anymore.
- Someone better call 911.
- Move.
Move!
- Snart, freeze.
- Mick!
- Gaaaah!
- What the hell?
- Why do they call you people
the heat?
I'm the heat!
- Forget them, mick.
Get ready for him.
- It's beautiful.
- Mick.
Mick.
Mick!
We go, now!
Is he all right?
Okay.
- Hey. Hey, are you okay?
- I'll call you back.
I'm fine.
Snart's new partner,
He's got this
handheld flamethrower.
Almost everyone was treated
on the scene, but...
We got two in the burn unit,
though.
- I'm sorry.
I should've listened to you.
- It's all good.
But...
The next time snart
and his pyro pal show up,
You make them sorry
they ever messed with you.
I got to call the hospital.
- The cop's bullet ruptured the
secondary internal fuel chamber.
It could've been worse.
You were right to get me
to learn every part and circuit
Of this thing.
Repairing it was...
A snap.
- Give me one reason
I don't kill you right now.
- It's gonna be hard to find
Someone else to listen
to your winning speeches.
- You lost it out there,
just like the last job.
You lost focus, became obsessed.
- I'm obsessed?
What about you?
You're usually counting
the seconds, got the whole thing
Planned out,
dotting "t"s, crossing "I"s.
But all you care about now
is the flash.
- We have to put him down.
- Why?
We got the finger painting.
It's worth millions.
It's ours.
We're rich. Job done.
- And what about the next job,
mick?
And the job after that?
With weapons like these,
No one can stand against us,
no one except the flash.
If you want out,
take the painting and go.
But if you want central city
to be our home where we can do
And take whatever we want...
This is our chance...
Your chance.
- Mm.
Very motivational.
How do we get him?
- The flash
isn't so different from us.
He's got partners too.
- Jason rush?
- Yes. Dr. Snow?
- Please, call me caitlin.
Thank you for meeting me.
- Oh, happy to.
Although,
to be totally up front,
If this is about the resume
I mailed in to s.T.A.R. Labs,
I've already accepted a position
at mercury labs.
- No, actually, I wanted to talk
to you about f.I.R.E.S.T.O.R.M.
- I'm sorry. This was a mistake.
I have to go.
- No, look, someone
I care about is in trouble,
And you're the only clue
I have to help him.
Please.
- What's the line?
I never got paranoid till they
started plotting against me?
- Why would they be
plotting against you?
- Because of our work,
because of f.I.R.E.S.T.O.R.M.
- Transmutation,
The ability to alter matter
on a molecular level.
- We had some rudimentary
success
With our stage one testing,
working with sand grains.
But professor stein
said that we should...
- Sorry, professor martin stein?
He was the co-author
of the paper?
- Yeah, he was our team leader.
He didn't believe in baby steps,
so we skipped to stage three.
- Which was?
- We melted a concrete wall.
But the university
threatened to shut us down.
So professor stein
Published his paper
without them giving permission,
And they went nuts.
So he went to talk
to a friend of his
To secure private backing.
- And who was that?
- He didn't say.
He just said he'd call me later.
And no one has seen or heard
from professor stein since.
- What do you think
happened to him?
- All I know is that the army
showed up the next day
And confiscated
all of our research.
So tell me, dr. Snow, do you
think I'm being too paranoid,
Or not paranoid enough?
- Car trouble?
Aah! Aah!
- I hope we're not enemies.
- What? No, of course not.
- I thought you might blame me
For pushing you
to pursue your training
Rather than help the police.
- Look, I'm an adult.
I make my own choices,
my own mistakes.
And I'm glad
you push me to be better.
It's so weird.
There was a time in my life
That I would've paid money
for your autograph.
And now we're...
- Partners.
- I was gonna say friends.
- In case you doubt it,
you push me to be better too.
- Guys, you have to come
look at this.
When the heat gun was fired,
It increased the surrounding
temperature of the air
Dramatically, sort of like
an extreme heat wave.
Heat wave.
- Stop doing that.
- Okay. I measured
the temperature output
Of both the cold
and heat guns, right?
And while the cold gun
achieves absolute zero,
The heat gun successfully
reaches absolute hot,
Or the hottest temperature
an object can reach.
- Planck temperature.
- So potentially,
These two guns
could cancel each other out.
- Yeah, but to do that, you'd
have to make them cross streams.
- You mean like ghostbusters?
- That film is surprisingly
scientifically accurate.
- And really quite funny.
- Hey, joe. What's up?
Joe, anything?
- There's no sign of caitlin.
Oh, my god.
We're getting her back.
We have to find snart.
- Damn right we do.
Come on, let's go.
- Joe, joe.
We got a hit,
a second pair of prints.
They belong to a mick rory.
- Who is he?
- Big-time arsonist.
He and snart worked a job
last year that went bad.
Half of rory's body
was burned in a fire
That got out of control.
He escaped from an ambulance
on the way to the hospital,
Hasn't been seen since.
Why would they kidnap
someone like caitlin?
- Joe, thawne,
it's on every station.
- Greetings, citizens
of central city.
I am leonard snart.
But you can call me cold.
I'm gonna make this very simple
for everyone.
That red streak you've been
hearing whispers about,
The one mysteriously saving
people these past few months?
Well, surprise, he's real.
He calls himself the flash.
Porter and main, tonight,
sundown.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are, flash.
Show the whole world
you're real.
Or this woman dies.
- No, don't come for me.
Stay away!
- You're a friend of his, huh?
He's fast...
Like fire.
Fire, it's undefinable.
Heat, light, energy.
It's an evolution
when things burn.
- You're sick.
- Maybe you're the sick ones.
You ever think about that?
- Not really.
- Mm.
You've got third-degree burns.
Why didn't you get skin grafts?
- The fire revealed
my true self,
Showed me who I really am.
I wonder what your flash
will reveal
When I burn his suit
and skin off.
- Do whatever you want to me,
but leave him alone.
- Oh, okay.
You and this flash must be
really close
If you're willing
to die for him, hmm?
You want me to show you
who you really are?
That'd be fun.
Show you who you...
Really are.
- Mick.
Time to go.
- You better pray
the next people
That come
through this door is us.
- Hey.
- Okay, you're on.
Good luck, son.
- Thanks.
- Barry,
after tonight,
Everyone's gonna know
that the flash exists.
Are you ready for that?
- I'll see you soon.
- Did... did you see that?
That was him.
That was the flash.
- I don't believe it.
- Believe it.
- The scarlet speedster.
Any preference
on how you'd like to die?
The flame or the frost?
Not in the mood for chitchat.
Gotcha.
Ready when you are.
- Cover me!
Run on this.
- Barry.
Barry, are you okay?
You know what you have to do.
- Yeah, get them
to cross their beams
And cancel their guns out.
I know.
- Mick!
- Ah!
Gotcha!
Yeah, not as easy
as it sounds.
- Eddie, eddie!
- Iris, what are you doing here?
- They evacuated jitters.
I saw your car.
- No, you can't be here.
It's not safe.
- Are you sure caitlin's here,
cisco?
- Starting from caitlin's car,
I pieced together surveillance
footage that led us
To his general area.
- But there's over a dozen
warehouses here.
- Yeah, but only one of them
Has had the heat on
the last three nights.
And I'm betting
mick rory likes it hot.
- Okay.
Stay behind me.
- Caitlin.
- Hmm!
- Caitlin, is that you?
- Mm-mm.
- Caitlin.
- No!
- We're gonna get you
out of here.
Cisco!
Cisco, down!
- The fight is spreading
beyond the evac area.
We need to expand the perimeter.
- We can't.
We can't let this spread.
Oh, my god!
- Thawne, where are you going?
- Eddie, eddie.
- Thawne!
- I thought I was gonna die.
- Not while I'm around.
Or him.
- Hold on!
I got him!
- Look out, look out, look out!
- I can't get them
to cross streams.
Speed isn't getting it done.
- You're right.
Maybe the way to do this
is not by going faster.
- It's going slower.
- Yes.
- Okay.
- Thanks for playing, kid.
- Ha ha ha ha ha!
I didn't see that coming.
I guess you win this time.
- There won't be a next time.
Thank you, detective.
- Aah!
I'm gonna burn
Every last one of you pigs!
Get your hands off me!
- Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Yaaaaah!
- Partner's a real hothead.
- That's funny.
- You know what's hilarious,
snart?
We got you.
- Congratulations.
- Get him out of here.
- Nice work, eddie.
- It wasn't me.
It was the flash.
We're not gonna
be needing these for the trial.
You'll make sure...
- they'll never hurt anyone
Ever again.
- Mr. Ramon.
Thank you.
- He was like a lightning bolt,
zipping through the streets.
Took them both out
singlehandedly.
- That's amazing.
- I wonder who he is.
- If you ask me, he's a hero.
- Okay, all right.
- I think that's it.
- This better be it.
- Well, like you said,
You're ten minutes away,
so if you forget something...
- Okay.
Dad.
- I can't say it enough.
I'll miss you.
- You know you can come
around anytime, joe.
Just give us a heads-up.
Or not.
Come around whenever.
You want a key?
I'm gonna go.
I'll wait... In the truck.
- Why don't I give
you two a minute?
- Well...
Look, I know things have been
Really weird
between us recently.
- Yeah, they have.
- Well, did you know
that I can see into the future?
- Really?
- Oh, yeah.
Did I forget to tell you that?
- You did not mention it, no.
Wow.
So what do you see?
- I see you and eddie
being really happy together.
And things aren't weird
between us anymore.
It took a little time,
but everything's back to normal,
And we're still best friends.
- The future
doesn't sound so bad.
- No.
And it'll be here faster
than you think.
- Dad, is it okay if I...
- Yeah.
My baby girl.
- See you.
Pffft.
Well...
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
How about you?
- It was bound
to happen sometime, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Want to order some pizza
and watch the ball game?
- Make it pizzas and you're on.
- You know, if you ever
need somebody
To come and eat your food,
I'm there.
Besides, the laundry machines
in my building
Have been broken for,
like, a month, so...
- I don't know why you
Moved into that deathtrap
in the first place,
Since you still got
a perfectly good room here.
- You said you were turning it
into a gym.
- We both know I'm not
turning it into a gym.
- Yeah.
- Besides,
You got me running around enough
as it is.
- You know, it is getting hard
to hide the blasting
In and out of my apartment
at all hours of the night
From my neighbors.
I suppose it would make sense
for me to move back in.
I mean, I am a millennial.
That is what we do.
Well, don't do it
on my account.
I'll be fine on my own.
- Oh, yeah, me too.
Sure.
All right, roomie.
You order the pizzas.
I'll unpack.
- No way.
I want to help you.
I want to enjoy this.
- All right.
You know this does nothing
to me.
- Just drink it.
- Mm-hmm.
- I should've burned
the entire city block down.
But instead, I listened to you.
We had the painting.
We had the guns.
We could've had everything.
But you had your stupid plan.
How is that stupid plan
working out for us now?
- Everyone's seen the flash now.
This changes things, again.
- What the...
Snart!
- Relax, mick.
- What's going on?
- The plan.
Hey, sis.
- Nice.