[pensive music playing]
[Alice] You know, most times when people
tell us something's for the best,
it's for the worst.
This time it's true, okay?
-[car door opens]
-I'll be right back.
[car door slams]
[knocking on door]
[Alice sniffles]
[door opens]
Hi, my name is Alice.
Um, is Paul home?
-I'm sorry, ma'am, this isn't a good time.
-[Paul] Hey, what's going on?
-Paul, who is that?
-I'm--
[Paul] Take Christopher back inside
right now.
-What are you doing here?
-[Alice] I came to say you were right.
I was wrong.
-Beth's in the car, just so you are aware.
-No, Jesus! Alice!
It's been five years.
You can't just show up here!
-[Alice] I came because I can't do this.
-Listen to me.
-Okay, I understand.
-I cannot.
-I feel that I am letting her down.
-You cannot be here. Listen to me.
I need you to get back in the car,
and you'll come back.
-We'll talk another time.
-We can't.
-[Alice] We can talk now.
-No, we can't talk now.
No, you shouldn't have brought her here!
-Why did you bring her here?
-Because I need your help!
It's too late! Please go.
[somber music playing]
[car door opens]
[door slams shut]
[Alice moans]
[young Beth] Mama?
Who was that?
A mistake.
A-A rounding error.
It's just a problem I gotta solve.
What problem?
[Alice] What I do with you.
[Jolene] This whole house belong to you?
[chuckles]
You're no orphan.
Not anymore.
-[tea kettle whistling]
-You've been in Lexington this whole time?
[Jolene] Uh, Louisville.
-What brought you back here?
-[liquid pouring]
You don't seem
to like answering your phone.
[busy signal heard through receiver]
Mr. Shaibel died.
There's a funeral day after tomorrow.
I thought…
we could go together.
Thank you.
Mm.
God, Beth.
[Beth] Yeah.
I know.
I'm working as a paralegal.
-You went to college?
-I did, Kentucky State.
I got a Physical Education scholarship.
But when I found out
the school used to be called
the State Normal School
for Colored Persons,
it made me want to study history,
which pissed me off
way more than I already was.
-That's hard to imagine. [spits]
-[laughs]
I switched my major to Poli-Sci.
I'm saving up for law school.
I know, me, a lawyer,
but the world is fucked up.
And if I'm gonna change it,
I can't spend all my time
teaching white girls
how to hold a badminton racket.
[Beth laughs]
-I'm gonna be a radical.
-Didn't know that was a career choice.
It will be.
Mm-hm.
[footsteps receding]
-[pills rattle]
-[Jolene] Hm.
I still take them.
Looks like you're doing
more than pills, honey.
Haven't had anything today.
Not yet, anyway.
I'm supposed to go to Russia
at the end of the year.
-I'm afraid.
-Then don't go.
I have to go.
If I don't, there's nothing for me to do.
I'll just drink.
Well, looks like you do that anyway.
I need to quit the wine,
and the pills, and…
clean this place up.
That'd be a good place to start.
I have to study chess eight hours a day.
They want me to play in San Francisco,
be on The Tonight Show.
-I should probably do all of that.
-Who's they?
Chess Federation.
Oh.
But what I want…
is a drink.
If you weren't here,
I'd probably have a bottle of wine now.
[laughs]
You sound like Susan Hayward
in one of those movies.
I read about this pop artist once.
Bought an original drawing
by Michelangelo.
When he got it home,
he took a piece of art gum, and just…
erased it…
leaving nothing but a blank page.
I remember being really shocked by that.
Now, I wonder if I haven't
somehow erased my own brain.
Let's pretend that you didn't
just compare yourself to Michelangelo.
And let's look at where you're at,
which after being here
all of five minutes,
looks like it's at the bottom
of a fucking hole.
It's looking a lot
like you dug it yourself.
My advice,
stop digging.
Well, maybe it's in my blood.
My mother went crazy.
Went crazy or always was?
I don't know.
She drink or any such?
No, never.
She gone.
Quit thinking about it.
It's not doing you any good.
Besides…
I got you a present.
[book thuds]
[Jolene] It was me all along.
I was pissed at you for being adopted.
What about for being
a white trash, cracker bitch?
Who could forget?
["Jimmy Mack"
by Martha and the Vandellas playing]
♪ Oh, Jimmy Mack
When are you comin' back? ♪
♪ Jimmy
Can you hear me, Jimmy… ♪
[Beth]
How much does a paralegal make, anyway?
Not enough to buy this car,
if that's what you're wondering.
Was a gift
from one of the partners at the firm.
-Was it, now?
-Mm-hm.
He wants to marry me,
soon as he divorces
the wife he's already got.
Sounds like a real peach.
[laughs] He's white, too.
Rick, his name is.
He's teaching me how to play squash.
Squash?
A game rich white people play.
I bet you'd be good at it.
Whole firm is white.
They hired me to keep up with the times.
Instead of the usual Black cleaning woman,
they wanted a clean, Black woman,
with a nice ass and a good vocabulary.
-And you are very clean.
-Mm.
When I did the interview,
I made sure to use a lot of words
like "reprehensible" and "dichotomy."
They perked right up.
But I'm gone the second I pass the bar.
What I want is what you got.
You've been the best
at what you do for so long,
you don't even know
what it's like for the rest of us.
So, what will your fellow radicals think?
You being with a rich white lawyer?
Fuck 'em if they can't take a joke.
♪ Jimmy Mack, when are you comin' back?
Ooh ♪
-♪ You better hurry back ♪
-♪ Ooh ♪
[Jolene] A trailer?
Wow, you really were the gold standard
for white-trash girls everywhere,
weren't you?
My mama came from money.
Then she married into more of it.
Then how did y'all end up way out here?
It's complicated.
I'll say.
[contemplative music playing]
[Jolene] You wanna go in?
Throw some rocks through the windows?
[children chattering indistinctly]
[Miss Lonsdale] Choices have consequences.
[pills clattering]
No more chess.
[Miss Lonsdale] You're here
because your parents made certain choices.
You will need to learn
to make different choices.
I just realized I don't ever
wanna go back in there again.
[man] "Come to me,
all who are weary and burdened,
and I will give you rest."
"Take my yoke upon you,
and learn from me,
for I am gentle and humble at heart."
Mrs. Deardorff isn't here.
-[priest continues indistinctly]
-None of them are.
Deardorff fell and broke her hip.
Right after you left.
She had to walk with a cane after.
Was never the same.
Made me almost believe in God.
[priest] I didn't know William Shaibel,
but I'm told he was not a religious man,
so much as a solitary man.
[Beth] None of them are crying.
[priest]
And I'm told that for the past 23 years…
[Jolene] They all look like
they're waiting in line at the bank.
-[priest] …Methuen Home for girls…
-You okay?
-[priest] He performed his duties…
-I feel bad.
…quietly and diligently.
I owed him ten dollars.
-[suppressed laughter, clearing throat]
-[woman] Shh!
Jolene.
[priest] The director of the Methuen Home,
Helen Deardorff, says that…
he was beloved by the staff
and students alike,
that he had an admirable work ethic.
I changed my mind.
I'll only be a minute.
[girls singing hymn in Latin]
[door closes]
-[door locking]
-[keys jangling]
You should be in chapel, young lady.
Yes, ma'am.
[singing continues in Latin]
[inhales sharply]
[emotional orchestral music playing]
[Jolene] Beth?
[sobbing]
Oh, honey.
Aw, did you bite off
more than you can chew?
Aw, it's okay.
[sobbing continues]
[Jolene] Shh. It's all right.
What we would really like
from you, Elizabeth,
would be some kind of statement.
Statement?
Christian Crusade would like you
to make your position public,
in a world where so many keep silent.
What position is that?
As we know, the spread of communism
is also the spread of atheism.
I suppose so.
Oh, it's not a matter of supposing.
It's a matter of fact,
of Marxist-Leninist fact.
The Holy Word is anathema to the Kremlin,
and the atheists who sit there.
-I have no quarrel with that.
-[woman] Good.
What we want
is a statement to that effect.
-To the press?
-[woman] Exactly.
We had something prepared. There you go.
I'm a chess player.
Of course you are.
But you're also a Christian.
I'm not sure about that.
I have no intention
of saying anything like this.
-Why not?
-Because it's fucking nonsense?
Christian Crusade
has already invested a good deal of money.
We paid
for your last trip to San Francisco.
We were all very proud of you.
And we've already spent a good deal more
on your upcoming trip to the Soviet Union.
Okay.
Fine.
I'll give it all back.
[pen clicks]
[pen writing]
I hope you know what you're doing, dear.
[Benny] Oh, it's official now.
You're crazy.
You are out of your fucking mind.
[Beth] Maybe. Probably.
But I did it,
and it's too late to undo it.
-Are the tickets paid for?
-No.
Nothing's paid for.
You understand you gotta pay Intourist
for the hotel in advance?
I know that.
I have 2,000 in my bank account.
It would be more,
but I've been keeping up the house.
It's gonna take a thousand more
to do it, at least that.
-I was wondering--
-I don't have it.
What do you mean? [blows]
-You've got money.
-I don't have it.
Did you gamble it all away?
What difference does it make?
You can call the Federation
or the State Department.
The Federation doesn't like me.
They think I haven't done as much
for chess as I could've.
Should have gone on Tonight,
Phil Donahue…
Benny, come on.
I don't wanna go to Russia by myself.
[exhales slowly]
-Benny?
-Are you kidding me?
-What?
-First, you don't come back to New York,
and you basically tell me
that you'd rather be a drunk
than be with me.
Now you pull this crap?
No, you can fucking well go alone.
Maybe I shouldn't have done it.
Maybe I didn't have
to give the money back.
Maybe? Maybe is a loser's word, Beth.
-Benny…
-Don't call me anymore.
-[phone hangs up]
-[dial tone]
[man on phone] What money the Federation
has comes from the magazine.
Four hundred dollars
is the most we could possibly spare.
[racquetball thudding]
[Muzak playing through phone]
-[woman] State Department, please hold.
-[inhales]
-[Beth] Thought you said you could play.
-[Jolene] I said I'm learning.
[Muzak playing through phone]
-Cultural Affairs, O'Malley speaking.
-[Beth] Hello?
[Beth screaming] Oh, my God, I won!
[squealing]
[O'Malley whistles]
Three thousand dollars?
[Beth] Yes, straight away.
I'll see what I can do.
-I'll get back to you in an hour.
-An hour?
[Muzak playing through phone]
[O'Malley] No dice.
I'm terribly sorry.
There's no way government funds
can be handed out to you
without more time and approval.
Don't you have some petty cash
or something?
I don't need funds
to undermine the government in Moscow.
I just need…
money for my trip.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry,
but we will be sending
one of our men with you.
Keep you safe.
Keep me safe?
-I shouldn't have bought the house.
-Or all those dresses.
Three thousand is a lot.
It's expensive to go to Moscow.
I'll give it to you.
What?
No, you just said it's a lot of money.
I have it and more. I've been saving.
You need it for law school.
I do.
And you'll give it back…
when you win.
What if I don't win?
It's still worth it.
Or you could give me the black dress.
-Or the purple one. I like them both.
-[laughing]
You're like…
my guardian angel.
For crying out loud.
Hey, Beth.
Fuck you.
Shaibel isn't the only one
who kept after you all these years.
I know how you lost to Benny Watts
in Vegas and then beat him in Ohio.
I read the papers.
Even on a group trip into town,
I spent my ice cream money
on the damn chess magazine
had your ugly face on it.
For a time,
I was all you had.
And for a time,
you was all I had.
We weren't orphans.
Not as long as we had each other.
You understand what I'm saying?
I'm not your guardian angel.
I'm not here to save you.
Hell, I can barely save me.
I'm here because you need me to be here.
That's what family does.
That's what we are.
Someday, I might need you.
It's doubtful.
[laughing] But you never know.
But if I do…
you'll come, won't you?
I might.
[laughs]
[passengers speaking indistinctly]
[liquid pouring]
You been to Russia before?
Have you?
Once or twice.
There's a few rules.
One, stay in your hotel
at all times unless you're with me.
Two, do not answer your door
or your phone, unless it's me.
How will I know it's you
if I don't answer it?
Three,
no drinking.
You just offered me a drink.
That was a test.
Let me know if any of the Russian players
tries to speak with you.
In particular, Vasily Borgov.
He sends a signal in any way,
or sends a note,
I wanna know immediately.
What exactly would a signal look like?
Could be anything.
-He could do it in one of your matches.
-How?
I don't know.
I don't play chess.
Just be on the lookout.
I'm told they may wanna talk.
Talk about what?
What part of the State Department
did you say you were from again?
-[rain pattering]
-[men speaking Russian]
[door closes]
[man 1, in Russian]
That the chess player?
She looks like Ann-Margret.
[engine turns over]
[man 2]
Let's hope the Russians like redheads.
[man 2 speaking Russian]
[anticipatory orchestral music playing]
[in English]
This is definitely better than mine.
Remember, stay in your room at all times.
Do not leave the hotel
unless you're with me.
I'll get you in the morning.
Will you knock two times fast
and one time slow?
Good one.
Welcome to Russia.
[dramatic string music playing]
[door closes]
Yes.
This will do nicely.
[in Russian]
In the words of Thomas Huxley,
"The chessboard is the world,
the pieces are
the phenomena of the Universe,
the rules of the game
are what we call the laws of Nature,
and the player on the other side
is hidden from us."
[tournament director]
Ladies and gentlemen, dear comrades,
please welcome…
Elizabeth Harmon...
-[crowd applauding]
-[dramatic string music continues]
[introduces Laev in Russian]
[crowd applauding]
[introduces Hellstrom in Russian]
[introduces Duhamel in Russian]
[crowd applauding]
[introduces Luchenko in Russian]
[introduces Flento in Russian]
-[crowd applauding]
-[dramatic string music continues]
[excitedly introduces Borgov in Russian]
[thunderous applause]
Thank you.
-[buttons clicking]
-[thrilling music playing]
[commentator 1, in English] As far as
they knew, Harmon wasn't at their level.
Someone like Laev
probably didn't spend a lot of time
preparing for their match.
Elizabeth Harmon's not at all
an important player by their standards.
The only unusual thing about her,
really, is her sex.
And even that's not unique in Russia.
There's Nona Gaprindashvili,
but she's the female world champion
and has never faced men.
My guess is
Laev was expecting an easy win,
and not at all the 27-move thrashing
Beth Harmon just gave him.
[crowd applauding]
[crowd clamoring in Russian]
[in English] Um, yeah.
[woman speaks excitedly in Russian]
[laughing,
indistinct conversations in Russian]
[thrilling music continues]
[chess clock ticking]
[indistinct conversations]
[crowd applauding]
[chair slides]
[crowd cheering, clamoring in Russian]
[Beth] Um… [chuckles]
[in English] Yeah? Okay.
Um…
[crowd cheering loudly]
[commentator 1] Beth Harmon's games
with Hellstrom and Shapkin were rigorous,
and I'm sure,
for the young American, rather exhausting.
But there was a solidity
to her opening moves
that she was able to maintain
through the middlegame,
and on to the point each of them resigned.
-[opponent grunts]
-[chair clatters]
[commentator 1] Hellstrom, it must
be said, clearly took it rather hard.
Didn't speak to Harmon afterwards.
[crowd applauding]
[commentator 1] Shapkin, however,
was very decent, very civilized,
and took his loss with grace,
even though Harmon's win over him
was decisive and merciless.
[crowd applauding]
[crowd clamoring in Russian]
[indistinct conversations]
Vodka?
Nyet.
[gentle piano music playing]
[commentator 1, in English]
Luchenko's the oldest player here,
was World Champion
before Elizabeth Harmon was born.
He defeated the great Alekhine
in an exhibition when he was a boy,
played to a draw with Botvinnik
and crushed Bronstein in Havana.
And while he's no longer
the tiger he once was,
he's a dangerous player
when allowed to attack.
Harmon will have to be very careful.
[chess clock ticking]
-[piece clatters]
-[button clicks]
[crowd clamoring and chanting "Harmon"]
I don't understand.
Did we win, or did we lose?
We adjourned.
-Meaning?
-[crowd continues chanting "Harmon"]
Meaning we didn't finish.
-[car door closes]
-So, uh…
when do we finish?
-[engine turns over]
-Tomorrow.
But right now, we really need some sleep.
[elevator dings]
[indistinct conversation in Russian]
-[knocking]
-[attendant speaks in Russian]
[man responds in Russian]
[men speaking indistinctly in Russian]
[pensive music playing]
[man] And maybe she takes with check.
[Borgov] He takes back.
[man] But then she takes his rook.
[Borgov] So what? He's got h5.
[Luchenko] Yes, that's a nasty pin.
[Borgov] And she's done.
[liquid pouring]
[door creaks shut]
[exciting music playing]
[yawns]
-[in English] Oh, good evening.
-Good evening.
[chess clock ticking]
Harmon had her 90 minutes of play,
and Luchenko had the same,
along with 35 minutes
he had left from the day before.
This put three things against her.
Luchenko having the white pieces,
his still unstopped attack…
and that extra allotment of time.
So, it was all the more impressive
when she beat him with 25 minutes
still on her clock.
Excellent.
What a brilliant recovery.
I resign with relief.
I've played your games
since I was a small girl.
I've always really admired you.
You are how old again?
-I'm twenty--
-Oh, no. Don't tell me.
It will only drive a stake
through my heart.
[laughs]
I went over your games
at this tournament.
You are a marvel, my dear.
I may have just played
the best chess player of my life.
You will get used to it.
[chuckles]
Thank you.
[crowd clamoring in Russian]
[commentator 1] So far, Harmon
is proving to be the biggest attraction
since the Youth Festival in 1957.
Some in Moscow are even calling her
an ambassador of sorts.
This evening she played
the English opening against Flento,
a sequence I've always found
to be like the Sicilian in reverse.
He's nowhere near her level,
and I don't think she expected
the game to go on for nearly four hours.
But Flento put up quite a fight
along the two main diagonals,
and played the Four Knights Variation
with a sophistication that looked,
for a while at least,
like it was far beyond Harmon's.
But by the middlegame,
she'd traded herself out of that position,
and ultimately forced Flento to resign.
The result being
she could come to her match
with Borgov tomorrow, exhausted.
[crowd applauding]
[distant traffic sounds]
[exhales slowly]
[pensive music playing]
[Paul and Alice arguing indistinctly]
[Paul] You shouldn't have brought her.
Why did you bring her here?
-Because I need your help!
-It's too late!
-[young Beth] Who was that?
-[Alice] A mistake.
A-A rounding error.
It's just a problem I gotta solve.
[young Beth] What problem?
[sighs]
What I do with you.
Mama?
Close your eyes.
-[car accelerating]
-[horn honking]
[somber music playing]
[pills clatter]
[pills splash into water]
-[toilet flushes]
-[crowd squealing and clamoring]
[indistinct whispering]
[footsteps echoing]
[crowd applauding]
-[chess clock ticking]
-[thrilling music playing]
[commentator 2, in Russian]
Elizabeth Harmon plays pawn to Queen four.
Borgov plays pawn to Queen four.
Harmon plays pawn to Queen Bishop four.
The Queen's Gambit.
Borgov declines,
moves pawn to King four.
[commentator 1, in English] Borgov's
second move is a bit of a surprise.
Normally, Borgov would do
something more solid,
but here, he's going against his own style
and playing a rare line to win.
He must win.
Harmon's response
was a complete deviation from the Albin,
which must've surprised him right back,
whilst allowing her
to get out into the open.
Now, the two of them can fight it out
from here with their own wits.
[chess clock button clicking]
[tournament director, in Russian]
Knight to G6. Go!
[exciting music playing]
[yelling] Knight to G6!
[crowd murmuring indistinctly]
[Russian commentator
speaking indistinctly]
[chess clock button clicking]
[Russian commentator
speaking indistinctly on radio]
[button clicks]
-[piece clatters]
-[button clicks]
[in English] Adjourn.
-[footsteps approaching]
-[crowd murmurs]
[pen writing]
[paper tears]
[reporters] Miss Harmon, Miss Harmon!
Paris Match, Time Magazine,
The Observer, Reuters, UPI…
You're bigger than The Monkees.
Please, I just wanna go to sleep.
Don't be like that.
It'd be good to talk to them.
Tell them that being in Russia
has made you feel lucky to be an American.
[reporters yelling] Ms. Harmon!
One question!
Hi, Dick Evans from Time.
Do you have a minute?
That depends.
Will you put me on the cover?
-Hmm. Are you going to beat him?
-I haven't made any mistakes so far.
Hm. Neither has he.
Is it true you learned how to play
at an orphanage when you were two?
-I was nine.
-Such a young age. Who taught you?
His name was Shaibel.
William Shaibel.
He was a janitor.
We played in the basement.
-The janitor taught you to play chess?
-[Beth] That's right.
William Shaibel was a fine player.
He spent a lot of time at it,
and he was quite good.
Now, will you please
promise to print that?
Absolutely. Thank you.
Yes, yes. Sure.
Thank you.
If you'll excuse me, I'm very tired.
[man, over clamor] Excuse me, Miss Harmon,
I'm with the Lexington Herald-Leader.
[warm music playing]
Our readers back home in Kentucky
would like to know if it's true.
That you're here all by yourself?
-[both laugh]
-[camera clicking]
How did you even get a visa so fast?
The newspaper helped me.
I'm an associate editor now.
And the Moscow Embassy.
-Really?
-Yeah.
I'm guessing
they thought I'd distract you.
[Beth chuckles]
If they only knew.
I know you were angry with me.
And I'm sorry.
I should've told you the whole story.
No.
I'm sorry.
I should have let you.
I will admit…
I was a little…
confused.
You really are something.
But, um, what I really wanted
was for us to be friends.
And you kind of broke my heart.
I have a way of doing that.
Do you forgive me?
Clearly.
[laughs]
[kiss]
Consider me your second. What do we need
to do to help you beat Borgov?
Well, what I need are…
the pills.
The booze. I need my mind cloudy to win.
-I can't visualize the games without them.
-Really?
-You think that's what brought you here?
-I think that's what I'm used to.
Yeah, but you've been doing fine
without all that.
-Haven't you?
-Yes, I…
threw away the pills.
And then I asked the front desk
where I could get more. [chuckles]
I just really need them right now.
Or I thought I did.
[thoughtful music playing]
[birds chirping]
Hey.
Lady, you were out!
What time is it?
It's late.
Thank you.
[phone rings]
I'll get it. Drink your coffee.
[receiver picks up]
[Townes] Yes, put him through.
[moans]
You all there?
I'll put her on.
-Hello?
-If he goes for the knight,
hit him with a king rook pawn.
Benny?
If he goes for the bishop,
do the same thing,
but open up your queen file.
How do you know?
It's in the Times.
It's 7 a.m. here,
but we've been working on it
for three hours.
We?
Hi, Beth.
Hi, Harry. [chuckles softly]
-It's really nice to hear your voice.
-[Harry] Oh, well, hang on.
[group] Hey, Beth! Hey!
-It's Mike!
-It's Matt!
We're so proud of you!
-[group overlapping dialog]
-[Beth laughs emotionally]
All right. Hey, assholes,
this is costing me a bundle.
Beth, listen to me,
you gotta open up that file, okay?
[sighs] How do I do that?
There are four ways,
depending on what he does,
and we've each been working a way through.
You have it handy?
[chuckles]
Yes, I do. Yes.
Great, okay. Well, let's start
with his knight to rook four.
We push that king knight pawn.
You got that?
-Yes.
-Great. I'll pass you back to Harry.
[Harry] There are three things
you might do now.
So, after the queen to knight three,
you play knight to king six,
then if he plays rook to rook five,
then you play pawn to king three.
Another variation: If he plays
knight takes pawn on king five,
then you take the rook.
But if he plays rook to rook seven,
check, then play rook to bishop two.
[crowd chanting] Harmon! Harmon!
Harmon! Harmon!
Harmon! Harmon! Harmon!
[Beth] Benny?
It's almost five here.
Okay.
Go beat him.
[suspenseful music playing]
[commentator 2, in Russian]
Borgov withdraws his queen to G6.
-[piece clatters]
-[button clicks]
Harmon’s knight boldly invades E6.
[button clicks]
Borgov attacks Harmon’s king-pawn.
[whispering] Shit.
-He's not doing what he's supposed to do.
-Shh!
[inhales deeply]
[exhales slowly]
[pensive music playing]
[music transitions to exciting]
[music intensifies]
[button clicks]
Draw?
Borgov never offers draws,
but he's offering Elizabeth Harmon one.
If she accepts,
she leaves the stage in a tie
with the world champion.
If they play on,
once the dust settles
and the endgame emerges,
she could find herself
in a very different position.
Borgov is death on endgames.
He's famous for it.
Harmon, on the other hand, is not.
She's more known
for coming up early and strong,
demoralizing her opponents from the start.
So, I think she should accept the draw.
The world will see it
as a solid achievement.
A draw, however, is not a win.
The one thing
we know about Elizabeth Harmon
is that she loves to win.
[suspenseful music building]
[button clicks]
-[button clicking]
-[pieces clatter softly]
[commentator 1] That was
the point of the sequence,
beginning with the bishop,
cutting down the scope of the rook
by forcing it to a less threatening rank.
-[overlapping Russian commentary]
-The question is…
what will she do now?
-[button clicks]
-[commentator speaking Russian]
-[clock ticking]
-[dramatic string music playing]
It's your game.
Take it.
-[victorious music playing]
-[crowd applauding]
[thoughtful music playing]
[man speaking indistinctly on phone]
She won!
[all yelling and laughing joyously]
Thank you.
[phone receiver clatters]
[sighs]
Good for you, cracker.
Good for you.
Mm.
[crowd applauding and cheering]
[emotional music playing]
[bodyguard] The president has invited you
to the White House.
There'll be a chess board
set up in the Oval Office,
and, of course,
a photo-op of you kicking his ass.
Texas being more of a checkers state.
And there's a dinner tonight
at the Russian Chess Club in Georgetown.
A lot of prominent dissidents belong, so…
we've prepared a list of talking points.
It's a big deal.
Beating the Soviets at their own game.
Could you stop the car, please?
I'd like to walk.
To the airport?
-You're gonna miss the fli--
-[door slams]
[engine turns over]
[uplifting music playing]
[music intensifies]
[man 1] Harmon?
Liza Harmon?
Da.
Harmon!
[introducing Beth in Russian]
[laughing]
[all chattering excitedly in Russian]
[Beth laughs]
[man 2] Liza!
[chatter continues indistinctly]
[warm music playing]
[sighs]
[in Russian] Let's play.
[thrilling orchestral music playing]