Barry: My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened
up our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
When my mother left us, she was pregnant.
Dad, I'm so sorry that
I didn't tell you sooner.
Hi, I'm Wally. I'm Francine's son.
You want Barry to get faster?
The more power he has, the more I can take.
- Don't let him take me back there.
- I won't.
You're going to help me
in return for your daughter's life.
I will help you steal The Flash's speed.
I know I'm moving pretty fast,
but stop me if you've
heard this one before.
Boy meets girl. Happens every day.
Except this boy was struck by lightning
and became the fastest man alive.
So nothing is ever that simple.
- Ho!
- Oh, my...
Oh... ah... Careful!
- Oh, boy.
- Sorry!
- It's all good.
- [laughing]
It's all good.
Those weren't for me anyway, right?
They were. I didn't realize
roses were so flammable.
Oh, my gosh.
Well, it's the... it's
the thought that counts.
And, you know, and proper
fire safety management,
- that... that counts most.
- Yes.
I have spent most of my life
feeling very unlucky.
Yeah, and now?
Feels like I've been
struck by lightning twice.
[romantic music]
- [whoosh]
- Aah!
Help!
[gagging] Help me...
Flash, everything you have will be mine.
- No!
- Aah!
[gasps]
[suspenseful music]
♪
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
WEB-DL resync by kinglouisxx
- www.addic7ed.com -
Okay, so there's my desk.
Upstairs is anti-crime and the CSI lab...
that's where Barry works.
And we have the open files...
And that is a pencil.
That: stapler.
Okay. Sorry, Wally.
Obviously, your sister got the funny genes.
Captain. I want you to meet somebody.
This is my son Wally West.
Handsome young man, Joe.
Hey, he's a West. He can't help that.
Your pops here is a hell of a detective.
Obviously not.
Well, pleasure to meet you, Wally.
Anyway, I'm glad you're here, Wally.
Yeah, I've always wanted a baby brother.
What about the White Shadow?
You're joking, but yeah,
we did call Barry that.
Well, he's been pretty busy.
He's doing a whole lot of running around.
But why don't we do
dinner? The whole family.
I, uh, I got plans.
Oh, Iris'll cook.
Dad, we just met the kid.
We don't want to kill him.
All right, we do takeout. Chinese.
Whatever. Come on.
Where are your cuffs, taillights?
Come on, let's go.
You know that kid?
Uh, no... no.
You know, it's just what they say.
I got one of those faces.
I'll see you guys at dinner.
Uh, okay.
Any chance I could chat
with you for a minute?
Yeah, what's up, Detective?
Oh, uh, I... I meant Iris.
Yeah, you're not needed.
I am needed... somewhere.
I'ma... go there.
[laughing]
What can I do for you?
Uh, I just wanted to talk with you, um,
about Barry.
I know that Barry's...
you know, practically your brother.
So I understand that your loyalty
is obviously to him, not me.
But I was just hoping that
maybe you think I'm good for him,
so you'd want to help me figure him out.
[laughs]
Well, I mean, if you did that, you...
you would be the first.
Wonderful. That gives me tons of hope.
[both laughing]
It's just, um...
he's being not distant, but...
Guarded.
Yeah. He's being guarded.
And he's waking up from these bad dreams
and not telling me about them.
And I know that we got close really quick.
It's just... it's like there's
something holding him back.
Here's the thing about Barry.
He has a bad habit of
carrying the weight of
the world on his shoulders,
burdens that aren't even his to bear.
But he doesn't have to do that with me.
Which is exactly what you should tell him.
[thoughtful music]
♪
[objects clattering]
Hey... no! Absolutely not!
You don't get to throw
somebody else's stuff
when you're pissed off.
[clattering]
Thank you.
What is this?
Wrong answers.
Maybe you're asking the wrong questions.
What does that mean?
I've been thinking about
this a lot recently.
We keep trying to come up
with ways to make Barry faster,
but I still think we can figure
out a way to make Zoom slower.
We tried that already, remember?
Those darts didn't slow him down at all.
Yeah, I know... I'm not
talking about the darts, okay?
The darts clearly didn't
work. They just pissed him off.
I'm talking about something else...
a way we can steal Zoom's speed.
[suspenseful music]
♪
How?
The Turtle.
As some of you may well know,
I've been deeply embroiled
in a secret, one-sided battle
with an invisible enemy.
No, not the Turtle again.
What? What is the...
- Or who is the Turtle?
- It's Cisco's white whale.
Half whale, half turtle.
No.
Do you see what you're doing, Caitlin?
Everybody's confused now.
Get to it.
I stumbled upon a few of these cases
when we were looking for the Reverse Flash,
robberies that were seemingly
committed at high speed...
people holding their
beloved items one second.
Those items were gone the next.
Tell me what you see.
[dramatic music]
So he can... what? Stop time?
No, no, no. Look at the time code.
It's still running.
Yeah, okay. So if he's not stopping time,
what is he doing?
He's slowing down everything around him.
And that is why we call him the Turtle.
Why have you never mentioned
this guy to me before?
Oh, I don't know, I think we've just been
a little distracted, you
know, what with Captain Cold
and the Weather Wizard and Gorilla Grodd.
Do I need to go on?
Okay, so if we can catch him,
figure out how he uses his powers...
Maybe we can show Zoom what
life is like in the slow lane.
How would you even know where to find him?
Well, the robberies in the videos
all correspond with police reports
that were dismissed as
lost or missing items
instead of thefts.
The suspect's M.O. being...
Items of immense personal value.
[dramatic music]
♪
Uh...
oh, it appears that there's
a press conference at CCPD,
because the Vandervoort diamonds
have just been recovered.
"From Hell's heart, I stab at thee."
The perpetrators who
committed this heartless crime
have been apprehended and
are now in our custody.
And we're happy to report that
the famed Vandervoort diamonds
have been returned to their rightful owner.
The real gem is the return of
my great-grandfather's ring.
Getting that returned to the family
is what's most priceless to me.
Gotcha.
[suspenseful music]
♪
The ring is gone. What happened to it?
Lock this place down.
No one leaves this room.
Sweep the precinct!
Well, the good new is
whatever the Turtle did,
it only affected you temporarily.
Yo.
What was it like being in Turtle Time?
Yeah, no, it was weird.
It was like waves of inertness...
like all the energy was
suddenly sucked out of my body,
and then it would return.
That's because that's
exactly what was happening.
He has the ability to transfer
all the surrounding
kinetic energy into himself.
Leaving everyone else in a temporary state
of potential energy.
That's right.
So why could I still move?
Your speed.
Your speed allows you to change positions
faster than anyone else.
So you can convert your
stored potential energy
back to kinetic energy.
Excuse me, where are you going?
Trying to figure out
how to use this against Zoom.
You remember Zoom?
"Cisco, please join me.
We'll use your idea and take
it to new scientific heights
and save the world."
Yes, I'd love to!
Okay.
Facial recognition
software found us a match
from the press conference footage.
The Turtle's name is Russell Glosson.
He was a small-time
thief who stopped thieving
after the particle accelerator explosion.
All right, I'm gonna head to work...
catch Joe up.
Let me know if you find anything else.
You okay?
Yeah, yeah, it's just, um...
[clears throat]
It's hard to... look at that
and not think about how I
can't help people anymore.
Well, we have lots of technology here.
Why don't we figure out
how to get your speed back?
I'm a scientist too, Caitlin.
When I first got here,
all I did was work on
how to get my speed back.
Believe me, whatever test you could run...
I've already done it.
[somber music]
♪
The Turtle.
Cisco's been looking for this guy forever.
Singh just put an APB out on him.
Um, how did everybody know
about Glosson before I did?
Mm-mm.
Cisco's got a whole list
of unidentified metas.
The boys around here are calling him
Cisco de la Mancha.
[laughs]
Are you good? You seem a little jittery.
A little anxious.
Let's be honest.
I'm really nervous about this
whole dinner tonight
with Wally.
Come on, why... why are you nervous?
You're, like, the best dad ever.
He'll see that.
It'll be a whole lot
easier, you being there.
Joe, I wouldn't miss it.
- See you tonight.
- All right.
Hey, you.
- Hey.
- You got a sec?
Yeah.
I just, um...
I just want to make sure everything's okay.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm... I'm... I, uh...
don't want to nag.
That's not, you know, who I am.
I just, uh...
I don't... I don't want you
to feel burdened by anything.
No, I don't.
Okay.
Hey, wait. Patty, uh...
The New Years was always
a hard time for me.
Um... that's when my mom died,
so it's just those memories
all come out, and they're hard to put away.
So if it feels like I
haven't been communicating...
I'm sorry, Barry. I'm sorry.
I... I didn't know.
No, no, no, no, no.
Look, um, we haven't had a
romantic night in a while.
What do you say tomorrow night
we get some dinner and drinks
and maybe a little... kissing?
That sounds like what we need.
Okay. All right, I'll see you later.
- Okay.
- [both chuckle]
Okay, I think we can call it.
Wally is not coming.
I'm sorry, Joe.
I know how much this meant to you.
He's a kid, right? I get it.
He could have at least called.
Well, there could be a number of reasons
why he didn't.
Thank you for being here.
I love you.
- Love you.
- Mmm.
See you in the morning, Bar.
Yeah.
Well, West family 2.0 is not
really off to a great start.
You've been quiet all evening.
The Turtle?
How do you know about him?
[laughing]
No, um...
no, I've just had a lot on my mind.
Patty?
We... we may have met for coffee.
Iris...
She really cares about you, Barry,
and she's just wondering
why you've been so guarded.
And what did you tell her?
I told her to talk to you.
Oh, that's not cool.
You know, she did mention that...
you've been having nightmares.
About Zoom...
killing her.
Look.
I know that things have
been moving pretty fast
between you two.
But you realize you can't keep
things from her forever, right?
One day, you're gonna
have to tell her the truth.
That I'm the Flash?
I can't do that.
Barry, I wish a year ago
you had told me the truth.
So, what, you think that
I should just tell her?
I think that if you are serious
about being with her,
you have to.
[musical buildup]
♪
All right, then that's what I'm gonna do.
I'll tell Patty I'm the Flash.
[dramatic music]
Hey.
You guys got anything?
I think we found the next target
for our 30-something,
meta-human, not-a-Ninja-Turtle.
How long did it take you
to come up with that one?
It just came out of my
mouth... did you see that?
- That was amazing.
- That was nice.
Central City Museum
is hosting a special
black tie event tonight
showcasing "The Crystal Ball."
It's a famous painting, apparently,
recently recovered from Markovia.
The painting is on loan to the museum
from the Silverberg family.
Jacob Silverberg himself said,
"The painting's safe
return means more to us
than all the money in the world.
It's like they're begging Turtle to rob it.
Okay, yes. This is a plan.
So the Turtle will make his move,
and we can be there
waiting to take him down.
How do you look in a tux?
Come on, he's 6'2", he's
square-jawed, and he's jacked.
I think he looks fine.
I'm 6'4".
Oh, crap!
Problem?
No.
An opportunity, maybe. Hold on.
- [beep]
- Hey, you.
- I'm excited to see you tonight.
- Yeah, me too.
Actually, about that...
um, so I know I said
"let's have dinner," but, uh,
you've been wanting me to share more.
So I thought that I would share that
I love art.
- Okay, interesting.
- Yeah.
No, I just, you know, I
can't get enough of art.
Anyway, there's this event
at the Central City Museum tonight.
They're showing this really famous painting
that I've always loved.
Actually, I don't know anything about art,
but what's the saying?
I know what I like,
and I like you,
so count me in.
All right, great. I'll see you at 8:00.
- ALL: 7:00!
- Or 7:00.
- I'll see you at 7:00.
- Okay, 7:00 it is.
Bye.
You know, you're a
really great superhero...
- Thanks.
- A really great superhero...
- Thank you.
- But do you think
it's a good idea when you're fighting crime
to bring a date?
I'm gonna tell Patty that I'm the Flash.
Is that a bad idea? What do we think?
I will say, she put bullets
in King Shark and Harry.
- Yeah.
- So as far as I'm concerned,
that's Team Flash material to me.
All right, yes. Thank you, Cisco.
Yeah, thank you. Cool.
I'm gonna do this...
I'm gonna tell her.
Don't tell her.
Huh?
You care for this woman.
That's nice.
Then keep her as far away
from this as possible.
And here's why.
If Zoom finds out who you care for,
who you love,
who you live for,
he'll take them from you.
[somber music]
♪
[soft dinner music]
[sighs] All right.
Keep your eyes open for the Turtle.
A sentence I never thought I would say.
♪
Cisco, are you and Harry in position?
I'm the security feed.
I've got the facial
recognition software running,
so we'll be able to spot
Turtle before he makes his move.
Turtle.
Why do you insist on giving them
ridiculous nicknames?
Me?
Who's the genius that came up with "Zoom"?
Yeah, well...
I'll tell you, about two years ago...
this is on Earth-2, now.
The CCPD there...
they got a 911 call
about a hostage situation,
but when the SWAT team got there,
there were no hostages.
It was a trap.
Zoom set a trap
in order to show the police
that they could not stop him.
And he killed 14 officers.
Men and women. Slaughtered them.
Left one alive to tell what happened.
That officer described
blue lightning
"zooming" all about
as his comrades, brothers
and sisters in arms,
were murdered.
That officer...
considered himself to be a lucky one,
spared in order to tell the tale.
Until Zoom went to his house
that night and killed him too.
Anyway, that's how he
got the nickname "Zoom".
[somber music]
♪
If you ever need me to Vibe...
so you can know if she's still alive...
She's alive.
Right.
[soft dinner music continues]
♪
- No!
[voices echoing]
You have a really weird look on your face.
- Do I look weird?
- No, no.
You... look... like a dream.
You look very handsome.
I can't wait to see this painting.
What painting?
The painting. Uh, yeah.
Me too, um, yeah.
How about we talk first?
I thought you'd never ask.
♪
I can't figure you out, Barry Allen.
That is because I work hard
to hide who I really am.
You don't have to hide with me.
I just have to
really trust someone
if they're gonna know the truth.
Do you?
I trust you, Patty.
I trust you, too.
Patty, um...
After I was struck by lightning,
when I woke up...
[suspenseful music]
We've got eyes on Turtle.
♪
Barry, you were saying?
I have to go. I'm sorry.
What? What?
But Barry...
CCPD! Freeze!
♪
- [crowd commotion]
- What?
[crowd murmuring, exclaiming]
Are you as fast as the Flash?
Oh, no. He is much slower.
This is a trap?
I'm slow...
not stupid.
[gunshots]
[exciting music]
♪
[crystals shattering]
- Oh, my God!
- [breathing hard]
[glass tinkling]
I got it. Come on.
[dramatic music]
♪
Your pupils are normal.
Your heart rate's a little low.
But other than that,
no concussive symptoms.
I really do feel fine. What about Turtle?
- No sign of him.
- Or the painting.
He, uh, must have gotten
away with it in the chaos.
Yeah, things went a little sideways
after your girlfriend decided
to go all "Lethal Weapon"
1 through 4 on Turtle.
Oh, my God.
Patty's gonna think I ditched her.
I... no, I got to go.
Where are you...
finding Turtle is what's
important right now.
Yeah, uh, this is important to me too.
But we need to see if
your speed still works.
I think... I think it still works.
We still have to find out
how Turtle drained him of it.
Can I talk to you...
for a second?
You never got your champagne.
I couldn't find any flutes.
Hope that's okay.
Of course.
Here you go.
[glasses clinking]
Mmm.
[sighs]
Let me go see if I can make myself useful.
Mmm.
[knocking on door]
I was right.
I thought that you would
look mad, and you do.
What happened?
Um...
I don't really have a good excuse.
Nothing?
Nothing? I mean, come on, Barry.
Anything is better than nothing.
I mean, come on.
Holy crap, I've been a
really, really cool girlfriend.
Most girls don't have the self-esteem
to handle the... plans?
Oh, no plans. That's cool.
Or the... or the...
waking up in the middle of
the night screaming again.
Fine, whatever.
And then... and then the
really, really fancy plans...
which were awesome.
And then you ditched me
right before I almost died.
I mean, when you put it that way, it...
I'm actually really upset.
Yeah, I know.
Look, we've been having fun.
And fun has been so great.
But... I'm moving past fun
to the close part.
That's what I want, okay?
That's where I'm going.
You need to figure out
what it is that you want.
And do it fast.
[solemn music]
♪
Fast is my specialty.
[sighs]
[rock music]
[overlapping shouting]
[engine revving]
♪
[revving]
[tires squealing]
[rock music]
♪
[tires screeching]
[loud revving]
[indistinct shouting]
♪
Yo, pay up.
[laughs]
What?
You got someone tailing me now?
Why didn't you show up
for dinner last night?
Couldn't make it.
You tell someone you're gonna be somewhere,
you show up.
Guess I didn't have my
dad to teach me that, huh?
Is this why you came to Central City?
Not to get to know me or your sister,
but this nonsense?
No one in Keystone will race me anymore.
But I don't actually have
to explain myself to you.
Actually, you do.
This is illegal. I'm a cop, remember?
Oh, yeah. Yes.
The detective who didn't know he had a son
and who doesn't know anything about me.
I am trying to get to know you, Wally.
These races... that car...
that I won?
That's the only way that I can
pay for my mom's hospital bills,
get her the help that she needs.
You don't have to do this.
I have money saved. I
can dip into my pension.
I don't need your money.
I can take care of myself and my mom, okay?
I'm the man of our house.
That position has been filled.
Go home to your family, Joe.
[jazz music]
♪
[light knocking]
Barry?
Hey... [gasps]
[suspenseful music]
- [thud]
- Uhh!
[clattering]
♪
What?
[gasping]
What do you want from me?
The thing most precious to the Flash...
you.
[knocking on door]
Patty?
[tense music]
♪
[shell clattering]
[whispering] No, no, no, no, no.
No.
Come on.
No... Joe!
Joe, um, I think the Turtle has Patty.
I... Look, just meet me at
S.T.A.R. Labs, all right?
[clicking]
[clicking continues]
[gasping]
What do you want from me?
I want you to stop moving...
Forever.
What do you get out of killing me?
Oh, I'm not gonna kill you.
That's much too... fast and messy.
I like to take things nice and slow.
You don't have to hurt me
to try to prove a point.
This isn't about hurting you.
This is about hurting
someone who values you.
Who, Barry?
No.
The Flash.
What does he have to do with this?
[dramatic musical buildup]
I saw the way he saved you.
Yes, that's what he does.
He's a hero.
He saves people who need saving.
That's a waste of time...
saving people.
♪
They take everything for granted.
So you take the things
that matter most to them.
My wife Rosalyn took me for granted.
She wanted to leave me...
the thing I valued most.
So that's what this is about?
You're hurt because your wife left you?
I couldn't let that happen.
So I made her mine.
Forever.
♪
[exhales]
[musical buildup]
♪
I do hope I spelled your name right.
Bar... we'll find her.
I'm not getting any leads on this guy.
It's like he's totally fallen off the grid.
You know, it... any of
the stuff he's stolen,
- I can't find it.
- He keeps them.
He keeps them the way a serial
killer collects trophies.
He's stolen a lot of stuff.
Which means he needs a lot
of space to store it, right?
That's where we start.
See if he rented any storage spaces.
No, no...
I'm not getting anything.
Wait a minute.
His ex-wife used to be an
archivist for antiquities
at the Naydel Library before it shut down,
and it shut down three months
after the accelerator exploded.
That place is big enough
to hold Turtle's stuff.
Okay, all right.
Wait, Barry... we haven't even figured out
how to neutralize the Turtle's power.
Well, I'm gonna have to power through it.
[exciting music]
♪
All right, I'm outside the library.
Barry, the only way to save Patty
is if you grab her in between
each of the Turtle's pulses.
You'll only have 2/10ths of a second
to make your moves.
I got it.
[breathing hard]
[moaning] No!
[gasping]
[muted sound]
[dramatic music]
♪
- [thud]
- [echoing] Uhh!
- [whack]
- Uhh...
- [thud]
- Ugh!
- [whomp]
- Ugghh!
[whoosh]
I guess he doesn't care about you
as much as I thought.
No...
No, no... please!
♪
[intense musical buildup]
- [thud]
- Ooh!
[gasping]
[whispering] No, it's all right.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, whoever you are.
[sobbing]
[whispering] It's okay.
It's okay.
Hey, Turtle.
So you want to know my
new definition of irony?
Now you... are our most prized possession.
[chuckles]
Arrrhhhh!
- Patty okay?
- She is, yeah.
Jay?
Yeah?
I know.
Why didn't you tell me that you're sick?
The champagne.
You took my DNA off the glass.
You know I lost my husband...
how hard that was for me to move on.
How could you let me get close to you
knowing that soon I'd lose you too?
I just...
I didn't expect... this.
I didn't expect you.
Then help me find a cure.
There is no cure.
The only way to save me
is to get my speed back.
And the only way to do
that is to stop Zoom.
Then let's stop him.
Yeah.
[knock on door]
Hey.
I think I left my sweater
here the other night.
It's green.
Oh, yeah.
I thought that didn't look like Barry's.
Heading back to Keystone tonight.
That's a fast trip.
Yeah, well, it's getting a little hot
in Central City for me.
Don't worry.
I'll try not to run too
many lights on the way there.
You know, if you're waiting for an apology,
it's not coming.
No.
No, I'm... I'm the one that should be
apologizing to you.
I felt bad
not being there while you
were growing up, and...
I was pushing this whole father-son thing.
I'm sorry.
Let's just slow down a bit.
I won't try to be your instant dad,
and you won't have to pretend that
you want to be my son.
Deal?
All that food for you?
Doesn't have to be.
You like chow mein?
No.
But I like kung pao chicken.
[gentle music]
♪
[elevator dings]
Initial and sign.
There you go. Thank you, guys.
Patty.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Um, can we talk... like, really talk?
Yeah, uh, no.
Now's not really an awesome time.
I have a mound of paperwork
on my desk I need to finish,
so I'm sorry, I can't.
No, no, okay. Real... really quick.
Um, so you were right.
You were right about everything.
Um, I've been closed off and weird,
and, um, all the things
that you said I was.
But mostly, I have not been honest.
Barry, um...
I'm leaving Central City.
What?
Um, before Mardon, and before my dad...
before everything...
I always wanted to be a CSI.
And four years ago, I was accepted
into the Forensic Science program
at Midway City University.
That's a really great school.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know, I just, uh...
I didn't go.
You know, I deferred to become a cop and...
catch my dad's killer.
And I've done that.
So, um...
so it's time to move on.
From the job?
From everything.
Patty. Patty...
Pat...
[solemn music]
♪
Journal log entry number 113.
[ominous music]
Jess...
I'm coming for you soon.
I promise.
I was thinking earlier today about the time
that you were four.
I took you to the
planetarium, just you and me.
I remember because it was the first time
I took you out all by myself.
The planetarium was crowded,
and you held my hand for dear life,
or maybe it was the other way around.
But it was in the Mars
exhibit that I lost you.
Panic.
I had that place locked down in one minute.
I had every security guard looking for you.
And I could feel the fear
rise in the back of my throat
and something else rising also,
some... dark instinct inside me
about what I would do
to the person who had taken you...
the things I would do...
[groaning]
Unspeakable things.
And it was in that moment that I realized,
for certain,
that I would do anything to get you back.
[suspenseful music]
♪
[breathing hard]
- Gideon.
- Yes, Professor Thawne?
Where the hell am I?
[dramatic music]
Synced and corrected by VitoSilans
WEB-DL resync by kinglouisxx
- www.addic7ed.com -