My name is Barry Allen
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly I use my speed
to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother
and get justice for my father.
I am... The flash.
Previously on The Flash...
I'm sorry
I didn't believe you.
But you really did see something
that night your mom died
and your dad is innocent.
The explosion that put you
in a coma also killed my fiance.
Can you imagine if
you could control his power?
If you could harness it,
you could change
what it means to be human.
He's called the flash.
Or, at least,
he will be one day.
He must be kept safe.
It doesn't matter
if you're the slowest kid
in gym class
or the fastest man alive.
Every one of us is running.
Being alive means running--
running from something,
running to something
or someone.
And no matter how fast you are,
there's some things
you can't outrun.
Some things always manage
to catch up to you.
Regular movie scale,
that was a seven or an eight.
Zombie movie scale,
it was, like, a four, tops.
There's a zombie movie scale?
Did you know that zombies
exist in nature?
There's a species of fungi
that infects ants,
causing the ants
to attack plants
that can release spores
which in turn infect new hosts.
I'm going full nerd again,
aren't I?
- Yep.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
It's okay though.
You are still the cutest nerd
that I know.
Anyways,
I'm a lot more interested
in the amazing as of late.
You mean 'cause of
this "Streak" thing?
He's out there.
People are talking about him.
How do you even know
he's a he?
Maybe it's a she.
It's a man, okay?
You know I am really intuitive
about this kind of stuff.
Someone even posted a picture
after being yanked
from a car accident.
It's a red blur
leaving the scene.
Here, what do you see?
I see
your boyfriend's calling.
Oh,
I should probably get this.
I'm crashing at his place
tonight,
and he's supposed to leave
a key for me somewhere.
Hey, babe.
What's up?
Not much,
just hanging out with Barry.
You off yet?
Hello.
Code 237 on Waid Boulevard.
Public indecency?
Wait, I think I meant a 239.
Dog leash violation?
Bad man with a gun
in a getaway car.
Go.
You don't have a mat.
Do you have a planter?
Full Privacy Pro VPN: 1.85 USD/mo
www.byespies.com
He's got a gun.
Look out!
Where'd he go?
What the--
Key's in the mailbox.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
Eddie says hi.
Nice of him.
You wanna grab a bite?
I'm feeling a little famished.
After the Mongolian barbecue
we had before the movie
and the extra large popcorn
you had at the movie?
How are you not fat?
I've been jogging.
Oh, okay.
Why so public a meeting,
Uncle?
We're dining out to show
our enemies we're not afraid.
Relax, nephew.
We've replaced the windows
with bulletproof glass.
Close it up.
Come.
Have a drink.
Our own drivers
are ripping us off.
Someone is paying them
to steal from us.
None of you will sleep
until we find out who.
And then those thieves...
Those thieves...
will draw
their last breath.
Uncle!
?Flash 1x03?
Thing You Can't Outrun
Original Air Date on October 21, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
- Where'd you cut him off?
- So we cut him off at Eighth.
I mean, the perp was in
the backseat of the cruiser
before he even knew
what happened.
Congratulations, Paulson,
on that arrest last night.
Hell of a job.
You come by later, Joe.
I'll give you a driving lesson,
okay?
Wasn't even him last night.
It was me.
I figured.
I just didn't realize
you were helping people
for the glory.
It's not like I want a museum
built in my name.
Keeping what I can do a secret
from Iris and everyone,
it's harder than I thought.
I know,
but it is safer that way.
Besides, me and you
got work to do.
The evidence
from my mom's case.
I had it brought up
from storage.
I've been through this box
1,000 times.
Before, your story about what
really happened that night--
the lightning storm,
the man in the middle of it--
I thought that was a kid
trying to protect his father
from prison.
But now that I know it's true,
we're gonna go through
every scrap of evidence
until we find something
that helps us.
It took the jury 52 minutes
to come back
with a verdict of guilty.
They moved too fast,
which is why we got to
take our time.
Barry, Joe,
we got multiple homicides.
Do you know
the Darbinyan crime family?
Barry?
Ah.
Anything?
Signs of histotoxic hypoxia.
The cells in their bodies
were unable to utilize oxygen.
It's consistent with exposure
to poison gas.
What kind of poison?
I'll need to take
a lung sample,
see if I can narrow it down.
The only other exit was bolted
from the inside.
They were trapped.
I was thinking someone
pumped gas in from the outside,
but witnesses say
the street was empty.
So it was from the inside.
That means there should be
a canister
or a container left behind.
The gas just didn't
come in by itself.
Unless it had
a mind of its own.
Eddie, would you mind
canvassing again?
Somebody had to have seen
something suspicious.
Okay, explain.
The boss collapsed
by the table.
This guy made it 10 feet away.
That guy had a chance
to move off
and fire three shots
into the window
trying to break the glass.
But they all started
in the same spot,
which means they should have
all been affected by the gas
at the same time, but instead,
it's as if...
They were attacked one by one.
My gut feeling,
if we're gonna solve this one,
you and me are gonna need...
Backup.
Yeah.
Fascinating, a meta-human
that can manipulate poison gas.
Is it just poisonous gas,
or can he control
all aerated substances?
And how is he able
to formulate the connection?
Is it physiological
or psychological?
This individual can create
a mental nexus
using gaseous substances.
You mean connect with gases
on a molecular level?
- Yes.
- That is ridiculously cool.
They get really excited
about this stuff.
The only thing
I'm excited about
is putting criminals
behind bars.
Except Iron Heights
isn't exactly equipped
to handle meta-humans.
Then I guess it's fortunate
the ones
you've encountered so far
are no longer with us.
Well, unless we're planning
on executing
every super criminal we stop,
you geniuses are gonna have to
come up
with someplace else
to hold them.
A meta-human prison.
Sweet.
Until we figure a way
to remove their powers.
There is one place here
that might hold them.
You can't be serious.
I mean, we haven't been
down there since--
it's cordoned off.
Cisco is right.
It could be modified to act
as a makeshift prison.
What could?
The particle accelerator.
Tonight, the future begins.
The work my team and I
will do here
will change our understanding
of physics,
will bring about
advancements in power,
advancements in medicine.
And trust me,
that future
will be here faster
than you think.
Dr. Wells, we just got
the latest weather report.
A big thunderstorm
is rolling in.
We're not launching
a space shuttle.
We'll be fine.
Tahiti?
I know it's a long flight,
Ronnie,
but we can binge watch
Orange is the New Black.
Oh, okay.
But what about Italy?
Pizza and wine and more pizza.
Yes, but Italy
doesn't have Mai Tais,
and a honeymoon
isn't a honeymoon
without Mai Tais.
Dr. Wells,
the accelerator is primed
and ready
for particle injection.
Well, I feel I should
say something profound
like "one small step for man,"
but all I can think of
to say is,
I feel like I've waited
for this day for centuries.
That's it?
You'd think there'd be, like,
a loud bang.
If there was a loud bang,
we'd all be in big trouble.
Take it from the guy
who helped build it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we did it.
Mai Tais it is.
Was that...
A loud bang.
Caitlin.
Did you hear me?
We're going down
to the accelerator ring.
Actually, Dr. Wells,
I could use Caitlin's help
identifying the poison gas.
Okay.
If that's okay with you?
Let's go.
Welcome to the CCPD.
So this is your day job.
Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna rip out your hearts
and eat 'em for lunch.
Delightful.
Lab rat, I need prints
off this gun pronto.
Allen!
Where the hell is the fiber
analysis on the Orloff case?
Upstairs.
It's all finished.
I can just run up
and bring it down.
With you, that could be
three days from now.
I'll go with you.
Who are you?
Dr. Caitlin Snow,
Barry's personal physician.
The fiber analysis
for the Orloff case,
like you asked for,
sir.
Clean up your lab.
It's a mess.
The lightning
was in the house.
I told my son to run,
he disappeared,
and that's when
I saw the blood.
Your prints were
on the murder weapon.
I needed
to stabilize the knife.
I'm a doctor.
I was trying to save her.
I didn't kill my wife.
Joe, tell them.
You know me.
Our kids are friends.
You tell them, Joe.
Do I even want to know
what you were looking at?
It's just work.
Some old cases
weren't filed properly.
Detective.
What are you doing here?
Joe, I thought
you were at the morgue.
I decided
to bring some work home.
Why are you here?
Yes, well,
I've been looking for you.
I thought maybe we could
go back to the crime scene,
re-canvass,
see if we missed anything.
Always work the case, right?
That's what you taught me.
Wow, you've been listening.
Okay, let's hit it.
You mind
if I use your bathroom?
It's the first door
on the right.
I'll be in the car.
Bye, baby.
Bye, Dad.
Okay, this has got to stop.
I came here
to surprise my girlfriend,
and now I'm going
to a crime scene with her dad--
not exactly the afternoon
I was planning on.
I know, I know,
it's just--
it's not the right time
to tell him.
When is, Iris?
I know my dad.
He'll kill us.
Right now,
you're killing us.
The copper in the tube
is arranged to form cavities,
and we can use those cavities
as containment cells.
Of course, we'll have to
design them to counteract
meta-human abilities, but--
might just work.
First, we have to decouple
the main injection system
on the gantry level.
I'll be right back.
Why don't I do that?
I need the exercise.
There's an anomaly
in the core chamber.
The ring's
structural integrity is holding.
It's started a chain reaction.
The system is collapsing.
We need to shut it down.
We can't ramp down
the accelerator from here.
We need to do it manually.
Go.
- I'll come with.
- Ronnie, no.
I'm the lead engineer.
I know how to operate
the shutdown valve.
- It's not safe.
- Cait, I have to go.
Okay, you stay here.
We've only got a few minutes
before this thing blows,
and if I'm not back in time,
you need to initiate lockdown.
No way.
I am not closing this door.
I won't be able
to open it again.
Cisco, if you don't seal off
the blast,
everyone in this building
will die,
including Caitlin.
Okay, now promise me.
Set your watch.
Two minutes.
You're coming back.
Cisco.
Cisco, we're ready to go.
Must be hard,
coming back down here.
A lot happened that night.
If you feel the need to talk--
I was just thinking,
we need to nail
those voltage calculations.
One fault,
and the helium blowback
could damage the mountings.
Smart.
Can I ask you something
that you don't have to answer?
My least favorite
kind of question.
Shoot.
Ronnie.
What was he like?
You just never talk about him
that much.
We met when we were working
on the particle accelerator.
He was the structural engineer.
He liked to joke
that he was basically
a very high-priced plumber.
We were very different.
You might have noticed
I can be a bit...
guarded.
Ronnie knew how
to make me laugh.
He used to say we were
like fire and ice.
He wasn't supposed to be there
that night.
He was just there for me.
If he hadn't--
This says that there was
no residue of gas in the tissue,
poisonous or otherwise.
It must have evaporated.
We'll need to get
a fresh sample.
Wait, this can't be right.
This says that there are
two distinct strands of DNA
inside the tissue.
How did someone else's DNA
get inside the victim's lungs?
Well, my docket was clear,
so I stopped by the mall
to pick up
your homecoming dress.
I am a great mom.
I'll see you for dinner,
sweetie.
There's no DNA match
in the database.
I don't understand.
Why would a chemical attack
leave behind another person's
DNA inside the victim?
What if the meta-human
we're looking for
doesn't control gas?
What if he becomes it?
Judge Howard.
It's nice to see you again.
You died.
You say that like
it was an accident.
You remember the last thing
you said to me
in the courtroom?
May god have mercy
on your soul.
All available units,
we have a report
of a toxic gas attack
in the Central City
shopping mall.
Barry, don't.
We don't know enough
about what we're facing yet.
It's not safe.
Caitlin, I have to go.
I patched into
the mall's security system.
According to witnesses,
the gas attack
was in the main elevator
in the north wing.
Which one is the north wing?
The one
with the Big Belly Burger.
I eat.
Back up.
Please, keep back.
Why did you kill that woman?
She deserved to die.
Now go run away.
I still have one more name
on my list.
don't make me add you to it.
Barry.
Barry, can you hear me?
His vitals are weak,
but he's alive, Dr. Wells.
I'm sure he's fine.
I can't breathe.
He needs oxygen.
Get the crash cart!
Barry!
Barry.
Cut me open.
The poison's still in me.
He brought us a sample.
Caitlin, we need to do
a pulmonary biopsy,
extract an active portion
of that gas.
I can't give you
any anesthetic.
Your metabolism will burn
right through it.
I heal quick, remember?
Do it.
Cisco, give me the syringe.
This is gonna hurt a lot.
It's a small needle.
You probably won't even feel it.
You're definitely
going to feel it.
The streak lives.
You'd be dead
if your lung cells
didn't regenerate
so quickly.
My chest feels like
that one time
I had a cigarette.
Yeah, teen me lived for danger.
This isn't funny.
You could've--
I didn't.
Now that we have a sample,
we'll get to work analyzing it,
figure out the makeup
of the poison,
maybe get a clue as to
his human identity.
Or at least a way to stop him
from turning into a mist.
The Mist.
Okay, that's his name.
End of discussion.
I have to get
to the station.
You should be resting.
I have to talk to Joe.
Joe.
I had him.
The meta-human.
We were wrong.
He's not controlling
airborne toxins.
He can literally transform
himself into poison gas.
That's new.
The victim was a judge.
We're going through
some of her old cases
to see if there's a connection.
It's too late.
I should have been faster.
Focus on the job.
Don't think about that
right now.
You don't want to know
what I'm thinking about.
My dad has spent 14 years
in a 6x8-foot cell
for a crime he didn't commit.
I couldn't save my mom,
but I can save him.
Didn't I promise you
that we would get your father
out of prison together?
I don't need your help, Joe.
I could be in and out of there
with him
before anyone even sees me.
Okay.
You break him out of there.
Then what?
He's on the run
for the rest of his life.
And something tell me
he's not as fast as you are.
You don't know
what it's like there.
You think I don't understand
what you're feeling?
I have been a cop
for almost as long
as you've been alive.
So you should know,
putting on that suit
does not make everybody safe.
For every person you save,
there's gonna be somebody
you can't.
And the hardest thing
you're gonna have to face
is not some monster out there
with powers.
It's gonna be that feeling
of uselessness
when you can't do anything.
Or the guilt that weighs on you
when you make a mistake.
Some things, Barry,
you can't fight.
Some things
you just have to live with.
Yes, I'm writing this down.
Red streak at the mall
during the gas attack.
Thank you for calling.
Never fails.
Tip lines bring out
the potheads and the crazies.
Did they get a good look
at the streak's face?
Not you too.
What are you doing here anyway?
We need to talk.
I thought about what you said,
and--
I know what you're gonna say.
I understand.
I'm your dad's partner.
No, no, no,
you don't understand.
I have never really had
a serious boyfriend.
Between dad and Barry and work,
my life has been full.
And I really like you,
but I thought that if I told
my dad about us,
then it would make this real,
and suddenly, it's something
that I could lose
or screw up.
I wanted it to be real.
Eddie.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you,
leaving like that.
It's okay.
I get it.
You had to go.
It's just--
that's the last thing that
Ronnie said to me that night.
My mother died
14 years ago.
I used to think that
the further away I got from it,
the less it would hurt.
But some days, the pain,
it's worse than the day
that it happened.
Some things you can't fight.
For so long,
I've been terrified
of going into that hole.
What if I went with you?
Where's Ronnie?
Cisco, where is he?
- He's still inside.
- What? Open the door.
I can't.
We're in lockdown mode.
Cisco, we have to get him
out of there or he'll die.
- Cisco, can you hear me?
- Ronnie, it's me.
Caitlin.
Is Cisco there?
Yeah, Ronnie, I'm here.
I'm listening.
I adjusted the magnets
to redirect the beam
to try and vent the system
so the blast goes up
and not out.
I'll need to reset
the particle parameters
to compensate.
Cisco's doing it.
There has to be another way
out of there.
You have to find it.
Cait, the chain reaction,
I can't reverse it.
The doors need to stay shut
to protect you.
You still there?
I'm here.
Caitlin, whatever happens--
Ronnie.
Ronnie!
He saved so many lives
that day,
and no one will ever know
what he did.
I do.
He was a hero.
I didn't want him
to be a hero.
I wanted him to be my husband.
Barry, Caitlin,
you down there?
You got to come look at this.
Hey, check this out.
It's a 3-D molecular model
of the gas
we retrieved from your lungs.
We have identified the toxin.
Hydrogen cyanide?
What's interesting
is what's mixed in
with the cyanide--
a sedative.
Of course.
The night of the explosion,
find out if anyone was executed.
Why?
That sedative is given
to criminals on death row
before they go
to the gas chamber
and breathe in hydrogen cyanide.
That's right.
There was someone executed.
Kyle Nimbus.
That's him.
He was a hit man
for the Darbinyan crime family.
They turned on him
and testified.
Judge Theresa Howard
was the judge at his trial.
She sentenced him to death.
He must have been affected
by the explosion
while he was being gassed.
Records indicate
the execution was completed.
That's why
there wasn't a match.
The DNA database only has
records of the living.
Right.
He said there was
one more person on his list.
Check the arrest record.
Who caught him?
That could be his next attack.
Barry, the lead detective...
Here to see Henry Allen.
Sign here.
Personal effects here.
- Eddie.
- Barry, what's up?
Hey, do you know
where Joe went?
He's not picking up his cell.
Uh, not sure.
Eddie, it's really important
I speak to him.
I need to know
where he went.
He went to Iron Heights
to see your dad.
Barry.
I reverse-engineered
an antidote to the toxin.
I hope you won't need it.
What are you doing here?
Is Barry all right?
He's fine.
Then to what
do I owe this visit?
I know I should have
come to see you sooner.
You just weren't up
for a little chitchat
with a man who murdered his wife
in front of his own son?
Except now I know
you didn't kill your wife.
Barry, I pulled up the specs
on Iron Heights prison.
It's maximum security,
but I think I can talk you
through breaking in there.
Don't bother.
I've been figuring out
how to break into that place
since I was 11.
Some new evidence
has come to light.
I can't go into detail.
It's just--
look, the important thing is,
I'm reopening the case.
I'm gonna find out
who really killed Nora,
and I promise you, Henry,
I'm going to get you
out of here.
I am so sorry.
It doesn't matter
that you didn't believe in me...
Because you always believed
in my son.
Nimbus.
You're supposed to be dead.
Same to you.
Joe?
Joe!
Help!
Guards!
Somebody help!
Go get him.
So you've come to finish
what the gas chamber couldn't?
You're going somewhere you
can't hurt anyone ever again.
Wrong.
He used the antidote on Joe.
You need to stay away from him,
Barry.
Do not breathe him in.
I'm not sure
how that helps me, guys.
You can't fight him, Barry.
Just keep him coming at you.
That should sap his strength.
Gas is the least stable form
of matter.
This meta-human will not be able
to stay in his mist form
for long.
His particles will need
to reform.
Barry.
We win.
It's been a while
since I watched you sleep.
Rescuing you is exhausting.
I really miss the ability
to be able to ground you.
Sorry I went and grew up.
I could have got my dad
out of Iron Heights tonight.
I know.
But you were right.
That's not the way.
- Daddy.
- Oh.
Baby, I'm fine.
don't worry.
I'll let you guys talk.
Partner.
You two arrive at the same time?
Dad, we have something
that we need to tell you.
Dad, the thing is--
You two are dating.
I know.
You do?
I'm a detective, remember?
And both of you
are lousy liars.
So you're not mad?
Oh, I'm mad.
And if the doctor
hadn't confiscated my gun,
we'd be having an entirely
different conversation.
Well, I should let
you two talk,
and I'll just be outside
looking into
the Witness Protection program.
I'm sorry.
Iris,
this is going to be complicated.
You know
I don't like complicated.
Do you like him?
Yeah, I do.
Then I will do my damnedest
not to shoot him.
That is all I ask.
Will it hold?
The barrier is powered by
an 8.3 Tesla superconducting
electromagnet,
which is about 100,000 times
the strength
of earth's magnetic field.
In other words, yes.
Hmm.
He's mad.
Well, good night.
So we're just supposed
to get used to
working above a makeshift prison
housing evil people
with superpowers.
You'd be surprised what
you can get used to, Caitlin.
Caitlin.
Could I talk to you
for a second?
Sure.
What's up?
It's about the night
that Ronnie died.
I--
Look, Cisco, I'm okay.
I thought coming down here
would undo me,
but thinking about
what Ronnie did to protect us...
It just made me love him more.
Come on.
I need ice cream or a drink.
Let's see which one
we hit first.
Joe's gonna be okay.
You know, lately I've been
thinking about mom.
A lot.
I miss her.
Did I ever tell you about
the time you learned to walk?
A couple times.
Everyone was walking
before you.
All the little babies
running around the neighborhood,
not you.
But your mom was never worried.
She just said,
"he'll walk
when he has someplace to go."
And sure enough, the first time
you took a few steps,
you moved so quick,
you didn't just walk,
you started...
To run.
And you ran to your mom,
Barry.
Right into her arms.
You had someplace to go.
I thought being
the fastest man alive
would make my life easier--
that I could outrun anything.
Turns out,
no one can outrun pain.
Somebody help!
Please, somebody!
Life is tragic.
but it's also precious...
and sweet...
and extraordinary.
and the only way I know
to honor my mom's life
is to keep running.
Dr. Wells.
Dr. Wells, Ronnie did it.
He vented the system.
S.T.A.R. Labs should hold.
Good man.
I'm on my way down.
See you soon, Barry.
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org