My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, i'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came back from the future to help,
she changed the present.
And now our world is more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one fast enough to save it.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
To be able to control the weather like that indoors.
He'd have to be a weather wizard.
This is Sherloque.
He's the greatest detective in all the multiverse.
I'm here to catch your killer.
The only part of the satellite
that would have dark matter levels that high--
Is the core, which is where Cicada's dagger came from.
We got a list from FEMA of everyone
who reported injuries the night of the Enlightenment.
Two of them are twins whose father is deceased,
third is a ten-year-old girl
by the name of Grace Gibbons.
So if my dad's right and Cicada's a father, then...
We may have just found his daughter.
Excuse me,
could you tell me where Grace Gibbons' room is?
One sec, let me check.
Actually, yeah, she's that first room right on the right.
Great.
Just where do you think you're going?
Into my patient's room is what I looks like.
I'm sorry. I am Barry Allen.
I'm with the CCPD.
I was hoping to speak with you, actually.
I'm looking for Grace Gibbons' parents.
Specifically her father.
I'm sorry, but the girl's parents are deceased.
Are you sure about that?
I can show you her charts.
See for yourself.
She came in with a wave of new admissions.
No legal guardian listed, no next of kin.
The sad truth is,
our staff is the only family this little girl has left.
Okay.
Thank you for your help.
Orlin Dwyer, are you in there?
It's CCPD. Open up.
Orlin Dwyer?
Hey, listen, man,
I don't care what that guy says,
he was drunk and I was defending--
This is about your sister, Mr. Dwyer.
There's been an accident, a meta attack.
Careful.
I know, I know.
This is a critical time.
Okay.
Steady hands.
Yeah.
Call time of death.
It's okay. It's a pie.
It's not supposed to be a piece of cake.
Hey, thanks for helping.
With Cicada's trail running cold,
at least we have the extra day to prepare
for our first Thanksgiving at the loft.
What about Joe and Cecile?
They're celebrating with Cecile's family this year.
So, yeah, this year it's just gonna be the five of us.
I'm down.
Six, actually.
Killer Frost just RSVP'd.
What--you guys can just talk to each other now,
even without the mental activity dampener?
Yeah, today's actually the first time.
Oh, gosh.
- Hi, guys. - Yo.
Sorry we're late.
It seems like everyone and their grandma is getting
pre-holiday manis and pedis.
Ooh, let's take photos and post them
on that old-fashioned Insta thingy that you guys use.
Those two seemed to have really patched things up.
Yeah, Nora's getting closer to Iris than she is with me,
and the timing couldn't have been better.
What do you mean?
I mean, Nora was so young
when I disappeared in her future,
so this would be her first memory of Thanksgiving
with both her parents.
Feel like it's my job to make it
the most perfect Thanksgiving ever.
And #HandModels.
Wow, I feel famous already.
Oh, man.
Mom, um...
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what, Nora?
For not giving you a chance to show me how great you are.
This year I'm just really thankful to get to know you.
The real you.
I'm thankful too.
You know, the West-Allens have never missed a Thanksgiving.
No gorilla army, no evil speedster,
no giant wormhole in the sky could break that streak.
Yeah, the singularity.
So the Flash Museum has a 3-D model of Dad
just running straight into it to save the city.
God, it must have been so epic to be there.
Actually, it was...
terrifying to be there.
We didn't know if your dad was gonna come back.
Ronnie didn't.
What?
The museum says that-- that Dad just saved everybody.
I guess there's things the museum left out.
Like your Dad giving himself to the Speed Force
to save the city.
That was another time we said good-bye thinking...
might be a one-way trip.
Sounds a lot like what took him from us in the future.
I didn't know Dad had so many close calls.
Look, your dad is always gonna
wanna put his life on the line for others.
That is what I love most about him,
but, yeah, it-- it does keep me up at night.
Did he come back?
No, the records I falsified convinced him for now.
So we're safe?
Orlin, I think you need to stay away.
Good idea.
I won't visit till after the weekend.
No, I think you need to stay away for good.
It's getting too risky.
You want me to give up Grace?
No, no, no, listen,
you can't put me on hold.
I don't care about this next of kin crap.
I don't want this kid. Hello?
Hello?
Damn it.
What?
It's breakfast.
Yeah, it is. Um...
Okay.
Now look, it's only a few days old.
It's still good, I swear.
I don't understand.
Explain again to me
what the difference between this day
and every other day in America?
It's a holiday when we all get together
and celebrate and eat a ton of food.
Like, a gross amount.
Again, what the difference between this day
and every other day in America.
- That's legit. - Hi, guys.
What's going on?
This guy, he try to explain the Thanksgiving holiday.
He's failing miserably. What is this holiday?
- Please explain. - It's very simple, actually.
It's just about getting together
to celebrate our loved ones and family.
So simple, this is why I don't understand this holiday.
I don't have any family.
Didn't you have, like, seven marriages?
I did have seven marriages.
Five wives, seven marriages, but no family.
This holiday is a cruel holiday.
What's going on?
I'm seeing a massive electrical surge
at the downtown power station.
Barry, Nora, you're up.
Guys, what's the problem?
Everything looks--
I think we found it.
- It's lightning. - Skies were clear a minute ago.
That storm must have come out of nowhere.
Uh, we got a bigger problem.
There's an experimental cold fusion core
from Mercury Labs in the plant, and if it blows...
It could take out the whole block.
I see it.
Nora, you've got to evac all the workers to safety.
- Barry-- - Yeah, I know, I got to grab the core.
No, no, no, something doesn't feel right.
Just listen to Iris. Grab the workers from inside.
Dad!
You guys, he's not breathing.
He's going into cardiac arrest.
She needs to restart his heart.
What-- how do I do that?
Rub your hands together to create lightning,
and then give him a chest compression.
Okay! Okay.
Come on. Come on. Come on.
It's not working!
We lost him.
No! No!
No!
Please. Please. Please.
He's back.
- I promise I'm okay. - Caitlin.
His vitals are stable. Speed healing to the rescue.
He shouldn't have needed rescuing.
Nora, I know you're upset,
but if that core would have exploded
it would have caused a lot of damage.
It did cause a lot of damage. Dad died.
We made the best decision we could, given the circumstances.
Maybe someone else should be making our decisions.
Wow, all right, well,
so much for mother-daughter holiday time.
She did just have to bring me back to life.
- Let's give her a minute. - Okay.
In the meantime, where did that storm come from?
A storm like that coming and going,
disappearing in a matter of minutes,
it shouldn't be possible.
Unless someone was making it possible.
I mean, we've seen that before.
- Weather Wizard. - But Mark Mardon is serving
a life sentence at Iron Heights.
Let's make sure he's doing just that.
Let us know if any other weather anomalies
pop up on the radar.
Okay.
Will do.
I think it's time for operation: Save the Turkey.
What...?
Art is therapy.
So, Sherlock--
Sherloque, simple pronunciation.
We heard what you had to say about not having a family.
Right. And we here at Team Flash are
sort of a family, and you're becoming part of that family,
so we would like to invite you
to celebrate Thanksgiving with us.
Caitlin, I'm afraid that I must decline, all right?
Because I don't have a lot of reason to celebrate,
and you of all people should sympathize with that.
- Why should I sympathize? - You lost your father, right?
And then you find him only to discover that his body
is being possessed by a icicle demon
who's trying to kill all of Team Flash,
yourself included. Not great, right?
Okay, that's enough, Debbie Downer.
Don't listen. You know what?
Maybe you should lay off the paint fumes.
Do you know what, young Ralph Macchio?
You have nothing to celebrate either, right?
What your last year has been, huh?
Let me recap for you. First, heartbreak.
And then second, Cicada crushes your powers
forcing you to fake your own death,
also not great, and as for me,
multiple divorces have left me
with a mountain of debt that's insurmountable.
So this past year, not been very kind to any of us.
Pardon.
She's had a few recent outbursts,
and we don't allow cursing here.
This type of behavior cannot continue.
Anyway, that's the long and short of it.
I'll give you two a moment.
You called a kid a rat bastard?
What's wrong with you? Don't you know
you can't go around saying stuff like that?
Why?
Well, 'cause then I get a phone call.
You know, I had to take off work to come down here.
- You don't even like your job. - What?
You stay on the couch all day,
and then when work calls
you curse and slam the door.
"Rat bastards."
Look, I get where you heard it.
All right, but you can't say those words.
- Rat bastard! - Hey, quit it.
- Rat bastard! - Stop.
- Rat bastards! - Hey, listen to me!
I'm supposed to be the parent here.
No, you're not a parent!
Parents are supposed to make the world better for their kids.
You make everything worse. I hate you,
and you hate you too.
You have to excuse our dim lighting.
Today's storm out at the power plant
knocked out our main generator,
So we're working off a backup for the time being.
So does that mean you can't dampen
the meta prisoner's powers?
Prison-wide dampeners are down,
but we got every inmate into meta cuffs incident free.
I hope you include that in your article about our readiness.
After the corruption of the last warden,
I am eager to assure the public
that their safety is in good hands.
Now, our CSIs, which inmate did you need to see?
And he's been here all day?
Never once out of our sight.
There was a crime committed today
with an MO similar to Mardon's.
Can I take a look at the security tapes?
Anything for our friends in the press.
Well, this is a bust.
Yeah, looks like you died for nothing.
Nora, hey, hey, look.
This has been a rough day for you,
but you can't blame Iris for what happened.
She's doing the best she can.
Besides, we both decided on the plan.
Oh, I know.
What the...?
Hey, don't mind me.
I'm just here to pick up my dad.
Did she say "Dad"?
Joslyn?
It's Joss.
Bring me my father! Now!
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
We'll see about that.
Bring my dad to Porter Plaza in one hour,
or Central City is gonna get wrecked.
I didn't know that Joslyn was busting me out.
I didn't know she'd do half the things she does.
I haven't spoken to her in years.
And you expect me to believe she woke up
this morning and was like, "You know what?
I wanna break my dad out of Iron Heights."
I get it, but it's the truth.
Joss was born when me and her mom were still in high school.
I never could work out how to be with that woman.
Then when Joss came I thought the best thing to do
was to focus on my career.
Your criminal career?
That's why I left her with her mom.
Least until she ran away because some of falling out.
What happened with Joss and her mom?
The last time I spoke to her
she told me that her and Joss are broken.
You know how it is.
Sometimes mothers and daughters break
and there ain't no fixing 'em.
Okay, watch your step.
And open your eyes.
Whose house is this?
It's my cousin Robbie's.
He doesn't live here anymore, but he said
if I fix it up, we could stay here.
What's this?
That is a dollhouse.
Or it can be
once we build it, and, you know, you can...
Pick out furniture, and colors,
or wall paper, decorate it how you want.
I know we didn't get off to the greatest start
these past few months.
Okay...
it was a lousy start.
But I want to fix all that.
Well, I was thinking that while I work on this place,
we could work on this one too... together.
Listen, you were right, kid.
I do hate me.
I don't really know any other way to be,
but I want to do right by you, Gracie.
I want to keep you safe, and warm, fed...
You know, just...
give you all the things a kid should have.
Let's start with the dollhouse.
Okay.
How's Dad's interrogation going?
Well, we'll know in a minute. Hopefully, he'll find something
that'll help us profile Mardon's daughter.
Okay, well, let me know.
Nora, look, listen, I know you're upset with me
for sending your dad into that situation earlier,
and I just--
- I wanted to say that I-- - Mom, it's okay.
I'm not upset with you.
- You're not? - No, we're good.
I-I promise.
Okay, cool.
That's the other thing, celebrating the decimation of an indigenous culture
so a bunch of greedy colonizers can get their turkey-lurkey on.
Do you know about this? Do you know about the sham?
The sham we call "Thanksgiving."
Okay, I'm sorry, am I missing something?
Since when did you guys become anti-Thanksgiving?
Since a bunch of guys wearing hat-buckles
fed us some old bull, wrapped in lies,
stuffed in propaganda.
Actually, I think the hat-buckles weren't real either.
Don't encourage him.
You get it.
Did you get anything from Mardon?
No, nothing that'll help us find his daughter.
What about you guys? What'd you dig up?
Meet Joss Jackam.
She is a delinquent teen turned amateur stormchaser.
A self-taught expert in theoretical meteorology.
How do we know she's a storm chaser?
'Cause Helen Hunt here has a blog.
Mm-hmm. She lost her grant from the Science Center
for doing too many dangerous experiments on the weather.
Well, look like she's way beyond the experimental phase.
Ooh, Weather Witch?
I'll allow it.
Dad, that weathervane,
doesn't it look a lot like...
The staff she was carrying, yeah.
Cisco, can you pull up the security footage
from her attack on Iron Heights?
Sure can.
It's infected with a satellite shard.
She's got meta-tech.
Like Spencer Young's phone.
Look, she has instant lightning on command.
There's no way you're gonna be able to get that staff from her.
She's gonna have to give it up willingly.
Okay, listen, we got 20 minutes
before she destroys the entire city,
so what is the plan?
We only have one choice.
We give her what she wants.
No Weather Witch in sight.
Okay, Singh cleared the perimeter,
so it's free of civilians.
And our satellites are on weather watch
for our Weather Witch. Nothing yet.
What?
I wouldn't say nothing.
My data leaves me to conclude
that there is artificially-created
pressure system of uncertain origin
headed rapidement toward the downtown core.
Listen, Galileo, you can lick your finger
and stick it in the wind all you want.
Why don't you leave the actual calculations
to actual compu-- oh, for Christ's sake.
And your exasperation leads me also to conclude
that you have realized, although late,
that once again I'm right. I'm right. I'm right.
I'm right. I'm right--
That's enough out of you.
She's here.
So the rotten apple doesn't fall far from the tree.
You're a poet. Awesome.
Where's my dad?
All right, Joss, we held up our end of the bargain.
You got dad.
There's no reason to hurt anybody--
Ah, so boring. Come on.
We'll handle it from here.
Hey, baby girl.
Dad.
That's a pretty cool staff.
Would you just--how about you just power that thing off for a sec
and let your dad try.
Try this.
Oh, oh, don't feel bad. He was a selfish dick
who abandoned his family.
Anyway, thanks for helping me drop a truck on my dad.
Uh...guys?
What now?
I didn't see the hummer coming.
I'm so pissed!
This city will drown,
crumble, burn, because of you!
Thanks.
I'm gonna follow her.
Wait, are you serious right now?
- What? - You almost just died.
Again, and you don't seem to care.
Where is this coming from?
You know how dangerous our job is.
Yeah, but I don't want to lose you again,
but you don't seem to give a damn if you lose me,
and-- and all for your job.
Nora.
How long you been holding that one in?
My best guess? My whole life.
Growing up without you, I was so angry...
but you were my hero, so...
it was easier to put my anger for you not being around
on criminals and meta-villains...
a lot of times on Mom.
But when I saw you die today
it reminded me that
I'm mad at someone else about losing you...
You.
I get it.
It's not easy having a parent
who puts their life on the line for others.
I remember feeling the same way about Joe
being a cop when I was a kid.
No, it's not the same thing.
Did he ever have to say good-bye to you knowing
that he wasn't coming back?
You did...
and you're gonna do it again.
Nora, you got to remember you're talking about
a future that we might be able to avoid.
We still have time to find our way to a solution,
and we will.
But there is a solution.
It's just one that you don't want.
Give up being The Flash.
Come on. It's the only way to guarantee
that you won't disappear again in the future,
or any other time.
- Nora. - Come on. Think about it.
You're not the only hero.
Let the others protect the world.
You don't have to keep sacrificing yourself.
You give your life again and again.
How many times does it have to be you?
It hurt so much losing you
when I didn't even know you,
but now after all of these months
getting to know you I just--
please, Dad, don't make me go through it again.
I don't want to go through it again.
Nora, people need The Flash.
I need my dad.
This is the third ice cream of the day, you know?
Something fishy's going on here.
Okay, you got me.
We're celebrating
because this is a very special day.
One year ago today,
I made you a promise
that I would turn my life around
and make things better for you.
I can honestly say that my life
is a million times better than what it was.
And it's all because of you, Gracie.
So I got you something.
It's the set I wanted.
I thought your little dollhouse could use a family.
I already have one.
I love you, kiddo.
Purple.
You know, I think four ice creams in a day would be the--
Gracie, run.
Run. Run. Come on!
Go this way! Go this way!
Help me!
Help me, please!
- Sir. - Somebody!
Save her, please.
Get him on a table.
Move!
Gracie...
Help her...
On the eve of Thanksgiving,
reports of devastating weather phenomena
are streaming in from all over the city.
The exact cause of these disturbances remains unknown.
I can't believe she's actually willing
to level the city to kill one man.
She doesn't know where Mardon is.
It's overkill, but it's the only option we've left her.
Well, Caitlin's on radar,
and Cisco's trying to juice the satellites,
but there's interference. We can't locate Joss.
You okay?
Look, babe, you're gonna find the words
to make her understand. I know it.
Not sure I have the words to make myself understand.
She's got a point.
We got a hit on Joss.
She's at Sheldon County Airport.
Barry, you got to move.
You're good?
Barry, do you have eyes on Joss?
No, she's damaged the terminal so badly
the hangar's the only safe place.
I'm evacuating everyone trapped on the tarmac.
I think I can bring Frost out. What can we do?
Flood control
down at the Marina.
Guys, how do we fight weather?
We fight weather with weather.
Nora.
We still have Mardon's weather wand.
I need you to get it from the archives
and take it to Barry, okay?
Okay.
- Hey. - Hey.
Mardon's wand?
Cisco says you can use it to counteract Joss's weather.
Where is she?
Last chance. Where's my Dad?
Joss, you know we can't give him up.
Then you know what happens next.
Joss, I deceived you, okay? Not them.
You want make someone pay, it's me.
This is how you make heroes pay!
By the beard of Zeus,
she's making a tornado out of lightning.
Cisco, how do I use this wand to stop this?
You can attract all the lightning to the wand.
That'll take down the tornado,
but all that energy will go through your body.
You'll be a human lightning rod.
It's okay.
I know you have to go.
Run, Dad.
Run!
Back. Everybody, back.
Barry? Nora, do you see him?
I, uh...
I...
I see him. He's still here.
We live in a world full of meta-phones
and meta-weathervanes.
What's next? My electric toothbrush?
Till we figure out how to remove those shards,
- better safe than sorry. - Yeah.
Well, now that Mardon and his daughter
are all tucked away in Iron Heights.
What do you say we spend some time with our own family?
Well, might just be us and Nora this year.
Caitlin and Cisco are skipping Thanksgiving.
What? Why?
- Don't even ask. - What?
A toast to...
The thankless.
- The thankless! - The thankless!
The thankless!
Allez-oop.
All right, boys, I'm tapping in.
Okay, let me get this straight.
You two losers are sitting here
in what I can only assume is the cantina of a starship,
drinking and eating terrible food
when you could be drinking and eating amazing food
with people who actually care about you.
All right, all right, look.
When you put it like that...
- She has a good point. - You have a good point, yeah.
And, by the way, I have the least to celebrate this year
because I spent most of it unconscious.
You nerds come to Thanksgiving, or what?
So it wasn't so much the taste as it was the crunch.
Wait, are you actually saying--
Yes, that was the year I found out
why Grandma Esther's yams tasted so good,
because she never cleaned her favorite skillet.
I take it this was also the year
you stopped eating Grandma Esther's yams?
Uh-uh, I didn't say all that.
Allow me to propose a toast.
Well, first to clean dishware,
and also to--to family, all right,
and to friends, old and new.
And to the colonizers who conquered this land...
- What? - And...
-the colonizers who grabbed-- - Remember-- no...
What they want, they just take what they want.
- Yes, I know, but our-- - To taking what you--
That's not--you know what? Let's go.
- Right now. - Okay, you know what?
I think that it's time to go carve a turkey.
Great.
Nora.
Um, we didn't have a chance to talk since the airport.
Oh, Dad, I know what you're gonna say,
and you don't have to.
I saw what it was like
when you hesitated to save those people
because of me, and I felt...
- Horrible? - Yeah.
And I never want to feel like that again.
I get it.
Sometimes you have to sacrifice yourself to save others.
Even if it means leaving your family behind.
Not exactly.
Look, when I ran into that storm I was thinking
I want to save everyone, but...
the person I was thinking about the most was you.
- Me? - Yeah.
I don't choose being The Flash over being with my family.
I'm The Flash for my family,
and I don't have to run to the future
to understand why I sacrificed myself.
I'd do it to save, and your mom,
all the people I love.
You know, maybe one day if I train enough,
I'll be able to save you.
I don't doubt it.
- All right, come on. - Okay.
- Ah, yes. - All right.
- Hey, thank, God. - Carve the turkey.
- Yeah, baby. - Here we are.
- Each person gets a turkey. - No.
We have the one for everyone.
- You all right? - Just Dad with a knife,
It's a little-- - It's the most fun part.
Oh, you're very good at that.
Am I?
Orlin.
I told you it's too risky.
CCPD's already looking for you. What are you doing here?
It's Thanksgiving, Doc. I'm here to be with my family.
I want you to be optimistic,
but I'm not gonna lie to you.
As far as how long,
with all the brain hemorrhaging she suffered,
you have to prepare yourself for the possibility
that she may never wake.
This is all my fault.
No, it's these metas.
Wreacking havoc unchecked.
She didn't deserve this, Mr. Dwyer,
and neither did you.
This was the scene Tuesday night as, once again,
The Flash saved Central City from certain destruction.
After a world-wide power outage
blanketed every country in darkness,
a bizarre purple...
The destructive phenomenon emanated
from a satellite that had fallen
into a decaying orbit.
Thankfully, before the satellite could
strike the city and create what scientists believe
would have been "A catastrophic event,"
The Flash was able to destroy it.
Once again, residents of our proud city,
and perhaps the entire world owe The Flash
and his allies...
A new meta was last seen jumping off a building
in order to evade capture after stealing jewels...
It was reported that he escaped Flash's grasp
after hijacking an armored vehicle.
I'm gonna make this right, Gracie.
Every meta...
will die.
Guys, this better be good.
Yeah, we've got an after-Thanksgiving tradition called sleeping,
so what's up?
It's good. Trust us. Detective.
Well, it occurred to me that if you,
monsieur and madam West-Allen,
you want to spend this holiday with your family.
Well, perhaps your meta-killer does as well.
So I had monsieur Cisco hack into the CCTV footage
of the hospital and this what we got.
Ever since Grace arrived,
only one man has come to visit her.
Every day.
Including tonight.
Team Flash, I give you...
Orlin Dwyer, also known as...
Cicada.