I want you to think about
the biggest secret in your life.
The one you keep from the people that you love
or even from yourself.
I want you to imagine what would happen
if that secret got out.
Remember when you asked me that?
I've been using all of your training.
Studying my pulse, managing micro-expressions,
limiting non-congruent gestures,
destroying any piece of evidence.
I don't know how much longer I can keep this up.
And not just because of the risks.
But because the closer I get to my parents,
the more I feel like I'm hurting them.
Data entry complete, Gideon.
Thank you, Nora West-Allen.
Shall I send this to the usual recipient?
Yes.
Send it to Eobard Thawne,
priority level urgent.
You ready for this?
Dad, I'm just--I'm not fast enough yet.
No backing out now, this is the biggest race of your life.
- Get ready, set, go! - Not really. Dad, Dad--
Wait, wait! Oh, God.
Gotcha.
This is so embarrassing.
I'm really good at the ice skating game on my Pocket Pal!
Okay, you're just gonna bend your knees...
- Kay. - And lead forward a little.
Just, yeah.
Yeah.
- I'm doing it. - You're doing it.
I'm skating. This is like schway city, Mom.
Thanks.
Look at you guys.
- Such a mom. - What? What about you?
You're the one who sprang for ice skating and game night.
Yeah, well, I know when Nora got hurt,
I got a little frustrated.
And now, I mean, we have an actual plan to stop Cicada.
Waking up his niece to appeal to his heart.
I know Dwyer's a killer, but he's still a person,
and he loves Grace just like we love Nora.
So I don't know. I just feel like
everything's heading in the right direction.
Here I come. Coming in. Here we go.
I'm sorry, why are you wearing a helmet?
I thought you were made of rubber.
Somebody's gotta set a good example for these kids.
Well--I thought you grew up on the ice.
Well, I did, basically,
my mom dated a zamboni operator, so...
And I tell you where I'm from we don't date zamboni drivers.
Why is that? Because there are no zambonis.
How do we clear the ice? All winter long,
we are on our hands and knees with a squeegee in hand.
Let me tell you.
Best eight months of the year for this guy.
It's a really great story, Sherlock.
Sherloque.
You know, speaking of squeegeeing,
you know who could use a good squeegeeing
is Larry Blumenthal. He's dead.
- Larry Blumenthal is dead? - Yeah.
The patent registrar across the hall from you
with the 400 square footage--
- And the courtyard views? - Yeah, dead as a doornail.
You can have that place if you want it. Yours to rent.
What? Oh, my God. This is perfect.
I mean, my ad revenue has been up this quarter, so...
Yeah, with the extra space you'd be able to hire
editors, photographers.
I could turn my blog into a real newspaper.
Oh, my package has arrived.
What package?
This is the solution to all our problems.
Allez, les amis. We must go.
Madames et monsieurs,
may I present to you la Machine ¨¤ M¨¦moire,
or as they say in Am¨¦rique, you know...
The Memory Machine.
Oui, Iris. Memory Machine. Many times...
I have entered into people's minds
using this very technology.
From the unfortunate comatose victims
of the Summerholt Institute to, yes,
the Terrible Mad Hatter Killer from Earth-221.
I come back from Tannhauser for one second,
just borrowing a splicer for the meta cure
and what do I find?
- This, this-- - Machine ¨¤ M¨¦moire.
Whatever. How did you even get this here from Earth-221?
Well, I used the Forerunner Multiversal Delivery Service.
You don't use it? You don't have a gold card like me?
Maybe I'll get you a discount.
We don't need a discount.
All right, we just need to wake up Grace.
This'll wake her up, right?
So in most coma patients,
high traffic areas of brain activity go dormant
and the low traffic areas spring to life,
but unfortunately, Grace isn't normal.
Not only has her coma lasted longer than the average,
but her consciousness has isolated itself
into one specific region,
her long-term memories.
It will be so facile, easy peasy for you.
All you do is you transmit your brainwaves
into Grace's memories, right?
And then you'll lead her consciousness
out of a neural nexus portal.
And Grace awakens.
It's sort of like when Barry woke me up
when the Thinker trapped me.
Surprisingly, that sounds kind of easy peasy.
As long as Grace's unusual brain damage
doesn't cause any unforeseen risks.
This is why I suggest you travel in pairs
when you're using this technology.
Every time I enter into someone's memories
when I use this I went with my partner for sure.
Your partner's name didn't happen to be Watson, did it?
No, his name was not Watson.
His name was Watsune.
Yes, together we went through dozens of minds, together--
until one time I found myself
in a memory of a motel room in Montreal
where what do I find but Watsune in flagrante deli
in interpersonal relationship with my wife,
fourth wife, but still.
You're saying you could see your partner's memories?
It's a possible side effect of traveling in pairs.
And speaking of which,
which pairs would like to volunteer for this mission?
I suggest the speedsters for this to be accomplished so quick.
- Yeah. - Elected.
Hey, if you see a memory of me stealing blank Scrabble tile
it's not what it looks like, all right?
That's a good one, Dad.
All that is left is to connect this transceiver disc
to Grace's EEG and we can transmit.
- Great. - Right.
All right, first thing tomorrow,
we save Grace.
Any big plans for the night off?
I'm gonna crash.
Killer Frost was up all night watching movies
from her two favorite Johns, Woo and Hughes.
Huh, I'm more of a Ford and Waters man myself,
but I will be up all night yet again
working with the radiated meta-human sample you guys got me.
There's something missing with this cure.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
- All right. - Night.
You know, there's something that I'm missing too.
- Your freshly healed hands. - Odd choice of words.
Well, I'm meeting with an informant tonight
and he might have a lead on Dwyer's location,
but I'm not sure if I should trust him.
So you need me to vibe him. Look, man.
I should really be working on this cure.
But my splicer algorithm won't technically be done
until 3:00 A.M.
Thanks, man, this is, this is really important work.
Okay.
Okay, Gideon, how do I hack this thing
so that Dad won't see my memories?
In any configuration,
if you and Barry Allen go in together,
you still risk exposing your memories.
So I can't do anything.
Gideon, is that...
Grace Gibbons' brain waves.
It would appear Sherloque Wells has planted the transceiver disc.
So I can go in alone.
And I'll be back before anyone notices,
but by that time Grace'll be awake anyway.
Activating brain wave transmission.
In three, two, one.
CCPD?
Okay, Jones, here's the kid.
We found her in the car hiding under the seat.
Her parents were at the ATM when the meta attacked.
Damn. We located her next of kin?
Maybe an uncle. Still tracking down
his last known address.
Well, she can't sleep on this bench.
We've gotta get her out of here.
God, poor kid.
Who are you? You can see me?
Oh, right, you're Grace's consciousness
in her old memory.
I'm Nora.
Can you take me to my parents?
No, um, I can't,
but if you come with me, I can help you feel better.
You know,
when I was your age, I had a friend just like this.
I bet he'd like to feel better too.
Okay.
All right, Gracie, let's get you through
this portal and out of your coma
before anyone notices I snuck in here.
Oh, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm trapped.
We're gonna find a way out of here, I promise.
I feel like I've been in this police station for a long time,
and now I'm gonna be here forever, aren't I?
Just leave me alone.
You know, when I was your age,
I had to come to this very same police station
all by myself too.
- It's kind of scary in here. - I'm not scared.
Well, I was. I'm scared all the time.
In fact, once, there was this really bad guy
and he wanted to hurt a whole lot of people on a plane.
A meta?
But I helped stop him.
- Whoa, really? - I was terrified, though.
But you know what my secret is?
I just imagine what will happen after I do the thing.
Do you want to try it?
Okay, close your eyes,
and think about what will happen once you're out of here.
I'll see Uncle Orlin.
Let's find our way out of here, okay?
So I can't use "Gazette"? "Chronicle"?
So the only name that's cleared is "Central City Citizen."
Uh, yeah, yeah, thanks.
Hey, who was that on the phone?
Um, a lawyer, she was helping answer some questions
about me starting a newspaper.
That's cool. What'd she say?
You know, it doesn't matter.
I-I'm actually not sure that the timing is right,
and I really just want to focus on team Flash
and stopping Cicada.
Yeah, but--
Oh, hold on.
Slow down, slow down.
It's Sherloque.
Nora did what?
Why would Nora go in alone?
And why isn't she out yet?
My working theory is that Grace's unique brain damage
has caused her brain to act defensively,
so when it sensed an outside presence,
it moved all of its neural nexus pathways
to seal the exits like a-a quarantine procedure.
Grace's brain thinks Nora's a pathogen.
Yes, we can expect its synaptic defense mechanisms
to try and eliminate her.
Remember I told you about the Mad Hatter?
He was also brain damaged, so after my dispute with
Watsune and my fourth wife, Watsune pursued the case
on his own until the day I found him
hooked up to the Machine ¨¤ M¨¦moire brain-dead.
You knew this was a possibility?
What happened to easy peasy?
That's why I say go in in pairs.
Barry, we have to go in after her.
I looked all over CCPD.
There's no sign of the portal.
How could you have looked everywhere?
You were gone for about two seconds.
Well, I'm really fast.
I-I used to run track in high school.
Go CC Squirrels.
Look, Grace, is there anywhere else you can take me?
Another memory?
Where are we?
My house.
Uncle Orlin!
Hey, kiddo.
How you doing? How was your day?
Let me run through this again.
So Mr. Truck, you said. You've seen Cicada here?
Dude's been up in here like a mean fungus.
I see, and how is the White Russian Hacker?
You wanna focus up here?
So can you tell me was he violent?
Hell yeah, every Thursday,
comes in and assaults anyone in here
Unnecessary.
But okay.
You're talking about a band named "Sickada"?
Yeah, bro.
You said "That dude" assaulted people.
He assaults everyone in here with that terrible music.
Dibs.
Well, that didn't pan out the way that I hoped.
We will have two Mother-In-Laws, please.
No, no, no, no. Truck, thank you for your time.
- I think we're done here. - One drink.
I'm paying.
One drink, but only because
you never pay for anything ever and I'm really curious
to see what hell looks like frozen over.
We can't warn her we're coming?
We wanted to install an emergency beacon,
but it didn't work.
So once you enter, it'll create a new portal.
You'll only have a few moments to find Grace and Nora
before Grace's brain tries to seal it off.
Remember, if you die in there...
We die out here. I remember from DeVoe.
We're gonna save her, I promise.
Commencing brainwave transmission.
Good luck.
CCPD.
All right, come on.
We found her hiding in the last car under the seat.
- And her parents? - No idea.
She was on the Red Line headed downtown.
Must've jumped the turnstile at Fourth and Waid.
We can't just let her sleep on this bench.
Oh, my God. Barry.
Wait, is that Joe West's granddaughter?
Nora? Hey, Nora.
Someone get her.
I don't think we're in Grace's memories.
We're in Nora's.
There's been no changes in Grace's brain activity.
But look.
Nora's brain activity has tripled.
That means...
Barry and Iris are in Nora's memories.
How did we end up in Nora's childhood memories?
I have no idea. I also have no clue
how we're gonna rescue Nora from here.
Okay. Okay, we're in a memory within a memory, right?
Yeah.
So if we went through a portal, then...
It should take us into Grace.
Okay, yeah, we just have to wander through Nora's memories
until we find where the portal went.
Okay.
Maybe she'll lead us right there.
What happened here?
I guess in Nora's future, S.T.A.R. Labs is--
- The Flash Museum. - The Flash Museum.
No way.
Look at this.
Flash toys and Flash phones.
Flash rings. Are you kidding? Wow.
This is all gonna go to your head, isn't it?
Oh, you know what? It looks like it might.
Oh, that is very cute.
Hey, I found her.
You think we can talk to her?
No. I wish.
This might be the only time I get to see her at this age.
Nora's consciousness isn't here, though.
It's in Grace. This is a fixed memory.
We can't interfere.
When I was ten, I wasn't running away from home.
That's 'cause you were a good kid.
I ran away all the time.
Yeah, only 'cause you were trying to see your dad.
Not 'cause you were running from someone.
Oh, hey, we should keep trying to find the portal.
Come on, Gracie, no cussing.
Please, can we, please?
Okay, fine.
A rare, old bird is a pelican whose beak can hold more
than his belly can.
He can hold in his beak enough food for a week.
But I'm darned if I know how the hell he can.
Grace, I was thinking maybe we could go now
and look for the portal?
Is something burning?
Oh, crap.
I mean, crud.
He thinks he takes care of me now,
but I really take care of him.
Okay, kiddo, you better eat up.
We've got a big day.
This is...
First we're going to the zoo...
This is an interesting doll house.
We're gonna get ice cream, and then...
Can't forget the fair.
Fair?
Where you got hurt.
Grace, I-I think that's where the portal is.
Can you take me there?
To the last place that you remember?
Okay.
Hey, check her out.
She's right up your alley. You should buy her a drink.
Damn. Look at that hand stitching.
No, no, I did not come here to admire jackets.
I came here to vibe and inform.
Is it just me or are there a lot
of ladies in leather in here?
Yep, singles night.
- It's quite a coincidence. - Is it?
What is it you're always saying?
- "I smell a mystery"? - That is trademarked.
I can vibe the anxiety coming off of you right now.
This whole thing was a setup.
Of course your informant didn't know Cicada.
I mean, he knew of Cicada.
You lied to me, you wasted my time
so I could be your wingman tonight?
No, no, no, dude, it's not like that.
You know, just when I think you're growing up,
you go ahead and do something that shows me
you're just as selfish as the day we met.
That's for the drinks.
Excuse me.
Wait.
These guys get their own wing?
Who is Cicada? Officials believe...
Barry, maybe we should keep looking for the portal.
Yeah.
But when Cicada resurfaced in 2024 after the Flash vanished,
some were left to speculate that Cicada is not a man at all,
but an immortal monster.
All we know for sure is his body count,
152 victims and rising.
Wait, what?
I knew we never caught Cicada, but he never stops killing?
Flash did everything he could,
but Cicada killed more people than Zoom
or even the Red Death.
And the way the city saw the Flash, his legacy...
it was never the same.
Nora West-Allen, you are in serious trouble, young lady.
Grace, what are we doing here?
You wanted to go to my last memory.
Yeah, but I thought that was supposed to be at the fair.
Grace?
Hello?
The destructive phenomenon emanated from a satellite
that had fallen into a decaying orbit.
Thankfully, before the satellite could strike the city...
How does she remember this?
A catastrophic event...
A new meta was last seen jumping off a building
in order to evade capture after...
I'm gonna make this right, Gracie.
Every meta will die.
Grace, how did you hear Orlin that night?
- You were in a coma. - I know.
But I've been listening.
- You have to stop. - Not until I'm finished.
Did they come after you tonight?
I killed his partner, Vibe,
but there was a woman there too,
banged me up pretty bad.
She had speed.
I think she's the Flash's daughter.
Grace, I don't know what you think Orlin said--
You said you looked everywhere.
I get it now. You have speed.
You're her, aren't you?
You're the Flash's daughter.
You're the one who hurt my uncle.
Grace, I want to help you.
No, you don't. Uncle Orlin told me about you.
You and your dad are trying to hurt him.
Only because he's trying to hurt other people,
innocent people!
No, he only hurts metas,
like the one who killed my parents.
Like you! You're a meta and a liar!
All metas aren't bad.
My uncle is a hero. He protects people,
and I protect my uncle!
My speed's gone.
Did you think that you could run away
and I wouldn't figure out where you went?
It's my job to find out the truth. I'm a reporter.
You're always a reporter.
Why not be my mom for once?
Oh, yeah? How's this for being your mom?
You are never coming back to this place again. Let's go.
Excuse me, what is in your pocket?
- Hand that over right now. - It's not yours.
Well, it is now. There are consequences to your actions.
Hand it over.
I hate you.
Leave it. Let's go.
Iris, that wasn't you.
Yeah, but it will be, Barry.
Nora's gonna grow up hating her mother.
No, she won't. You're gonna make different choices.
If you don't wanna be that person that we just saw,
don't be that person.
I know. I know you keep saying that, Barry,
and that's what I'm trying to do.
I had a moment today and I thought that
maybe if I could change the timeline now,
that even in the smallest way
that--I don't know.
That everything in the future would be somehow different.
This is why you changed your mind about the newspaper.
When I talked to the lawyer,
I asked her to check a dozen potential names,
and guess which one was the only one that cleared.
The "Central City Citizen."
I know it's got baggage, but it's just a name.
Is it? I mean, we've been looking at that front page
for four years.
"Flash Missing, Vanishes in Crisis."
And I'm the one that writes that article, Barry.
I just thought that, I don't know,
maybe if I don't start the paper, that--
Iris, this is your dream,
and the city needs somebody like you.
Yeah, but, Barry, look where it gets us.
These are Nora's memories right now in this timeline
after she interfered.
Let's keep looking for the portal, okay?
Nora needs our help.
I'll have whatever he's having.
All I want to order right now is a Lyft out of here,
but I get no bars in this bar,
so maybe I'll just have to leave the old-fashioned way
and breach on out of here.
Look, Cisco, I'm...
Sorry I lied to you.
Don't apologize to me.
Apologize to all the meta-humans out there
still waiting for a cure,
for their right to choose if they want these powers or not.
Before I was The Elongated Man,
when I was just nobody Ralph Dibny,
I could do whatever I wanted whenever I wanted,
but I didn't have any friends to do those things with.
So I just thought if, uh, we're getting a night off
from stopping Cicada, we could just
go out and...
have some fun, you know?
And I want that too,
but after we figure out this cure.
You know, my mom's friend Doug,
he had a saying.
"If you're always waiting to live your life,
you're gonna die before it starts."
And Doug, he would know.
He operated a zamboni.
May he rest in peace.
All right, I'ma go outside,
see if I can stretch my arm high enough
to get you some cell phone service.
Dark and Stormy on the house.
Do I look that pathetic?
You look like you belong here about as much as I do.
Thought I was coming here for a business meeting.
What do you do, sell leather?
- Nope. - Tattoo artist.
- Mm-mm. - Gun for hire.
Trust me.
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
Well, I'm a photographer,
so it looks like we're both a little lost.
So what's your excuse?
Taking pictures hasn't made me rich, yet,
so I bartend to pay rent.
My sister hooked me up here.
Forgot to mention I'd be working in hell.
Sisters.
If I looked at the DNA of two siblings,
one who became a meta and one who didn't,
I would have a close enough genetic match
to isolate the part of the genome
that controls meta-genes.
I'm sorry, did I just say that out loud?
Yeah, you did.
I-I just--that--I--
- Cisco. - Camilla.
- Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
I can't find the portal anywhere.
I can't even get out of Nora's memories of this one day.
Barry, get down!
Nora's in trouble. Grace's defense mechanisms
must be attacking her.
She's not the only one who's in trouble.
We need to get them out of there now.
It's Nora's defense mechanism.
What am I supposed to do now?
Hello?
- Nora, is that you? - Caitlyn!
Yes, I told you the M.A.D. 2.0
could complete your emergency beacon.
Uh, Nora, your parents went into your memories.
Uh, let me conference them in.
Sorry, my parents went where?
- Iris West-Allan. - Mom? Dad?
Nora, are you okay?
So listen. We made an important discovery.
To get you out of there.
The portals are hidden in perception gaps.
Things that you remember the way you want them to be,
not the way they actually were.
'Cause you're in denial or your perception
was colored by anger or what have you.
So these defense mechanisms, they're composed of synapses.
If you can break down the synapses in the false memory,
that will reveal the real memory
and the synaptic jolt will expose the portal.
Okay, so--okay, well, how do we do that?
Well, uh, we'll have to call you back.
You're burning up.
Hello?
Perception gaps.
The dollhouse.
How do we know which memories weren't real?
Of course... Iris, it's the Hall of Villains.
You and Nora.
Barry, I still dampen Nora's power.
She still grows up hating me. This is my future.
No, no, it's not.
It's just a memory, one warped from the perspective
of a sad, angry, little kid that ran away from home.
Don't you get it? That person that we saw in there,
the bad mom that Nora told us about,
she doesn't even exist in any timeline.
I told you you had to be different in the future,
but I was wrong.
You don't have to change who you are.
You don't even have to change the name of your newspaper.
I know any future with you in it is gonna be a good one.
You just gotta believe that too.
What are you doing here?
Please, this memory isn't real.
Your uncle's house, I don't think it's really like this.
Okay, better eat up, kiddo.
We got a big day--
Grace, get down!
I don't see the portal anywhere.
Barry, it's working!
Death. Failure.
Another broken family.
This is the legacy I gave you.
Nobody breaks up my family, you son of a bitch.
Oh, no.
You dropped your toy.
I just wanted to see the museum.
I know, honey, but you ran away.
I didn't know where you went.
I was afraid you could have gotten hurt.
You said that the museum reminded you of Dad
'cause Dad was the Flash's number one fan.
So I wanted to see it
'cause I love the Flash too.
It's not fair.
I know, honey. I know it's not fair.
I love you, Nora.
Your dad loved you too.
So, so much.
Come here, girl.
Come on. We gotta go.
Let's go get Nora.
Grace, I know you're afraid.
You think that you'll never be as happy as you were
that day with your uncle.
That's why you try to remember it as perfect,
but things can be that good, Grace.
You just have to wake up.
And then you and me and my parents,
we can all help your uncle together.
You're a liar.
Grace.
Maybe you don't have anyone who cares about you,
but I have someone who cares about me,
and I'm the only one who can help him.
Mom.
She's not coming.
- What? - Hurry!
Come on. Come on.
They're okay.
Neural oscillations are normal.
You three are perfectly healthy.
Oh, and we think we've figured out
how you two ended up in Nora's brain.
That is a satellite shard full of dark matter in Grace's head.
Mon dieu.
Sometimes surgeons leave a piece of shrapnel
in a patient's brain if it's too dangerous to remove,
and we think that the dark matter was seeping out
to create a barrier around her brain.
We can't go back in as long as it's there.
It's too dangerous.
Well, we need to find another way to stop Cicada.
I think I might be able to help with that.
It's the inside of Dwyer's house.
- Damn. - I mean, that's great.
But why did you go in without us? We had a plan.
No, I know, um...
You know, just with the machine being ready
and knowing that Cicada was still out there,
I guess I just... I got a little excessive.
It's not the only reason, though, right?
It was protecting her secret.
What secret is that?
Well, her feelings for her mother when she was a child.
Must be painful memories.
Is that correct, Nora?
Yeah, exactly.
Okay, um, let's get started on this lead.
Good job, Nora.
Thanks.
Monsieur Allen, just for my records of today's events,
what was the defense mechanism Nora was using?
It was one of the costumes from the museum.
What costume?
The Reverse Flash.
Surprise!
Happy first day in your new office.
You're so sweet.
So have you decided what you're gonna name the paper?
I don't know.
"Central City Citizen" has a certain ring to it.
- You sure? - Yeah, you were right.
Future isn't always what it seems.
We decide what it gets to be.
So, um, I just have to tell you one little thing.
See that ledger down there?
That's the year the paper was founded in my time.
2021.
That's two years from now.
You're changing the future already.
Hey, um, I gotta find Cisco,
but I'll see you guys later, all right?
Okay.
Let's head back.
- Mom? - Yeah?
Dad told me about the memory that you saw.
I know it wasn't real, Nora,
but it must have come from a very real place.
You must have been so angry with me to see me that way.
I was angry all the time.
Angry for not getting to have a dad,
angry 'cause nobody seemed to understand what I was feeling.
And it didn't matter what you did or said, Mom.
I was always gonna be angry at you...
because you were there.
You're going through a lot, Nora.
But so were you.
I mean, I thought you were trying to stop me from being me,
but you were trying to stop me from being Dad.
I mean, ending up like him.
You guys had a whole life together
and a child, and he vanished.
I-I can't imagine how hard that must have been for you.
And from that day, you...
you were protecting me.
I-I get that now.
So sorry for the way that I treated you,
both back then and now when I first got here.
You didn't deserve that.
Thank you.
You're an amazing woman, Nora West-Allen.
I will always love you,
past, present, and future.
I love you too, Mom.
It's hard to keep a secret, but it's a lot easier
when you're reminded why you're doing it.
- Ready? - Yeah.
I met someone who told me that she would do anything
to protect her family.
She helped me see that... so would I.
My parents can't know that you're helping me stop Cicada.
There's too much at risk.
And I'll do anything to protect them.
Even lie.
Liar.
Liar. Liar.
Nora lied to me.
She'll pay.
They'll all pay.
Doug was right.
Going out there, doing the ice skating thing,
that was definitely the right thing to do.
Yeah, all Doug, may he rest in peace.
Let's pour one out for the guy.
Camilla? The bartender?
- Uh, excuse me. - Dude, nice.
- All right, all right. - Yeah.
Hey, did you guys make a breakthrough
with the meta-human cure?
We did. I managed to locate a pair of
meta-non-meta siblings,
so this cure, it's as good as done.
All right, good, because I've been thinking.
I want to use the cure on Cicada.