- My name is barry allen,
And I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
But secretly, with the help
of my friends at s.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
But in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am the flash!
Previously on "the flash"...
- I get a vision of something
that's already happened,
And then it's gone.
I don't want anyone
to know about this.
- When you created
the singularity
Above central city,
you also created a breach
Between my world and yours,
connecting our two earths.
- 52 breaches in central city
and the biggest one
Just happens
to be in our basement.
- The person who broke
into my facility last night
Was harrison wells.
- Hey, put him down!
- [grunts]
- Who the hell are you?
- Hello.
For those of you
who don't know me,
My name is harrison wells.
- We know you.
[applause]
- Today, the future has arrived.
Our city
has seen incredible--
Impossible things:
Meta-humans--men and women--
With extraordinary abilities:
The ability
to soar above buildings,
To run faster
than the speed of light.
Unfortunately,
most of these meta-humans
Have chosen the wrong path
with these powers, a dark path.
My team and I at s.T.A.R. Labs
are committed
To keeping up
with these perilous times,
And so may I present to you
our new line
Of meta-human awareness apps?
[applause]
This technology will allow you
to instantly detect
The presence of a meta-human.
You'll be instantly alerted
to an approaching speedster,
Like zoom or like...
[alarm beeps]
[applause]
Flash.
Welcome, flash.
- Tell them the truth,
dr. Wells.
Everything that has happened
to this city the past two years
Is because of you.
You created all of us metas.
You created zoom.
[crowd gasps]
- I created zoom?
- 11 hours
before the first meta sighting,
Enormous blasts
of dark matter radiation
Were silently expelled
beneath this lab.
- I'm sorry, flash,
I believe all this fast running
May have scrambled your brain.
- You take no responsibility
for the wreckage
Your mistakes have caused.
Admit it, wells,
and then maybe you can truly
Help me do something
about it.
- Help you, because I'm
the greatest tech entrepreneur
Of all time?
You're the superhero,
And we would all be safe
If you would just do your job
and stop zoom.
[exciting music]
♪ ♪
[alarm sounds]
Well, I guess it's safe to say
the speedster sensors work.
[crowd laughs]
- You okay, dad?
- I'm fine, sweetie.
Now where was I?
Oh, that's right,
the future.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Very strange to be holding
your autobiography,
Especially when you
didn't write it
And it's not about you.
- Dr. Caitlin snow, cisco ramon,
meet dr. Harrison wells
From earth-2.
- Hi.
- So let me get this straight.
You're the doppelganger
of the man who murdered his mom
And is responsible
for both ronnie
And eddie's deaths?
- Yeah, but he's
not even the doppelganger
Of the dr. Wells that we knew
Because that dr. Wells' body
had been taken over
By the reverse flash,
who was really eobard thawne
And eddie's distant relative
from the future.
- Yeah, I didn't follow
any of that. I'm my own man.
I had nothing to do
with the murder
Of your mother
or your friend ricky.
- His name was ronnie.
- Him either.
- You told me you have proof
of your identity?
- This almost hit me
when I went through the portal.
Your stabilized breach
downstairs connects directly
To the s.T.A.R. Labs
on my earth.
- Technically,
this could be mine,
But I want to run some tests
on you.
- I'll be genetically
indistinguishable
From my earth-1 counterpart.
Your tests will reveal nothing.
- Great!
Still gonna run 'em.
- Be my guest.
- Why are we even listening
to him?
How do we know he's not evil
like the other guy?
- He saved my life last night.
The question is why.
I'm guessing you didn't
travel between dimensions
Just to meet the flash.
- That's exactly what I did.
I came here to help you, barry,
to stop your greatest enemy.
- He already did that.
- I'm not talking
about reverse flash.
I'm talking about zoom.
I see
you've already heard of him.
- Yeah, zoom has been
sending meta-humans
From your world through
the breaches to fight me.
- Well, they're the symptoms.
Zoom's the plague,
One that's infected my world,
and now he's coming for yours.
- What do you know about zoom?
- Everything.
I created zoom.
I'm responsible
for all the earth-2 meta-humans,
A fact I've ignored
for far too long,
But now I'm doing something
about it.
- Yeah, well,
we're batting a thousand
Against these breachers.
- You're batting a thousand,
crisco?
What's your sample size?
Ten? Less?
Zoom is obsessed with speed.
He will never allow there
to be another speedster
In the multiverse,
and he's gonna keep sending
These metas here,
one after the next,
All with the same goal:
To kill the flash
unless we stop him together.
- Last time we listened
to a guy with your face,
Some bad things went down.
- We lost people we cared about.
- Everyone loses someone
they care about, snow.
The real test of character
is what you do
Once they're gone.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
[bullets clink]
- Joe!
Put the gun down!
- How is he still alive?
How are you still alive?
- I don't know,
because you missed?
- Hey, I'm trying to keep him
from shooting you.
You're not helping.
Let's take a walk, all right?
It's all good.
- We know someone
who can verify everything
That this guy just said.
Be careful.
- I don't suppose
you have a big belly burger
In this universe, do you?
- This isn't happening.
- I know that this is a lot
to take in,
But that guy back in that room,
that's not wells.
- Dr. Mcgee swore she saw wells.
He broke into mercury labs.
- What?
Why didn't you tell me this?
- Because I didn't believe her.
I didn't even want
to consider wells was alive.
- Eddie erased that wells
from existence.
This guy is--
he's someone else,
And he says he's here
to help us stop zoom.
- How can you even look at him?
- You think this is easy
for me?
The guy in there looks, moves,
sounds exactly like the guy
That drove a knife
through my mother's heart.
I have to resist the urge
to kill him.
I'm trying my best
to get past that, okay?
You shooting him--
that's not helping.
- After all our losses,
I thought at least
We were free of wells.
I just want one week
where we're not surprised
By somebody from our past.
I better go fill in iris.
- Good luck.
- I hope you're happy, linda.
Tanner's lawyers
are threatening to sue us.
- I'm sorry, chief.
I don't care how many touchdowns
tanner throws.
I'm not interviewing some
roided out jerk who hit his wife
Unless it's
to hold him accountable
For domestic violence.
- All right,
run your story, park.
The sports page used to be
a lot less complicated.
- She shoots.
[imitates swish]
she scores.
- Larkin's the best editor
I've ever worked for.
It's just,
every once in a while,
You have to remind him
it's the 21st century.
[both laugh]
- But that's not really him,
The wells who eddie
gave his life to stop?
- Apparently not.
- [sighs]
That's life in central city
these days, right?
- You sure?
- Dad, I'm fine, really.
- Good.
I want to keep you that way.
- Dad.
- Take it.
I taught you how to use it
for a reason.
And I'm praying
that barry's right
And this wells
means us no harm.
Last year, you had eddie
to look out for you,
But now,
you can't murder somebody
That everybody thinks is dead,
right?
Put it away.
- You do realize
that when I said
I wanted a drink,
I didn't mean a latte, right?
I was talking about alcohol.
Like, mind-numbing alcohol.
- All right, look,
you got give him a chance, okay?
He's not a speedster.
He's just a regular, normal guy
from another universe.
- I never thought
I'd miss time travel.
- Time travel, huh?
- Hey! Are you kidding?
- Hi!
[laughs] is there a meta-human
who can time travel?
- Time--no.
Time travel's not real.
- 'cause that would
be pretty cool!
[all laugh]
- not so sure about that.
- Patty, you know cisco ramon,
right?
- Yeah, you're the scientific
advisor on meta-humans
To the ccpd, right?
- Yeah, that's me.
- Nice.
Hey, barr, did you hear
I was right about king shark?
- King shark?
Nice name. I like her.
- Yeah, yeah, king shark
almost ate the flash.
- Oh, nah, I'm sure
the flash had it handled.
- Oh, no, I was there.
I saw it all.
Some hooded guy saved his life.
- Wait, and you're not,
like, traumatized or anything?
- I just watched
a half man-half shark
Take on the fastest man alive.
[laughs]
I love this city.
[phone vibrates]
see...Sorry.
Oh, uh, captain just texted me.
He wants me to write
my police report.
Uh, you maybe want
to write it with me?
- Uh, I can't tonight.
I'm busy. Um, yeah, sorry.
- Oh, yeah, okay.
- I've just got science stuff.
Stuff I gotta science
the stuff out of.
Maybe next time.
- Yeah! Coolio.
- Yeah.
- But I'm gonna actually
skip the coffee
And go get a head start, so...
- Oh.
- Good to see you guys.
Both: Yeah.
- For real?
- Stop, all right?
I was gonna ask her out,
and then a man-shark
Tried to eat me, and then
dr. Wells the sequel showed up.
- Okay, can we not use
the name "dr. Wells"?
I'm just gonna call him "harry."
- Okay. Harry, yeah.
- Listen, there's always
gonna be harrys out there,
But you can't let
the harrys of the world
Get in the way
of you living your life.
Ask patty out.
You gotta--
you gotta be bold.
- That's tough talk.
When was the last time
you asked a girl for her number?
- Watch and learn.
- I'm watching.
- Hi.
What can I get you?
- Hi, there.
- Hi...Again.
- Uh...
- Do you want some coffee?
- Yeah, I'll get some coffee.
No, uh, no,
I don't want coffee.
You know what I do want though?
I want to ask you this.
Do you want to go out with me?
- Oh.
- To--we--I mean, we could
go get coffee or we--
- No.
- That's a no.
That's totally cool.
It's cool.
Respect.
[rock music playing]
♪ ♪
[woman whimpering]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Yo, dude, you good?
It's her loss.
- [breathes deeply]
- Hey, what's up?
- We have another breach.
- What?
How do you know?
- Central city bank.
You gotta go now!
- All right.
- [breathes heavily]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You got my attention.
- Flash.
- [grunting]
- Her name is doctor light.
[exhales]
Small-time thief on my earth
until exposure
To the dark matter
from the particle accelerator
And became a meta-human
with the ability
To derive power
from starlight.
- Oh, very cool.
- Stars having a temperature
of 5,300 degree kelvin
And a blinding luminosity,
I would say,
"not very cool at all."
- You know, our dr. Wells
may have been evil,
But you're just a dick.
- Okay, so obviously,
zoom brought her here
From your earth like the others.
- Mm-hmm.
Now that we know that,
We can use that
to gain advantage.
- What do you mean?
- We capture doctor light
and use her to lure zoom here.
- You are insane!
Okay, we are not
luring zoom anywhere!
- Apparently,
they know each other,
And jay is not a fan.
- Huh.
- Well, well, well.
Like everyone else, I assumed
earth-2 flash was dead.
Why am I not surprised
to find jay garrick here,
Still alive and in hiding
a full universe away from zoom?
- I'm not in hiding.
Zoom nearly killed me
and stole my speed
Before the singularity
pulled me here.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Well, whatever the case,
in your absence,
Zoom has only gotten
more powerful, faster.
Barry, you have to defeat zoom
now while you still can.
- No, this isn't the time
to be reckless.
We don't even know
why zoom sent doctor light here.
She's a thief,
not a killer.
- Zoom can make people
do things out of character.
Thief or not,
she'll kill you.
- All right, look, hey,
We can decide what to do
with light later.
First, we have to find her,
okay?
- [slurps]
- [sighs]
Hey, how did you know
That she was breaking
into the bank?
- I got an alert on my phone.
There's a little ring-a-ding
[imitates ring]
Every time, like,
there's a robbery at a bank.
- What?
- But you know what?
I think I can get
the s.T.A.R. Labs satellite
To scan for any irregular
solar radiation emissions
And we can find
doctor light's light.
- Okay, I'm gonna also call joe,
see if ccpd has any leads.
Why don't we keep them apart
until I get back?
- I am sure
that won't be a problem.
- [sighs]
[elevator bell dings]
- Hey!
- Hey.
- How's your science stuff?
- I finished it.
Um, did you get
your report done?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It wasn't as much fun
writing it by myself, but...
[laughs]
I'll see ya.
- Yeah.
Hey, do you ever feel
completely overwhelmed
By everything
that you have to do in a day
And it feels like
the one thing
That you actually want to do
is the thing that gets lost?
- I'm confused.
What?
- I've been thinking,
for a while now actually,
Would you want to get dinner
with me sometime?
- Yeah, this isn't gonna be
one those things
Where I get really excited
and then, you know,
More science stuff comes up,
right?
- No, no, that's not--
um, tomorrow?
We can grab an early dinner.
I don't want to wait anymore.
- Okay.
Looking forward to it.
- ♪ feeling better
'cause I'm over you ♪
♪ I learned my lesson,
it left a scar ♪
♪ now I see
how you really are ♪
♪ you're no good,
you're no good ♪
- Hey, harry.
Hey, over here.
Hey!
[volume lowers]
Come inside. Use my workroom.
Use my computer!
I don't care!
- Thanks.
- You and wells prime have
very different musical tastes.
His were better.
- This harrison wells and I
are very different
But similar in some respects.
I see he made
almost the same mistake I did
With the particle accelerator.
- He did a lot
of terrible things,
And none of them
were by mistake.
- What did he do to you?
I know he caused
the singularity,
Murdered barry's mother,
blah, blah, blah, blah.
What did he do to you?
You can barely
look me in the eye.
Why is that?
What did he do to you?
- He shoved his hand
through my chest.
He stopped my heart.
- [chuckles]
Ouch, okay, that would do it,
But you survived that.
- Only because barry
erased that timeline.
- I see.
Barry traveled in time.
- Twice.
- Hmm.
Here's how it is.
- What's the deal?
- You don't have to like me.
I don't like you,
But you have to work with me
to stop zoom and doctor light.
Can you do that?
- I guess we'll see,
won't we?
- I guess we will.
One more thing--
You said
you were going to re-task
The s.T.A.R. Labs satellite?
- To scan for solar emissions,
yeah, we're up and running.
- I'd like to examine
your program.
I want to see if it works.
- Don't worry.
It'll work.
Harry's starting
to get on my nerves.
- The silent alarm just went off
at the bank of central city.
- That's gotta be doctor light.
- Could be a trap.
- Barry, trust me,
doctor light is not a killer.
You can talk to her.
- Okay.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Looking for this?
I know zoom sent you here
to kill me.
Good news,
you don't have to do that.
- Not if I can get out of town
with that cash.
- And then what?
Zoom's not gonna like
that you ditched him, right?
My friends and I can help you.
- Nobody can protect me
from zoom!
- All right,
why don't we take it down
A lumen,
have a normal conversation,
All right?
Thank you.
Linda?
Linda park?
- How do you know my name?
- I don't understand.
- This was a mistake.
- [grunts]
[panting]
- Barry, what's happening?
- I can't see.
Guys, I can't see.
- I still can't see.
How long is this gonna last?
- You're suffering
from solar retinopathy.
Your retinas
are severely damaged.
You're lucky you're not
permanently blind.
- But with your rapid
regeneration abilities,
Your sight should return soon.
- 6.25 hours by my estimation.
All this could have been avoided
if you just stopped light
Instead of chitchatting
with her.
- She caught barry off guard.
- Always an excuse with you,
right?
He's the fastest man alive.
How could she possibly do that?
- Because light looks exactly
like my ex-girlfriend,
Linda park.
- That's why zoom sent her--
because he knew you'd hesitate.
- That means
zoom had to have known somehow
That linda was your ex.
- Which is why
barry has to act now,
Before zoom sends another double
from barry's life.
- All right, right now,
I'm more worried about linda.
When I saw who was
under the mask, I said her name.
What if light didn't even
realize that she had
A doppelganger here
until I accidentally told her?
- The first thing
that atom smasher did
When he crossed the breach
was to kill his doppelganger.
- Yeah, but light's
not like atom smasher.
- We should keep an eye
on your linda.
- All right, I'll go.
- Oh!
- Sorry.
- Bro.
- Barry!
- What? Ooh!
- Okay, okay.
You can't do anything
until your sight returns.
No, no, no, come on,
here's the little rail here.
I'll do it.
- I'll go with you!
- Hey, barry!
- Hey.
- I came as soon as I heard--
You look just like him.
- I'm guessing my counterpart
did something to offend her
As well?
- Her fiancé died
because of him.
- Oh.
- Iris, I know it's weird
seeing him.
- Yeah, it's just a lot
to process lately.
Wells, my mother.
- How are you doing with that,
by the way?
- I mean, now that she's gone,
Okay.
- Yeah, iris, um, look--
- Yeah.
[giggles]
- Thanks.
You know you can talk
to me about it.
- Yeah, I know,
but really, I'm fine, okay?
I should be asking
how you're doing.
[phone vibrating]
- that's me. I got it.
- Barry, let me help you.
- I got it.
- All right.
- [laughs]
Uh, "running a little late.
P."
Who's p?
- [sighs]
p.
That's patty.
- My dad's partner patty?
- Mm-hmm.
- What is she
running late for?
- Um, our first date.
- That's so great!
She's great.
- Yeah, no, patty's great.
I just, you know--
I doubt she's gonna give me
another shot
When I have to cancel on her.
- Don't cancel.
- I'm blind, iris.
A literal blind date.
It's not gonna work.
- Hey, we are in s.T.A.R. Labs.
Come on, there's gotta
be something here
That can help you
get through the night.
- Yeah.
- Or someone.
- Cisco, hey!
- To your left. Other left.
- Cisco.
[jazz music playing]
Sorry.
Ooh, sorry.
- Okay.
She's two steps in front of you.
- Nice glasses.
- Hey, hey!
- Touchdown.
- I'm so sorry I'm late.
- No, don't be.
You know, I actually judge
my dates on whether or not
They stand me up,
so you are off to a great start.
- What do you mean?
Who would stand you up?
- Oh, I have a reputation.
Not that kind of reputation.
That's not what I meant.
- [laughs]
that's embarrassing.
- You know, I actually--
I arrested a boyfriend once.
- Oh.
- A very ex-boyfriend,
while we were at dinner.
He got really wasted and decided
to insult the waitress,
So I cited him
for public intoxication.
- That is hilarious.
- Yeah.
[both laugh]
special.
So...
- Dude, she looks amazing.
You have to tell her
how amazing she looks.
- You look amazing, patty.
- Uh, thanks, I actually
had a really hard time
Trying to figure out
what to wear, like,
If I should wear a dress or if
this color was a little weird.
- No, you look great.
Um, yeah, no, that--
what would you call that color?
- Um, uh--
- I can't tell.
The feed's black and white.
- I don't know.
- Yeah, whatever it is,
that color should thank you
For wearing it.
- [laughs]
my man.
- Smooth.
- Not smooth.
[both giggle]
- Oh, wine list.
Here we go.
- Uh, yes, uh, got it.
Thank you.
Um...
Um, you know, why don't you--
- oop!
- Sorry.
- No, that's okay.
- The guy always picks.
Why don't you choose?
- Yeah, what do you want,
red or white?
- Whatever you'd like.
Uh, yeah.
- You got this.
Why do you even need me?
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Classic stakeout fuel.
- Yeah.
- You have coffee
on your earth, right?
- I think coffee's the one
constant in the multiverse.
[both laugh]
- So I don't mean to pry,
but when wells keeps referring
To you and zoom,
what's he talking about?
- I fought zoom many times,
Each time barely escaping
with my life.
[sighs]
so yeah.
Maybe I didn't always
confront him when I should have.
Truth is, zoom scared me.
He stole the most precious thing
from me: My speed.
I didn't want barry
to suffer the same fate.
- Well, maybe if you just
sat down with wells,
Talked to him about it...
- No, no, no.
Do not trust wells, caitlin.
The guy was more than happy
to make money
Off the meta-human problem
with his tech apps,
And now he's obsessed
with zoom.
Something has changed and not
just because I disappeared.
- Well, I don't trust wells.
I trust you.
- [laughs]
- [giggles]
So I've actually
been dying to ask you,
What was it like
to be struck by lightning?
- Mm.
Life-changing, to be honest.
- Did it hurt?
- I mean, all I really remember
is feeling electricity
Surging through my body.
It was an intensity
I had never felt,
Like I was instantly connected
to everything around me.
Then I woke up from a coma
nine months later.
- Waking up in the future
like that,
It's like time travel.
[all chuckle]
- Sort of, yeah.
- Yeah.
When I was nine,
I actually drowned.
I hit my head
on the diving board
And fell into the swimming pool.
Uh, my heart stopped for,
I think, two minutes
Until my dad rescued me
and saved my life.
Yeah.
So I guess we've both
cheated death.
[both laugh]
I've been through a few things
in my life
That taught me
not to be afraid of anything.
I think fear is
what holds people back
From being who they should be.
- Ugh, preach!
- [clears throat]
- Yeah, I'm still here,
creepin' and peepin'.
- You okay?
- Sorry, I just--
yeah, I really agree with that.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- I think another thing, too,
I think you can't see me.
- Abort!
- What? What do you mean?
- I think you can't see me.
Come on, I would not
be a good detective
If I couldn't have figured
this one out.
[both laugh]
I don't know.
- Uh, yeah.
- Yeah.
- I'm really sorry
and embarrassed
I didn't say anything.
I had my pupils dilated earlier.
- Barry.
- Oh, my god!
- Barry!
- And I really didn't want
to cancel.
[both laugh]
- barry! I lost my eyes!
- No, you have a great smile.
- Really, how do you know
I'm smiling?
- Just a hunch.
[laughs]
- Okay, so what else
is different about our worlds?
Do you have tahiti?
- Never been,
but I do love atlantis.
- As in the lost city submerged
in the ocean somewhere?
- Well, it's actually
above water on my earth.
One of my best friends
is from there.
- I would love to see it.
- It's special.
It's the kind of place
you never want to leave.
- [gasps]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Hello, gorgeous.
Everybody out, now!
- Go!
Go, go, go.
Go, move, quick.
- Except you.
- I don't think so.
- No, no, she's leaving
with us.
- Not today.
- What do you want from me?
- Your life.
- [groans]
doctor light.
- Oh, no. Go.
- [grunts]
- I've never killed
anyone before,
But it's not murder
if it's your double, right?
- Why are you doing this?
- It's the only way
that I can stay alive.
To become you.
I'm sorry, linda.
- [cries out]
- No!
How is this possible?
- You couldn't understand.
- Light!
- Flash.
I thought I took care of you
outside.
- [breathes heavily]
- Please don't let go.
I may trip.
[both laugh]
- okay, I won't. I promise.
Two more steps.
- All right. Missed one.
- There you go.
[both laugh]
It's funny how we skipped
Straight to
the hand-holding part.
[laughs]
- yes.
- We, uh, have arrived
at my car, so--
- Ah.
Well, do you think we've reached
the good night kiss stage?
- Um...
[gentle music]
♪ ♪
[both laugh]
- Um, this is burgundy,
by the way,
And you look great in it.
- Now you can see?
- I can.
- That must have been
some kiss.
- I guess so.
[phones vibrate]
- Sorry.
- No, it's mine too.
- Weird.
Cisco, hey.
- Sir?
- I saw myself.
How is that even possible?
- Sounds like
you have an evil meta-twin.
- [sighs]
and now larkin's dead
Because someone who
looks like me wanted to kill me?
- Linda, none of this
is your fault.
We're gonna figure it all out,
I promise.
- How you doing?
- I'm alive, thanks to iris.
Turns out she's as badass
with a gun as she is with a pen.
- Yeah, she is.
- I'm just happy
that you're safe.
- I've arranged
a security detail
Around the clock,
just to be sure.
- I can take you to them
if you're ready.
- Yeah.
[indistinct radio chatter]
- This is because of me.
I should've been here.
- Barry, you were blind.
There's nothing
that you could have done.
- You think this mask
can help us find that woman?
- Any evidence on this
is just gonna match linda.
I'll think of something else.
Light's not gonna kill again.
Caitlin, are you guys okay?
- Yeah.
- Barry, I'm sorry.
Doctor light's
never killed before.
I thought we could reason
with her.
- You cannot reason with someone
under zoom's influence,
And now a man is dead
because of you, garrick.
This whole thing
is because of you.
He doubts himself
because of you,
But believe me,
barry can do what you could not.
Barry can stop zoom.
- I spent two years
hunting zoom.
- Wrong!
Zoom hunted you!
You spent the last two years
of your life
Running, running,
running from zoom.
- Zoom would have killed me
just like he will kill barry
If you lead him down this path!
- No, because he is not
like you.
Barry runs towards danger,
not from it,
Because barry's not a coward.
[both grunting]
- Enough!
[sighs]
You were pretty hard on jay
in there.
- Maybe you should be
hard on jay too.
I've seen what you can do,
barry.
I've calculated how fast
you can run,
And you should be teaching jay,
not the other way around.
- You know, before I learned
that the other wells
Was the man who murdered my mom,
I looked up to him.
He was my mentor, actually.
- So my doppelganger,
A man who looks exactly like me,
Betrayed you.
- Mm.
- I'm sorry, I'm not him,
So you need to listen to me
when I say you can
Take care of zoom,
and all we have to do
[snaps fingers]
is capture doctor light.
- I thought about testing
the mask for light's dna,
But it would only have linda's.
- The mask, what mask?
- Light's mask.
- How did you get this?
- Iris shot it off doctor light
when she attacked linda.
- You know how to use the mask
to find light?
- Yes, I do.
All we have to do
is give it to him.
- Why me?
- Because you have powers.
- [laughs]
- What are you talking about?
- I developed this watch
to detect meta-humans.
[alarm beeps]
You never got an alert
on your phone.
You never reprogrammed
the s.T.A.R. Labs satellite,
And this is why.
[alarm beeps]
He's a meta-human.
- Cisco, have you known
about this,
And you didn't say anything
to us?
- Yeah, I was gonna tell you.
Thanks a lot, harry.
I swear I was,
but I didn't.
I was just--I was afraid.
- Afraid of what?
- Dr. Wells said the dark matter
gave me this, this gift.
He said that one day
I'd thank him for it.
What if I become like him?
- Cisco, I don't think
any of us would become evil
If we all of sudden got powers,
Even if they were
from dr. Wells.
- Yeah, maybe you're right.
I should have said something.
That's my fault.
I'm sorry.
- Well, you can be sorry later,
Because right now,
we have to use your powers
To find doctor light.
- Cisco, your abilities,
how do they work?
- Uh, I get
these feelings sometimes,
These vibes,
visions of the breachers
When they come to this earth.
I just--I'm not sure
what triggers it.
Sometimes it just happens.
Sometimes it's when I'm touching
something of theirs.
- Touch the mask.
You want to find doctor light,
do it.
- [exhales]
[exhales]
Hmm.
I don't think it's working.
- Try again.
Try again!
- Whoa.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [exhales]
I'm sorry, it's not--
- again!
- I can't control it.
- Because you're afraid.
- I'm telling you
I don't know how it works!
I can't just make it happen!
- I'm telling you, yes, you can!
- [inhales deeply]
[indistinct pa announcement]
South plaza train station,
platform 15.
- What are you waiting for?
- Oh, guys,
the platform's crowded.
Are you sure she's here?
- She should be wearing
a black trench coat.
- Black trench coat.
Found her.
Everybody, get out of here.
Go, go, hurry!
[dramatic music]
- Why won't you just
let me leave?
- I can't let you leave.
You killed an innocent man.
- That was an accident.
- Trying to kill linda park
wasn't.
- It's the only way
that I can be free from zoom,
Unless I kill you.
- I can't let you
do that either,
So we've got a problem.
- We'll see.
- Guys, should have talked
about this before I left,
But how should I stop her?
- Keep trying different angles,
barry.
Find her blind spot.
- [grunts]
I can't get close enough.
What should I do?
- I don't know.
- I gotta tell ya,
that's not exactly
The answer I was looking for.
- You need to confuse her.
Give her more than one target,
So she does not know
who to fire at.
- All right,
how do I do that?
- By running so fast,
you create multiple afterimages
Of yourself,
you create a speed mirage.
- A wha--speed mir--
I've never run that fast.
- Well, from what
I've been told,
You've traveled through time.
You'll be more than fast enough.
- Okay.
[grunts]
- Barry?
- I can't do it.
- Yes, you can, barry.
Hey, dr. Wells is right.
You are fast,
faster than I ever was
And better than I ever will be.
Don't let fear and doubt
hold you back like it did to me.
You're the flash, barry.
Show light what that means.
- [exhales]
- Where are you?
[grunts]
- I'm right here.
- Doctor light is safely locked
in the pipeline.
- Nicely done.
- Wells, thank you
for helping barry
Put away doctor light.
- So what now?
- [exhales]
we do what dr. Wells said.
We use her to lure zoom here,
end this once and for all.
- You can't be serious.
- More breachers are gonna come.
More innocent people may die.
I can't let this happen anymore.
- You're making a mistake.
Okay, zoom is a nightmare
you can't wake up from.
- I've already had
my worst nightmare.
His name was reverse flash,
And I spent a long time
being afraid of him.
I'm not gonna
be afraid anymore.
- Okay, barry.
You may be faster than me,
But you're not ready
to fight zoom by yourself.
- That's just it, jay.
I'm not gonna fight him
by myself.
I've got all of them
to help me.
I've got dr. Wells.
I've got you.
- No, I can't in good conscience
help you when I know
It'll only lead
to you losing your speed,
Or even worse,
Your death.
- Optimism must be
an earth-1 thing.
- You all need to ask yourself
why this man, for years,
Wouldn't admit
that he was responsible
For the particle accelerator
exploding underground.
He may not be harrison wells
from your earth,
But he has just as many secrets
as the one you knew.
- Jay, please don't go.
- I'm so sorry, caitlin.
- Have a nice day.
What can I get...You?
- Yeah, I know,
this is supes awkward,
Probably more for me
than for you,
But I just want coffee, okay?
Just three flashes,
one of them decaf.
That's it.
- Are you sure
that's all you want?
- Oh, that's funny.
You just want to shoot me down
again, huh?
- No, no, no, no.
What I mean is,
I just moved to central city,
And it's a pretty big change
from where I come from.
Everything here is
so big and new
And filled with meta-humans.
- Yeah, well, when you factor in
the size of the city,
The chances of running
into a meta-human are
Actually pretty low.
- [giggles]
I guess what
I'm trying to say is,
You kinda caught me off guard
the other day,
But now
I'm a little more prepared,
So I just want to make sure,
is coffee all you want?
- Hi, I'm cisco ramon.
- Kendra saunders.
It's nice to meet you.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I just--
I was getting used to jay
being part of the team.
- Well, look,
jay is a hero.
They always seem to show up
just when you need 'em.
- Yo, peep that.
- Wow!
- That's how it's done,
young padawan.
- Nice.
- Going on a date next week.
- Things are looking up
for cisco ramon.
- I guess so.
Still stuck
with these powers, though.
Just don't know
how to feel about 'em.
- Hey, look,
You don't gotta go
through it alone.
- And now you need a cool name.
- Oh, snap!
You're totally right.
[sighs]
I gotta think about this one.
Well, you know me.
It's gotta be perfect.
- Mm-hmm.
- Something that really sings,
You know?
Something like--
- Vibe?
- Vibe.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Your father
has abandoned you.
- You're lying!
My father's
the smartest man alive.
He'll find me, he'll save me,
and then he'll kill you.
- I will not die.
What happens to you
and your father
Is still to be decided.
- Greg, move your head.