My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened
up our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
No!
The man who saved Central City.
Why did you want to kill me?
- He promised he'd take me home.
- Who?
- Zoom.
- Wells killed my mother.
I don't know anything anymore,
especially who I can and can't trust.
S.T.A.R. Labs is now safer than ever.
People can't just waltz in and out of here.
Exactly.
- Stay where you are.
- My name is Jay Garrick.
Your world is in danger, Barry Allen.
Please, just let me explain.
I mean you no harm.
How do you know my name?
I know all your names. Caitlin Snow,
Cisco Ramon, Detective Joe West...
Enough.
That part about explaining
needs to happen right about now.
This world is in danger.
What other worlds are there?
When you created the
singularity above Central City,
you also created a breach
between my world and yours.
I'm sorry, a breach?
Yes, a portal connecting our two earths.
And what precisely is your concern?
A few days ago, you found a dead man
named Al Rothstein at the nuclear plant.
But then a different Al
Rothstein tried to kill you.
Atom Smasher.
That man was from my world.
If he got through the breach,
I suspect there'll be more to follow.
Okay, so, Jay, how exactly
do you know all of this?
Where I came from, I
was a speedster like you.
They called me The Flash.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
WEB-DL resync by kinglouisxx
- www.addic7ed.com -
Before I arrived on your earth,
I was in a fight with a man named Zoom.
Zoom?
I've heard that name before.
Atom Smasher, he said Zoom
sent him here to kill me.
Who is this guy?
He's a speedster, like you and me.
And fast. Maybe the fastest of all.
But evil.
He is an unstoppable demon
with the face of death.
We were engaged in our
fiercest battle ever,
racing throughout my city.
But I wasn't fast enough to stop him.
Zoom had me beaten.
Aah!
He was about to kill me
when suddenly there was a blinding light
and the sky split open.
A breach, between my world and yours,
caused from the singularity.
It pulled me in...
And I somehow ended up in your world.
Powerless. Unable to return home.
What do you mean?
I lost my speed.
How?
Not entirely sure.
So, you've been in Central
City for six months.
Why haven't you come to see us before?
I'm in a foreign world here, Detective.
I didn't know who you all were.
Took me that long to piece it all together.
So that's how you know our names.
You've been following us.
Look, I know how this sounds.
The existence of another earth,
you, another Flash,
it all came as an
unexpected shock to me, too.
I just wish there was something
I could do to convince you.
There is.
We're gonna... do some tests on you.
See if you're telling us the truth.
'Cause if you're not, this Zoom,
he's not gonna be your only enemy.
Where the hell am I?
You want to go home?
You only have to do one thing.
What's that?
Kill The Flash.
So, Mr. Garrick,
how long have you been
The Flash on your world?
Not long enough to call me Mister.
Please, it's Jay.
Jay, of course.
On my world, I've been The
Flash for about two years.
And how did you get your speed?
Not really sure. I was at my lab
trying to purify heavy water
without any residual radiation
when there was a blinding light.
I fell into a coma. When I woke up,
I could run almost as
fast as the speed of light.
Sorry. Did you say lab?
Are you a scientist?
Well, I certainly didn't
work at a place like this,
but, yeah.
I had a respectable solo operation.
Part-time chemist, part-time physicist.
Part-time superhero.
I can forget that superhero
part now, though, huh?
Is any of this possible?
A breach to another earth? It's not, right?
The contrary. Just recently,
the many-different-worlds
theory proposed interaction
with parallel universes was plausible.
Now, if what Mr. Garrick's saying is true,
that theory's been proven
sooner than we all thought.
It doesn't add up.
I'm gonna be honest here,
I don't understand what the hell
any of you are talking about.
So, Jay is saying he's from,
like, a mirror-world.
Or a parallel universe
that's very, very similar to ours.
Multiverse would be a more apt description.
- No, not helping.
- Bless your heart.
Okay, let's see if this helps.
This is our earth.
Let's call it Earth-1.
And this second Earth,
let's call it Earth-2.
This is where Jay claims to be from.
And these other earths, three, four, five,
to infinity, all of them,
are nearly identical to ours.
And they all exist at the same time,
giving us endless alternatives
to what we have here.
For example, the Joe West on
Earth-2, your doppelganger,
he might not be a detective.
He could be a Nobel
Prize-winning physicist.
And you, the Barry Allen here is The Flash,
but over there, he could be an electrician.
So, I'm assuming that the
people on all these other earths
work to make money to pay bills and such.
- I would imagine.
- So we got that in common.
I'm heading back to the station.
Call me when this makes
a little bit more sense.
I'm still trying to wrap my head
around this whole idea of time travel.
There is, one problem that remains.
If Mr. Garrick is telling the truth,
there is a breach
somewhere in Central
City that we need to find
and close for good.
Yeah, but how do we find it?
We don't even know what to look for.
Well, I... I suggest we
put our heads together
and come up with a solution.
Not literally, of course.
Those days are over.
- What'd you find?
- Well, Jay's heart rate is extraordinarily low.
And he does have regenerative capabilities.
Other than that, I'm
not seeing any evidence
of the Speed Force in his system.
We don't even have proof
that he's a speedster,
much less from another earth?
Not necessarily.
What does that mean?
Well, Jay doesn't know this,
but while I was testing his heart rate,
blood pressure, and motor responses,
I also measured his autonomic
reactions while we were talking.
You gave him a lie detector test?
And he passed it.
What if he's not a good guy,
and he just wants to find our weaknesses?
Keep running tests. See
what else you can find out.
Detective West, sir.
Yes, Officer...?
Spivot. Patty Spivot.
Captain Singh mentioned
there may be positions
available on your
anti-meta-human task force.
Yeah, everybody quit. There
is no task force anymore.
Well, I know someone who's
interested in being on it.
Me.
You do realize that
meta-humans have super powers, right?
And even if they didn't,
you wouldn't be a good fit for the team.
Because I'm a woman?
I didn't mean to imply that.
Good, because I know how
difficult this job would be,
but I think I'm an excellent candidate.
I triple-majored at Hudson in
biology, chemistry, and physics.
I'm in prime physical condition.
And I rated top of my
class in marksmanship.
Your class?
You don't even have your stripes yet.
Soon. Been on the job seven months, sir.
Are you aware of what happened
to my previous partner?
Detective Thawne, yes.
I know that he died and the one before him,
Fred Chyre, died, too, but
the one before that's not dead,
just transferred.
I'm sure it had nothing to do with you.
- Listen, Officer...
- Spivot, Patty Spivot.
Yes, Spivot, the answer's no.
All I'm asking for is a shot, sir.
- Please, just an interview.
- You just had the interview.
Didn't get the job.
I hope you understand
why we have to do this.
I get it, kid.
You're doing what you think you have to.
But you'll all realize
soon enough that this,
the tests, it's unnecessary.
I want to help you, Barry, not harm you.
You're not the first person
that's said that to me.
If what you told me about Zoom is true,
that he sent Rothstein here to kill you,
instead of locking me up in here,
you better start listening.
Because if Zoom is involved,
you are gonna need a lot
more than just me at your side
to stay alive.
Barry, there's a fire at the waterfront.
Fire department's en route.
I'm on my way.
Be careful.
That was the Flash.
That was a big fire.
It's out, Cisco.
Copy that, see you in a bit.
I thought it would be harder than this.
Barry?
Hello? Are you there?
- What was that?
- I don't know.
We need to find out.
- Bar.
- Hey.
What are we dealing with here?
Pfft. Well, definitely a meta-human.
Had a pretty solid look
at him between punches.
And he was, like, made of sand.
Sand?
- Okay.
- These walls are too porous
to pull any prints.
I can't even get one off the boat,
but check this out.
There's gasoline burns everywhere.
Water didn't go off.
Sprinklers weren't working.
This was arson.
Excuse me? Barry Allen?
- Yeah.
- Hi.
Two days in a row,
Officer. What a coincidence.
Or kismet, if you believe
in destiny or fate.
- I'm Patty. Patty Spivot.
- Hey.
I'm really excited to meet you.
- I'm a huge fan.
- Excuse me?
Your forensic reports.
I... I read them sometimes.
Who am I kidding? All the time.
I've actually read them all.
Wow, I don't think that I've read them all.
They're always so detailed.
You know, they really paint
a picture like you were
somehow actually there
when somebody was being brutally murdered.
Thank you.
Anyhow, I... I found, something.
Well, I think I found
something. It's just a theory,
- but I would like to show you.
- Great.
So, this right here is the
point of origin of the fire.
And look.
I don't know a sandblaster on the market
that can make a cut that precise,
so I think a meta-human may have done this.
Here. Took a sample for you.
There's also some fingerprints
on the back of the pipe.
You should have gone into CSI work.
I love the science, but out
here's where all the action is.
Isn't that right, Detective West?
The answer's still no, Officer S...
- Spivot, yeah.
- Spivot.
What was that about?
I'm trying to join the
anti-meta-human task force.
- Ah.
- But you heard him.
Hey, he's kinda like your dad, right?
So, do you have any advice on
how I can crack his no-code?
Yeah, I've been trying to
pick that lock since I was 11.
So, if you figure it out,
how about you let me know?
- Deal.
- All right.
It was nice to meet you, Barry.
Yeah, you too. Ahem.
His blood pressure is
low, his heart rate is low,
his oxygen levels are impressive.
Yeah, but nothing compared to Barry's.
No, but he's certainly in
the physical specimen range.
In more ways than one.
Oh, I wasn't paying attention.
That's enough for today, Jay.
Thank you.
Found it at the crime scene.
I mean, it's gotta be from the
meta-human that attacked me.
What is this stuff? Sand?
It's not sand.
It's human cells whose myosin II protein
have migrated to the cell's periphery.
Jay's a fellow science nerd.
Those cells have the ability
to rearrange and harden,
giving them the appearance of sand.
And how do you know this?
They belong to a meta-human
I've fought before named Sand Demon.
I know you're new here,
so I'm just gonna break it down for you.
The whole "naming the bad guys thing,"
that's my jam. But you know what?
I'm gonna let you have that one
'cause I actually kinda like it.
I'm not mad at that one.
Is that Barry's sweatshirt?
Oh, sorry.
It was all we could find, so...
I was gonna say, 'cause
it looks a lot smaller
on you, right?
I gotta do this thing.
So, who is this Sand Demon?
I don't know his name,
but I know how to stop him.
You know what?
I think we'll be fine on our own.
Look, Barry, I don't
know what else I can do
to prove to you I'm on your side.
I've been poked, prodded.
I even subjected myself
to a full body scan.
I was being thorough.
Sand Demon's from my world.
Let me teach you how to stop him.
Yeah, I don't need you
to teach me anything, Jay.
Zoom sent Rothstein here to kill you.
He must have sent Sand Demon
here to do the same thing.
Don't you get it? Anyone
close to the Flash,
all of you, are in a lot of danger.
All right.
If you're so good,
you would have caught him already.
Let's get Jay back to his cell.
Hey, beautiful mind,
I think you need to take a breather.
After some, lengthy calculations,
I believe I have discovered the key
to proving the proposed breach theory.
Exotic matter.
You mean, like,
transdimensional energy?
Precisely. Exotic matter,
transdimensional energy
will theoretically leak
from one universe into another.
Now, if this breach Mr.
Garrick's talking about
is real, if there is indeed
a hole in our universe
which leads to his earth...
We can make some adjustments
and upload an electrophotography program
to the S.T.A.R. Labs satellite
and essentially photograph
the exotic matter leak.
Thereby giving us the
locale of said breach.
Last time I saw the kit, it
was in the fabrication room.
- I shall return.
- Oh, hoo, hoo.
- Ha-ha!
- Getting gooseys.
All right.
Let's see what you're made of.
That's too much.
Barry?
I thought it'd be harder than this.
What's happening to me?
- Hey.
- I found our meta.
His name is Eddie Slick.
We tracked those prints to his address.
All right, where are
you? I'll meet you there.
Too late. He made me.
What? Joe?
So, can I be on your task force?
That look familiar?
How about now?
- What's it look like?
- A fire.
There you go, genius.
It's the fire you started
in the third ward last night.
Man, I didn't start no
fire there last night.
What? Were you out of town?
Your cat get sick?
Well, let me guess.
You don't start fires anymore.
You been rehabilitated.
Yeah, I done it before. So what?
I didn't do this one.
I always start a fire with
something that's hard to trace.
You know, like acetone or something.
Or maybe you don't need
to use accelerants anymore.
Iron Heights can hold people like you now.
You know that, right?
You think I'm one of
those meta-human freaks?
If I had powers, you don't
think I would have used them
to get away from you?
December, 2013. Where were you?
- Why?
- Answer the damn question.
- Where were you?
- Blackgate Penitentiary.
You don't believe me. Check your records.
Jimmy, I need you to
confirm something for me.
So, Joe told me what you did.
I'm impressed.
No, all I did was, you know,
run the other print
from the electrical pipe,
then track Slick down from there.
That's all.
Yeah.
How's it going with Joe?
You any closer to cracking his no-code?
Are you kidding me?
He's like the permission Sphinx.
Or like a magic eight
ball with just one answer.
Or like, you know,
the Bridgekeeper protecting the Holy Grail.
- What is your quest?
- Oh, to join your task force.
- No.
- Aah!
Well, maybe I can put
in a good word for you.
That would mean a lot to me, Barry.
- He needs me.
- Yeah.
Okay, so, Slick wasn't in Central City
the night the particle
accelerator exploded.
He's lying.
He's a dirt bag, and an arsonist,
but he's not lying about
this. He's not a meta, Barry.
Slick is the guy who jumped me.
Do you think it's possible
that the Slick in there has a...
A doppelganger? I don't know.
Yesterday's surprise broadcast
from a Star City vigilante
who is calling himself the Green Arrow
has spawned a massive outcry of
both support and dissenters...
Catchy.
I hate it when they put
a color in their name.
- Yo.
- The sample you gave us?
- Yeah.
Not sand.
Definitely human cells.
Yeah, I know. It's not him, I get it.
I hate to say it, but I
think this Earth-2 theory
- is starting to make sense.
- For real?
What, you think Jay is
lying about the Sand Demon?
I don't know. That's my point.
But I'm not gonna just believe
some guy that walks in here
and says a few things
that sort of check out.
Sort of? He was... he was right about Zoom.
We don't even know anything about Zoom.
What is Zoom? Is Zoom even real?
Right now, that's just, you know, a story
around a campfire.
I mean, have you discovered a breach yet?
Not yet, but we know how to now.
Have you found one thing to
suggest that Jay is a speedster?
Is the Speed Force even in his system?
It doesn't appear to be, no.
See?
We are scientists.
You are a journalist.
We test, we prove, we
report. That's what we do.
Except right now, nobody
here wants to do any of that
except me.
Can we have the room for a minute?
What has happened to you?
Are you... me?
Yes, you.
The you that I grew up with.
The you that is my best friend.
The you that became The Flash.
I haven't seen that
you in a very long time.
A lot's changed, Iris.
Yeah, it sure has.
You have learned how to not trust people.
What is it about Jay that you don't like?
I don't know.
It's because he reminds
you of Harrison Wells.
I trusted that man.
For months. We all did.
And you know what?
Eddie is dead.
Ronnie is dead.
And a whole lot of other
people in this city,
they are dead
because we trusted him.
I'm not gonna let us
make that mistake again.
Barry, not everyone is Harrison Wells.
Besides, you defeated him
because you trusted in people.
Because you believed in them.
This team that you have here,
they will follow your lead.
They'll do what you say.
But if they think that
you don't believe in them,
it won't be long before
they don't believe in you.
Get to walking.
I don't want to see your
ugly mug around here again.
Sayonara.
We didn't have probable cause.
I get it.
One thing you should know
about dealing with these meta-humans,
nothing is ever as it seems.
Speaking of which,
you're the only person here
who wants to be on my task force.
You want to tell me why you're
so hell-bent on being on it?
You want to tell me why
you're so hell-bent I'm not?
Didn't I just tell you
I didn't want to see your
ugly mug around here again?
Well, you're gonna have to, Detective West.
So I can get to the Flash.
I like you. You'll do the trick...
just fine.
Finally come to your senses?
Sand Demon kidnapped a police officer.
A woman that I know.
And you need my help?
I need you to help us save her.
Before something happens.
I guess you're gonna have
to trust me now, huh, kid?
We're looking for any structures
that promote humidity.
Greenhouses, grow rooms,
anything of the sort.
His body will literally start to fall apart
if he becomes dehydrated.
- Like dry sand.
- Exactly.
Sand Demon always attacks on two fronts.
He creates a diversion, then
strikes when you're distracted.
Okay, then what do we do?
We use your speed to get to him
before the distraction can happen.
Jay, how do I stop somebody
who can slip through my fingers?
The way I was never able to.
With lightning.
Yo, are you about to pull a Zeus right now?
What are you talking about?
Barry's gonna hurl lightning
from the energy he creates when he runs.
Because lightning plus sand equals...
Glass.
Time to learn something new, kid.
All right.
Choo!
Give me a sec.
Hey, are you good?
That was Singh.
CCPD still hasn't found anything yet.
Irony is, I didn't want Patty
to have anything to do with
the damn task force in the first place.
And she gets taken because of me.
No, no, no, this isn't
your fault, all right?
It's hard not to think that.
Well, look, we're gonna
find Patty, all right?
Whatever it takes.
Flash is coming for you, you know?
Yes, I'm sure he is.
You can't beat him.
I don't care what powers you have.
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Is that why you need to
build that concussive bomb?
Yeah, I know what it is.
I'm a cop. I've seen one before.
This isn't gonna kill the Flash.
I am.
This... is gonna kill you.
You know you got lucky, right?
You think you were chosen.
The rest of us don't mean anything.
But it's not true.
You were just at the right
place at the right time.
Getting those powers
didn't change who you are.
They only highlighted the worst
parts of who you already were.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe not.
Either way, you and the
Flash are about to find out
what those worst parts are.
I've searched all the vacant
buildings in Central City
and none of them fit the
description that we need.
And I've looked at any draw
upticks on the electrical grid.
Nothing out of the norm, I'm afraid.
We gotta do whatever it takes.
I'll be back.
Okay, come on.
Flash is coming for you, you know?
Yes, I'm sure he is.
You can't beat him.
I don't care what powers you have.
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
Oh, no.
Mr. Ramon?
What are you doing down here?
I figured out where Patty is.
And how exactly did you do that?
Just a hunch.
We gotta tell Barry.
Again.
I've been doing this for an hour.
It's not working.
It's because you're trying to rush it.
This is the one time you need to slow down.
Let the energy pass over you,
then simply direct it to
where you want it to go.
All right, Jay...
I don't know if I'm gonna get this in time.
You'll get it. I believe in you.
The last person that helped me like this
was a man that I looked up to.
Idolized.
He taught me how to get
faster, how to get stronger,
how to use my powers to save people.
That same man murdered my mother.
It's a tough break,
but I'm not him.
Yeah.
I know where they are!
The abandoned Woodrue grow house.
That's where Slick's keeping Patty.
Dude, great job.
And I was thinking, if I were Sand Demon
and I were attacking a
speedster on two fronts,
I would probably want to slow you down,
like, by using a concussive bomb
- or something like that.
- That's a good thought.
He's actually used one on me before.
His body absorbs the blast
so it doesn't affect him.
Well, kid, gonna have
to think of something.
You know what?
What if we give Slick a diversion?
He knows you, right?
You said you went up against him.
Yeah, but, Barry, I don't have my speed.
He doesn't know that.
You got your suit?
Sure. Well, except my helmet.
- Helmet?
- Silver kettle helmet?
Gold wings?
Don't tell me you guys found it.
Never thought I'd see that again.
It was my father's,
from the War of the Americas.
Did you just say War of the Americas?
I wish you would have just
told us you lost your helmet.
Would have saved us all a headache.
Well, sure you want to do this, Flash?
Yeah.
Let's go see what you're made of... Flash.
I'm in the security feed.
Go, Barry!
Is that you, Flash?
Found your way here.
I came quite a distance.
I thought you were dead.
You were wrong.
Like usual.
Let the girl go.
Have at it. But you touch her,
she goes boom.
And I think even you aren't
fast enough to save her.
Quite a bit slower on this
Earth, aren't you, Flash?
You don't have your speed, do you?
Slick's distracted. Go, Barry.
- Jay!
- Barry!
Patty's alive.
Must be my lucky day.
Zoom sent me here to kill you.
Now I get to kill The Flash from two worlds
before I go home.
He's choking Jay.
Barry, you gotta do something now.
Come on!
Aah!
You okay?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Nice shot, kid.
Flash?
Coming.
You're pretty good at this.
I've had a lot of practice
over the last year.
It was really courageous
doing what you did today,
standing up to the Sand
Demon without any powers.
Ah, Barry did all the work.
I just stood there and took a few punches.
It was more than a few.
This is a lot harder than I thought.
Losing something that was such a big part
of who I was for so long.
I lost something that
was a part of me, too.
It's hard,
but it gets easier every day.
You just have to find a new way to live.
Just because it's a different life
it doesn't mean it's a worse one.
And, speed or no speed,
in my book you were still a hero today.
I'm just sorry
we didn't all realize
it a little bit sooner.
Especially me.
I'll leave you two speedsters alone.
So, I hear they call you
"The Scarlet Speedster"
Yeah.
- What about you?
- "The Crimson Comet."
What is it with
alliteration and nicknames?
Hey, look, Jay...
So, thank you for all your help.
And for being so patient with me.
Nah, anytime, kid. You're a quick study.
Took me a lot longer to
learn how to toss lightning,
believe me.
Then I suppose I had the right teacher.
It's going to be a lot
harder to take down Zoom.
Who is this guy?
No one knows.
He showed up around the same
time as when I got my powers.
Killed a lot of people in my world.
I spent about two years tracking him down.
But he was too smart, too quick.
He's always one step ahead.
You really think he's just
bringing these guys here to kill me?
Zoom is obsessed with destroying me.
- Now he wants to destroy you.
- Yeah.
He needs to be the best.
And he will do whatever it takes
to ensure he's the only speedster.
In any world.
- Officer Spivot?
- Detective.
You're supposed to be home resting.
I'm okay, sir, really.
Look, I'm sorry you got
mixed up in all this mess
because of me.
It's not your fault.
Do you really think you have what it takes
to be part of my task force?
I know it, sir.
Well, I always check the jacket of anyone
I'm considering for it.
In my research on you,
I found out we got a mutual acquaintance.
Mark Mardon.
I need you to be honest with me here.
Why do you want to do this?
Mark Mardon killed my dad.
He had a little shoe
shop down on Chesterfield.
It was a cash business.
One night he went to Fairfield bank
to make his weekly deposit,
and the Mardon brothers showed up.
While he was waiting in line,
Mark shot my dad in the face
for a few hundred dollars.
Then a few months later, Mark
and his brother got powers.
Two murderers got superpowers.
So that's why I'm here, Sir.
That's why I'm so hell-bent
on being on your task force.
'Cause there's some bad people out there
and they can do anything.
And I may not have powers,
but I want to stop them.
You're the only person I know
who wants to do that, too.
Monday, 8:00 a.m.
Don't be late.
Late for what?
The task force, Detective.
Joseph.
Hi.
Been a long time.
Yeah, it has.
Why are you here?
Because you didn't return my calls.
And I wanted to see you.
And our daughter.
Any progress with the electrophotography?
The satellite picture of
the city's still rendering.
While we wait,
care to tell me what's going on with you?
What? Nothing.
Two hunches in one day.
Slick's locale,
and that he'd be using a concussive bomb
to thwart Barry.
Do I need to inform you of
the odds of such a prediction?
Something's happening to me.
I'm starting to perceive things.
Horrible things.
It started after Wells killed
me in the other timeline.
It came back when Atom
Smasher attacked on Flash Day,
and then again when Sand Demon showed up.
I get a vibe,
and then a vision of something
that's already happened,
and then it's gone.
That's how I knew where Slick was.
Cisco, this is amazing.
We... we have to study this,
figure out just what to do.
No, no, no, we're not doing any of that,
and we're certainly not
telling anybody, either.
Cisco, I would think you'd
be the one most intrigued
with knowing exactly what
this is and how it works.
I'm seeing things I don't want to see.
And knowing things I don't want to know.
I just want it to stop.
Professor, I don't want
anyone to know about this.
Not yet.
It's okay to be afraid, you know?
Wells told me this was my future.
That he gave me this power.
But everything he did was evil.
That's what scares me, Professor.
You have to promise me
you won't tell anyone about this.
I promise.
Oh, wow.
It appears that while
we were indeed successful
in closing the singularity,
there was an unfortunate side effect.
- What are you talking about?
- Using electrophotography,
Cisco and I were able
to search Central City
for any signs of energy entering our earth
from another dimension.
From any "breaches" , as
Mr. Garrick described them.
But, of course, there
isn't just one breach.
There's 52 of them scattered
throughout the city.
These breaches are
pockets of time and space
folded into and upon itself.
But the most significant
breach of all appears to be
this one.
And where exactly is that located?
It's here, inside S.T.A.R. Labs.
And just beyond that breach
is an entirely diff... fferent...
Professor?
Professor!
I'd like to personally welcome you
to the Scientific and Technological
Advanced Research Laboratories,
or, as it's more commonly known,
S.T.A.R. Labs.
Founded in 1991, S.T.A.R. Labs is leading
the world in exciting new
technological discoveries
that, as our motto suggests,
are truly bringing us
tomorrow's world today.
Specializing in artificial intelligence,
genetics, and meta-human stu...
Oh, are we in for an unexpected treat.
It is my absolute honor to
introduce you to the founder
of S.T.A.R. Labs,
the savior of Central City,
Dr. Harrison Wells.
Hello, kids.
- synced and corrected by chamallow -
WEB-DL resync by kinglouisxx
- www.addic7ed.com -