- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
- Previously on "The Flash"...
- I stabbed your mother
in the heart
and I was free.
[gunshot]
- Eddie is his ancestor.
If Eddie dies,
he'll never be born.
He's being erased
from existence.
- Gideon?
- Yes, Professor Thawne?
- Where the hell am I?
- I was accepted
into the forensic science
program
at Midway City University.
I'm leaving Central City.
- Joe, you have a son.
- Hi, I'm Wally.
I'm Francine's son.
These races?
That's the only way
that I can pay
for my mom's hospital bills.
- Jesse's my daughter.
Zoom has her.
- Daddy?
Please help me.
Don't let him take me
back there.
- I would do anything
to get you back.
[bone snaps]
- There are many reasons
why we run,
but usually it's to avoid
what's right in front of us...
A decision to be made
or a dilemma we have to face.
Lately, for me, it feels like
running is all I've been doing.
What you got for me, Cisco?
- You've been playing
Good Samaritan all morning.
Take a break.
Are you sure you don't want
to get to CCPD,
give Patty your attention?
- No, I can see her later.
- 'Cause we cannot afford
to waste any more time.
- What, 'cause we've just been
sipping Mai Tais
since you got here?
- I don't know what you been
sipping since I got here,
but Barry needs to get better,
stronger, faster.
We need to train
to prepare for Zoom.
- Oh, I see.
You haven't had your coffee
this morning.
- I had my coffee this morning.
Don't slurp.
- [slurps coffee]
- Don't. Don't.
Don't.
- [extended slurp]
[computer chiming]
Runaway chemical transport truck
heading south on Kester.
- On it.
[dramatic music]
[sirens wailing]
¶ ¶
Hey, I can't stop the truck!
Somebody rigged it!
Sorry!
- You can't let
that truck crash.
If you do, you'll take out
a whole city block.
- Great.
Thank you.
Thank you for that.
[honks horn]
[horns honking]
That was close, that was close.
- Oh, and the plot thickens.
Uh, dead-end up ahead.
You got to get out of there!
- Oh, come on.
Yes!
[sirens wailing]
¶ ¶
That one was a little close.
[tire iron clangs]
- Nice!
Now can you please,
please take a break?
How's that for training?
- Great.
- Look, we're gonna catch Zoom.
We got Turtle locked up
in the pipeline.
All we got to do is use him
to figure out how to steal
Zoom's speed and then we'll get
your daughter back.
- That might take longer
than we thought.
- Why's that?
- Because Turtle's dead.
¶ ¶
- Barry, we need you
back here stat.
- All right.
I'm on my way.
¶ ¶
- Gideon.
- Was the trip a success,
Professor Thawne?
- I believe it was.
I've finally figured out
what time period
The Flash is from.
Now let's figure out
a way to get home.
- He better not be pulling
a Juliet.
Yeah, that's right.
I see plays.
- He's dead, Cisco.
- How'd this happen?
- Preliminary brain scan shows
an acute brain aneurysm.
- The night we captured him.
How's that for timing?
- What does that mean?
You think I did this, Garrick?
This man is the key
to us stopping Zoom,
the key to me saving
my daughter.
Why would I want that?
- Never understood why
you do anything, Harrison.
- That's fine with me, Garrick.
- Guys, look.
We need to figure out
how to stop Zoom.
Everything we've tried so far
has failed.
We need to start thinking
outside the box.
I mean, we haven't even
figured out how
to close the breaches yet.
Maybe that's where
we should start.
- That's a good idea.
- I'll get on that.
- I'll help.
[cell phone vibrates]
- I've got to get to the CCPD.
I'll check in
with you guys later.
- Okay.
Every time you think
that Wells is on your team,
something happens
that makes you doubt it.
- Hey, I just wanted to see if
you could run this trace for me.
Someone messed with an ethanol
transport truck this morning.
They cut the brake line and
tampered with the gear shafts.
- Okay, yeah.
- Okay.
Wow.
Backed up, huh?
- I am, yeah.
- Yeah, I guess I'll find out
what that's like
once I finish CSI school.
- Yeah, you will.
- [whispers] Yeah.
- I guess.
- Look, Barry,
I know that you're upset,
but I was hoping it wouldn't
be like this between us.
- Uh...
[stammers]
I mean, what did you think
it was gonna be like?
- I ju... I just thought we could
at least talk before I left.
- You're moving.
I don't know.
I mean, it just doesn't feel
like there's much
to talk about now, right?
- I guess not.
Hi.
- Hey.
I sort of overheard some
of that.
- Mm-hmm.
Um...
Patty's going to CSI school
in Midway City.
She's moving in two days.
- I mean, you don't
have to let her leave.
- She's wanted to be a CSI
her whole life.
I'm not gonna stand
in the way of that.
Hey.
What's wrong?
- Just went to see Francine
and, uh...
she doesn't have much time.
I already said my good-byes,
if...
If you want to do the same.
[keys clacking]
[computer chimes and trills]
- It's not gonna work.
Closing the breaches, that's
like solving Einstein's riddle.
- I solved Einstein's riddle
when I was ten.
- Yeah, well,
maybe Earth-2 Einstein
wasn't as clever as ours.
- You realize this Earth
is my Earth-2, right?
- Listen to this.
What if we can figure out how
to control my powers?
We could find Zoom,
get the jump on him.
- That's a good idea.
You should get on that.
- I need your help, Harry.
- What you need, Ramon,
is to figure out
what triggers your vibes.
- Exactly, and I don't know
what triggers them.
It's completely inconsistent.
Sometimes it's when I touch
something that belongs
to a breacher,
sometimes it just happens.
- There's always a cause.
Cause, effect.
Doesn't take Einstein
to figure that out.
- Okay, so what is the cause?
You saw when I tried to vibe
Dr. Light,
when I tried to vibe you,
took a while to work.
- Yes.
Yes, it did.
Meet me in the Time Vault.
- For what?
[sighs]
[ominous music]
¶ ¶
Hello?
Harry?
¶ ¶
Of course,
now he's gonna make me wait
in this freaky-ass braille room.
¶ ¶
- Hi, Cisco.
- [high-pitched scream]
Stop!
Don't do that!
[grunts]
- I figured out your trigger.
A rush of adrenaline.
Dopamine floods the brain.
And the quickest way
to achieve that result...
¶ ¶
Fear!
[dramatic music]
- Do not move!
- You can't be.
¶ ¶
- What did you see?
- The Reverse-Flash.
He's here.
[alarm blaring]
[dramatic music]
- Oh, my God!
- Christina McGee.
- Who are you?
- You're coming with me.
Flash.
- Eobard Thawne.
- You know who I am?
- You died!
- Good to know.
And guess what, Flash.
I know what time period
you're from.
So that means very soon...
you will die.
¶ ¶
- No.
- You okay, Bar?
- I'm good, yeah.
It's just a lot.
- Eddie Thawne died,
so Eobard Thawne
should have been erased
out of existence, right?
- Not necessarily.
It's possible Eobard was
in the Speed Force,
protecting him
like a bomb shelter,
keeping him alive
and his time line intact.
It's what's known as
a "time line remnant."
- A what now?
- Here, let me... show you.
This?
This... is now.
Here, today.
This is the time
Thawne comes from.
This is the moment you all
erased him from existence,
but since Thawne
is from the future,
this is where
his time line begins.
That's why he's still alive.
This Thawne has not yet
traveled back
in time to kill Barry's mother.
He's here now in this
time period for the first time.
"Time line remnant."
- Explains why
nothing's changed.
- Yeah, it also explains why
he didn't know my name
or that we have met before.
- To him, you hadn't.
Not until the future.
- If Thawne dies before
he can time travel again,
will that save Barry's mother?
- No.
That's not how it works.
In our time line,
Barry's mother is already dead,
and her death is a fixed point.
Nothing can change that.
- All right, well,
I'm gonna end this,
him, in this time
once and for all.
- Let's find Dr. McGee,
then we'll figure out
what to do about Thawne, okay?
I got to go check on Iris.
- Ramon.
- Caitlin, I know you're worried
about Dr. McGee,
but we're gonna get her back.
- It's not that.
It's Jay.
- What about Jay?
- He's sick,
and it's getting worse.
When Zoom stole his speed,
it affected him
on a cellular level.
We need to do
something about it.
- All right, like what?
- I think we should replace
his dying cells
with healthy ones
indistinguishable from his.
- How do we do that?
- We find his
Earth-1 doppelganger.
- There.
- Tachyons?
A man in a yellow suit tried
to steal
another tachyon prototype
last year.
- I must have gotten stuck here
once before
and not been able to access
enough of the Speed Force.
Tachyons should do it.
I want you to isolate
and accelerate
their energetic properties
for me.
- I don't know if I can do that.
¶ ¶
- If you want to stay alive...
learn.
¶ ¶
- Franny.
- Hey.
- How you feeling today?
- Better now.
- I'm gonna let you two talk,
okay?
- Okay.
- Can I get you anything?
- Oh, just that brother of yours
so all of us can be together
for the first time.
- Yeah, he should be here.
- His mother is leaving him.
Can't blame him for
being angry about that.
I just wish he'd get
all that anger out
while I'm here to help.
Same thing goes for you, Iris.
One thing you learn
when you're dying
is not to hold anything back.
You want to say something to me?
You need to say it
while you can.
[somber music]
¶ ¶
- I have so many great memories
from when I grew up.
Now when I think about
those memories,
I can only wonder
what it would have been like
if you and Wally would have
been there.
[voice breaking]
I'm not angry at you anymore
for what happened.
I just wish you would have
come back to us a lot sooner.
¶ ¶
Because I would have
forgiven you then...
just like I'm forgiving you now.
- Mm.
- [sobbing] I'm sorry.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
[sighing]
¶ ¶
- [sobbing]
I don't know why
this is so hard.
I barely even know her.
¶ ¶
- The facial recognition
software at S.T.A.R. Labs
didn't find anything either.
- No, but there's still
more databases to check.
We'll find his doppelganger.
- Thanks, Barry.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
Hi, Caitlin.
- Hi.
- Uh, can we... talk?
- Uh, yeah, yeah, for sure.
Um, I'll let you know
what I find.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
What's up?
- I didn't know you were working
with S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Yeah, um, uh, yeah.
Joe and I help out
every once in a while.
- Really?
Yeah, I probably shouldn't
tell you this,
but there's a lot of weird stuff
that happens over there.
- [chuckles]
Is that what you came
to tell me?
- Um...
[sighs]
You're just rolling with
the whole "me leaving" thing.
- Yeah, well, I don't know
what to tell you, Patty.
Everyone in my life that I love
leaves at some point.
Kind of getting used to it.
- You... never told me
you loved me.
- Yeah, I guess I don't get
that chance now.
- I don't understand.
What is it?
What's going on with you?
Why are you being like this?
- My life is complicated,
and I don't want you
to have regrets, all right?
I don't want you to miss out
on something that you've
always wanted to do.
And I wish that
things were different
for both of us.
You know, but they're not.
Sorry.
- Me too.
¶ ¶
- So what did you do
to my goggles?
- I added a wavelength trigger
to stimulate the fear receptors
in your brain.
Then I took what you already had
to induce slow-wave sleep,
upgraded it to get you
to stage-four sleep.
- [groans]
- No, this is good.
This will give us more control.
- Okay.
- Now I'll be able to dictate
how long you vibe for.
Put 'em on.
- What am I gonna see?
- I don't know.
Never done this before.
You'll have to tell me so I can
steer you where you need to be.
Ramon, you want to find
Reverse-Flash,
put on the goggles.
- Okay.
- Attaboy.
- [sighs]
- Go ahead.
[goggles power on]
[indistinct voices echoing]
- Oh-ho-ho, yeah, man.
I'm in full-on vibe mode
right now.
- What do you see?
- It's hard to explain.
It's different events.
Different events in time.
- Concentrate on
The Reverse-Flash.
- Okay.
I see him.
- Move toward him.
- Okay, now what?
- Try to picture him
with Christina McGee.
- Where the hell am I?
- It's charged.
You can go now.
You said you'd release me.
- Yes, I did.
Didn't I?
- No!
[gasping]
- Well, what is it?
- She's dead.
- Dr. McGee is dead?
- Harry and I were trying
to hone my powers to find Zoom,
and then we ended up using them,
finding The Reverse-Flash,
and that's when
I saw him kill her.
And then he left.
- He left?
What do you mean, he left?
- McGee built him
some kind of speed machine
and he ran into and got flung
back to the future.
- [sighs]
- You'd need superluminal energy
to send someone through time.
- You mean like tachyons?
- Tachyons.
- We can track their location
once they've been activated.
[computer trilling]
Anything?
- Nothing.
- Cisco, you're sure
that's what you saw?
- I'm positive.
- All right.
- What else did you see?
- There was all sorts
of weird tech everywhere.
There was a clock.
- What time did the clock say?
- 9:52, I think.
How... how is that relevant?
- It's 6:00 now.
- Are you telling me
I can see the future?
- That's exactly what
I'm telling you.
- Those goggles are getting
named immediately.
- But that means
Dr. McGee is alive.
- That's right.
- Yeah, okay.
We have 3 hours,
52 minutes to find her
and stop Reverse-Flash.
Let's do it.
[rousing music]
- Spivot.
- Hey.
- Can't get away
from those case files, huh?
- Oh, just following up
on a hunch.
- You're gonna miss the action,
right?
- Maybe.
A little.
- I'm gonna miss you.
- Miss you too.
It's nice to know someone will.
- Wait, we talking about Barry?
'Cause it sounds like
we're talking about Barry.
- [sighs] He kept telling me
there was stuff
he couldn't share with me and
I've been going a little crazy
trying to figure out
what that stuff is.
- Yeah, Barry's not great
at sharing.
- Neither are you.
- What do you mean?
- Barry just told me that,
you know,
sometimes he helps you out
with S.T.A.R. Labs stuff.
- Yeah, he does when he has
a few extra minutes.
- I didn't know that.
I mean, the whole time
I've been working here
you never mentioned it to me,
but then I realized why.
I went through some
of Barry's old cases.
All of them involved
The Flash saving the day
with details that Barry couldn't
have possibly even known.
- That's weird.
- Yeah, it...
It is weird.
The only thing
that does make sense
is that Barry is The Flash.
- Have you ever seen Barry run?
He waddles
like a slow-ass duck.
There's no way
he's The Flash, Patty.
- You know,
when I started this job,
you told me I had to
learn how to lie to do it.
You're a terrible liar, Joe.
See you.
- Nice nitrous kit.
You're gonna get caught
one of these days.
You know that, right?
Get thrown in jail?
- I'll stop racing when these
hospital bills stop coming in.
- I saw Mom today.
She says you haven't been by
in a while.
- Yeah, she knows why.
- She thinks it's because
you're angry with her.
- I have every right
to be angry.
Nothing for 20 years,
then out of nowhere,
she tells me I have a sister,
I have... I have a father.
- Yeah, the same thing happened
to me too, remember?
But that shouldn't keep you
from seeing her
before you can't anymore.
- No.
Look... that's not what it is.
- Then what is it, Wally?
- I got to go.
- Last year, my fiancé died...
unexpectedly.
One moment he was here,
the next... gone.
I didn't get a chance
to say good-bye to him,
to tell him everything
that he meant to me,
that he was my world...
that he was loved.
But today I got to say good-bye
to your mom.
My mom.
And it helped us both find peace
with what happened
to our family.
Wally, don't make a mistake
you're gonna regret
the rest of your life.
Go see your mom
while you still can.
[somber music]
¶ ¶
[computer trilling]
- No sign of tachyon activity.
- We're running out of time.
We've got to find them.
- It'll take a few minutes for
the device to reach full power
once it's activated,
but when we find it,
you're gonna have
to get there fast.
- Hey, Barry.
- Yeah?
- Have you found out anything
else about Jay's doppelganger?
- There's no Jay Garrick
on this Earth.
- That's so weird.
Everyone has a doppelganger.
- Maybe just ask Jay.
He's a good guy.
Just ask him.
I'm sure he'll tell you.
- Okay.
- Hey.
Hold on.
What's up?
- We got a problem.
Patty knows you're The Flash.
- What?
- She caught me off guard.
I mean, I played it off,
but come on, she's a smart girl.
Anyway, she was going through
some case files
and you were acting
all squirrely.
- This is my fault now?
- No, it's nobody's fault.
- Oh, my God.
- Maybe you should tell her.
- No.
- Patty's trustworthy.
- It's not even about that, Joe.
I-I don't want another person
that Zoom or Reverse-Flash
or any of these meta-humans
can use against me.
I don't want it.
Patty can't get hurt over this.
[alarm blares]
- Tachyons!
87th and Avenue J.
[dramatic music]
Must be one of Mercury Labs'
off-site facilities.
- Hack into their se...
- I've hacked in
the security feed.
- And once that...
- I'm one step ahead of you.
[computer chimes]
Uh-oh.
Barry, hurry up!
- It's charged.
You can go now.
You said you'd release me.
- Yes, I did.
Didn't I?
- He's gonna kill her.
¶ ¶
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay, get out of here,
all right?
Go! Go!
¶ ¶
- That was my way home!
- You're not going anywhere.
¶ ¶
- You haven't won here, Flash.
I'll find another way back.
- You're gonna have to get
through me first.
- You really think
you're fast enough to stop me?
- Let's find out.
- Catch me if you can.
¶ ¶
[computer beeping]
- Oh, it's on.
¶ ¶
[computer beeping]
- [grunts]
- Get him, Bar.
¶ ¶
- [grunts]
- Not fast enough, Thawne.
[grunts]
I will never lose to you again.
[both grunting]
¶ ¶
This war between us,
it ends now!
- [screaming]
- Bar, you got to stop!
Bar, don't kill him!
Just bring him in!
- [groans]
¶ ¶
- Get the cell ready.
- Hey, he can't...?
- Phase his way out?
No, he can't do that.
- It's the same cell we used
to hold Dr. Wells last year.
- Barry, where you going?
- I'm going down there.
- No, you're not.
The more he learns about you,
the more you will alter
the time line.
- He killed my mom!
- He's from the future.
He hasn't done that yet.
He doesn't even know
you're The Flash,
and you need to keep it
that way.
- You already said
that his mother's
gonna die no matter what we do.
- There's ramifications any time
anybody messes
with the time line,
and it's impossible to predict
what those ramifications
are going to be.
- Barry, you caught him
and you stopped him
from killing Dr. McGee.
In my book, that's a win.
- This doesn't feel like a win.
[cell phone vibrates]
I got to go.
[tense music]
¶ ¶
- So, what'd you want
to talk to me about?
[light rock music playing]
- My dad had multiple sclerosis.
Every day for years, I watched
this amazingly strong man fight
for his life... and lose.
So, I can't sit by and watch
another man I care about
fight for his life
and not do something about it.
I tried to find
your doppelganger.
Same DNA,
same cellular structure.
I could replace your dying cells
with his living ones.
But... you don't have
a doppelganger on this Earth.
- Caitlin, there is
a good explanation.
Meet me at Hofherr Park tomorrow
and I'll show you.
- Why can't you just tell me?
- Because you need to see
for yourself.
[dark music]
¶ ¶
- How'd you get your suit
in your ring?
- Who are you?
- My name is Cisco Ramon.
- And we know each other well,
don't we?
We have a history together.
- You could say that.
- And that's all you want
to know?
How I got my suit in my ring?
- I want you to know
that I'm the one
who figured out you were back.
I helped stop you.
Me.
- And how'd you do that?
- I have powers.
And I helped track you down
and I put you in here.
¶ ¶
- That's quite the ability
you've been given.
- And here's what's
so ironic about it.
You gave me these powers.
Have fun thinking about that
while you rot away in this cell
that you helped me build.
Bye, Felicia.
[suspenseful music]
¶ ¶
[plaintive music]
- Hey.
- Got your text.
- I wasn't sure
that you would see me,
considering you've been
avoiding me lately.
- Patty, I haven't been
avoiding you.
- No, just, uh, busy...
you know, speeding around
Central City.
¶ ¶
I know you're The Flash, Barry.
- Patty, come on.
- Please don't make me feel
any more stupid
than I already do.
Look, I'm a detective
and I should have known.
I was just...
I was so smitten with you.
- Okay, look, what...
What you're saying, it's insane.
- Look, you don't have to
lie to me anymore, okay?
I understand... I understand why
you didn't want to tell me.
I understand why
you've been distant.
Look, I understand everything.
But just tell me the truth now.
Just be honest with me.
Just... admit to me
you're The Flash and I'll stay.
- I can't do that.
I'm not him.
¶ ¶
- It's too bad.
It would have been nice to stay.
[voice breaking]
Fight crime during the day
and be with you at night.
[crying]
But I was... I was wrong.
Take care, Barry.
¶ ¶
- Is that you, Flash?
- Why do you hate me so much?
- I didn't always.
[ominous music]
I was obsessed with you.
For so long,
I wanted to be The Flash.
I spent years figuring out
how you came to be.
Duplicated the reaction...
and it worked.
[chuckles]
I became like you.
- Right, so what happened?
- This ability to travel
through time revealed a truth.
My fate was to become
your greatest enemy.
I was never going to be
The Flash,
so I became the reverse
of everything that you were.
The more people you saved,
the more you were loved,
the more I had to take from you.
- That is why you killed
my mother?
That's why you ruined my life?
Because you couldn't be me?
- I became better than you!
I am the one thing
you cannot stop, Flash!
- No, no, no.
Not anymore.
Our race is over.
And you lost.
- I've learned what time period
you're from, Flash.
And one day soon,
I'll learn your name.
¶ ¶
Caitlin: We need you
in the cortex now!
¶ ¶
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
- What's happening?
- He's experiencing
an uncontrollable amount
of electrical energy
in his brain,
putting him in a prolonged state
of chronic seizing.
- What?
Can you stop it?
- I don't know.
- Hold him down!
- We're trying!
- Sedate him, Snow, now!
- Come on! Come on!
- Benzodiazepine.
This should do it.
[dramatic music]
¶ ¶
- Finally.
- [gasps]
- Oh!
What?
- What was that?
- What's going on?
Where the hell am I?
- Cisco!
- It's the time line.
- What?
What are you talking about?
- When you... when you captured
Reverse-Flash,
we ruptured the time line.
That's what this...
All the blood and the seizures
and that and all...
Cisco is being affected to... to...
By the changes to the time line.
The changes to the past
or the changes to the present...
This is what this is.
We need to do something.
We need to do it fast.
- Like what?
- We need to restore
the time line.
Barry, you need
to get Reverse-Flash
and send him back to the future
as quickly as possible.
- What? Are you...
- Barry...
- I just caught him!
You want me to let him go?
- Keeping him here
is killing Cisco!
- Barry, if this is the only way
we can save him,
you got to do it!
You got to let go of Thawne!
- I can't.
Okay, all right, look.
I destroyed the tachyon drive
in the speed machine.
There's no way it'll reach
a speed necessary
to send him back home.
- You can.
- What?
- Your speed coupled
with Thawne's speed,
that'll be enough to catapult
him through the time continuum.
You can do it.
¶ ¶
- All right.
All right.
Let's do it.
- Time to send you home.
- The time paradox.
Yeah.
You've all messed with something
you don't understand.
- Can you do me a favor
and just shut up?
- [laughs]
And how exactly are you
going to send me home?
- Don't worry about it.
- You fixed Dr. McGee's
tachyon device?
- No, I came up
with a different method.
¶ ¶
- Is that so?
- Uh-huh.
- Who are you?
¶ ¶
- No one of consequence.
- No.
I doubt that.
¶ ¶
I win again, Flash.
- All you have to do is provide
him with enough momentum
to get him past
the space-time barrier.
- All right.
- Hey, listen to me.
Thawne knows about you.
Right here, right now.
This is where he learns
about you, all of you.
It's how he knows about
S.T.A.R. Labs,
how he knows about me...
The Harrison Wells
from this Earth.
And there's nothing
I can do about it.
There's nothing you can do
about it.
This is his origin story,
and it's going to happen
no matter what you do.
But right here, right now...
you can send him back
to his time.
You can save your friend.
You can save Cisco
and then move on with your life.
- This could be a good thing.
You can finally let go of him.
- I could throw him
three centuries from now.
He'll always be a part of me.
¶ ¶
Time to send you back
where you belong.
¶ ¶
- We'll meet again soon, Flash.
- I know.
And every time,
I'll be ready for you.
¶ ¶
[suspenseful music]
- Hurry.
¶ ¶
- He did it.
[dramatic music]
¶ ¶
- He's gonna be okay.
- I don't understand what
we're doing here.
- Well, just like you,
I thought that if I could find
my doppelganger on this Earth,
I could replace my damaged cells
with some of his healthy ones.
And believe me,
I was just as shocked as you
when I couldn't find
a Jay Garrick anywhere
on this planet.
Took me a while
to figure it out...
but eventually I found him.
[plaintive music]
His name is Hunter Zolomon.
- Hunter Zolomon?
Why doesn't he have
the same name as you?
- From what I could gather,
his mother died
during childbirth.
He bounced around
from family to family,
but eventually was adopted
and raised by the Zolomons.
¶ ¶
- But why does that mean
he can't help you?
- My DNA was mutated
when I became a speedster.
There's only one way to reverse
what's happening to me.
If we can catch Zoom,
I can get my speed back.
- Then let's finally figure out
the best way to do that.
¶ ¶
[keys clacking]
[knock at door]
¶ ¶
- Wally, hi.
- Hey.
- Um, do you want to come in?
- No, I-I can't stay.
I just...
I wanted to tell you
that I'm gonna take your advice
and go see my mom.
- Okay.
- Iris, I was...
I was wondering
if you would come with me.
- Yeah, yeah, I would...
I would love that.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
Um...
¶ ¶
- [groans]
My head feels like
it's in a vise.
What happened?
- I think you vibed
one too many dimensions.
- Maybe I should stop
doing that.
- [laughs]
Yeah, he's gonna be fine.
- How did you, um...
get the vibing to stop?
- We sent Thawne back
to his time.
- You let him go?
- I couldn't let him take
another person I cared about.
¶ ¶
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Okay, I think I need
a Big Belly burger.
Anyone?
- I'm good, thank you.
- Yeah, no pickles.
- Two triple triples, please.
- You got money?
- Mmm.
- Rest up, all right?
I'll be out here.
- So, Patty... she's on a train
to Midway City right now, huh?
- Mm-hmm,
I had to let her go too.
- Mm-hmm, I was thinking about
what you said,
that part of being The Flash
is that you have the ability
to do amazing things
that nobody else can do.
And we see now
that a hundred years from now,
you'll still be doing them.
But the other part is,
you're gonna be loaded
with sacrifices,
and you're gonna have
hard choices to make,
and there's gonna be a lot
of things where eventually
you'll have to let 'em go.
You got to be ready for that.
- I am.
I'm ready.
- That's my boy.
[cell phone vibrates]
- That's weird.
Hey.
Patty: Barry, I'm on the train.
There's a... there's a man
with a gun.
- All right, hold on.
I-I-I'll get you help.
[dramatic music]
¶ ¶
Is everyone okay?
- Everyone's fine.
It was a false alarm, but...
thanks for coming so fast,
Flash.
[gentle music]
¶ ¶
- Just want to make sure
everything's okay before I go.
- Don't worry.
Everything's good.
¶ ¶
Good-bye, Barry.
- Greg, move your head!