- My name is barry allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother killed
By something impossible.
- Run, barry.
Run.
- My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident
made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensics scientist,
But secretly, I use my speed
To fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother.
- Mom.
- And get justice for my father.
I am the flash.
Previously, on the flash...
- Who do you think you are?
- This is what we talked about,
using my speed to do good.
- We talked about you helping
us contain other meta-humans.
- After all of these journalism
classes, I started a blog.
- I thought you were taking
journalism,
Not science fiction writing.
- Ever since I have known you,
You have believed
in the impossible.
What if you were right about
the night that your mom died?
Something out there
is saving people.
- See you soon, barry.
- How often do you think about
Why your friends came
into your life?
Was it random, by design,
or maybe a little of both?
- Nice.
- Regardless of the reason,
some friends you just know
Are gonna be by your side
for a while.
Others, you're not so sure.
And then there's that one
friend who, well, you hope,
Someday becomes something more.
But "friend"
will have to do for now.
And that's okay.
I guess.
- I'm glad
you invited caitlin and cisco.
- They're cool, right?
- They saved your life, barry.
That makes them the coolest
people I've ever met.
It's nice
that you guys became friends.
To friends, old and new.
Ooh.
I'm up.
Wish me luck.
I'm going to destroy you.
- Don't get cocky, west.
- Guys?
I have a problem.
- We all do when guys
like him exist.
- Yeah, he's so hot.
Uh, I mean,
genetically speaking.
Because I'm a geneticist,
of course.
Oh, my god,
do I sound like felicity?
- I'm not talking about eddie.
I'm talking about this.
I can't feel anything.
- Yeah, that's usually what
happens when you drink too much.
- No, the alcohol
is not affecting me.
I mean I literally feel nothing.
- It's your hypermetabolism.
I need a sample.
- I'll get more shots.
- I swear,
I had a vacutainer here.
- Wait, you carry a blood
collection kit in your purse?
- You have your hobbies.
- 14th floor is secure.
- Roger that.
Hold off on that check.
Lock down the building!
Hold it!
- Don't come near me.
- You need to come with me.
Come on.
- Get down!
- Still nothing?
- I can't get drunk.
I mean, I'm only 25,
And my drinking days
are already over.
- Come on, allen.
You're up.
There was a bombing
on 8th and pass.
I got to go, babe.
- Okay.
- Sorry, guys.
- I've got an early shift
at jitters.
Barry, we'll catch up tomorrow.
- It's getting late, anyway,
so I'm just gonna...
- Help! Help!
Somebody!
- Guys, there's a window washer,
and he's gonna fall.
- Don't try and catch him.
You don't have super strength.
- Well, is there,
like, a bed store near here?
What if I get a bunch
of mattresses and stack them?
- Barry,
this isn't a roadrunner cartoon.
- Help! Help!
- How fast would I need to go to
run up the side of a building?
- How far up do you need to go?
- Hurry, somebody!
- I don't know.
50 meters, give or take.
- 32.56...
- Guys, hurry!
- Help!
- Just run really fast
and you'll be fine.
But you need to maintain your
velocity on the way down, or...
- Or what?
- Splat.
- Great.
- Help!
- All right.
All right, all right, all right.
Here goes.
- Barry?
What do you got?
- Bombers typically have
their own unique signatures.
Crimped wires, fragmentation.
The level of sophistication is
telling once I've analyzed it.
You show me a bomb,
I can usually find a clue in it.
- It sounds like
there's a "but" coming.
- Yeah, I haven't found any sign
of an oxidizing agent.
It's as if the floor
just blew itself up.
- Things don't just blow up.
- Security guard said our bomber
was a woman, red hair.
Must've cut
the security camera's feed.
There's no footage, but
there might be something else.
Some kind of small charge
blasted the doorknob off.
- Any idea what's missing?
- My guess is one
of these files.
It's gonna take days
to figure out which one.
- Let's let barry do his thing.
- What's going on?
- I have no idea.
But they came in here
like they own the place.
Been talking to singh
for the last half hour.
- This can't be good.
- General eiling,
this is detective west.
- Detective.
- What's this all about?
- The army's taking over
the bombing investigation.
- I'll need everything you have.
Physical evidence,
photographs, witness interviews,
And all your personal notes.
- I've been on the job
nearly 20 years
And never heard of the army
investigating anything civilian.
- Well, it's not civilian.
She's one of ours.
- We'll send over
everything we got.
- Very kind of you.
I think we'll take it now,
though.
- Give them what they want, joe.
- You heard him, joe.
Give me what I want.
- Hey, what's going on?
- General eiling is relieving us
from the bombing case.
Give these men everything
that's relevant.
- Sure thing, yeah.
- You and a few civilians
from S.T.A.R. Labs
Might want to check into that.
- I think we might.
- Can I talk to you for
a minute, joe?
It's about iris.
- Hey, dad.
You're home early.
- What were you doing
at the bomb site last night?
Don't deny you were there.
Officer vukuvich saw you.
- It's... Complicated.
- You can't be coming
to every crime scene
Because you're worried
about eddie.
He's a big boy, iris.
- I didn't go there
to see eddie.
I went there to see the streak.
- The streak.
Hmm, why is that?
- My blog.
I've been collecting
internet posts
About the streak sightings,
and writing about them.
- Baby, there's no streak.
- Yes, there is.
I saw him last night, dad.
I looked right at him.
Something incredible
is happening in central city.
And I am gonna write about it.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to get to work.
Blogging about supernatural
events doesn't really pay well.
- A va file number is all
the info you have on the bomber?
- Ccpd's been ordered
off the case.
- Well, who has the power
to do that?
- The army.
Some general.
His name was eiling, I think.
- General wade eiling.
- You know him?
- Yeah, I know him.
About ten years ago,
general wade eiling
Contracted S.T.A.R. Labs
to develop
Enhanced gene therapies
for soldiers.
I was interested
in the potential
Medical benefits for civilians.
General eiling really wanted
to develop
Mind reading capabilities
for interrogation purposes.
I stopped the study when I
saw his techniques up close,
But our split
was less than amicable.
- He took all the evidence
I collected on the bombing.
Everything but the folder.
- Well... Lucky for us,
the va finally
Joined the new millennium
and digitized their records.
A lot of redacted info.
But our girl's name
is bette sans souci,
An eod specialist for the army.
- Eod?
- Bombs.
- Is there an address?
- Hold on.
Here, we go.
One person in case of emergency.
Cameron scott.
Inglewood.
- Bette sans souci?
I need you to come with me.
- Don't touch me.
Get whatever you're wearing
off of you.
Hurry.
- Barry, can you hear me?
Barry?
- There must be a perfectly
reasonable explanation
For why he's not answering.
Barry?
Uh...
- Don't ask.
- I'm gonna ask.
Where's my suit?
- It's... Gone.
- What do you mean, it's gone?
What did you do with my suit?
- It blew up, dude.
I managed to get out of it
before it went, "kaboom."
- My suit went "kaboom"?
- Fun fact about
bette sans souci.
She's not carrying bombs.
She touched the emblem
on the suit
And turned it into a bomb.
She's a meta-human.
- With the ability
to cause spontaneous combustion
Upon tactile contact.
- She blew up my suit.
- You have, like, three more.
- Okay, I have two.
And I loved that one.
- All right,
what else do we know about her?
- Oh, I don't know.
She's pure evil.
We're gonna find this girl
And send her butt
into the pipeline.
No one blows my tech
to smithereens
And gets away with it...
Unless she looks like that.
- I don't think
she meant to hurt me.
- Well, her being a meta-human
Explains general eiling's
interest in her.
- And why he stole the case
from us.
He didn't want anyone
to know what she could do.
- Detective.
- Doctor.
So... Human bomb.
Must be Tuesday in central city.
- Yes, and general eiling's
Not one to give up a potential
asset without a fight.
- We have to find her
before he does.
- Barry?
Can I see you for a second?
When were you planning
on telling me
That iris saw the streak?
- That was not planned.
She caught me off guard.
- We had a deal.
You keep her in the dark
about the meta-humans,
And I don't go floyd mayweather
on you.
- Okay, joe, I know.
- And she's writing a blog now.
- I already talked to her
about that.
- Talk to her again.
And be more convincing.
- Okay.
You mean, right now?
- Yes, I do.
- All right.
You've got
to stop writing about this guy.
He doesn't even exist.
- I saw him, barry.
He wears a red suit,
like, a uniform or something,
With a lighting bolt
on his chest.
- I mean, iris, come on.
You were drinking last night
at the bar.
- I was not drunk,
and I know what I saw.
He wears a mask.
I think he smiled at me.
- Okay, first of all,
if he is wearing a mask,
That probably means he doesn't
want people to know who he is.
- It doesn't matter who he is.
What matters is that people
know that he's out there.
What is wrong with you?
This is important to me.
Why can't you be more
supportive?
- I'm just... you haven't even
put your name on it.
How serious can you be
about an anonymous blog?
- Okay, you know what?
Our entire lives,
You couldn't scream loud enough
that the impossible existed.
And now it's actually happening
in central city.
I have proof of it, and you
don't want to know about it?
That doesn't make sense, barry.
So when you're ready to tell me
what this whole routine
Is really about, then we can
talk.
- yeah.
- We've piggybacked onto general
eiling's own surveillance.
According to what they're
saying,
The lovely ms. Sans souci
was just spotted in inglewood.
- The same neighborhood
as dr. Harold hadley's office,
The military surgeon
who performed
Several procedures on her.
That's why she was looking
for the folder.
- You got to get to her
before eiling does.
- Okay.
- Sgt. Sans souci.
- You remember me.
Good.
Because I remember you, doctor.
I remember waking up
from a coma.
You started cutting me open.
- I was only trying
to help ease your condition.
You couldn't control it.
- You did this to me.
You and eiling.
- Go bring me my asset.
- You okay?
Look, I can get you out of here.
I can help you understand
what happened to you.
- How?
- Because it happened to me too.
Please.
- Target is gone.
- As the detonation dispersed
throughout central city,
A number of people were exposed
to a wave
Of unquantifiable energy.
One of those people... Was you.
You were in central city
ten months ago.
- I had just returned
from afghanistan.
I was there
defusing roadside bombs
And... Shrapnel ripped
through me.
I was flown back state side.
Spent months
at the base recuperating
And next thing I know,
I became the thing that almost
killed me.
And eiling's favorite,
new lab rat.
- The dark matter must have
combined
With the bomb particulate
inside your body.
- I thought eiling
did this to me.
- Eiling is not smart enough
to create someone like you.
Clever enough to see your value.
- Do you know of any others
who were changed?
- There've been a few.
- But no one
that looks like you.
I'm sorry.
That was inappropriate.
Please don't leave.
- I know how to perform
a lobotomy.
- Her cellular structure's
unlike anything I've ever seen.
- Her nitrogen levels
are off the charts.
- Do you think we can help her?
- To answer that question,
we have to understand
How she works,
and to understand that,
First we have to study her
in action.
- You want her to blow stuff up.
Yes, now we're talking.
- Not in here.
She's too unstable.
- I know.
- I know you know.
- So this is your life now, huh?
Testing people like me?
- Stopping people like you.
It's not what I thought
I'd be doing.
Actually, aside from barry,
You're the first meta-human
that we've tested.
- "meta-human"?
- It's just a term.
Oh, my god, what happened?
Why didn't you say
that you were shot?
- It just grazed me.
- There's something in there.
- A tracker.
- Lock down the pipeline.
Get bette out of here.
I'll take care of eiling.
- Harrison wells.
How the mighty have fallen.
- General.
- S.T.A.R. Labs.
This place used to be
so important.
Tell me, what does one do
After such a spectacular,
public failure?
- One adapts.
One evolves.
One becomes intent
on reversing one's fortune.
- Always the idealist.
- What do you want, wade?
- Where's my asset?
- I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- We tracked her here, harrison.
Turn her over to me
before you see the rest
Of your precious palace crumble.
- Oh, wade, wade, wade.
- We could've changed
the world, you and I.
- 427 kpa's.
Her trauzl rating is around 45.
That's the same
as any plastique.
Plastique.
Ha... first try!
- Didn't really think
this one through, did you?
Downrange, insurgents
started booby trapping cars.
The rest of my tour,
I was terrified
To touch another vehicle.
Now, I'm gonna spend the rest
Of my life terrified
to touch another human being.
Have they tried to help you?
- Yeah, they've helped me learn
how to use my powers.
Not reverse them.
- If they could reverse it
so you weren't a meta-human,
Would you?
- A friend told me I was
given my speed for a reason.
That I was chosen.
I don't know if I believe that,
But I always wanted
to help people.
Now I can.
Sorry.
Hey, joe.
- I see your little conversation
with iris was a rousing success.
She just posted another story
about the streak.
- Joe, I tried.
I really tried.
- She's got her name on it now,
barry.
- What?
Joe...
- It's my fault, I shouldn't
have asked you to say anything.
I just wanted you to know.
Okay?
Bye.
- What was that about?
- Iris posted about the streak
again.
She signed her name to it.
- Oh, that's not good.
- No.
- If one of these bad
meta-humans
We're dealing with
figures she knows something...
- Then they may target her,
I know.
- Sorry, we're closed.
- Oh, my god, it's you.
- Iris west,
I hear you've been
writing about me.
- You are real.
I should, um...
Let me just clean up...
- Meet me on the roof.
I'll give you a head start.
I need you to
stop writing about me.
- There are a lot
of people who need someone
Like you right now.
To know that you're out there.
I have so many questions.
Where are you from?
- I can't say.
- Who are you?
- I can't tell you that, either.
- How can you do what you do?
You're a terrible interview.
- There's more to this
than you can understand.
Just trust me, please.
I need you to stop.
- Can you stop?
Running into buildings
and rescuing people
Without them
even knowing that you're there?
- I don't do this for the glory.
- So why do you?
Look, I have this friend,
And he had something terrible
happen to him when he was a kid.
His whole life,
he's been telling stories
About this impossible thing.
And people laughed at him.
And shrinks analyzed him.
And he's been searching
for an explanation ever since.
But now, suddenly,
it's like he's lost his faith.
But you... you are proof
that he wasn't crazy.
Help me save my friend.
- He's a lucky guy.
Hey, what's wrong?
Did eiling find out you're here?
- No.
Caitlin was about to give me
the not-so-good news.
- The shrapnel in your body
Has merged with you
on a cellular level.
- And the technology required
to unsplice your dna...
It hasn't been invented yet.
- Bette.
- It's okay.
Roger that.
I just need a minute.
Don't worry.
Pretty sure I can cry
without blowing stuff up.
- What now?
- She joins us.
Becomes a part of the team.
- Barry...
You have an amazing
ability to help people.
She makes things explode.
- She's the first meta-human
not hell-bent
On destroying this city.
- It's too dangerous.
- Well, she's not going
in the pipeline.
- I'm not suggesting
she go in the pipeline,
But were she to remain
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
It would put all of us at risk.
- From who?
Eiling?
- Eiling is a dangerous man,
barry.
We do not want him as an enemy.
- After the lighting bolt,
what if you hadn't found me?
It could've been me.
Hunted, on the run, cut off from
everyone I know and care about.
You guys saved me.
- And I want to save her
just as bad as you do, barry.
We all do.
- Joe.
What are you doing here?
- Going over the materials
in your mom's case.
How's it going with you?
- Stellar... I made friends
with a human bomb
Who I promised I could help,
and then, I couldn't.
And I finally diagnosed why iris
is writing about the streak.
She's doing it for me.
To prove the impossible
is possible.
- How do you know that?
- The streak may have talked
to her.
- Barry, don't you think
iris would recognize your voice?
- No, I can do this cool thing
with my vocal cords,
Where I vibrate them
so I sound like this.
I know.
It's cool, it's cool.
- Whoa.
Well, you put that
out there now, so.
I want to keep her safe.
- You know the only real way
to get her to stop
Is to tell her the truth.
- Man, you really want
to tell her.
- I tell her everything.
- Mm...
Not everything.
- Is it that obvious?
- Not to her.
- But how long
have you known for?
- I have watched
you be in love with iris
Since you were old enough
to know what love is.
And I've been waiting years
for you to tell her.
But you haven't.
- Guess I was too slow.
Now, she's happy
and with someone else, so...
- When the universe
wants to make something happen,
Whether it be giving a young man
lighting speed
Or putting two people together,
It has a way
of figuring those things out.
And I got to get home.
- Thanks.
- Cisco?
- He went home.
I think our cisco's developing
a little bit of a crush on you.
- Not sure I'm prize winning
date material anymore.
- Change is hard.
The same accident that changed
you put me in this chair.
- Sorry.
I didn't know.
- I don't share that story
with you to garner sympathy.
I tell it to you
to illustrate a larger point.
- And what point is that?
- That I would do anything
to get back what I lost.
As would you.
- I would.
I just don't know how.
- You soldiers, you call
yourselves sheep dogs.
Am I right?
- Happy and normal until someone
attacks our flock.
- Every good person
who was changed that night,
People like you,
people like barry allen,
Those people
are your flock now, bette.
And general eiling will never
stop attacking that flock,
And he always gets his target.
Unless you stop him.
You know your duty, sergeant.
Kill eiling.
One last mission.
And then you go home.
- Where's bette?
- She left.
- What do you mean?
Where did she go?
- She didn't say.
- Well, where the hell
could she be?
- Go, go!
- On me.
- I'm ready to give myself up.
- Oh, I highly doubt that.
You think you can pull one
over on me?
You can't.
Stand down, soldier.
- I got back
on the military feed.
Looks like they've gone
to the waterfront
To rendezvous with bette.
She's turning herself in.
- She's not turning herself in.
- Please, let him get to her
in time.
- All over the world, people are
plotting to destroy our country.
To end our lives.
Brave american soldiers
are gonna die in that fight,
But they don't have to.
Because of you,
we could have victory.
- All I've ever wanted was
to make the world a safer place.
And it will be
when you're not in it.
- Take cover!
- What are you doing here?
- Being a soldier
doesn't mean you're a murderer.
Don't become one now.
I'm sorry.
I didn't see him.
- Don't be.
It's not your fault.
I'm glad you stopped me.
- I'm gonna get you back
to S.T.A.R. Labs.
- Barry, dr. Wells.
He... he...
- Guys, we have a problem.
- Is bette okay?
- No.
Eiling killed her.
She's glowing.
She's gonna detonate.
- Oh, my god, a mass that size,
the explosion, it would be...
- Devastating.
- Barry, you have to get her
away from the city.
- But there's no time.
Can I run on water?
I built up enough speed
to run up a building.
How fast do I need to go
to run on water?
- Assuming your weight...
450 pounds of force per step
for vertical suspension.
Accounting for fluid drag.
- Approximately 650 miles
an hour.
- You have to outrun
the blast or you'll die too.
- Nothing out of the ordinary
occurred.
The military was
simply conducting
An underwater weapons test.
There is no need
for panic or alarm.
Central city is safe.
I guarantee you.
- He murdered bette right
in front of me.
And there's nothing
we can do to him.
- Powerful men have a way
of avoiding consequences.
- You gonna be okay?
- Yeah.
- You can walk on water.
Puts you in pretty interesting
company.
- If you came to do laundry,
I already have a load in.
- Uh, no.
I-I came to talk.
I was working a case.
Someone I really thought
I could help befriend.
But they died.
- Barry, I'm really sorry.
- I didn't know her that well.
But it still hurts.
And as bad as I feel right now,
I know how much worse it is
to lose someone who's family.
Iris... Writing about this stuff,
putting your name out there,
It's dangerous.
So I'm asking you one last time,
please, stop.
- And I am asking you
one last time
To tell me what is really
going on with you.
Why am I the only one of us
who's interested in this?
- I guess, just,
all this stuff with my family,
I finally just put it behind me.
I'm asking you to also.
- That may have been
how this started,
But it's about something more
than that for me now.
Whoever this streak is,
wherever he comes from,
I am not stopping until the rest
of the world believes in him.
- Maybe we shouldn't
see each other for a while.
- Yeah.
Can I get another club
soda, please?
- Hey.
- Hey, what are you guys
doing here?
- We thought we
should have a toast.
- Doesn't work on me, remember?
- Barry allen, you of all people
Should know
that nothing is impossible.
I distilled a highly fermented,
potent suspension.
It's basically 500 proof.
I figured if anybody could use
a drink tonight, it was you.
So here's to bette.
- Bette.
Whoa, oh.
That hit too quick.
- Are you buzzed?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I'm buzzed for sure.
Whoa.
Whoa, that is good stuff.
And it's gone.
- Work in progress.
- For a guy who has experienced
his fair share of mysteries,
One mystery
I still can't figure out
Is why some people
come into our lives.
Why some people go,
And others become a part of you.
Some friendships
feel like they'll last forever.
- Hey, sweetheart.
- Hey.
There's dinner in the fridge.
- Okay, thanks.
Iris, about your blog...
- I don't want
to talk about it, okay?
- And others end far too soon.
Not every friendship
is meant to last a lifetime.
What does last forever is the
pain when that person is gone.
- I was wrong about you,
harrison.
You're still one step ahead.
Impressive for a man
without the use of his legs.
- I'm afraid I don't know
what you're talking about, wade.
- A girl who can transform
ordinary objects
Into explosives with the touch
of her hand.
Today I saw a man who can move
faster than the blink of an eye.
Extraordinary.
The night your particle
accelerator died
Was the night
the impossible was born.
I think we should start working
together again, harrison.
- I think you should leave.
- You know, I can have
a squadron of soldiers here
In minutes.
- You know, I can have an army
of press here like that.
Believe me, general,
I'd be more than happy
To testify to your involvement
In activities
that were less than humane.
Threaten me again
and I will end you, general.
And I am not talking
about your career.
- You know, I figured out
your little secret, wells.
Won't be long before the public
catches on as well.
This is everything
we've been working to achieve.
- We may have the same goals,
general, but not the same means.
- I will not have this project
end before it even begins.
- And as long
as he's on my premises,
I will not have him subjected
to that kind of cruelty anymore.
We're done.
General.
Get out.
Hey.
It's okay.
- It's okay, boy.
- He's gone.
Don't you worry.
I have a whole different future
in mind for you.
- Greg, move your head.