The cure is finished, and it works.
Now we can use it on Dwyer,
and then his connection to the dagger will be broken.
What's wrong?
The timeline.
I've charted this timeline from Anthro the First Boy
to Kamandi the Last.
I know all of it.
I know its crests, I know its valleys,
I know what we must do to defeat Cicada.
Or rather, I knew.
This is a photo of the last public sighting
of Flash and Cicada.
Their final confrontation.
Dad's last chance to use the cure on Cicada.
I've been trying to engineer a moment like this
the whole time I've been there.
Now, watch.
See this?
That is a new timeline struggling to break through,
manifesting itself right before our eyes.
Is it a good timeline, or is it a bad timeline?
That doesn't matter.
What matters is it's new and, as such, unpredictable,
and we may lose our window of opportunity.
So we need to find Cicada before the timeline changes.
Why did it change?
Did I screw something up?
No.
No, no.
You've done very well, little runner.
But a new variable is coming, something big is coming.
Or someone.
Well, it's interesting that you say that, sir,
since it's your company that's denying
the Robertson family's claim.
Yes, of course, I have the contract right in front of me.
And it says that animal attacks
do not fall under Acts of God,
and that includes gorillas.
The Citizen looks forward to your statement.
Thanks, babe.
Are you ready to do this thing now?
Hell yeah, we just got to find Nora.
It's her big day after all.
You don't think she's too busy, do you?
Okay, people, think!
We haven't seen Cicada since the rooftop fight,
which means the only way to track him down is to figure out
who his next meta-human target's gonna be.
Have we double checked every bank robbery,
every lab break-in?
Yes, yes! We have looked at all of that, all right?
And all the criminals that are in custody
are simply mere mortals.
What about the ones on the street?
Frost says that no new metas have shown up
since Norvock went into WITSEC.
Are the satellites tracking for dark matter
or meta-gene bursts or Element X?
Yes, yes, and yes.
They're scanning for everything.
Congratulations, you raised a menace.
Your daughter, so energetic.
This is pretty impressive.
Um, and I... and I know with the cure working,
we're all ready to put Cicada to rest,
but I'm sure he'll resurface soon.
And then you're going to give him the chance
to take the meta-human cure?
Yes, exactly.
Even Dwyer deserves a choice,
we just got to convince him to do the right thing.
Are you ready?
This is gonna be one of the biggest challenges
of your career as a hero.
Do you know what you're going to say?
Oh, yeah... you know, yeah.
I've... I've got some loose thoughts.
Oh, great.
Well, that instills all of us with confidence, right?
Loose thoughts? What are you going to say?
"Hey, most bloodthirsty enemy! Stop."
Guys, it worked for Marlize.
Maybe not so much for Savitar, but...
I will figure out what to say to him, all right?
I got this.
I know you do, Dad.
Which is why we need to try everything to try and find him.
Okay?
Maybe we should go on patrol?
- Patrol, you say? - What this is, World War II?
Wow, this is crazy.
There is something nuts going on at Jitters.
Do you think it's a meta-human?
- Probably. - You should...
- We should check it out. - Yeah.
- For sure. - Yeah.
- Y-yeah. Go! - I'm...
- You two did this. - You made her.
You are responsible.
Well, well, well.
It is nice to see someone back at his desk.
Oh, hey, Foxy.
It's good to be back.
After three months of sipping Wally's Tibetan butter tea,
I actually kind of missed this break room coffee.
Hey, you have any idea where I can get my hands
on the Cicada task force file?
Babe, you're standing in it.
What?
I've been trying to catch up on what I've been missing.
Uh, speaking of which...
you ever seen this woman?
Uh, Dr. Vanessa Ambres.
Born and raised in Central City,
got her MD from McNider U.
Oh, that's interesting.
This says she treated Orlin Dwyer and Grace Gibbons
on the night of the Enlightenment.
Yes, and she has been treating Grace ever since,
even though she's an ER doctor,
and the nurses report a whole slew of drugs missing
from the coma ward.
You think she's working with Dwyer?
The guy got stabbed, struck by lightning.
He's got a hole in his chest.
Somebody has got to be patching him up, right?
I think we should be asking the doctor a few questions.
All right, let's do it.
Oh, you want to come with?
- Yeah, I want to come with. - What?
Uh, yeah, yeah.
- Yeah! - All right, partner.
- Partner. I like that. - Yeah.
Okay, I thought something big was supposed to be going on down here.
Oh, I don't know. It's pretty big.
Feast your eyes on the newest addition
to the Jitters menu.
The XS-presso.
I got my own drink!
It's pretty schway, right?
Think of what could be next.
An XS action figure? XS Day?
Guys, you are embarrassing me.
We're just really excited.
I mean, we still haven't even gone on a trip together
or made Grandma Esther's famous sweet potato pie recipe.
Did you put karaoke on the list like I asked?
I think so, actually.
- Just a sec... - Let me see this.
Okay, there are so many things on this list.
Well, I mean, we've got time.
Okay, is that a real alert or another fake one?
No, this one's real.
M-20 at CCU, Chemistry Department.
- A meta attack. - Yeah, let's go. Come on.
Been a while since high school chem,
but that does not look like proper lab safety.
I need this! Leave me alone!
Sodium bicarbonate neutralizes any acid.
You have the cuffs?
Let's go get him.
- We don't need to. - What?
Look at this burn mark.
That acid guy, he... he must've been there
when the photo was taken.
What are you talking about?
Dad, today's the day you stop Cicada.
Slow down. Say that again?
There's a photo, it's in The Flash museum, of Flash and Cicada...
the last time they were ever seen
confronting each other in public,
and in the photo, by Flash's feet,
the exact same burn mark left by the meta
that we just fought.
This acid meta was at their final confrontation?
He must be Cicada's final target.
His final target before I vanish
and he starts killing again.
Why is Nora just telling us
about this crucial meta now?
Because a lot of the stuff from my timeline is unreliable.
You know, uh, different metas, different victims,
different circumstances.
But this time, everything's exactly the same.
So far.
If Cicada goes after this acid meta,
that means that today's the last day
we're going to confront him.
And our last chance to stop him.
Yeah, all right, well, then, I gotta figure out exactly
what I'm gonna say to him.
You'll find the words, Dad. I'll help you.
And I am going to start working on facial rec
for this Acid Master.
Yup, that's what I'm going with.
Always trust your gut, kids.
And we'll figure out a way for you to talk to Cicada
without him killing you.
Well...
if it all works out, then...
looks like today could be the end of our journey.
Yeah.
And I guess everyone starts moving on.
- Nora. - Oh, hey, Mom.
Um, look, I've really gotta hurry and go help Dad.
Yeah, I know, it's just...
I guess you might be going home tomorrow.
Yeah, I guess so. Um, mission accomplished.
Well, if you two need a break after a while,
Papa Joe taught me the famous West family right hook.
I-I would love to teach you.
- Nora? - Sorry, uh, sorry, Mom.
I just, uh, thought of something
that's going to help Dad... I-I got to go.
Babe, this is a first!
We've worked together before.
We have, Detective,
but anytime we did anything even close to this,
I didn't have my abilities.
Okay, here we go.
Uh, if I fiddle with my ring, you know,
assume that means she's lying
and then you just get in there and, mm, mm,
do your thing.
You cop it up.
Prednisone, sirolimus, abatacept.
All drugs classified as immunosuppressants.
They also happen to have all been reported stolen from this facility.
I'm aware of the report.
What I'm wondering is
why it warrants the interest of the DA?
We believe that the missing medications
are connected to a much higher profile case.
Orlin Dwyer.
Grace Gibbons' uncle.
Is he still at large? I don't really watch the news.
Yes, he's very much at large.
And we have reason to believe that those exact medications
are the ones that Dwyer would need to treat his injuries.
What are you saying exactly?
The records of the stolen meds
continued after Dwyer stopped visiting the hospital.
Which means that someone here
may be still supplying them to him.
Sounds like a good theory,
but I don't know who that could be.
Everything I know is in those reports.
Okay, okay.
That's enough for now.
Thank you very much for your time.
Of course.
What are you doing?
You're just gonna let her walk away like that?
I-I didn't want to scare her.
We don't have enough evidence.
We don't even have a motive.
So, then, let me keep doing my thing!
I'm not used to going into an interview
factoring in your meta-abilities.
I-I'm used to going in using my gut.
What about my gut?
All due respect, this isn't about your gut.
Look, Cecile, what I meant to say was...
No, no, no, no, no, no, Joe.
You said exactly what you meant,
and you know what, right now,
I'm about to say something that I mean.
Maybe we shouldn't be working on this together after all.
Oh, man.
Okay, the clock's ticking,
and we have no clue how to convince Cicada
to take the cure,
but we still have our best weapon.
- Your journal. - Your legacy.
One of the biggest things history remembers
about The Flash is your ability
to change people's hearts and minds,
especially your enemy's,
and I have dozens of entries about those times.
Any chance you've got the future words
I say to Cicada in there?
Nope, but I have your past words.
Magenta, she wanted to drop an oil tanker on a hospital,
but you convinced her she was a good person.
You said, "Use that good to beat the bad."
Magenta had split personalities.
She literally had a good side and a bad side.
That's not gonna work with Cicada.
Leonard Snart,
he said he didn't want to be saved
and you still found a way to convince him to save himself.
"There's a part of you that knows
you don't have to let your past define you."
Except Snart had already worked with us at that point.
Killer Frost, you dared her to kill you.
"Come on, live up to your name, Killer Frost!"
- And what did she do? - Nora.
Amunet, Plastique,
the list goes on and on.
Nora, all... all of these times are... are different.
Cicada doesn't even care if he lives
when this is over.
What am I supposed to say that he'll care about?
You'll know.
The Flash always knows.
So, when you think about it, an anti-dampening array
is the way to stop him in his tracks.
Sherloque, are you happy to be going home soon?
Of course I'm happy to go back.
I just feel that...
somehow there's more work to be done here.
I think he's, uh, talking about his lady friend.
You know, I have a bit of experience with these, uh,
long-distance relationships.
I got one word for you. Holo-cube.
These things work wonders.
And I request that you stop speaking possibly forever.
I can deduce from your conversation when you came in
that you have indeed tracked down Cicada's next target
but do need help facilitating the conversation
between Cicada and The Flash.
Correct? Yes? Oh, good.
Come with me and I will give you the solution.
When did you figure it out?
I will miss you both very much.
But you will miss me more! Allez!
Philip Master!
We good?
Yes, Philip Master is secure in the pipeline.
Wait, Acid Master's real name is Philip Master?
This is it. Just like in the photo.
The last confrontation between Flash and Cicada.
Oh, what's the matter?
You don't have one of these?
Bye-bye.
Cicada!
How long does he have?
He has to hold that dagger for 60 seconds, maybe less.
Flash better figure out what he's going to say fast.
He will. I know he will.
I don't want to fight.
We have a cure.
What are you talking about?
We have a way to cure meta-humans.
We have a way to take their powers away.
We want you to take it.
And why would I agree to do that?
Your legacy.
I know how this ends.
You keep killing,
and you're remembered as a monster, not a hero.
But we can change that together,
you can have a different legacy.
You just have to choose it.
I don't give a damn about my legacy.
That was it. That was our last chance.
We ran citywide facial recognition scans
and scanned for dark matter signals
from Cicada's dagger.
That was our last shot at confronting Cicada.
We don't know that.
We're changing the timeline.
That photo that Nora saw at the Flash museum,
it could be different now.
Maybe it doesn't even exist.
After all... the timeline is malleable.
I just don't understand why our plan didn't work.
Yeah, you guys did everything right.
The only reason it didn't work
is because I couldn't convince him.
Dad, you're the Flash.
When the Flash speaks honestly from his heart,
people listen.
Not all people.
Let's keep searching.
I'm gonna check the Cicada files at CCPD.
See if I missed anything.
Nora.
We just... we just need to create
another window of opportunity, okay?
Dad couldn't convince Cicada to take the cure.
He just... he just needs to find the right words.
Bare.
What are you doing here so late?
We hit a wall at S.T.A.R. Labs tracking Cicada.
Thought a change of scenery would help, but...
Keep your head up, man.
We'll find him. We always do.
Honestly,
I'm more worried about what happens when we do.
Our whole plan depends on me being able to convince Dwyer
to just take the cure.
The last time I tried...
I don't think I've ever struck out so hard.
Wow, that's saying a lot
considering your track record at the plate.
Wait, what exactly did you say to him?
That he was creating a legacy of fear,
one that would go down in history,
but that we could work together to change that.
That sounds like something the Flash would say.
Well, I am the Flash.
Look, that man's a zealot.
He sees you in that suit
and all he sees is the thing he hates.
Meta-human, superpowers,
the thing that took his niece away from him.
He can't see past the Flash,
but what he doesn't know...
There's a whole lot more to you than that.
Be more Barry Allen. Human.
Yeah, you're right.
Thanks. I'm gonna dive back in.
I'll let you get back to running down Ambres.
Actually...
me and Cecile ran into a wall ourselves.
We are... uh, she... like, working together.
I mean, ever since she got her powers,
it's like she's a human lie detector.
How is that a bad thing?
You know I've always prided myself
on being able to read people, right?
But Cecile and these powers, I mean, she puts me to shame.
Well, you just got to remember that you guys are a team.
That makes her strengths your strengths
and yours hers.
So if you let her do what she's great at,
it's only going to create more room
for you to do more of what you're great at too, right?
Well, damn.
You're getting real good at these pep talks, Bare.
Well, I had a pretty good teacher.
Hey, Nora.
Hi, Nora.
Yeah.
Do you want to turn that down a little bit?
Oh, sorry.
What are you listening to?
Sped-up archives of the Flash's comm recordings.
I thought that if I listen to his best appeals,
I could figure out what exactly worked so well.
And did you?
No, not yet.
But if I run the transcripts through the computer,
I can extrapolate recurring key words
from his most successful appeals
and create a sort of "Best of Speeches" Speech.
Well, um,
why don't you let your dad think about it
and we could go to the rooftop of Jitters.
It's a great place to clear your mind,
plus it's got the best views of the city.
You want to go sightseeing? Right now?
What... is this from that list of yours?
Well, yeah, but...
All day I've been trying to figure out a way to stop Cicada
and all day you've been trying to pull me away.
Why are you pushing this list?
I mean, it's just the last time
that we may get to spend together.
Nora, I mean, once we stop Cicada,
you'll go back to your time and...
Us like this together will end.
Mom, it doesn't end.
We have our whole future together.
Yeah, for you it'll feel like no time has passed
but for me, it'll be decades before I...
see you like this again.
Uh, no, it's okay.
Um, I will catch up with you later.
Joe.
What's going on?
Why'd you want me to meet you here?
Look, I know the last time we tried to work together
went a bit south.
Oh, a bit?
You're right. I'm sorry, Cecile.
I let my pride get in the way,
and I didn't lean on your strengths
when I should have.
But you know me,
I'm not a man who makes the same mistake twice.
So...
Would you do me the honor
of joining me in this interrogation?
You do what you do best, I'll take care of the rest.
Get 'em, girl.
Detective. DA.
This is starting to border on harassment.
I have told you everything I know.
That's not true.
We know that you've been funneling meds to Orlin Dwyer.
Well, if you knew that,
then I'd be arrested and not sitting here.
Let me correct myself.
We have a strong hunch,
but I bet if we were to go through
the video camera footage from the hospital,
we'll find proof that you were assisting Dwyer.
I'm a doctor.
I mean, why would I condone a vigilante murderer?
Because of what happened to Darius.
Darius.
It hurts you to even think about it.
My fianc¨¦  was killed by meta-humans
during Zoom's rampage.
So, yes, it hurts to think about him.
Hurt enough for you to help Dwyer kill other meta-humans?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
you took an oath to do no harm, right?
Can you truthfully say you've upheld that oath?
That guilt that you feel right now?
There's a way to make up for it.
All you have to do is help us find Orlin.
What, so... so you can put him in jail? Kill him?
No, so we can cure him.
It's not possible.
Maybe not with the medicine you've been giving him,
but S.T.A.R. Labs has created a treatment
that turns metas back into normal human beings.
I can't take you to him.
Okay, okay, then help us set up a meet.
Look, Dr. Ambres, it's clear.
You've come to truly care for Dwyer.
So we're asking you now...
help us save his life.
I can make contact, and I can share the location.
I have rounds in an hour
and patients that I can save tonight.
So am I free to go, please?
I love my job.
I can stay here all night.
And we will, unless you tell us
what you're keeping hidden right now.
Yo, yo. I got your text. You talked to Ambres?
Cecile and I together got through to her.
She's going to show us where to find Dwyer.
Joe, that's amazing.
Yeah, Ambres told us something else.
Dwyer's niece, Grace? She's a meta.
So le petit Dwyer is a meta.
Wait, I thought we scanned Grace for meta powers
when Nora entered her brain.
We did but that was back when her DNA was 100% human.
Her powers must have activated
in just the last few weeks, right?
Yeah, Ambres told Joe that the wound in Grace's head
recently started glowing and mutating.
Now all we need to do is get Dwyer to listen to you, again.
Killer Frost can put him on ice from the neck down.
Better yet, I can re-sequence the Speed Force Bazooka
- to overload him with negative tachyons. - Yes.
- Absolutely. - So that he's stuck there...
Tachyon, shmack-yon. No, no.
La Machine  ¨¤  M¨¦moire!
We could go inside Dwyer's mind.
- Oh, about that... - Guys...
- No, La Machine  ¨¤  M¨¦moire! - Last time? I think...
Guys, hey!
I appreciate the enthusiasm,
but I think we need to take a different approach.
No powers, no crazy plans.
The Flash can't convince Cicada to stop this,
but... maybe...
I can.
Dad's back.
He says Papa Joe's got news about Dwyer.
Okay, good. I guess we should get over to the Cortex.
You know, I had a list too.
Your wedding, Auntie Jenna's baby shower,
Jitters, The Enlightenment.
Those were all the moments in time
you wanted to go back and see us?
Yeah, so I could have memories and experiences
with all of you.
I get it.
I should've been sensitive and I-I'm so sorry.
- It's okay. - No, it's not.
I was so focused on making sure Flash beat Cicada,
I forgot what I was supposed to really be focused on.
You and Dad.
You're the reason I came back to this time,
not fighting big bads or getting my own XS-presso.
So that I could spend time with my parents.
My family.
I don't know how much time we have left together
or how much of your list we're going to get done,
but from now on, every moment we have left,
we're going to make it a memorable one.
I promise.
Well, I guess we can cross off "Hugging while drinking tea"
- off our list. - Yeah.
Hey, guys, sorry to interrupt.
- No, it's fine. - We were just...
We were just talking about Mom's list.
Um, so I heard Dad has a lead on Dwyer?
We have a location.
I'm going to head there any minute.
Does Flash know what he's going to say this time?
Actually, I think I'm just gonna talk to him,
father to father.
That's a really good idea, Dad.
Hey, Doc.
Dr. Ambres told us where to find you.
I just want to talk.
There's no more talking.
Every time one of you metas comes near the rest of us,
good people get hurt.
This is what you all deserve.
Does that include Grace?
Ambres hasn't told you.
Grace. She's a meta.
The night the satellite crashed,
she was hit with a piece of shrapnel inflected with dark matter.
That's... that's why she's in a coma,
and now it's changing her.
That's a lie.
And that's why Ambres told us where to find you.
She's afraid.
She's afraid you're going to do the one thing you can't come back from.
I know how much you care about Grace.
You're trying to make the world a better place for her.
She didn't choose to be a meta,
but she is.
Does that mean she deserves to die?
No.
I would never hurt Grace.
Then you'd let her grow up in a world of fear.
Where there's someone out there hurting people like her.
The cure, it will heal Grace and you.
And why should I believe you, Flash?
Because I'm a father too.
My daughter, I love her more than I ever thought possible.
I would do anything to make the world
a better place for her.
And I think you would too.
So do it.
We made an arrangement.
We cure him and then Grace.
Okay.
Why are we here and not at a hospital?
We have to be sure that the cure is successful.
We created it.
We're the ones who know how it works.
Once administered, the cure will take 60 seconds
to eliminate the meta-human powers in your system.
That means the wound in your chest will then open.
You'll need me to suture it shut
so you don't bleed out.
Why not Doc Ambres?
She's being held for questioning.
No, it's Ambres, or we're done.
All right, we'll get her.
If anything goes wrong,
or if you're lying to me,
I'll kill every...
last...one of you.
And we're certain everything in this room is sterile?
Of course.
Everything except that.
That thing's not negotiable.
That rage of his, it's...
Joe, I can't.
Are you going to stay?
Uh, yeah, just in case.
- Okay. - All right, babe.
Good job today.
You too. Partner.
We never could have done this without you guys.
Well, I'm glad it worked out,
but when this is over, he's going to jail,
for a long time.
Okay, one fresh serving of piping hot meta-human cure.
I'm just supposed to trust that that thing works?
Has it gone through any human testing?
It's gone through giant shark testing.
It's a long story.
It's okay, Doc.
I wanted to tell you the truth about Grace.
I just couldn't find the words.
You were just trying to keep her safe.
I'll always be thankful for that.
See you on the other side.
There we go.
Injecting the cure.
His vitals are spiking.
How can we tell if the cure is even working?
Oh, it's working.
My powers are back.
Which means Dwyer's powers must be gone.
It appears your sojourn into the past was a success.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You as well. It's your, uh, 38th Cicada?
That's right, yes.
38th Cicada. Trente-huit Cicada.
Alley-oop!
But, of course, there's some business here
that remains unfinished.
For instance, how did you know before you saw the burn marks
in the photograph that it was a meta-human
that would lead us to Cicada?
Uh, I...
You know, I just had this feeling
that something big was coming.
They're working on him now.
I will be so happy when this is all over with.
What's going on?
What happened to the power?
I have no idea.
I should check the Med Lab.
- Someone's coming. - Who?
Cicada?
Where's that coming from?
Cisco!
- Hold on! - Iris.
- Careful. - I can't see anything.
Here.
Cisco, we need power.
We got a much bigger problem.
Cicada?
How the hell did that happen?
I don't know, but he's coming here and he looks pissed.
We have to move now.
I've got to keep patching him up.
Stand back.
There.
- He's in the hallway. - Get the hell out of here.
Iris! Get down!
Come on!
Who are you?
Please, whoever you are.
I only came here to make him human again!
I helped him!
Please!
Please don't do this!
Nope. They're all toast.
Well, better the computers than us.
- Joe. - Are you okay?
- I'm okay, I'm okay. - I'm a little bruised, but...
Everybody else?
Yeah, we're okay.
- Guys... - Dr. Ambres didn't make it.
There's no sign of them anywhere.
I don't understand what happened.
I mean, we got Dwyer, we gave him the cure.
If... if Cicada doesn't exist anymore, who was that?
Someone worse.
I've missed you.
Uncle Orlin.