ZiMuZu.tv
My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
After defeating Zoom and saving the multiverse,
I ran back in time
and created the alternate timeline, Flashpoint.
I restored the timeline to how it was,
only to find things weren't as I left them.
I brought new threats to our world,
and I'm the only one fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
They don't see your potential.
- I do. - You want to train?
I'll train you.
You're Allen's friend, Dr. Snow.
I'm begging you, don't turn her in.
I will do anything you want.
Tender your resignation, effective immediately.
It's a story--it used to be written by Iris West-Allen.
Something's changed with our future.
- God, what did I do? - My brother's dead.
Now I'll never make another memory with Dante again.
You're only a man, Flash.
But I am a god.
I am Savitar.
Now we know Alchemy's just a lackey.
Julian, become my servant once more.
Become Alchemy.
It's been six months since I arrived here in India.
Though I have faith it's out there,
the voice that once drove me has waned.
And I fear my quest may be for naught.
Julian, come quick.
I think we found it.
This is it. Here, hold this.
This is it.
I can feel it.
I think we should wait before we open it.
It needs to be set free.
Took the words right out of my mouth.
Well, I guess Earth-19's Christmas is just like ours.
Some traditions are multi-versal.
So, um...
any more info on Savitar?
Nope, all the we know is that he's a speed god
and you're the only one who can see him.
All right, well, Alchemy is Savitar's high priest
and he gets his power from the stone
that he uses to create meta, so I was thinking
if we can find out what that thing is,
maybe we can figure out how to stop him.
I want to see if I can dig something up.
Okay.
I know this is our first Christmas together as a couple
and I want everything to be perfect, but...
You need to get to this.
Yes--no, I totally get it.
I got a dissertation here from Oxford University
about the myth of an ancient Hindu weapon
called the Brahmastra.
Legendary artifact with incredible powers,
capable of--wait for it--
Creating metas.
Creating meta-humans.
Guys, that looks just like Alchemy's stone.
More importantly...
look who wrote this paper.
Julian?
Love what you've done with the place.
Allen.
Thought we had a deal.
I keep your frosty friend's secret,
and you never darken these doors again, remember?
I just need some information from you
about that stone that Alchemy uses.
And you've come to me because?
Apparently, you know a lot about it.
Well, why don't you tell me everything you know?
And you'll never hear from me again.
Fine.
Many years ago, I heard about the Brahmastra,
or as it's colloquially called,
the Philosopher's Stone.
It is said to be the first object to give human beings powers.
Like the Particle Accelerator.
Over the years, it got lost.
I became quite obsessed with trying to find it.
Did every piece of available research I could
and much to my parents' dismay,
I used my future inheritance
and funded an expedition to try and find it.
But we never found it.
Pretty soon after that, I came here.
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have work to do.
In your research, have you ever come across
the name Savitar?
How do you know that name?
I've done some research of my own.
As far as I know,
Savitar is the first meta with speed.
That's all I know, Allen.
And I suggest that you don't waste your time on this.
Move on.
All right.
Julian.
Here you go.
One whiff of aliens and all the crazies come out.
I'm gonna be buried under these alien files
until next Christmas.
Well, if by some Christmas miracle
you dig yourself out sooner,
we do it up at the West house on Christmas Eve.
Turkey, tree, Grandma Esther's eggnog,
the whole shebang-- and we would love for you to come.
One condition: I bring the nog.
My Grandma Millie's recipe, it is gonna knock your socks off.
Oh, wait a minute.
We gonna have a little nog-off.
Really?
Grandma Esther versus Grandma Millie.
Oh, you know I love a challenge, Joe West.
May the best grandma win.
I am so sorry for your grandma.
We'll see.
- Fine. I'll pick you up, all right? - Christmas miracle.
I told everyone inside I'd let them live
if they followed instructions.
But I tricked them.
Which is so me.
Give it up, Trickster!
Hiya, Swiftie.
Will you do me the honor of allowing me to kill you?
You're out of ammo.
But I'm not out of bombs.
What do you say we take in the afterlife, big boy?
- Nice timing. - You're welcome.
There's something wrong with my eyes.
I'm seeing double.
The Flash hit me too hard!
I'm gonna sue you, saucer-head!
One day, I'll own that helmet,
and I'll use it as an ashtray or a candy dish.
No, wait, a hubcap!
I had that, kid.
That's what I always say.
Let me go.
Especially when I didn't have it.
So I'm assuming you didn't come all the way to Earth-3
to stop my Trickster.
I have something I need to talk to you about.
A speedster.
Calls himself Savitar.
- So... Savitar. - Yeah.
Apparently, you've grown powerful enough
to challenge him.
Who is he?
Don't know, never seen him.
You're the first speedster I know of who has.
But every story I ever heard about Savitar
is basically the same.
Savitar was the first man ever granted speed.
And over time, he became the god of motion,
the fastest of us all.
Before Savitar graces an Earth with his presence...
He sends a predecessor to prepare for his arrival.
Alchemy.
What's he preparing for?
A battle with you.
Why me?
You're threatening his power.
How do you know all this?
Speed Force myths, legends, rumors.
If Savitar's come for you once,
he'll be back.
Then I'll be ready.
We'll be ready.
Run! Wallace, run!
You got to torque to the left!
- How'd I do? - How'd you do?
Oh, I don't know, why don't you see for yourself.
Hold up, are you saying I'm faster than Barry?
I'm saying that at this point in his training,
you're faster than Barry.
You're faster than Barry, you're faster than Barry,
you're faster than Barry!
- We got to tell everyone. - Not a good idea.
- Why not? - Self-preservation, basically.
Look, Wallace, you have tremendous potential.
Yes, clearly, but one thing I've learned
since coming to this Earth is you do not trifle
with the West household.
No, you know-no, say you're with me.
- Yeah, I'm with you. - Yeah!
Now, we're gonna work on your--your--yeah, your dodging
and your weaving.
I've read every Hindu textbook there is on mythology
and spirits and demigods and nothing.
No mention of Savitar, not once.
In my experience, the answers usually tend to come in time.
Yeah, I can't just sit back
and wait for Savitar or Alchemy to attack.
You can't worry about what may or may not lie ahead.
Besides...
it's Christmas.
A time to be with the ones you care about.
You know, it's just, Savitar's still out there.
Yeah, but not right now.
And your beautiful girlfriend is.
Get your head out of the books
and back into your life with your loved ones
while you have them.
Hey, Jay thinks he figured out a way to find the stone.
You okay?
I don't know.
I keep seeing my brother.
Everywhere-here, in the cortex...
Well, this is your first Christmas since Dante died.
Maybe your mind's playing tricks on you.
Yeah.
Probably.
There was this one Christmas, big family affair.
and Dante and I, you know,
we used to fight all the time as kids,
but that one Christmas,
we didn't fight.
We just sat and we talked and we drank
a whole bottle of whiskey, and...
that whole night, we were laughing.
It's...
And that one night--
that one night, it was like we felt like brothers.
The last Christmas before my dad died,
it snowed and snowed.
He and I just sat inside, watching old movies
while the whole world turned white.
It was magical.
Are we about to be the Grinches this year?
Nice use of restraint.
Yeah, well, I shopped,
and I shopped, and now,
I am ready to drop into your arms.
I'm sorry I missed Christmas shopping with you.
It's okay. I have everything I need.
So are you as excited to give me my present
as I am to give you yours?
Yeah, of course.
Definitely. Yeah.
You did get me something, right?
I did get you something, yeah.
I just--I haven't wrapped it yet, is all.
- Okay. - Okay.
Okay, um, by the way, after you told me about
Julian's archeological dig,
I started doing some digging of my own.
Turns out, a few years ago,
four scientists were killed in an excavation in India
and Julian was the point person.
He didn't mention that.
You said he was obsessed with that stone for years.
What if he was covering something up?
Or someone?
You think this is about Alchemy?
There's only one way to find out.
Julian lied about the Philosopher's Stone.
I think he found it back on that archeological dig.
You think he's working with Doctor Alchemy?
He's not answering my calls.
Hey, everyone.
Gang's all here, what's going on?
I think that Julian is connected to Doctor Alchemy.
Jay, we got a hit.
There's energy coming from the top of the Schults building.
- That's the stone. - Are you ready?
- Ready. - All right.
I'm coming, too.
- No you're not. - No.
Dad, I'm ready.
You--just tell them about how fast I am.
Tell them about the training.
- Training? - Training?
Training. The vocal training.
Because we're thinking of going caroling.
We're gonna talk about this later.
We're definitely gonna talk about it.
With energy form this stone,
and this building as a refractor,
I shall restore the powers of all the metas from Flashpoint.
They will become the servants of Savitar.
It's over, Alchemy!
Please tell me you're seeing him.
I see him.
We have to take him together.
No, I'll cover Savitar,
you just get that stone!
This is not your fight, Garrick.
Julian.
Where am I?
What's going on?
Let's just say you're gonna be our guest for a while.
You.
I always suspected you had your own private facility
for holding enemies.
You care to explain what I'm doing in it?
- I know you're Alchemy, Julian. - What?
Turning innocent people into meta-humans,
worshipping this Savitar?
Sorry, um, I'm still not following.
You think that I'm Alchemy?
That's the most absurd thing I've ever heard.
Is that a mask?
I've never seen that before in my life.
I caught you!
I caught you wearing this mask.
You're trying to set me up.
You're framing me, aren't you?
The Flash, of all the people, you're setting me up.
- The hero. - You're insane.
The great hero!
I want my phone call, when do I get my phone call?
How you feeling?
Not too bad for a guy
that got beat up by a myth.
- Yeah? - You stopped him.
Well done, Barry.
It was nice, having you out there with me.
Yeah, I never had a sidekick.
- Oh, I'm your sidekick? - Well, as a senior partner.
Senior citizen is more like it.
I'll bet your dad would've been proud of you.
Right?
Hey, why won't you just take it easy, all right?
- I¡¯ll see you in a little bit. - Yeah.
What do you think about what Julian was saying?
I know that every bad guy we've ever had
has pretended to be our best friend, while really being
an evil, murderous bastard, but...
I think if he's lying,
he sure believes the hell out of his own lie.
Okay, well what do we think about this box?
It's creepy.
Like, "Indiana Jone" melt your face creepy.
Have you guys figured out anything about it yet?
It's nothing.
It's something.
No, I mean the box is literally nothing.
I've run it through every possible test I can think of--
MRI, X-ray, mass spectrometer, the photon shifter.
Not a single reading. Nothing.
It's like the box
doesn't even exist.
Two weeks ago, I almost lost you to Alchemy,
then last week aliens.
- My heart can't take it, Wally. - Dad, he gets it.
- Iris, does he? - I think so, yeah.
And you...
A couple weeks ago. You were telling me
how you believed in me and my instincts,
and now you're encouraging Wally to do exactly the opposite?
I don't know how much encouraging he needed.
What's the deal with you?
You have some psychotic need to make other people like you
no matter what?
I wouldn't call it psychotic.
No, my deal is,
I find people's true talents,
and I just marshal them along.
Do you even have your own opinions?
Stop. Stop banging on H.R.
This was all me, okay?
I pushed him to train me.
I pushed him to help me.
Wasn't like anyone else was lining up to do it.
Hey. What's up?
It's Wally.
I don't get it, Bar, it's like his brain goes to sleep
and somebody else is at the wheel.
Have you been losing time? Blacking out?
Hours passing, waking up somewhere different?
Not being sure of how you got there.
- No. - No?
No!
I've had enough of these baseless accusations
and ridiculous theories of yours.
Julian, I'm trying to help you!
But you need to trust me.
Says the man in a mask.
No, you're right.
I should've known.
I should've guessed it.
The unexplained absences, your passion for metas.
Your general thumbing your nose at authority.
I'm sure you had a good laugh behind my back.
I actually wished I could've told you before.
So why tell me now?
Because I need you to trust me, Julian.
You are Alchemy.
I just don't think you're aware of it.
Now, have you been blacking out?
Yes.
When did it start?
My sister, Emma, died when I was 20.
And it really broke the family up, you know?
Mom and Dad weren't speaking,
they wouldn't even stay at the house.
One night, I was there alone,
and she came back to me.
She stood right in front of me,
clear as day--a ghost or a vision, I don't know,
but...
she was real.
What happened?
She told me about the stone.
She told me where to find it,
she told me that if I got it,
then it would bring us back together again.
And at that point, mate,
I would've done anything to have her back.
That's what I did.
I mounted an expedition to India.
Days we searched, weeks.
Nothing.
And then we found it.
And the next thing I remember, I woke up in the hotel room.
I...
didn't remember anything,
and that's when the blackouts started happening.
There was a news report saying that
every other member of my team had been found...
dead at the site.
I panicked, I thought they were gonna blame me for their deaths,
so I ran.
I ran to America.
What happens when you black out, Julian?
How does it start?
I hear the voice.
Cisco.
You're losing it, man,
you're losing it.
Stop scaring me!
Whatever you are, it's not cool, okay?
I know exactly what you are.
You are a figment of my grief.
Please just leave.
I can't do that, Cisco.
This is not real.
Okay, I need an anti-psychotic. Caitlin!
If you leave,
I'm gonna have to leave, too.
So you're telling me that -- that
every time I'm blacking out...
You've become Alchemy.
That's impossible.
Alchemy is a monster,
he's been terrorizing people for years.
Look, it's not you.
Just like it wasn't you back on that dig.
I know that this is hard to believe,
but you have to start accepting what's happening to you.
Don't you want us to be together again?
The stone.
It's the key to everything.
It can transform people.
Open it and I can be reborn.
We can be together again.
We can have that bottle of whiskey.
After all, it is Christmas, hermano.
It's the time of miracles.
I just want this to be real.
Just open the box.
I love you, Cisco.
Dante.
Dante?
What's that?
- Guys, what's going on? - Cisco's workshop.
Barry, he opened the box.
Wait.
Cisco?
Bow to your god.
What is happening?
We can't see it,
just like at Alchemy's lair.
Savitar's loose.
Hey, Jay, Jay, you're still too badly hurt.
Remember: dodge and weave.
Wally, no!
I can see him.
Great. Get his attention.
Yo, metal mouth.
Clearly, nobody taught you how to play nice with others.
Cisco? Cisco, you have to close the box!
I'm gonna save Dante.
It's -- that's not Dante, it's Savitar.
Please, he's using your memories against you!
You're a good brother, Cisco.
Cisco, we're running out of time.
Please, just hand me the box.
I won't lose him again.
I will not lose my brother again!
Cisco, Dante is gone.
I'm so sorry, but there is nothing you can do about it.
But there are people you can save right now.
If you don't close that box,
Barry and Wally will die.
If you do, we can't be together.
Cisco, listen to me!
Don't.
Lo siento, hermano.
Thanks.
You kidding? That was awesome.
Are you sure you're okay?
Still in one piece.
I don't know what happened.
So now that the box is closed,
Savitar's, what, gone for good?
I don't know, but we need to find out.
Cisco?
If we can't use this box,
Julian, he may be our only link
to Savitar now, right?
I think we can use both of them.
If Caitlin's right and this thing
messes with brainwaves,then I have a plan.
You put my son's life in danger again.
And he saved Barry's life.
Joe, why...
why do you think I help Wally?
'Cause I'm selfish, I get something--
I don't get anything out of it.
I help Wally 'cause the kid is special.
He's extraordinary.
His powers are extraordinary and--look, I get it.
I'm--I'm not his dad and I don't have the same
safety concerns as you, of course not,
but Joe, one thing I do know,
the longer you deny someone their potential,
the more they're gonna look for it elsewhere.
So what am I doing here?
Okay, Julian, today when I was fighting Savitar,
it--he and Alchemy, they had the same voice.
All right, what does that mean?
I don't think there is an Alchemy,
I think it's Savitar speaking through you.
Savitar clearly possesses someone who rallies worshippers.
But he's like a poltergeist, he needs a medium to manifest himself.
You.
Right, but what does that mean?
We think we figured out a way
to sync your brain to the stone.
And it'll allow us to speak directly to Savitar.
I thought--
If you want to try to be free of this,
you need to trust us.
I've never liked you, Allen.
Yeah.
Having a little s¨¦ance with your friends now
is not gonna help change that fact.
You do know that.
Fine, I'll try it.
Deep breaths.
- Okay? - Yeah.
You're gonna count backwards from ten.
Te--
That was quick.
Okay, so, um, how long till this works?
Not really sure, it may take a minute for his brain waves--
Hello, Barry.
It's been a while.
Savitar?
None of you are on your knees.
It's a smart move to bow before a deity.
You're not God.
To be a god, you just have to make people
believe you are.
No one believes in you.
You should, Iris.
I hold the power of life and death over all of you.
How do you know so much about us?
I know you, Caitlin.
Cisco, Joe, Wally.
The fake Wells.
I know your fears and I know your weaknesses.
I know you better than you know yourselves.
I know your destinies.
One shall betray you.
One shall fall.
One will suffer a fate far worse than death.
This is the knowledge I have for you.
About your everlasting damnation.
Who are you?
I am the future, Flash.
What do you want from us?
Everything!
Everything you took from me, I want it back.
And I'm gonna take it back.
Then, I will destroy you.
Then why haven't you already?
If you're all-powerful, then why don't you just
go ahead and kill us all now, be done with it?
Because you can't.
You did this to me.
You trapped me in eternity.
Your future self-- you did this to me, Barry.
And now the age of my revenge rises.
My freedom is at hand.
You will feel my wrath.
The wrath of Savitar!
Did it work?
That was so scary.
I mean, that was-- was it not truly frightening,
what the voice and the prophesies and the--
it was--I mean, that a scare-a-thon, wasn't it?
I'm gonna have a mint tea and a coffee and a lay down.
Do you think the things that he said about
one of us betraying him and one of us dying
could really be true?
I mean, if it really was future Barry
that pissed him off and locked him up somewhere,
then maybe he knows what happens to future us.
He doesn't.
He's never getting out of wherever he's trapped.
So how are we supposed to stop him?
The stone.
Jay's right, the stone has been the key to everything.
It's--it's how he controlled Julian,
it's how he's created more metas.
So we destroy the stone and Savitar is gone for good.
It's impossible to destroy.
It's been around forever, there's a reason for that.
Why don't we just bury it again,
put it back in the ground where you found it?
"Jumanji"
Someone would just find it and we'd be right back
where we started.
We need to make that box disappear forever.
There's only one thing we can do with it.
Throw it into the Speed Force.
- Wait, you can do that? - Oh, yeah.
The Speed Force is eternity itself,
an endless void of time and energy.
It'd be like trying to find it after it got lost in space.
But that stone is loaded with gravimetric force.I mean,
I don't think you could run fast enough
to reach the Speed Force and carry that at the same time.
He can with my help.
We run as fast as we can.
You trail behind me, siphon off some of my speed,
combine it with your own, and when you have enough,
throw that thing deep into the Speed Force.
And that would work?
We need to find out.
Sure you're up for this, Flash?
You got it, Flash.
I'll let you know when you reach optimal speed.
All right.
Ready...go!
Jay's moving really fast, this might actually work.
Now, Barry!
In other legal news, the highly publicized trial
of Jared Morillo, AKA "Plunder," comes to a close.
Morillo was found guilty of grand theft
and aggravated assault after he was caught by the Flash
robbing the Central City Museum earlier this year.
Don't!
Please don't!
Don't do this.
Now, finally, I am free of you.
Barry, I love you.
No, don't say that, all right?
You're gonna be all right.
- I'm begging you, just-- - Barry!
You lose, Barry.
No!
Iris. Iris, hey...
No. Iris.
Iris, Iris...
Jay?
What the hell was that? Where was I?
The future.
I've never run to the future.
I've traveled to the past,
but I always came back to the present.
I saw myself.
And Iris. And
Savitar, what--
he killed her.
That's five months from now.
Is that actually gonna happen?
- I don't know. - You don't--
You shouldn't have seen that.
This doesn't make sense, we--
we just got rid of the Philosopher's Stone.
I mean, Savitar shouldn't have even been there!
Oh, my God.
This is where the newspaper in the time vault changed.
The byline, this is why it's not Iris, this...
Iris didn't write that story anymore
eight years from now, because...
she's dead.
Barry...
I just watched her die.
I saw myself try to save her, but I wasn't fast enough.
Jay, tell me that this isn't my destiny.
What you saw was one possibility of the future.
What may be, or what may not.
Okay, then I can stop this from happening.
- I can run back there-- - You can't go back there.
Not again, not ever.
All right, then I'll figure out exactly how it happened,
how we wind up on that street,
and I'll just make sure that we don't go there.
- And if we don't go there-- - Barry!
This is why speedsters don't travel to the future.
Nobody should know this much about their own.
Just as their are infinite Earths in the multiverse,
there are infinite possibilities to the future.
It's always bending, always changing.
Every decision you make creates another alternative.
I won't let Iris die.
The future isn't written yet.
And it might not even turn out to be what you saw.
You need to focus on the here and now.
You have to live your life.
- Hey, guys. - Hey.
Are you okay? You and Jay disappeared, and...
Naw, I'm okay.
- I'm just glad to see you. - So where's Jay?
Jay, uh, decided to go ahead and go back to Earth-3.
But he wanted to wish everybody a Merry Christmas.
So, it worked? The stone...
It's gone.
- It's lost in the Speed Force. - Good, good.
I don't know about you guys, but being mind-punked
by a speed god that we piss off in the future,
it's--it's enough to kill your Christmas spirit.
Guys, Christmastime is here.
We need a little Christmas.
Right this very minute. Who's with me?
- BA. - Well, he's right.
It's Christmas, we should be together.
Let's have it.
I'm still in if everybody else is.
- Yes! - Okay, we'll be there.
Yeah!
Julian...
Where's he going?
Hey, where ya going?
Do you have Christmas plans?
The West's are having a Christmas get-together.
After what you've been through, you shouldn't be alone.
I actually prefer to be alone at Christmas.
Rain on Christmas.
That's neither holy nor jolly.
Hey, listen, um...
about Dante.
Thank you for talking me off the ledge.
Of course, you'd do the same for me.
In fact, you did the same for me.
I was gonna say.
Caitlo--Caitlo, Ciscan...
okay--whoo-- you got to try the eggnog
a holiday concoction done by Joe
and his hot girlfriend...
Babe.
- What's up? - Nothing.
You seem a little weird. No?
You do know we won, right?
We defeated the bad guy.
- Yeah, I know. - Okay.
- Grandma Esther. - Grandma Millie.
Let's see.
Damn, that's strong.
So is that, my God!
Our grandmothers are alcoholics.
Yes.
You know, technically, we don't have to be standing
under the mistletoe to-- mm.
Finally.
No comments from the peanut gallery.
No, but really, it's about time.
Hold on.
And it's my daughter.
ah, just give me a quick minute,
and then we can--yeah.
- Hey, kiddo... - Joe.
I saw you kiss her, good job.
We're--oh, that's right, the thing.
BA, hey. Come on.
How many of those have you had?
- B--where'd you go? Here. - I'm right here.
Oh, I see ya.
Now that Cecile's away,
this is from all of us to you.
Merry Christmas, son.
- Are you serious? - Yeah, man, it's time.
You're ready, Wallace.
Welcome to the team.
Kid Flash.
Are we really calling me "Kid Flash"?
Yeah, I think we are.
Kid Flash!
- Police! - I got it.
It's not the police. We're the police.
You're the police!
Calm down.
Hey, Julian.
- Come on in. Here, let me get that. - Thanks.
after everything that happened,
being alone felt a bit lonely, so...
This is for you.
What's this?
I spoke to Captain Singh, and he hadn't put through
your resignation paperwork yet, so...
well, if you'd, uh, you know, like your old lab back,
or you'd like to share it again.
Thanks, Julian.
Merry Christmas, man.
- Cheers, mate. - Yeah, thank you.
- Merry Christmas. - Merry Christmas.
- Can I offer you some eggnog? - I'd love some, yeah.
Happy Christmas, everyone
I'm glad you came.
Thank you, yeah.
- Do you hear that? - It's outside.
Carolers.
Caroling in the rain.
That sucks.
- What're you doing? - It's okay, I got this.
We may not be able to have a perfect Christmas,
but we can have a white one.
So.
When are we gonna exchange presents?
How 'bout right now?
- Okay. - Follow me.
- Okay. - Let's get out of here.
Okay, going through a door, be careful.
Okay, right here.
- Okay, are you ready? - Yeah.
All right.
Open your eyes...
now.
I--I don't understand, where are we?
Home.
What?
I couldn't sleep on Cisco's couch anymore,and
your place is sort of small for two,
so I signed a lease
and I put both of our names on it.
I got you a wallet.
I'm sure I'll love it.
Barry, this is a big step.
Not for me.
I don't know what's gonna happen in the future.
All I know is, right here, right now,
I want to spend every moment I can with you.
You're the first thing I want to see when I wake up.
And the last thing--
I love you, Barry Allen.
I love you, Iris West.