- My name is barry allen,
and I'm the fastest man alive.
When I was a child,
I saw my mother
Killed by something impossible.
- Run, barry, run!
- My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible.
To the outside world,
I'm an ordinary
forensic scientist,
But secretly I use my speed
to fight crime
And find others like me,
And one day I'll find
who killed my mother...
- Mom.
- And get justice for my father.
I am the flash.
- Previously on the flash...
- Ronnie!
- 17 people died that night;
many more were injured.
I'm not the most popular person
in town these days.
- We're just supposed to
get used to working
Above a makeshift prison
Housing evil people
with superpowers.
- What is this?
- Somewhere you'll never
hurt anyone ever again.
[upbeat music]
[laughter]
- Farooq!
- It's not safe.
Come down.
Farooq, I'm serious.
It's gonna rain.
- Y'all are tripping.
This is the best seat
in the house.
Whoo!
- You know, when I said
we should watch
The particle accelerator
turn on,
I just meant we should get naked
and howl at the moon.
- It's already on.
Consider me unimpressed.
[distant boom]
- Whoo!
Yeah, baby.
- Oh.
- This is awesome.
- Are you seeing this?
Oh, man,
I think I am tripping.
Oh, man.
- Get in the car!
Get in the car!
[electricity crackling]
- Farooq!
[screams]
- Good day, dr. Wells.
- One can always hope, gideon.
Bring up my log, would you?
- Certainly.
Go ahead, doctor.
- New entry.
It has now been 311 days
since lightning struck.
Subject has begun relying
on his speed in everyday life,
Using his extraordinary powers
to solve ordinary problems...
[alarm beeping]
- I'm late.
- And accomplish ordinary tasks.
Unfortunately, his penchant
for the heroic persists.
- I hate it
when they let the new guy train
During the morning rush.
[people talking at once]
- Did you get one too?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
- The fact is...
- Don't try nothing.
- He can be a bit of a showoff.
- Wallet.
Now.
- Oh, this is awesome.
You've got to be kidding me.
Hold on, okay?
I'm just gonna--
I'm gonna set this down.
[laughs]
I mean, this is crazy.
There are literally
hundreds of thousands
Of people in central city,
And out of everyone you could
have picked to rob, you pick me.
- What, are you sick?
Money, now.
- I just--you're really gonna
be kicking yourself, man.
I mean, if there was an olympics
for bad luck,
You didn't just medal, pal.
You michael phelps-ed.
- I'll count to three.
Then I'm gonna shoot you.
One...
- Yeah.
[gun cocks]
- two.
- And while his desire
to help others is commendable,
It is impeding him
from realizing the full scope
Of his abilities.
But there's still time,
As the future remains intact.
Where's barry?
He's late.
- Late is kind of
his signature move.
- Hey, you guys
want to see my signature move?
- Sorry, guys,
I got a little held up.
You had to be there.
- I'm gonna need a moment
or two alone with barry.
- Ooh, you're in trouble.
- Now, may I remind you,
mr. Allen, we had an agreement.
We would help with your heroics
out there
While you would help us
research and develop
Your abilities in here, right?
- Yeah.
No, I know.
I-I guess I've just
Gotten a little caught up
with being able to help people,
You know, put bad guys away.
It feels good.
- Imagine how good
it will feel
To cure diseases, stop aging,
reverse paralysis.
- All good causes.
So how can I help you do that?
You need more mris,
more blood, or--
- I need more speed.
- Okay.
- Speed is the key to progress.
[cell phone vibrates]
You need to kick it up a notch.
- There was a homicide.
I'm sorry.
I've got to go.
- This is not just about you.
Remember that, barry.
- Yeah.
[exhales]
I hope you both skipped
your breakfast.
- Whoa.
- What the hell could do that?
- 2,400 degrees,
give or take.
- This area's filled
with combustibles.
How come nothing else burned up?
Where you going?
- You see the soot on the ground
where the cement is burnt?
- Yeah.
- That's evidence of arc blasts.
Happens when
high-amperage currents
Travel or arc through the air.
- There's no live wires.
There's no utility poles.
- So how was this guy
electrocuted?
- Well, the first thing
we need to do is I.D. Him.
- Yeah.
His face is melted off.
How's that picture
gonna help I.D. Him?
- I got mad skills.
- Please don't ever
say that again.
- All right.
Hey, are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Why?
- I don't know.
You seem a little off.
- No, I'm fine.
- All right.
- Facial recognition software--
It's designed for archeologists,
And it should help us I.D.
Your crispy corpse.
- The question is, how did he
get fried in the first place?
Is there a metahuman out there
that can control electricity?
- It'd take a serious
electrostatic discharge
To cause that level
of tissue damage.
- Guys,
according to the software,
There's an 82% chance
your victim looked like this.
- 82%?
- Hey, it was zero
when you walked in here, pal.
- Can you cross-reference that
with the dmv database,
Maybe get a name?
- Absolutely.
This software can do
just about anything
Now that felicity
reprogrammed it.
Casey donahue.
No wife. No kids.
Used to work at the petersburg
electrical substation.
- That can't be a coincidence.
- That's weird.
Someone just used his I.D.
To enter the substation.
- The petersburg grid
is experiencing a power drain
Right now.
- Barry, be...
Careful.
[electricity crackling]
- I'm pretty sure
this is a restricted area.
Easy there, zappy.
- I have to feed.
- Whoa, what was that?
- More of that.
I need more.
- Barry, what's happening?
- [screams]
- Too much.
Too much.
- Get out of there.
Run, barry.
- I can't.
My speed...
Is gone.
- He runs slow
even for a normal person.
- You can't just
lose your powers, okay?
Your dna was transformed by
the particle accelerator blast.
There's no way
to untransform dna.
- Yeah, tell that
to the uber driver
Who charged me 65 bucks
to take me here.
I had to tell her I was coming
from a cosplay party.
- So we were wrong.
This metahuman
doesn't electrocute people;
He siphons electricity,
thereby removing your power.
- All right, do we think
this is temporary or--
- We have to run tests.
- Yeah.
I've got to warn joe.
- Barry, we will find a way
to restore your speed.
I promise you that.
- You didn't catch it.
- I loved that mug.
And what part
of "a metahuman stole my speed"
Didn't you understand?
- Barry, there's no part
of anything you can do
That I ever understand.
What does dr. Wells say?
- He's working on it.
- Barry, you have to get
your speed back.
People in this city
need protecting,
And if you don't get your speed,
How the hell
are we gonna keep them safe?
- Joe, the meta
who stole my speed,
He burned up the body
we saw in the alley today.
You need to tell the police
not to confront him.
He's dangerous.
- Who's dangerous?
- No one, just some thief.
- Well, criminals
better watch out.
Cops in central city
are the best there are,
And if you can't
protect this city, dad,
I know the flash will.
- What if he can't?
What if he's gone?
- Gone?
- Yeah, or maybe he's just done,
Or maybe it's like
whatever he could do before,
He can't do anymore.
- Huh?
- Barry?
Don't you have
someplace to be?
- Yeah, going.
- Aw, barry loved that mug.
- That's a quality
time piece, young man.
- Oh, uh, thanks.
- They took mine,
All of them.
- I guess
you shouldn't have done
Whatever it is you did.
- Come on.
- Gideon, show me the future.
- Certainly, doctor.
- Run a complete search.
Show any references
to the flash.
- Zero references to the flash.
- Look again.
- Zero references.
- Show any references
to barry allen.
- Zero references
- Look again!
- I've searched 3,452 times,
dr. Wells.
There's nothing.
- You think I'll ever
wear it again?
- I hope so.
- I didn't have my speed
for very long,
But now that it's gone, it feels
like part of me is gone too.
- With or without your speed,
you're still you, barry.
- But I'm not.
I'm not the best version of me.
I love being the flash.
I love everything about it:
The feeling of running
hundreds of miles per hour,
Wind and power
just rushing past my face,
Being able to help people.
I'm not sure
I can live without it, caitlin.
- Farooq gibran.
- Who?
- The powers vampire
who jacked your speed.
I hacked into
the surveillance footage
From the petersburg substation.
Once I got his face,
it was easy to find a match.
- He climbed an electrical tower
The night
of the accelerator explosion.
- No surprise
where his powers came from.
[alarm beeping]
- Oh, you've got
to be kidding me.
This is not happening.
- Dr. Harrison wells,
I need to see you!
Come on,
I know you're inside.
Open the door.
I just want to talk, dr. Wells.
Wells!
Let me in!
- Joe.
Hello, iris.
I am out.
I need you to cover for me
until the shift change.
Only one headline,
Prison transfer,
william tockman.
[electricity crackling]
[gunshot]
[people scream]
- Guns on the floor!
It should take you
less than three seconds
To discard any thought
of rebellion and comply.
I take it I don't need to
count out loud.
[gunshot]
Hmm.
Striking resemblance.
[electricity crackling]
- He's inside.
- Captain,
Tockman has
at least ten hostages.
Two officers down.
- Copy that.
When is the power back?
- We're on gennies for now.
[cell phone rings]
- Not now.
- Wait.
Captain singh,
I've been trying to get in touch
With joe or anyone
at the precinct.
- There's a hostage situation,
barry,
And joe's inside.
So's his daughter.
I'll call you when I know more.
- Wait--
[line clicks]
Joe and iris are in trouble.
I need my powers back now.
- I have a theory.
It's untested.
- I'm willing to roll the dice.
- Okay,
you've lost your speed, yes,
But nothing has changed
inside you on a subatomic level.
In other words,
your cells are still primed.
- They just need a jumpstart.
- Okay, how do we do that?
How do we jumpstart me?
- We need to replicate
the initial jolt to your system.
- But that would mean
a peak current
Of at least 20,000 kilo-amps.
- Are you insane?
That's more electricity than
they give to people
In the electric chair.
- Caitlin,
with farooq in the building,
We're all looking
at a death sentence here.
- The spare generator's offline.
If we reboot it,
we could get a charge that big.
- We need something
that can transmit the load
From the generator
to barry's body
Without shorting out.
- The treadmill.
My baby could take the charge.
- What if barry can't?
- Well, that's up to mr. Allen.
- Where are you going?
- I'm gonna talk to him.
- No. No.
- Okay, you didn't see him
at the substation.
He needed to feed.
I got super speed out of
the particle accelerator blast,
But his best friends died.
He woke up with a disease.
- Earlier today,
you worked a crime scene
Where this metahuman
electrocuted an innocent man.
He's a murderer!
And you are powerless
to defend yourself against him.
- He may just need help
like I did.
I don't need my powers
to offer him that.
I have to try.
- Tockman?
Tockman.
Tockman!
- I am presently in control
Of eight
of central city's finest,
Three underpaid assistants,
And one very brave
civilian girl.
- You've got demands;
I want to hear them.
But first let the civilians go.
- Would you prefer
I sent them out alive or dead?
Please be more specific.
One helicopter,
one vegetarian takeout meal,
One laptop
with eight gigabytes of ram
Will be delivered on this roof
at exactly 53 minutes
And 27 seconds from now,
Or I shoot a hostage.
- There is a citywide blackout.
I'm gonna need more time.
- Captain, you may delay,
but time will not.
- Benjamin franklin.
- Very good, detective.
- Hey, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, easy.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- You can't hurt me.
Where is harrison wells?
- Look,
I know what happened to you.
The night of the accelerator
explosion, it changed you.
It changed me too.
- You were the one
in the red suit.
- I fed from you.
I have to keep feeding.
- All right, I know
this has to be terrifying.
That's why I want to help you,
okay?
- The night of the explosion,
when the light hit me,
It stopped my heart.
Jake and darya--
- They were your friends.
- I woke up,
and they were beside me, dead.
They tried to give me cpr.
They were touching me,
and I electrocuted them.
- This is not your fault.
- I know.
Wells did this to me.
- Farooq,
you need to listen to me.
- Not sure
how long that will hold.
- Done being noble, mr. Allen?
Caitlin, get him
to the treadmill.
Cisco,
bring the generator online.
Make sure barry gets the charge.
- What?
You're not coming with me?
I am not leaving you.
- Listen to me.
Of everything
I've done in my life,
Of everything I have invented,
My most important creation
is the flash.
Barry allen must have a future.
Now, go.
Go!
- End this now,
and I'll talk to the d.A.
- It was your district attorney
that denied me furlough
So I could visit my dying sister
one last time,
Say good-bye to her in person.
That's time I'll never get back!
So however long
I have in this life,
I promise not one second more
will be spent in a prison cell.
[gunshot]
- Got him.
[gunshots]
- eddie!
[screams]
Eddie.
Eddie, eddie.
- An officer was just shot
9.2 seconds ago.
I'd pick up the pace in meeting
my demands, captain.
- I'm not healing fast anymore.
That's unfortunate.
- Don't worry.
When dr. Wells has a theory,
he's usually right.
- What if something happens
to joe and iris first?
[electricity crackling]
- Come to check on your pet?
Why don't you just kill me, huh?
Get it over with.
- Quid pro quo.
That's latin, mr. Woodward.
You've heard of latin?
Quid pro quo means something
for something,
And in this case
that something is your freedom.
I'm prepared to grant it to you.
- How do you know
I won't kill you?
- Let's call that
a calculated risk,
One I'm willing to take.
- Really?
- That's right.
- Why would you do that?
- Because there is
another metahuman
Loose in this facility.
I want you to kill him.
[electricity crackling]
- Did you know the human body
generates electricity?
The average person
gives off 342 watts,
And I can smell it
coming from you.
[suspenseful music]
♪
[electricity crackling]
- Turn on the treadmill.
- You're still hurt.
- We don't have time!
- Been dying to punch somebody.
Ouch.
- Caitlin!
- I can't.
- We don't have a choice.
- If I turn this on,
it could kill you.
- If you don't,
we could all die.
- I already lost someone
I cared about in this building.
I can't do it again.
- Listen, someone once told me
That I was struck by that
lightning for a reason,
That it chose me.
I'm not sure I believe it.
Right now, it doesn't matter
what I believe.
What do you believe?
Come on.
- [grunts]
- my god, are you okay?
Did you feel anything?
- It didn't work.
[loud boom]
- Please, he's bleeding.
You have to let us
get him some help.
- You'll stay where you are.
- And while you're killing time,
he's bleeding out.
- [laughs]
As if you could kill time
without wounding eternity.
- Henry david thoreau.
- Ooh, good.
A little battlefield trick.
- Eddie.
- [screams]
- If he lives long enough
to receive medical treatment,
They'll know the exact time
the tourniquet was applied.
What?
No "thank you"?
- They call you the clock king,
right?
- A somewhat florid appellation,
But I've grown to see
the humor in it.
- You're going back to prison.
- Really?
[laughs]
And--and how do you reckon?
- Because the flash is coming.
- Oh.
- Oh, where are you?
[electricity crackling]
- Tony.
Hey, tony, what are you doing?
- Oh, come on.
You know me, allen.
I never run from a fight.
- All right,
well, stay with me, okay?
You're good.
- Run.
- What?
Hey, tony.
No.
- [gasps]
barry.
[helicopter blades whirring]
- Early.
You ever seen the city
at night by helicopter?
It's quite spectacular.
- You're winded.
That's not good.
- I need to take your blood
and figure out what happened.
- I can't believe he's dead.
- Dr. Wells?
- No, no.
Tony woodward.
- He escaped from the pipeline.
- He must have got out
when the blackout hit.
- Not possible.
The pipeline was designed
to withstand a power outage.
Someone had to have let him go.
- I did.
I released him.
- Why?
- To divert
our intruder's attention
While we worked
to restore your speed.
- You used him as a distraction?
- An unnecessary one,
as it turns out.
It seems the plan has failed.
- I--
I have his blood on me.
How could you do that?
- You're showing a lot
of sentiment for a man
Who tormented you as a child.
- Tony might have been
a bully then and now,
But he didn't deserve to die.
- Does caitlin or cisco or me
Or you?
I had a choice to make,
him or us.
I chose us
without a second thought.
- Well, all your talk
about miracle cures
And scientific breakthroughs,
But you don't care about people
at all.
- Well, maybe you care too much,
barry.
I know being a hero
is important to you,
And I respect your ideals.
I just don't have the luxury
of sharing them.
- I forgot.
Your game's chess.
We're all just pawns to you,
right?
So what's your move, doctor?
Which one of us
gets sacrificed next?
[electricity crackling]
- We have to get
out of the facility.
- We just left him on d level.
- We'll never make it
to the main entrance from here.
- What about the garage,
the mobile lab van?
- It's my move, mr. Allen,
And I say we make a run for it.
- Oh, my god.
Barry, look.
Your cells, they're rapidly
regenerating.
- I still don't have my speed.
- It must be mental,
not physical.
- Oh, you have the yips.
- The whats?
- You know.
When a second baseman all of
a sudden can't throw to first
Or a golfer tries to putt
And they get all embarrassed
and upset,
And then that makes
the yips worse,
And it's a hot mess,
And then they feel
like even more of a failure.
- That's not helping.
- Look, you asked
if I believed
You were struck by lightning
for a reason,
If you were chosen.
I believe.
You should too.
[loud boom]
- Let's move.
- Tockman, no.
No, don't do this,
not her.
No, take me, please.
- Something tells me you
will not be a docile passenger.
She will.
- Dad. Dad.
- Wait, wait!
Let her say good-bye.
This is her boyfriend
lying here dying,
And I think you and me both know
that he probably won't make it.
It's wrong that you didn't get
to say good-bye to your sister.
Give them what you deserved.
- You have 20 seconds.
- Eddie. Eddie.
- Sorry, babe.
- No, please.
You have to hang on
for me, okay?
I'm gonna be right back.
- [whispers]
- Let's go.
- Second van, keys are inside.
Come on.
[engine turns over]
Get in!
Come on!
Come on.
- He's here.
- Barry.
- Quickly.
Time and tide wait for no man.
- Wait, let her say good-bye.
- You have 20 seconds.
- Ankle holster.
[gun cocks]
[gunshot]
- Iris!
- Oh, my god, are you okay?
- I'm okay.
Come on.
- Did he hit you?
- I'm okay.
Guys.
- Oh, my god.
Oh, my god.
No, please.
- Hey!
You're here for me.
- Finally you show your face.
- Well, I wasn't exactly eager
to be killed.
- Neither were my friends.
- I know.
I hurt a lot of people
that night.
- People?
You don't even know their names.
- Jake davenport.
Darya kim.
Ralph dibny, al rothstein,
Grant emerson, will everett,
Bea da costa, ronnie raymond.
I know the names of every person
who died that night.
I know they all mattered,
And the fact that the world is
now deprived of their potential
Is something that I have to
live with every day,
But these people--these people
have done nothing wrong.
You want to punish me?
Fine, let's do that,
But let these people live.
- You died that night too.
[electricity crackling]
- No!
- You just didn't know it
till today.
- [screaming]
[panting]
Iris.
[indistinct radio chatter]
- We could have called him
"blackout."
- He had a name, cisco.
- I'm just not sure
what happened.
Why didn't he just siphon
all my powers like before?
- Because you finally stopped
thinking about your powers
And just connected to them.
Look, this is a sample
of your blood
From just after you were struck
by lightning.
Now your cells are generating
more energy than ever before.
It was more energy than the meta
could safely handle.
It's almost like
he choked on you.
- But what does that mean?
- It means you've
kicked it up a notch.
- Dr. Wells.
What I said about how you don't
care about people, I--
- No, look, barry.
There is a reason that
my biography describes me
As arrogant, prickly, brusque--
- "at times contemptuous."
I read it twice.
- You were right.
I don't care much for people,
barry.
I find them misinformed,
shortsighted.
- So why do you do what you do?
Why get up in the morning?
- Because I believe
in a better future,
One that I very much
want to see,
One that you are a part of.
I might not much care
for people, barry,
But I care about you.
- Trauma team to the nicu.
Trauma team to the nicu.
[knocks]
- Hey, allen.
- Hey, eddie.
- Flowers.
That's so nice.
[giggles]
- Where were you all night?
- Home, trying to eat all
the ice cream before it melted.
- I love ice cream.
[laughs]
- He is on pain meds,
lots of them,
But he's gonna be okay.
It's been some night.
I am gonna get some coffee.
I'll be back.
- Dude.
- Awesome.
I guess you're feeling better.
- Oh, yeah.
- Did you guys see that?
- You're just high, partner.
- Right, I forgot.
[laughs]
- Oh, now you show up.
- I'm sorry
I wasn't there for you today.
It couldn't be helped.
- It's okay.
A girl's got to be her own hero
every now and again.
- I promise I'll never
be late again.
- My best friend
is always saying that,
And he is always late.
- You're worth being
on time for.
- Honey, you all right?
- Yeah, why?
- You forgot your coffee.
- Oh, uh...
- Good day, dr. Wells.
- Yes, it is, gideon.
Bring up my log, please,
new entry.
It has now been 312 days
since lightning struck.
In the past 24 hours,
Subject has taken
a great leap forward,
Causing me to revise
my initial thesis.
I thought--well, I thought
his attachment to people
Was a distraction
slowing down his progress.
Now I realize
the opposite is true.
Barry's attachment to people,
the people he cares about,
Is actually the key
to getting him up to speed.
In the meantime,
good news.
The future remains intact.
You're early.
- Yeah, I know.
It feels weird to me too.
- I thought after yesterday,
you'd want to sleep in.
- Can't.
There's too much work to do.
I'm ready to do it.
I want to push myself,
Find out how fast
I can really go.
You were right.
This is not just about me.
- Let's get to work.
Now, you...
Had the ability
to steal the flash's powers,
And I...
Would love to know...
How you did that.
- Greg, move your head.