My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
But when my daughter came back from the future to help,
she changed the present.
And now our world is more dangerous than ever,
and I'm the only one fast enough to save it.
I am the Flash.
You failed.
Why are you doing this?
You did this to yourself.
And now all of you will perish.
My name is Dr. John Deegan, and I, like most of you,
I'm a psychiatrist.
Do you know what my patients tell me the most?
They feel inferior.
I'm here to tell you, whether we admit it or not,
some people, they're just born lucky,
which leads us to the real problem, imperfection.
How can we ever hope to feel like
supermen or superwomen
without first becoming super ourselves?
I'm here to tell you how, folks.
If we utilize eugenic insights, I feel--
Hey, Frankenstein, go back to your mad scientist lab.
Ma'am, ma'am, please-- would you wait, please?
Folks, folks, folks, please listen.
I'm just saying, we can truly help our patients.
Listen to me!
Idiots!
Doctor.
Dr. John Deegan.
I need your help, John.
Go find someone else to prank, douchebag.
My God, what are you?
Something beyond your comprehension.
I've traveled far to this place and time
to lay this precious burden at your feet.
Use this book to reshape the world as you see fit.
Show them what a real god can do, John.
Why me?
You have vision.
That book holds the key to your transformation, John,
and all you have to do is open it.
Use it wisely, John.
The universe is in your hands.
I can--I can see...
I can see everything.
And a word of advice:
think big.
Honey, breakfast is ready.
Honey.
It'll get cold.
What?
Morning.
Look, babe, they're perfect this time.
What if Barry walks in?
What if he could have seen that?
See...
Where's Barry?
Did you get enough sleep last night?
Look, babe, I know that we haven't caught Cicada,
but Caitlin's immunity can help us.
Who's Cicada?
Our big bad.
Barry, are you okay?
I'm Barry?
What is wrong?
Honey, hi. Talk to me.
I did not get enough sleep.
Are you--you sure it's not my cooking?
'Cause...
No, no.
These smell delicious.
Thank you.
You know what?
I think that you call Captain Singh
and you ask for a day off.
Look, with all the superhero-ing you've been doing,
I think you've earned it, honey.
You think maybe I should go into S.T.A.R. Labs?
What-- what?
Only my husband would think working on Speed Force equations
would be called a day off.
I love you, Barry Allen.
I love you, Iris West-Allen.
Break in at Ivo Labs.
Cisco's on comms.
I'll meet you guys at S.T.A.R. Labs.
Whew. That's a rush.
Sorry, I polished it last night
and left it on our dresser.
Oh, Barry, what have you done this time?
Barry, we got a break-in at Ivo Labs,
two armed men going after diamonds,
the ones they use for conductors.
Hey, pump the brakes.
You're gonna have to hang a U-ey,
'cause you passed Ivo by about 18 blocks.
Found it.
Someone's excited to get to work.
It is too early for this.
Forget it, Flash.
We're leaving with the diamonds, or this guy dies.
I said back off.
Hey, what are you doing there?
Just hit the guy with the lightning punch.
You have failed this city.
Pretty sure that's not your line.
Your adrenaline levels are off the charts.
What's going on?
Overkill much?
Cops are on the way.
Why don't you just let them take over from here?
So he's fine, Caitlin?
Oh, God, thank goodness.
Really? There are no anomalies?
I don't-- I don't have a brain tumor?
Nothing?
Barry, you're in perfect shape.
Babe, tell me about it. I mean, hi, these abs.
And they're all mine.
Maybe we could lay off the public displays of affection,
just at work, you know?
Since when?
You're always saying that touch is your love language.
That's right, Ralph.
Just feel like we're being very insensitive to all of you.
Oh, man, we've talked about this.
I'm over Gypsy, okay?
But I appreciate the thought.
I'll be all right.
I'm gonna go home...
Because I need to think.
Think?
What are you guys doing?
Following you into the hallway.
'Cause something is definitely up.
You need to talk about it?
Yeah, Barry,
you haven't seemed like yourself all morning.
I'm fine.
I just think that maybe I should go
and talk with someone who might better understand
what I'm going through.
I'm gonna go see Oliver Queen.
I'll be back.
Dig, what are you doing here?
I'm kicking your butt.
Now get up, come on.
You guys redecorate the Bunker?
Oliver, you've been to ARGUS a million times.
Oliver?
I'm Oliver Queen.
Yeah, I'll say.
I'm the Green Arrow.
Holy crap.
I've been hanging with a tough crowd, huh?
Yeah, you think?
Look, I need to make a call, just to S.T.A.R. Labs,
just for some important Green Arrow business.
- You know how it is. - Later.
What's that?
We've got Bratvas fighting Bertinelli's
over in old Diaz weapons cache in the Glades.
I could really use some backup, Oliver.
Oh, man, I don't know if I'm feeling up for it.
I think I just tweaked something.
ARGUS rapid response is on another mission.
We're the only ones that can make it in time.
- Okay, yeah, I'm in. - Good.
Suit up.
How do I put this...
I forget, do--do I need help putting this on?
What are you doing?
I thought you going to fire an incendiary arrow.
So did I.
Did you freaking see that?
Stop fooling around and get the driver.
Damn.
Diggle!
No--no.
Oh, man. Oh, I'm glad to see you.
Uh-huh, yeah.
Nice outfit.
This can't be a coincidence.
There--there has to be a reason behind this,
which means that someone is responsible.
We need to know who--hey, can you--can you not do that?
Man, what a total "Freaky Friday."
No, wait, we didn't switch bodies.
It's more of a "Quantum Leap." Where's a mirror?
Focus, just for a second,
and take this seriously because the world thinks
that you're Oliver Queen and that I'm Barry Allen,
and I would really like to know why.
- Totally. - Is that cool?
- Yes. - Thank you.
I'm sorry.
Weird.
Hey, Mayor.
Just, if you could--just for 90 seconds of seriousness.
You gotta admit, this is a little cool.
I will find it a lot cooler when I wake up
in my own bed tomorrow morning.
You woke up in bed with Iris?
We have to fix this right now!
Let me get this straight.
You believe that you are not Barry Allen,
but in fact, he is?
Barry, did you time travel again?
No, I didn't.
- She's talking to Barry. - Sorry--
I am Barry.
- Yeah, and I'm Wild Dog. - Easy, Wild Dog.
Sarcasm.
It's not great sarcasm, Cisco.
- Do you mind if I... - No, of course not.
Oliver's brain scan is perfectly normal,
no signs of hypnosis or psychic interference.
Tachyon meters are clear.
No one's screwing with the Timeline.
Guys, come on, this is crazy.
I mean, there's no way that
I could be married to Oliver Queen.
Sorry, but, babe,
you know he's not my type, right?
Iris, you really don't believe me?
We're telling the truth.
Okay? We're telling the truth.
Something is very, very wrong with reality.
Yeah.
All right, Team Flash meeting.
Not you, Barry.
Th--uh...
I've only got eyes for you, you know that.
I sw--if you touch her...
I didn't touch her.
You thought about it.
All right, well, if your team's not gonna help us,
then we have to keep moving.
They'll help us, okay? They'll help us.
We just gotta get--we just gotta get Iris on board first.
Good--fine, how--how are you going to convince her?
I'm not, you are.
- She's your wife. - I know, man.
I know, I don't--I don't like this anymore than you do.
You just gotta tell her how much you care about her.
Tell her she's your lightning rod.
I'm not--I'm not saying that.
Just say it. Trust me.
It works every time.
Mind if I join you?
Yeah.
This should help.
I guess you forgot you can't get drunk?
This day could not get any worse.
You really think that you're Oliver?
Yeah.
You know, Felicity called me when Oliver was in prison.
Do you know how he ended up in Slabside?
She--she called you?
He cut a deal, Barry,
completely behind Felicity's back.
He didn't even warn her.
The FBI just showed up and took him away.
She said all that?
She's hurting.
Oliver's life, it's completely defined
by anger, vengeance.
That's why I am so lucky to have you in my life.
Are you not the least bit worried
that reality might be broken?
Don't you have to consider what we're telling you is the truth?
Isn't it possible?
Yeah, yeah, it is,
which is why I'm really sorry, Barry.
Would you--I thought I couldn't get drunk.
Nanites, courtesy of Ray Palmer.
Whoever you are, we need to get you to a safe place
until we can figure out what happened.
I hope you can understand.
Oh, come on.
Sorry, dude.
Guys, come--
Guys, come on!
Let us out of here!
Come on.
Why are we in your secret prison?
It's not a prison.
It's a Tesla conductor tube that dampens meta-powers.
Okay, it's a prison.
We just need to convince everybody
that we're not crazy!
How?
How do you suggest that we do that?
Because everyone on Earth thinks that we're each other.
- That's it. - Hmm?
Maybe it's just Earth-1 that's been affected.
If we can get an extrapolator,
breach to Earth-38 and find Kara.
If she remembers us, then maybe she can help
fix whatever's happened.
You skipped the part where you explain how we escape.
Were you able to get in touch with ARGUS?
Well, I tried, but I kept getting interference
at 650 nanometers.
Isn't that the wavelength for red light?
Red light, exactly.
And when I checked the city's weather cams,
this is what I found:
red skies, yellow lightning.
So you think Barry and Oliver's shared psychosis
is a result of weird weather?
Stranger things, right?
Okay, I'll run their scans again.
Best off giving up now.
Who the frak is that?
I spent the past seven months in a maximum security prison,
and no matter who bad things got--and they got bad--
every cell had a toilet.
You sure you can't hold it?
Oh, you wanna back up the pipes.
And fry the dampener, yes.
That's a good idea.
Okay.
One problem, I'm not gonna be able to reach the valve
with these on.
You're gonna have to dislocate your thumb.
Are you crazy? I'm--
I'm not crazy. You need to dislocate your thumb.
Just apply pressure to the joint.
No, I'm gonna break my hand--
You're not gonna break your hand,
because in this reality,
your ligaments have been stretched and conditioned
in the art of escape by Anatoly Knyazev.
Now, man up, apply pressure to the joint,
and dislocate your thumb.
- It worked. - Yeah.
All right.
Okay, now just wait for it.
Dampener's down. Now what?
You're gonna have to phase us out of here.
What?
Phasing.
That's when I vibrate at the frequency of air,
causing all the cells in my body to get so excited
I can pass through solid objects.
Right, "Phasing."
Want any advice?
One-second cure. Barry, please.
I'm just saying, it's not an easy move,
and if you screw this up
then you're gonna come out of the phase
halfway through the glass.
What?
Why are you laughing?
I didn't realize...
- Your thumb looks ridiculous. - Oh, my God.
I didn't realize that's how mine looked.
Well, look at that, you did it.
Great.
Don't leave me, man.
Figured it out.
All right, let's go.
Get the extrapolator and get out of here.
I can't let you do that, Barry.
Iris, please, I know how weird this is,
but somewhere inside, you know we're telling the truth,
that it's me, Barry.
Do you remember when I first moved in?
Joe brought me to the house after my mom was killed.
I looked at you and I said, "My dad didn't do it."
- And then you said... - "I believe you."
You always did.
And now I need you to believe me again.
Iris, you're my lightning rod.
Quick, before I change my mind.
We'll fix this, I promise.
I'm writing it.
We've been over this, hon.
No, you talked, I ignored.
You need a new muffler.
I think this is a tie rod end.
Come on, Kara, back me up here.
Uh, no, thanks.
I know better than to get involved
in a debate with Lois Lane.
But you do know the feeling,
that itch, that fire in the back of your head,
the siren song of a story that has to be written.
Yeah, I do, I do.
The world is gonna want to know why Lois Lane
went to Argo City with Superman.
Details, I'll make up a reason.
Oh, so much for truth in journalism.
Says the reporter who writes about
his own exploits as Superman.
I was the first human to set foot on what's left of Krypton,
to lay eyes on the Jewel Mountains,
to endure the endless,
torturous deliberations of the High Council,
and I have to write about it.
One small step for Lois Lane,
one giant leap for Lois Lane's career.
Says the woman who is already the most famous, feared,
and intrepid reporter on two planets.
And yet someone on this farm
is still making 21бщ on the dollar more than me.
And it ain't Kara, honey.
You two catch up.
I am gonna go slam some small things really hard.
Okay, just be careful on that ladder.
It's really old.
You'll catch me.
Break time, boss?
I've never been challenged like that before,
just to my face:
"Tell us who you are, Supergirl."
Well, except for Ms. Grant.
Well, and I'm sure it was harder
when it's the president doing the threatening.
- Cat was scarier. - Yeah.
Do you think I did the right thing?
Our secret identities, they protect the people we love
from being threatened by our enemies.
There aren't a lot of things more important than that.
I'm just sad I have to leave the DEO,
and now Alex is there alone. I feel like I let her down.
Oh, and then I left you to defend Earth alone
so I could go to Argo.
- Nah-- - I'm sorry.
No, don't be sorry about that. It's home.
I'm really glad you got to see it finally,
connect with it.
It was more than just connecting with our culture, you know?
I'm okay.
You know, it was Lois.
Everything new that I experienced on Argo,
she was experiencing it too.
You know, out there we were-- we were both strange visitors.
I must sound so selfish.
No, love is the most unselfish thing in the world...
On any world.
Well, about that.
There's something that I've needed to talk to you about.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
- Who are you? - We come in peace.
Lois, wait, wait.
This is Barry and Oliver. They're friends.
Wait.
So you know that I'm Oliver and he's Barry?
Yeah, w--why wouldn't I?
Oh, man.
Okay.
Um, you guys, this is my cousin Clark.
I'm so glad you get to meet.
Your cousin. That cousin?
The super cousin?
Oh, please, call me Clark.
Uh, welcome to our farm.
Cool.
Are you puffing out your chest?
Yes.
Lois Lane, "Daily Planet."
Wait, why did you guys think I wouldn't recognize you?
Well...
Oh. Well, that's new.
We could use your help.
All units to Waid and Augustyn.
Something's destroying IVO Labs.
He has our powers.
Okay, come on, man.
I mean, I've been shooting paint cans all afternoon.
Unless--unless a paint can rewrote reality
- and made us swap lives... - I get it.
Then you need actual combat training, Barry.
All right, fine. You know what?
Why don't you go over there, run at me,
and I'll try and hit you with an arrow.
Right, okay.
Where did you bury the remote control bows?
Dude.
Come on, I'm not you.
Yeah, well, okay.
Ready!
Here we go.
Nice try.
Oh, I've been waiting four years for that, man.
Oh, it's priceless. Hold on.
Need to get a photo.
What?
I got it, don't worry. Hold on a second.
That's great.
You think this is funny?
Do you think my skills are a joke?
Come on, man.
I was a much better sport when you shot me.
I shot you to teach you how to case an environment.
You shot me to get a laugh.
- All right. - You know what?
Fine, fine. Come at me.
Try to get--try to get one hit in.
Deck him, Barry!
What? He's a jerk.
I'm not doing this. This isn't how I train.
Oh, you train? Really?
I thought your powers just dropped out of the sky.
If you're trying to get a rise out of me,
it's not gonna work.
Need a peanut gallery?
Can you not do anything without your wife in your ear?
Are you serious, man?
Felicity invented quarterbacking.
I don't think that you can go more than nine hours
without some sappy motivational speech.
I'm not doing this.
Your team betrayed you.
You needed them, and they weren't there.
I'm not doing this.
You know, if you really knew how to use my speed,
I never could have laid a finger on you.
That's the guy who attacked us at Ivo Laboratories,
Anti-Meta-human Adaptive Zootomic Organism.
A-m-a-z-o, "Amazo."
Sometimes these things just fall into your lap.
It says Ivo Labs was contracted by ARGUS
to build a unit capable of identifying meta-powers.
He doesn't just scan powers.
He's pumping a nano-adaptive hybrid of the "Mirakuru" Serum.
So that's how he stole our powers.
He scanned our meta-human genes,
then used the Mirakuru hybrid to copy them.
is coming to klaatu barada kick-to our asses,
and we can't let out Flash and Green Arrow to fight it?
Well, we could if they were still here.
Why don't you tell them, Iris West-Allen, what happened.
Hurry.
You let them out?
Okay, look, I know what you're thinking.
But I spoke to Oliver, or whoever he is,
and I could feel something.
Guys, I felt like I was really talking to Barry.
I believe you.
It is weird out there.
These red skies, Barry and Oliver--that,
and I vibed somebody in the Speed Lab.
- What? - Yeah.
Some guy with ridges on his head,
these big muttonchops.
Do you think that the red skies, this guy,
these disparate events are somehow connected?
So Barry and Oliver were mind-swapped
by a guy with muttonchops?
Man, it's not even Tuesday.
It's AMAZO.
He just entered city limits.
Don't tell me you came to say sorry.
I try to avoid saying that word.
Look, man, I get it.
You were just trying to help in your own Oliver way,
trying to get a rise out of me
so I'd fight like you.
Yeah, it's more than that, Barry.
I've been doing this for a very long time.
And nearly every time that I learn a lesson,
it comes with a painful memory.
Watched friends die. I've had to kill to survive.
When I'm the Green Arrow,
I channel those painful memories.
I--I draw on a darkness
every time I draw back my bow.
So to see you with all of my abilities,
just laughing and joking around,
it pissed me off,
more than I would care to admit.
Whenever I run, whatever I'm feeling inside,
grief, guilt, I've gotta just let it go
and focus on whatever I'm running toward:
Iris, my friends, all the joy in my life.
When I'm happy, I run faster,
just like when you phased earlier.
You were having a good time.
You couldn't dislocate your thumb until you got angry.
If you're gonna be the Green Arrow
and I'm gonna be the Flash...
Maybe we need to start acting more like each other.
Yes, finally, God.
Super hearing, sorry.
But I've been sitting in there
waiting for you guys to figure this out
because I have a lot of thoughts, okay?
I should smile more.
Yeah, maybe you should. It might help.
You guys have to act the parts.
Come on, try it.
What?
I'm the Green Arrow.
Wear a mask.
Sound like that--I don't--
Cisco?
Hey, Supergirl, Barry...
Oliver.
You believe us now?
Yeah, we all do.
Sorry we locked you up.
But if you feel like forgiving us
and coming back to Earth-1,
we've got a little bit of a sitch back home,
like a please, for the love of God,
there's a killer robot destroying the city
kind of sitch.
We could use some help.
- Let's do it. - You wanna tag along?
Cool. Who are you?
A friend.
Where the hell is Cisco?
I'm right here.
And I brought the big guns.
What are they doing?
Trying to keep AMAZO off balance
before it has time to replicate their abilities.
Finish him.
No sign of movement.
Nice work.
We got lucky.
Uh, guys, you might want to get out of the way.
What the hell is he doing?
Exactly what we wanted to avoid.
Well, that's not great.
AMAZO copied all of their powers,
and now it's on the hunt for more.
Cisco, there's got to be something you can do to stop it.
It's a computer, right? So just turn it off.
- I hate it when you're right. - Well, I'm right.
Let's go.
- It can phase. - That's what that's called?
Well, we can't fight what we can't hit.
I've got an idea.
Bring him back here.
No problem.
Move.
When he comes back, knock him down.
He won't be able to phase and run at the same time.
Guys, where are we at?
I think we got it.
We reverse-engineered AMAZO's operating system
and whipped up a virus to wipe the CPU.
- Not so difficult. - Except...
Except it's a robot that has replicated
their super strengths, and, thus,
now it is impenetrable,
so you cannot put the virus inside it.
That's not great.
Okay, so what do we do?
Look, if AMAZO inherited all of their strengths,
then maybe it inherited their weaknesses too.
Only we're not gonna weaken it, Iris.
We're gonna send it straight to hell.
Oliver, you're gonna have to counteract AMAZO's phasing
while Supergirl and Superman hold it.
- Got it. - I'll only have one shot.
Now, bring me that virus, Cisco.
Come here.
Get ready.
Done.
Don't miss.
I won't.
Hurry up!
AMAZO, you have failed this city.
AMAZO has been dismantled
and every piece locked up in a S.T.A.R. Labs vault
except for this one. This is my souvenir.
A round of applause, everybody.
Felicitations, Flash.
That's quite a performance you did out there.
Well, I appreciate that, but still Oliver Queen.
And I am still Barry Allen.
I don't know, guys.
You took down AMAZO in one shot.
Only the Green Arrow can do that.
And, Oliver, you outran AMAZO, just like the Flash.
Maybe we should stick with this whole body swap thing
for a while.
Seems to be working okay.
I don't know that anybody would be too worried
if you two don't switch back.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
We need to figure out who did this to Barry and Oliver
and why and then we're gonna reverse it, okay?
Caitlin, any thoughts?
I haven't quite figured it out yet,
but until I do, I am confident
that Central City and Star City are in good hands.
Speaking of "In good hands,"
I should probably get back to Metropolis and Lois.
If anything were to happen,
her entire world's unprotected.
Yeah, yeah, I get it.
Thank you for helping us, Clark.
We couldn't have stopped AMAZO without you.
Oh, not so sure about that.
Hello, uh, Clark.
Help a genius out, would you?
Look, I want to give you this check...
I do this for free, the whole helping humanity thing.
Oh, you think that I'm giving...
no, no, not for that.
This is a alimony check for my third wife.
She also live on Earth-38,
and I might be a little bit behind in the payment.
If you could just do me the favor...
You want me to deliver this to your ex-wife?
To my ex-wife, my third ex-wife.
You're welcome.
You're welcome too.
It's super.
Man, I can trust him, right?
Are you okay?
No.
You did a great job with AMAZO,
but at what cost, Barry?
What do you mean?
Do you know why I let you and Oliver go?
It was because of something that I felt.
When I stopped looking with my eyes
and I started listening with my heart,
I realized that you,
Barry Allen, have always been
and will always be the man that I love.
No matter what mask I wear,
I'll always show you my true face.
I need you to promise me something, Barry.
Promise me that when we figure out who did this to you
and when you get your speed back
and you're finally back in my arms...
That'll you'll come back to me.
Of course I'll come back.
Barry, I heard what you said right before you took that shot.
You're the Green Arrow now.
But please don't become Oliver Queen.
I won't.
I promise.
Barry, we need you in the workshop.
So you think this person you saw has something to do
with what's happened to Barry and Oliver?
I mean, I saw him right after
these two swapped capes.
You've been having trouble with your vibes lately, right?
- Maybe it's that? - No.
This was beyond me.
It felt like something important.
We need to see it.
Okay, hang on.
My God, I can see everything.
Fascinating.
I wouldn't have thought the men of this Earth
had this capacity.
But it won't avail you.
None of you can stop what's been set into motion.
You're best off giving up now,
because nothing you can do can alter
what's about to happen.
Are you okay?
No, not even close.
What did you see?
This.
I don't recognize him.
Doesn't matter.
I know where to find him.
So what's our next move?
We go to Gotham city.