My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on "The Flash"...
His name is Geomancer.
I'm waiting on the man in red.
The Velocity-7's wearing off.
[gun blasting]
- You hurt?
- Only my pride.
Jesse's my daughter. Zoom has her.
Daddy, please help me.
Don't let him take me, Daddy.
I told you we're a team.
Now you're a part of it.
We're gonna help you save Jesse.
We're not sending you through alone.
We're going to Earth-2.
Just remember what Jay said, okay?
Things here are all sorts of trippy.
Caitlin...
If you knew me at all,
you would know that I hate the name Caitlin.
I'm Killer Frost.
Look out!
Dad!
You killed my father, you evil bitch.
You shouldn't have
palled around with a breacher.
- Flash, save us!
- No!
Zoom wanted him alive.
You know what Zoom will do
if you don't obey him.
No!
- Argh!
- [indistinct shouting]
Look around, Flash.
This is the last place you'll ever see.
I know you're here, Harrison Wells,
and you did not come alone.
[siren wailing]
You can try to hide...
[whooshing sound]
But I'm the fastest man alive.
I will scour this city
until I hunt you down.
And when I do,
all of you will feel my wrath.
CCPN is reporting that Dr. Harrison Wells,
the infamous founder of S.T.A.R. Labs
who uncharacteristically has gone unseen
for nearly four months is now a wanted man.
These images and messages
went up moments ago
throughout Central City by Zoom.
Have you seen channel 52?
You're not safe here, Dr. Wells.
Zoom's looking for you.
I know what he's doing. Alert security.
Evacuate S.T.A.R. Labs.
Lock down the facility.
- What about you?
- Don't worry about me, Henry.
Just get everyone out of here now.
Now! Go!
[gun charging] Harry!
Don't shoot!
[sighs] Damn it, Ramon.
[gasps]
Where's Allen?
- Zoom took him.
- What?
We tracked down Deathstorm and Killer Frost,
met my doppelganger, Reverb...
super evil guy, super evil powers.
The three of them almost
took down Barry until
Zoom showed up, killed Cisco-2,
killed Deathstorm for hurting a speedster.
But then he left Killer Frost alive
and then took off with Barry.
How are you still alive?
Looks like he cares even less about me
than you do, Harry.
No, no.
Zoom doesn't do anything by accident.
Did he follow you here?
I've seen “Heat” like 50 times, okay?
I know how to shake a tail.
He didn't follow me.
But check this out.
I jacked these from my dead ringer.
I think we can tweak these puppies...
use them to find Zoom.
Damn it, Ramon, we don't have time for this.
Zoom is hunting us...
Zoom is hunting us!
We need to make an alternate plan,
because if we don't, Zoom...
Stop thinking like that, okay?
We're gonna find Jesse,
and we're gonna find Barry.
I know we will.
Hello? Is anyone there?
Okay, whoever's responsible for this,
oh, ho, ho...
boy, we're gonna have words,
the two of us, okay?
This is... this is not okay.
Barry-2.
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
[sighs] Dr. Wells,
this is very disappointing.
I mean, the two of you
should be ashamed of yourselves.
You can't just lock someone
in a room like this.
How long was I in here for?
Barely a day.
One day?
Oh, jeez, my wife's gonna be worried sick.
- Dr. Wells.
- Yeah?
Doctor, I'm not sure
if you're aware of this,
but my wife is
a very well-respected detective
in the Central City Police Department.
She's got to be very upset.
Whoa, this is heavy.
It certainly is.
And I'm sorry, fellas,
but I demand to know what the heck
is going on here this instant.
Barry, this is a very long story.
One that we don't have time
to tell right now.
We're sorry we locked you in that room
for a day, but right now, you need to leave.
- You need to gather...
- [alarm blaring]
He's here.
[indistinct shouting]
Do not move.
[dramatic music]
♪
[whooshing sound]
Ugh!
Where are Wells and his friends?
♪
Dr. Wells, hey, what the heck is going on?
Oh, Zoom's after us.
Zoom? What do...
Why would Zoom be after you?
That's part of that long story
I was telling you about.
I don't know if I can
deal with something like this.
- You have a time vault?
- Yeah.
I'm an enemy of Zoom,
and I need a place to hide
when something like this happens.
- Get in!
- Yes, sir.
♪
That's Zoom! That's Zoom!
- [wheezing]
- Ramon...
Shut him up.
♪
[whimpering]
[gasps]
Okay.
Breathe, breathe, breath, breath...
Fake wall.
He's not gonna fall for another fake wall.
We need to move.
We need to find a different place to hide
and make a plan.
Wait, wait... hey, hey, hey, hey.
No.
I think before we do anything,
you have to explain to me everything
that is going on here.
You're wasting your time.
I used to think I could escape too
when I first got here.
There's no way out.
[tapping]
Who is that?
I don't know.
He's been here since Zoom
brought me to this place.
[tapping]
Stop, okay?
Just... just please stop.
Jesse, I think he might
be trying to help us.
Nothing is gonna help us.
That's not true.
We're gonna get out of here.
Your dad's gonna find us, I promise.
You sure have a lot of faith
in a man who only cares about himself.
[sighs]
You know, I actually thought that
at first too.
It's not true.
Every decision that he's made...
every action he's taken since we've met...
has been to save you.
Your dad hasn't given up on you, Jesse.
Don't give up on him.
[whooshing noise] [gasps]
Believe what you want,
but the only reason that you're still alive
is so I can kill you
in front of your father.
And the only reason
your father's still alive...
[ominous music]
Is to get me your speed.
♪
Once he does that,
he will die too.
Up after the break,
earthquake-causing meta-human
leaves citizens shaken and wondering,
where is The Flash?
It's finished.
Breach stabilized again.
Barry, Cisco, and Wells
have 20 hours to get back.
You're amazing.
When it comes to
stabilizing breaches, maybe...
not so much when it comes
to fighting meta-humans.
You were a little rusty.
I was too slow.
Geomancer's still out there, Caitlin.
He has to be stopped.
I have to be ready in case he attacks again.
How much longer till the Velocity...
8.
Velocity-8 is ready?
I need to finalize the compound...
make sure the extracellular
matrix stays intact
so you don't lose your speed as fast.
Okay, great.
What is it?
After your last encounter with Geomancer,
I ran some tests.
The Velocity-7 is reacting
with the damaged cells in your body.
It's causing more cellular degeneration.
Well, I have faith that the next batch
won't do the same thing.
Jay, I can't keep giving this to you
if it's hurting you.
If it'll help me defeat Geomancer,
you might have to.
Till Barry gets back,
I may be the only chance this city has.
I don't know how this is possible,
but you somehow made basketball
sound more boring than baseball.
Fix this.
Scott Evans, your new editor.
- Oh, Iris...
- West, I know.
You wrote the story about
the recent Geomancer attack.
- Yeah, I did.
- I'm not running that.
What, why?
It's a fluff piece to try
to make people feel good.
What they need to know is the truth;
The Flash might not always
be there to save them.
You disagree?
I think that he's saved a lot of people
in this city.
But where is he now?
I need to run a real story.
Okay, uh...
what if I could get you an exclusive
with the meta-human that fought Geomancer?
This... this other Flash.
What, you friends with him too?
Just, um, give me a little time.
Fine, but if it's the same
as the other crap that you wrote,
I'm gonna run something about how The Flash
may not be the hero we all dreamed he was.
[dramatic music]
♪
[sighs]
Iris... Hey, Iris.
Barry, where were you last night?
[whispering] Oh, my God.
My father died yesterday,
and you never even came home.
I know, I know. I heard.
I'm so, so sorry.
You... you heard?
You were there, Barry.
I actually was not there.
I'm... I'm gonna... yeah, okay.
Okay, look.
Come to my lab. Just come up to my lab.
I'm gonna explain everything, okay?
I'm gonna explain it.
So the Barry from yesterday was not you?
No.
No, look, I... I know
that this is hard to believe,
but I mean, it is just like
that sci-fi series,
“Commander Carl, Space
Marshal of the Galaxy, ”
where Carl gets sucked into a black hole
and ends up on another planet
that he thinks is Earth,
but really it's Earth...
of another universe.
Have... have you guys not s...
oh, it's a seminal episode.
You should check it out.
So that's why you weren't wearing
your wedding ring yesterday.
Well...
And... and that...
that kiss was... was so...
I'm... I'm sorry. He got frisky with you?
[sighs]
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay, I'm gonna have to find this guy
and give him a piece of my mind.
Don't give him too much.
Your husband tells us
you've been tracking Zoom.
Yeah, I've been trying to. Why?
- We need to find his lair.
- Lair?
He's a bad guy; I'm calling it a lair.
Zoom is looking for you.
Why are you going after him?
Zoom has my daughter
and our Barry, and we need
to rescue them both.
Look, I want to find Zoom
just as much as anybody,
but no one can track him.
The only person who would know
where he would be hiding someone
would be a meta that's worked with him.
A meta like Killer Frost?
Yeah, maybe.
But Zoom kept her alive yesterday
because she always obeys him.
There is no way that she's
gonna tell you where he is.
I'm not so sure about that.
If she loved Deathstorm as much
as my Caitlin loved Ronnie,
I think she'd be more than upset
at Zoom for killing him.
Look, finding her is gonna be
just as hard as finding Zoom.
But if anyone can do it...
My husband can.
Right, yes.
I can, actually.
Um, all right.
[humming]
Okay, well it looks like
Patty Spivot was a CSI tech
on most of the Killer Frost cases.
She's pretty thorough, so...
What's that?
Oh, this is Killer Frost meta-data
collected from numerous crime scenes...
DNA trace movements, facial recognition,
temperature fluctuations specific to her.
My algorithm compiles all the data
and gives us an approximate location.
It works on most metas,
except for Zoom, of course.
He's too fast... never leaves a trace.
Okay.
Looks like the best bet's the woodlands.
Best CSI in Central City.
You know where that is, right?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Wait, I'm going with you guys.
You're gonna need some help. Okay.
Iris, I...
Barry, Zoom and his followers
are the reason that my father is dead.
If I can stop him from killing anyone else,
I'm gonna try.
Okay, then I'm coming too.
- No.
Barry, this is not what you do.
I know that.
But I also know Joseph
didn't like me too much,
but he was my father-in-law.
If you're going,
I am coming with you.
[dramatic music]
All right.
You can come, but you stay out of our way.
[sighs]
[tapping]
That's not Morse code.
I know he's trying to tell us something.
We just have to find the pattern.
♪
[tapping]
There's no pattern, Barry.
♪
You know, your dad, who I'm pretty sure
is one of the smartest people
to live on either of our Earths,
told me the only person smarter than him
was you.
He said that?
♪
If that's true,
we work together...
I know we can figure this out.
♪
Worth a shot?
Okay.
[tapping]
Well, he never goes past five.
What?
He never goes past five knocks
without pausing.
Right? Listen.
[tapping]
♪
Hey, you're right.
I think...
I think I know what that is.
It's a five-by-five tap code used by POWs.
That would only get us to 25 letters,
and there's 26 in the alphabet.
Not if you combine C and K.
They sound the same.
Let's try it out.
♪
- Worth a shot.
- All right.
[tapping]
There it is.
Looks different than before.
That's because I realized
that there was a flaw
with Velocity-8,
so I reformulated
the extracellular matrix, and...
Velocity-9.
You know what they say,
ninth time's the charm.
Hey.
Hey, Iris. You okay?
Yeah, I'm just a little
worried about the time.
Well, don't worry.
They'll make it back before
we close the breach.
Um, actually I was here
to talk to you about something else.
Oh. Yeah, sure.
What is it?
Well, my new editor
wants me to write a scathing article
on The Flash not being able
to protect Central City
from Geomancer.
Really?
Yeah.
I was hoping to write
an article about you instead...
something that would calm people
until Barry got back.
You know, Iris,
I don't know if that's the best idea.
Well, I think that if people
knew that there was someone
that could protect them,
it would...
it would really help.
Would you just think about it?
[alarm blaring]
Some crazy alarm's going off.
Yeah.
Don't even think about running.
There's a new Flash in town.
You know, the one with the shiny helmet.
Not the speedster I was hoping to crack,
but let's see just how fast he is,
Central City.
[suspenseful music]
♪
Give me the Velocity-9.
Jay, we have no idea how long it will last.
We don't have time to
figure that out, Caitlin.
♪
[electricity crackling]
[shouting]
[crowd screaming]
♪
[whooshing sound]
[panting]
Jay?
I'm okay.
That just took a lot out of me.
[panting]
But it sure felt good.
[laughing]
That was amazing, Jay.
Thanks. I kind of surprised myself,
to be honest.
Caitlin deserves all the credit.
Looks like your Velocity-9's a winner.
I still need to run some tests.
[panting]
Iris, about the interview, um...
I think that I have everything that I need.
Great.
'Cause I could really use a nap.
I'll, uh, be downstairs.
[tapping]
Two down, five across.
- It's J.
- J?
That's what you're tapping... the letter J?
All right, what's next?
[tapping]
A.
All right.
[tapping]
Five down...
Four across. Y.
J-A-Y?
You're spelling “Jay.”
As in Jay Garrick?
He's... he's alive.
But he's on my Earth.
[banging]
Hey, hey...
Stop, stop... hey...
Stop... look, I'm sorry.
I don't know what you mean.
Jay Garrick didn't come with us.
Look, just keep tapping, please.
We don't understand.
Please.
[dramatic music]
Don't talk to them again.
♪
[panting]
I'm gonna get out of here.
And I'm gonna destroy you.
[groaning]
All I need from you is your speed, Flash.
And you only need to be barely alive
for me to get it.
[blows landing]
Stop!
♪
[grunting]
[blows landing]
Stop!
♪
Barry...
Barry, are you okay?
Yeah.
[panting]
I'm okay.
[grunts]
♪
Zoom just showed me how to
get out of this thing.
You're sure this is the place?
[exhales]
This is definitely the place.
You lost?
Or just back for more fun?
We just came here to talk.
Oh, really?
Do you bring your little toys
to every conversation you have?
Or do you just want to see me burn again?
Considering you killed my father,
the thought has crossed my mind.
Tell us...
where does Zoom keep his prisoners?
You really don't know
how to use your abilities,
do you, breacher?
It's a work in progress, Elsa.
[suspenseful music]
♪
Zoom killed the love of your life.
This hurts,
even for somebody with
a heart as cold as yours.
And you think that would
make me turn on Zoom?
Enemy of my enemy is my friend, right?
♪
What... don't tell me it doesn't
work like that over here.
If I tell you,
he'll kill me.
But if I kill you
and take you to him,
I bet he'd be pretty pleased with me.
♪
Maybe even let me off my leash.
So take a wild guess.
What do you think I'm gonna choose?
Move!
[exciting music]
[explosion]
Argh! That did not go as planned!
Her name starts with Killer.
This comes as a shock to you?
[ice shattering]
- We got to move now!
- Yeah, yeah.
- I will cover you.
- Okay.
No, no, no, hey, that's a horrible idea.
Hey, no! Hey, hey, no!
- Hey, guys...
- [gun blasting]
- [ice shatters]
- Where are we going?
Where are we going? Oh, God.
[gun blasting]
[ice shatters]
♪
Argh!
[gun blasting]
♪
Argh!
Stop...
or you'll never make another icicle again.
I can't believe it.
What is it?
I think I figured out
how to save Jay's life.
Hey, Jay... uh, wake up.
Come to the cortex. It's important.
It certainly is.
[ominous music]
What do you want?
I like to watch heroes fall
and never get back up.
He always gets back up.
Hard to do that when the Earth
swallows you whole.
♪
[rumbling]
[crashing]
Where is it?
Aw, don't go.
We're having so much fun.
[smashing]
[screams]
Oh, my God! Caitlin!
[crashing]
Caitlin, are you okay?
[gasps]
♪
Looks like this new Flash
isn't much of a hero after all.
♪
Let's see what a seven
will do to S.T.A.R. Labs.
♪
[electricity crackles]
[groaning]
♪
Nice shot.
I was aiming for his leg.
Where is Zoom's lair?
[cocks gun]
Where is it?
If I tell you,
he will kill me.
He'll kill you anyway, Caitlin.
Stop calling me that. It's not my name.
Yes, it is.
You just don't want to hear it
because it reminds you
of someone you used to be.
Trust me, I know that person very well.
You don't know anything about me.
I know the Caitlin Snow on my Earth.
I know that when she loves someone,
that person is her world.
That person was Ronnie Raymond.
And he died too.
It devastated her,
and I can see it's doing the same to you.
[dramatic music]
Zoom took that.
His daughter... my friend...
he's gonna take them away from us,
just like he took Ronnie from you.
♪
Caitlin...
all you have to do is tell us
where he's keeping them.
And then you'll never hear from us again,
and you can go.
♪
Please.
Fine.
I'll show you where it is.
But that's it.
Uh, where are we going?
Ascension Cliffs.
♪
[smashing]
Argh!
Gah!
Look, are you sure you
want to keep doing that?
You know, if Zoom catches you,
he's gonna hurt you again.
I don't understand why
I can't phase through this.
Well, your body would need
to have the same resonance
as the glass walls.
I should be going more than fast enough.
It's something else. [sighs]
Maybe you're resonating
at a different frequency.
♪
Yeah, your Earth vibrates at
a different frequency than mine.
Same reason Cisco can't vibe.
Is there any way to make up the difference?
Only if I can go faster.
[panting]
♪
Wow, wow, wow.
We're going up there?
That's where Zoom's lair is.
A place only a speedster could get to.
There are like the Cliffs of Insanity.
♪
So how do we get up there?
I can make you something
to climb on, darling.
Are you serious?
You want us to...
what, just climb to the top
of those cliffs...
on ice?
Got any better ideas?
No, ma'am, I'm just, you know, I...
I've got... you know,
I'm wearing wingtips here.
They, um, don't have much tread.
Barry.
Barry, um, maybe you should stay behind.
- Yeah?
- No... hey, no.
I'm not letting you go up there by yourself.
It is okay if you don't want to go...
if you don't want to do this.
You are my wife.
I'm not leaving your side.
- Okay.
- Can we go?
- Yeah.
- I'm ready.
Let's go before I change my mind.
♪
[ice whooshing]
You really think handcuffs can stop me?
I know they can...
just like this boot on your neck.
It dampens your power.
Same goes for the six-by-six cell
you'll be calling home at Iron Heights.
All right, let's go.
Caitlin.
So sorry I didn't come sooner.
That's okay, um...
can I show you something?
My cells...
they've stopped degenerating?
How is this even possible?
It appears that when the Velocity-9
is in your system, it kick-starts
your latent regenerative capabilities,
and your cells repair themselves.
And do you think you can
get this to work permanently?
I don't know, but I think
we're on the right track.
Caitlin, I don't know what to say.
This is... you are...
[uplifting music]
[alarm blaring]
What was that?
The speed cannon.
Geomancer's tremors must have damaged it.
Okay, come on.
Come on!
[exciting music]
♪
The breach isn't stabilized.
We need to fix this fast.
Otherwise they're never
gonna be able to come back.
So that was the sound that we heard.
Please tell me it's not as bad as it looks.
- Uh...
- Come on, seriously?
They still have an hour left.
What if they're trying to get
through the breach right now
and they can't?
Okay, the jolt disrupted the quark matter.
The electromagnetic insulators are failing.
How do we fix this in time?
I don't know if we can.
♪
[whispering] Barry?
Barry?
[laughing]
Cisco?
Dude, we made it.
How did you find this place?
Had some help.
Don't even get me started on this guy.
Oh boy.
♪
Dr. Wells...
- [door creaking]
- Stand back.
♪
[uplifting music]
[crying]
♪
I'm here.
Come on, let's get you out of here.
Okay.
♪
- Frost?
- A little help?
Not part of the deal.
- Frost!
- Hey, hey, hey.
Bringing us up here wasn't
part of the deal, either,
but here you are.
Something tells me you're not
as cold as I thought you were.
Maybe, maybe not.
[dramatic music]
[rumbling]
[chain snaps]
♪
What's going on?
Why... why isn't it working?
I don't know.
I've never had this problem before.
Dr. Wells...
Carbyne.
It's some form of carbyne.
This cell's made out of
some form of carbyne.
You'll never be able to
freeze him out of there.
You can't phase out of there?
♪
Just go, all right?
Before Zoom comes back.
We're not leaving you here.
I can't get out of this cell.
I've tried
a lot.
I'm not fast enough to phase through this.
You got...
just leave, all right?
♪
Just leave.
Do you know what we did
to get here, Barry?
We convinced her...
Killer Frost...
to show us the way.
Then we climbed some insanely steep cliffs
outside on footholds made of ice...
ice!
And all of us risked our lives,
knowing Zoom was after us,
to rescue Jesse...
and you.
Now, I don't know you,
and you don't know me,
but I can tell you that today,
I... I did things that
I never thought possible,
because I needed to prove to my wife
and to myself that I could.
Now, if I can do the impossible today,
so can you.
[sighs]
I'm just Barry Allen,
but you're The Flash.
♪
If you tell yourself
you can phase out of there,
you'll do it.
[whooshing]
[laughing]
Okay, let's go.
Go, come on. Wait, wait!
Hey, hey, hey! We're not leaving him.
Barry, there's no time.
He's not going anywhere,
and neither are any of you.
Thank you
for bringing them to me.
You double-crossed us?
He killed Ronnie!
Guess my heart is as cold
as you thought after all.
I can't believe you.
Just so you know,
you would be very disappointed
in you right now.
Zoom.
Let them go.
All you need is me and Barry.
You're right.
I may not be able to kill you yet,
but I can kill them.
[suspenseful music]
No, no! No...
I told you I'd kill you
in front of your father.
No! No!
♪
No...
Get out of here.
♪
Caitlin.
You were right.
He killed Ronnie.
Thank you.
♪
I'm not leaving without him.
Barry, there's no time.
There's no time!
- [ice crackling]
- I can't hold him forever.
Hey, I'm coming back for you
when this is over, all right?
Go!
I'm coming back!
Jay, we need to do something.
Our only chance is to reboot
the electromagnetic insulators
and hope the quark matter
redistributes equally.
How do we do that?
We have to do it manually.
But you can't be near the stabilizer rings
when they power on, or you'll get
sucked into the breach.
Not if I create a vortex
to counteract the pull.
You can't do both at the same time.
Cait...
I have to try.
[suspenseful music]
I'll help you.
What? Dad, no.
Look, if it brings Barry
back to this Earth, I'm doing it.
Are you sure?
The more we talk about it,
the less sure I'll be,
so let's just do it.
Okay.
There's an override switch
on every stabilizer ring.
- I'll create the vortex.
- Yeah.
And you flip all of them.
They should all reboot.
Got it.
Once that's done, you power up the cannon.
- The breach should stabilize.
- And what if it doesn't?
We're all out of luck.
[machinery roaring]
♪
The Velocity-9 is running out!
[alarm blaring]
[dramatic music]
Jay!
I guess now we know how long
the Velocity-9 lasts.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
I just hope they are.
♪
I'm fine. I'm just a mess.
You need to get out
of Central City, all right?
Any place you think
you'll be safe from Zoom.
Yeah, we, um... we have some family
in Atlantis that can help us.
Yeah, okay, good.
You may not have been struck by lightning
over here like I was,
but today, you risked your life
to save somebody you didn't even know.
That's a hero, Barry.
Thank you both.
Barry...
is my father still alive on your Earth?
Yeah, he is.
Give him a hug for me, will you?
I will.
♪
Hey.
You guys need to get someplace safe too.
Where are you going?
The only place we can.
- Dad, we can't just leave.
- We have to, honey.
What, you want me to leave
everything I have here?
My friends, my family...
I mean, my life.
You don't have a life here anymore.
Either do I.
Zoom is too powerful.
I can't stop him.
And as long as he is here,
he's gonna hunt us down
until we're dead.
[alarm blaring]
Wells, if you're coming
with us, we have to go.
[alarm blaring]
It's almost time.
I don't care what time it is.
After all we did to stabilize this breach,
we're not closing until they show up.
Y'all hear me?
[dramatic music]
Cisco!
Get ready to close the breach for good...
Zoom's coming!
♪
Forgetting someone, Flash?
Let him go.
Close the breach.
Tell Jesse I love her.
Tell her yourself.
Argh!
[growling]
♪
It shouldn't be taking this long.
[shouting]
Close it! Close it now!
[explosion]
♪
You did it... you made it!
Barry.
♪
[gasps]
[screaming]
No!