Previously on The Good Doctor...
You don't want me to do anything.
I spend every minute of every day with you.
Since you feel that our time together is something to be endured,
I decided to make that easier for you.
Your daughter's beautiful.
Needs you to get better so you can hold her.
I read about the CHILL study.
She's a good candidate. I'll take full responsibility for her.
Tell him he's going to be fine.
I can't.
The majority of COVID patients
who go on a ventilator never come off.
Put on a mask. Now.
It's covid. We've both been exposed.
My mother had a necklace.
See if I can find it.
Things will be okay.
Good morning.
Morning, Shaun.
I wish you were here.
Me, too.
Morning, Dalisay.
Woke up with a temp of 104.
I need heated, humidified oxygen on a high-flow cannula.
Mom, slow down. Just let her examine you.
Why, so she can find out exactly what I just told her?
Reznick. You're back.
Got sick, got better, got tested twice.
Always the overachiever.
Dr. Reznick, her pulse ox is 90.
We need to admit you.
Is my mom gonna be okay?
Don't worry. I'm gonna be fine.
Just please water my tomato plants,
give Darcy a big hug, and tell her Nana loves her so much
and can't wait to play with her again real soon.
Okay, Mom.
Nice hesitation.
Why not just suggest he get my house appraised?
Sorry. It took a while to find it.
Thank you.
Being able to hold this and keep it with me...
It's a connection.
Like she's still here with me.
It's stuff, Claire. It's meaningless now.
Each one of these tells an interrupted story,
a voicemail that'll never be heard,
a shopping list for a home-cooked meal that'll never be made.
Beautiful.
Cook spaghetti carbonara for a dead guy's family,
and the grief is gone.
Are you here to mock me or to help me?
Why are you here?
"Donald Sulkin."
We're reducing the pressure
of air going into his lungs
and watching his oxygen level.
So far, so good. O2 steady.
Okay.
Yes. But his end tidal CO2 is falling.
What does that mean?
It's not as bad as his O2 falling, but still not good.
Turn the pressure support back up.
End tidal CO2 is very low, not improving.
What's going on?
I think he has a blood clot in his lung,
interfering with his gas exchange.
Give him a bolus of heparin, start him on a drip.
Let's get him to the cath lab.
- Let's go. - What's going on?
Where are you taking him?
Dr. Andrews?
Dr. Murphy?
Martin.
This is isotonic saline, salt water.
It's 4 degrees Celsius.
I'll run this into your bloodstream
until your body temperature drops to 34 degrees Celsius.
The paralytic I gave you will stop you from shivering
while the cold slows your heart, your brain,
all metabolic functions.
All the energy saved there
will go towards healing your lungs.
Your baby's waiting for you.
Pete, follow him.
Pete! Follow him! He's got the axe.
I was getting shot at.
Well, stay low, reload, and head for the temple.
Stop messing around.
AG24, what's up with you? You okay?
Yeah, yeah, I'm hunting for the legendary Tusk of Ganesh
at 3 in the morning because everything's just super.
Can't go out, I can't sleep, I can't go to work.
Welcome to COVID. Everything sucks.
Great. Good... good pep talk.
You all sleeping in an empty bed?
Yeah.
It's like I killed a puppy or something.
Hey, Pete. Pete, heads up.
The fortress is a perfect place for an...
Okay. Pete's dead.
You should apologize.
Just play the game.
Not saying you have to mean it.
Just saying you should apologize.
That's... that's great.
Be a hypocrite.
You married?
I'm 15.
Oh, well, thank you for a lifetime of wisdom.
My girlfriend was pissed at me for something I didn't even do,
but I said sorry, and now we're back together.
Maybe I'm a hypocrite,
but at least I'm a hypocrite with a girlfriend.
Up and at 'em. We gotta be downtown by noon.
Oh, yeah, we're late for the protest.
Gotta get this state opened up...
Well, pulse ox is 82.
Everything else looks okay.
Sure, other than my steadily declining oxygen levels,
I am the picture of health.
Let's start making signs. Oh.
I'm thinking...
"Don't tread on my right to kill you."
How about, "Give me liberty and give me death"?
I need to go.
Nothing.
We haven't had a patient named Sulkin in over 10 years.
Being dead doesn't change
because your loved one gets a memento back.
And fixating on dead people
it's not a life.
How can anyone not be answering their phone right now
if they're not an essential worker?
Well, what nonessential worker are you trying to reach?
Lea.
People don't go out anymore,
but they do still go to the bathroom.
This is the second time in an hour
she hasn't picked up, Claire.
We keep learning more things about this disease.
It's...
I don't know.
It's not right.
We love you, Grandma.
Mom, I'm so sorry.
I love you.
And I want you to know that we'll be okay.
We love you.
He's gone.
She's gone.
They're gone.
It's not always fun.
Whatever you're talking about, no, it isn't.
But what are you talking about?
Do you love Mia?
Of course I do.
What do you love about her?
I love that she loves our son.
I love how she talks to him,
how she knows what he's thinking, knows what he needs.
I thought so.
You thought what?
You love Kellan.
Hello. Are you okay?
I'm sorry I didn't pick up when you called.
I didn't wanna upset you.
- It didn't work. - I had a sore throat,
so I got tested for COVID, and I'm negative.
COVID tests have a high percentage of false negatives.
Shaun, I feel fine now.
That doesn't mean you don't have COVID.
I need to go to work.
How are you adjusting to your new specialty?
It's great. Love being an internist.
Well, I'm convinced.
Dealing with conscious people isn't really your thing.
I'm fine.
You're rude, abrasive,
and now you've gotta hold people's hands and be nice.
It's a huge adjustment,
and I find it completely draining.
You happy?
There's a lot of different approaches to "nice."
Otherwise, I wouldn't have lasted 40 years as a nurse.
You'll find your own.
Or maybe you won't.
Overall, everything's looking up.
Fewer patients coming in.
When they do, we're getting better at...
Hey, buddy.
I'm sorry I keep missing your calls.
I've got this patient.
You know the mom of the baby I told you about?
I basically put her into suspended animation,
but it doesn't seem to be helping.
When are you coming to Phoenix?
I still don't know.
You're going to make my graduation party, though, right?
I don't think so.
- This patient needs... - You?
No one else can take care of her?
I kind of went out on a limb on this one.
Oh, well, if you made a commitment, then...
Your husband has blood in his NG tube.
He's developed heparin-induced thrombocytopenia.
We need to stop the heparin.
But doesn't that put him at risk for another clot?
Yes, if he's not on the heparin,
he could have a stroke,
and if he's on it, he could have a fatal internal bleed,
and he still has an infection,
so we can't stop the antibiotics
or he'll get sepsis and die.
All you do is tell me new ways that my husband might die.
Every time I talk to you, there's another way.
I mean, do you even know what you're doing?
What is the point of you? You're useless.
We understand your frustration.
COVID targets so many organs.
- Technically, this is your fault. - Shaun.
Martin never left the apartment,
but he still caught COVID.
You must have exposed him to it.
On the other hand, we are doing
- all that we can to... - That's enough. That's enough.
We're all going through crap,
but that woman's husband may be dying.
She's allowed to lash out.
You aren't.
I'm sorry.
Why?
What?
What are you sorry about?
Everything.
The fight and
you sleeping in the other room and you ignoring me...
So you're sorry because of the way I've been acting.
I'm apologizing.
I don't think you are.
I don't get it. Uh, you won.
I... I don't know what you want.
We... we can't have a difference of opinion?
No, not when we disagree
on whether you've been mean to me or not.
You've been mean to me.
Three tours.
Helicopter pilot.
Oh, he's got a medal in that one.
Hey, look at this, same guy again.
Funny. Almost as if they were in the same unit or something.
Greg Lavin...
...died here. Covid, one month ago.
Hello. Enid Lavin?
Hi. This is Dr. Claire Browne
from San Jose Saint Bonaventure.
I'm so sorry for your loss.
I just wanted you to know that
we have found something of your father's.
A memento of his service. Dog tags.
No, not his.
A man by the name of Donald Sulkin.
Donald Sulkin.
Thank you.
That's odd.
Yeah.
How does your father carry someone else's dog tags for 50 years,
and you have never even heard of him?
How are you feeling?
My son
plans to move to Montana.
Take my granddaughter 1,000 miles away.
The schools are better, air's cleaner.
So the upside of all this is...
I don't have to move to Montana.
Is that why you haven't okayed us
putting you on a ventilator if you need one?
I know what ventilators do to people.
Do you remember Dr. Pitcairn?
Pitstain.
Exactly.
Remember when I was a first-year resident?
One of two women, only woman of color.
I'd been warned he'd make my life hell.
And sure enough, second week,
Pitstain starts tearing into me
about the spacing of my sutures being inconsistent,
and I'm about to fall apart in front of everybody,
but then you stepped in.
Brought up some charting error he'd made.
A tiny blip of a mistake.
He never capitalized "STAT."
The whole point is for it stand out.
Well, you put him back on his heels in front of everybody.
You gave me time,
to regain my composure.
He never got to see me cry.
Please, if it comes to it,
give me a little time again.
To help you.
No, no, no!
I don't know what to do.
I love Lea, and I wanted her to love...
Okay, okay. I'll be... I'll be right down.
Okay?
I don't know what to do.
I... I love Lea,
and I wanted her to love me back,
and now she does, but we can't be together.
How can loving someone who loves you back make things worse?
Well, that's a...
That's a good question.
Let's start with what's making things worse.
I think...
I think I may be... cranky.
I've never been cranky before.
I don't like it.
I think I miss Lea.
I think I'm worried that she has COVID.
So you're going crazy because you can't see someone.
What am I supposed to do?
Should I not talk to Lea until the pandemic is over?
Well, that's an option.
Is that what you want?
No, no, I don't... I don't want that at all.
But I don't want to feel like this, either.
I want this to be over.
Well, we all want it to be over, Shaun.
I mean, we're... we're sick of ourselves,
we're sick of each other,
or we're pining for someone we can't be with.
We're confused. We're uncomfortable.
And on top of everything else,
we're scared that the world will never be the same again.
I mean, I don't know, Shaun.
I don't have a map for this kind of thing.
Best I can say is...
be kind.
Be kind to yourself. Be kind
to everyone.
'Cause what else is there?
BGM: Total Eclipse of the Heart by Bonnie Tyler
♪ Every now and then I get a little bit lonely ♪
♪ And you're never coming 'round ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ Every now and then I get a little bit tired ♪
♪ Of listening to the sound of my tears ♪
Oh, this is a nice song.
♪ Every now and then I get a little bit nervous... ♪
I hate this song.
Good. I was being kind.
Martin hates it, too.
It was... It was the first conversation we had,
talking about how weird this song is.
Who is Bright Eyes, and why is it so important
that they turn around?
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ Every now and then I fall apart ♪
Now it just reminds me of him.
♪ And I need you now tonight ♪
♪ more than ever ♪
You're probably right.
That he got COVID from me.
♪ We'll be holding on forever ♪
It's hard
to think of someone you love
when you can't be with them.
♪ Your love is like a shadow on me all of the time ♪
♪ All of the time ♪
He seems to have a posterior tibial artery thrombosis.
What... That... That sounds bad.
It is. It's a blockage in the artery,
causing ischemia to his lower extremity tissues due to lack of...
I want to be kind to you, I want to explain,
but it's a very long explanation,
and I don't have time for you to get mad and upset...
Just go help my husband.
Okay.
Your numbers are falling.
I know.
You need a ventilator.
There's a pocket in my purse.
Reach into it.
"Game 7, 2003, American League Championship."
Grady let Pedro go one inning too long.
The Sox handed the series to the damn Yankees.
My son and I cried in each other's arms.
I've kept them with me ever since.
It's like Jimmy's always with me.
You're not alone.
You're stuck with all of us.
Can you take your earbuds out, please?
I don't think that I've done anything wrong,
but I may be wrong about that. I suspect that I am.
I haven't been thinking straight lately.
What with everything going on at the hospital,
people are dying, and I'm... here.
And that makes me feel weak.
And then I feel scared, and that makes me feel
even more weak.
And then I feel relieved and safe
that I'm here,
and that makes me feel like a coward.
Thank you.
"Thank you"?
I just needed an honest moment.
Something
to let me know that you actually need me.
And...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
Hi, buddy.
Hey, Dad.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have gotten angry about you not coming to Phoenix.
It wasn't fair.
Thank you.
Did your mother put you up to this?
She was right.
I don't even really care about the party that much.
Then what was the issue?
We don't have to talk about that.
I wanna know what's bothering you.
I... I know your job is important,
but sometimes I just wanna know
you care about me more than you care about the job.
When your mom got pregnant,
I was so nervous.
Suddenly, everything was real.
Suddenly, I had a commitment.
And I wasn't sure I was ready.
And then you were born.
And in that moment, I mean, that moment,
everything changed.
I was instantly head-over-heels in love with you.
You were my best friend.
And, uh, I held you,
and the words just came out. I said, "Hi, buddy."
I'd never called anyone "buddy" before in my life.
But
you were my buddy.
I may make mistakes over and over again,
but don't ever think
you're not the most important thing in my life.
So, basically, you're saying
your love for me is like chemical, right?
Yeah.
Thank you for your call.
Your husband is still unconscious. Bye.
How is he? How was the surgery?
Dr. Andrews will explain,
but I'd rather not say anything more.
The last two times I gave you bad news, you yelled at me.
Bad news? What... What is the bad news?
Okay.
We amputated Martin's foot and ankle.
We are now trying to reintroduce anticoagulation
so he won't have more clots,
but he will be at risk for more bleeding.
Thank you.
Are you sure you understand?
He's still on a ventilator, and he... he lost a foot.
You were very upset yesterday.
Yesterday, I thought he was dying.
But today he's alive.
So, thank you.
You're welcome.
Can I hang up now?
Yes. Yeah, thank...
I figured you're bored of just hearing my voice,
so I brought a mutual friend.
The risks are minimal, and whatever time you have,
some of it should be with your family.
Yes, I'm trying to track down a Donald Sulkin.
Nope, no one here by that name.
Okay, sorry to bother you.
Your plan is to call every D. Sulkin in North America,
all to return a set of dog tags?
You've reached Diana Sulkin, please...
You want a happy ending for this guy.
'Cause you and I didn't have one.
Because we'll never know how our story could've ended.
Hello?
Is Donald Sulkin there?
- Sorry... - This doesn't change anything.
This can't change anything.
You're wrong. It changes things.
It makes me feel something besides sad.
And I need that. I need to not feel sad.
'Cause everything sucks.
Everything hurts like hell.
People are sick with... with COVID,
with cancer, with grief,
and we can't help them.
People are dying, and we can't help them,
and what is worse, you're not there!
It has to hurt.
A lot.
For a while.
When your mom died, you did everything you could
to not feel anything. At all.
But this time, you're facing it.
You're grieving.
You're healing.
It's time.
No. Not today.
Today.
We love you, Mom.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Mom...
I love you.
Good-bye.
BGM: Lovely Day by Bill Withers
♪ When the day that lies ahead of me ♪
♪ Seems impossible to face ♪
♪ And when someone else instead of me ♪
♪ Always seems to know the way ♪
She's been waiting patiently
to learn her name.
Aria.
I'm going to call her Aria.
♪ My, just one look at you ♪
♪ And I know it's gonna be ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day, lovely day, lovely day ♪
♪ A lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day ♪
Honey!
♪ A lovely day ♪
♪ Lovely day, lovely day, lovely day, lovely day ♪
You know, my mom used to talk about you.
A lot.
She told me what you did in the earthquake,
the price you paid.
She said you can rest easy
if you've got that
"tough Reznick" in your corner.
I'm thinking she didn't exactly phrase it that way, did she?
No. She didn't.
Donald Sulkin?
How can I help you?
I'm Dr. Claire Browne.
Greg Lavin died at my hospital last month.
Greg...
he had this with him when he passed.
I gave these to Greg at the end of the war.
We were...
friends.
Thank you.
That was beautiful.
That room is filled with stories that were cut short.
Like ours.
But you,
you have an amazing story ahead.
I can't wait to see it.
You can come home?
I can come home.
But...
But?
Do you love me?
Of course I love you.
What do you love about me?
I love that you love our son.
I love watching you two talk.
I love the way Kellan lights up when he's with you.
I love you, too.
For all the same reasons.
And we both wanna be there for Kellan.
And we are.
But...
You and I don't need to be together to do that.
Are you okay if...
Maybe it's time we stopped coming here.
You're ready to move on?
No.
But he'll still be with us, right?
Wherever we are.
He changed me.
That's not gonna go away.
I have everything I need to stay overnight,
including this... Negative for COVID.
I know negative tests are unreliable,
but it's my third in three days.