My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist.
But secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so I opened up
our world to new threats.
And I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Welcome to Earth2.
I met your doppelganger.
She's a cold-hearted
ice queen named Killer Frost.
- The name is Vibe.
- Reverb.
My brothers and sisters,
I've brought us to this new world,
ours for the taking!
Whose world is this?!
Our world! Our world! Our world!
Our world, our world!
Reloading!
David!
Back door! Captain's down.
Go, go, go, go, go!
Down, down! Down, get down!
Some people are calling
it the metapocalypse,
the days when Central City
was overrun by an army
with powers beyond imagination.
- METAPOCALYPSE CITY IN CRISIS
- But in these dark times,
we must never forget our own strength,
our own power to fight back.
That it is only in the
blackest of nights
that we can truly see the light...
and know for sure we are not alone.
We are never... ever... alone.
STAR LABORATORIES
LEVEL 600
We usually take these guys down
one at a time, not 100 at a time.
And yet, you don't seem overwhelmed.
I know we can do it.
Guys. You have to come see this.
Cisco, what are you...
Caitlin?
She's in shock.
A little... dehydrated and malnourished,
but I think she'll be fine.
I'm okay.
What happened? How did you get away?
He... let me go.
I didn't think he would;
I thought it was a trap.
But... he told me you were dead.
I'm not. I'm right here.
We're all here, together.
Snow.
Jay's not here.
You're safe.
He's gonna overrun the city.
You can't stop him.
Yes, we can.
Listen to me, he's not going to succeed.
We've got this. This is our Earth.
You don't know that.
You don't know what he is capable of.
I know from being in the Speed Force
that the universe is with us, not Zoom.
And if the universe is with us,
how could we possibly lose?
Right, guys?
Yeah, yeah, right.
You've been through a lot.
You should get some rest, come on.
You were in the Speed Force?
I... when you were gone.
It's hard to explain, but we
tried to get my powers back
and when the dark matter lightning...
Okay, I'm gonna say it.
We don't think he's
being just a little too...
Overconfident?
Yeah, maybe it was his
time in the Speed Force.
I mean, he's acting like he's
invincible now or something.
Yeah, like nothing fazes
him anymore, which isn't...
Realistic, no.
Somebody needs to talk to him
before letting his guard down
gets him hurt or worse.
He did bring me out of my coma.
That's bound to make someone
a little overly chipper.
Well, like I said, somebody
needs to talk to him.
Amazing job, Anupam.
This is exactly the kind
of groundbreaking thinking
I built this company for.
Well done.
Everyone, evacuate! Now!
Hurry!
Hey.
She's out like a light?
Yeah.
Jay really did a number on her.
It's not like he
exactly used kid gloves
on the rest of us.
She'll be okay. She just needs time.
And for us to finally bring Zoom down.
Which we will.
Yeah, because the
universe is with us, right?
Listen, man...
Cisco?
Hey. You okay?
- You just vibe?
- Yeah.
What'd you see?
I saw a bird.
Like, a dead bird.
Mercury Labs.
It's under attack.
All right.
Thank you, Mr. Allen.
I'm not stupid.
Boom.
So how did you know?
- Your real identity?
- Yeah.
Come on, Barry, I'm a scientist.
We're paid to be perceptive.
And you're always a
little too well informed
when things go pear-shaped in this city.
But I don't believe
we've ever met before.
Dr. Christina McGee.
Doctor Henry Allen.
I'm Barry's father.
Okay, now that the
cat's out of the bag,
did you happen to see who it was
that cause your building to collapse?
I didn't see anything.
It happened so fast.
Maybe the security
cameras caught something?
Can we access them?
Mercury Labs does have a
Crash-Survivable Memory Unit.
A what?
Virtually a black box for buildings.
It will have stored all
the security footage
right up until the building collapsed.
Okay, great, I'll go find it.
This wasn't some random meta-human.
Whenever Mercury Labs has been targeted
in the past there's always
been a specific reason.
Yeah, someone's after something.
Yes, and that someone
is probably Zoom.
There may be one more possibility.
A few months ago, I saw Harrison Wells
running out of my facility.
I know it sounds crazy, but
I'm certain it was him.
Is there any way he could have
anything to do with this?
A few months ago?
Sure.
Now?
No.
Yeah, there are a few
more things that we could
catch you up on, Dr. McGee.
Hey, my purse!
That ain't yours, punk.
Big mistake.
You picked a bad time to play hero.
Dad?
Wally.
What the hell were you doing?
That guy just jacked a bunch of people
so I had to go after him.
You could have got yourself killed!
I'm not just gonna let these
guys get away with this.
I have to do something.
Wally, these are not just guys!
These are meta-humans!
Leaves this to the cops and The Flash.
The Flash can't be everywhere at once.
I... I have to do what I can to help.
I have to show him I
was worth being saved.
Wally...
You are... worth it.
Really?
Am I?
'Cause last time I checked,
I'm the guy who avoided
his dying mother for weeks.
I'm the guy who shamed
a bunch of other guys
and illegally took their cars from them.
I'm the guy who caused The Flash
to lose his powers and start
this whole damn "metapocalypse"
in the first place.
Wally...
Last time I checked,
I've a whole lot to make up for.
That's what I intend to do.
Damn it.
Snow.
I didn't know you were here.
What you doing?
Jesse asked me to run some tests
to see if her genetic
structure had changed.
Why did you ask Dr. Snow...
to run tests on you again?
Because I got hit with
a dark matter, okay?
I mean, that must have
affected me somehow.
You're not a meta-human.
What you are
is a young woman
with a genius-level IQ that we could use
in our fight against this
new wave of meta-humans.
Okay. All right, fine.
Fine.
Snow?
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- Is this it?
- That's the one.
All right, great. Dad, Dr.
McGee, Cisco.
Why don't you guys crack this
open, see what you can find?
Sure.
We'll go see what kind
of meta-human powers
can take down a building like
that and how to stop it.
- Great.
- Sounds like fun.
All right, I'm gonna go
see if Joe needs any help
in the streets. Everybody cool here?
Should be a piece of cake, right?
- Hey, slugger!
- Hey.
Can I talk to you for a minute?
Yeah, sure.
What's up?
Well, I know you said that
what happened to you in the Speed Force
changed the way you see things,
but you seem very optimistic,
you know, with a lot
of meta-humans running
around tearing up the city.
What, did you see the future in there?
No... not this time.
No... I... look...
What I was shown in the Speed Force
didn't just change my mind,
it changed me.
I don't know... what
you're seeing as optimism
is, for the first time,
I'm just not afraid anymore.
Great, that's...
But...
You know you still have
to be careful, right?
What do you mean?
Well...
I don't... why are you trying to
take something from me that
I fought so hard to get to?
- Barry!
- I... you... you don't know
everything that I've been through, Dad.
You haven't been here
long enough to know.
I didn't mean... I'm sorry.
I don't know why I said that.
I think I do.
Hadn't been around.
Teach you how to drive or
take you to look at colleges.
But I've done everything in my power
to know who you are.
Barry, I don't want to
take anything from you.
I believe in you.
This isn't about my
not believing in you.
I know that.
And I'm fine. Okay?
Thank you, thank you very much
for worrying about me.
I love you.
But I'm fine.
Come on.
What is that?
It's CCPD.
Zoom.
Barry.
Don't do it.
You know, I never saw the crime photos
of my mother's murder.
Well, I guess I didn't need to.
I have a ringside seat while
you got whisked away.
Too delicate, I suppose.
Not just a hologram after
all, are you, Flash?
Interesting.
I know you didn't call
me up here just to banter.
Let's finish this.
Right now.
Actually, I did.
I called you up here to tell
you you can't keep running
from one meta to the next.
Around and around,
like a dog chasing its tail.
I'll do whatever it takes to stop you.
If only that were good enough.
'Cause here's the thing.
I know you.
I know you, I know
what's holding you back.
You and me...
we're really just the same person.
Yeah, you keep saying that,
but it's not gonna make it true.
You'll see. We are.
DOCTOR ACCUSED OF KILLING WIFE
Same tragic background.
Same reason for running.
Same desire to be the
fastest, to be the best.
The difference?
You think your anger is dirty somehow.
You want to be seen as pure, the hero.
Doesn't it get exhausting?
Doesn't it get exhausting, Barry!
It was exhausting playing
Jay, believe me.
I'm not pretending.
Now if it were me,
I'd let that building tumble
without a second thought.
But you,
you'll never let that happen, will you?
That's why I'm gonna beat you, Barry.
Because you always have to be the hero.
And while you're playing
the good little boy...
I'll be busy winning.
We can't let Zoom
destroy another building.
We need to take him down.
Now.
How do you propose we do that
with an army of meta-humans
laying waste to Central City?
We couldn't stop Zoom on my Earth.
What makes us different?
We're a team.
We start with the meta-humans,
they're his armor.
We take them down first,
then Zoom's more vulnerable.
Barry, we don't even know
how many of his minions there are.
There could be hundreds, a thousand.
And all of them, they're all
working with different powers.
It could take weeks
to track them all down.
Guys, we don't have weeks.
So what we need do to is
come up with a way to
stop them all at once.
Again:
how?
Cisco,
your goggles, your camera,
they didn't work on Earth-2, right?
Yeah, it was a whole
different frequency.
And the way you took
down the Time Wraiths,
that was based on frequency.
Hartley's entire shtick...
I think I'm smelling
what you're stepping in.
- Yeah.
- So basically,
we create some vibrational tech
that can take down the Earth-2 metas.
- Basically.
- Oh, I gotcha.
- Me too.
- I'll help.
Okay.
I'll let you know if I
hear anything from CCPN.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You guys...
we got this.
Barr, can I talk to you for a second?
Yeah.
Birds.
Why?
It's like a Hitchcock movie in my head.
What's up?
Man, it's Wally.
Is he okay?
Not really.
Earlier, he thought it
would be a good idea
if he used himself
as bait against a meta-human psycho.
Thought he could do things
the way The Flash would.
Joe, I mean, he... he did tell me that
he wasn't gonna waste the
opportunity The Flash gave him.
I don't know if you can stop him.
I'm gonna have to or he's
gonna get himself killed.
Look, he ain't you, Barry.
He can't just go Mach 50...
Mach 50 isn't a real thing.
The point is
thinking you're invincible
isn't any kind of armor.
Wally's already at a higher
risk than I'm comfortable with,
and him throwing caution to
the wind on top of all that?
No.
We got to keep him safe.
So... in the Flash,
talk to him.
Again.
Yeah, I'll talk to him.
I'll try, I promise.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I thought throwing things was
Harry's preferred method
of dealing with stress.
That is how frustrated I am right now.
I'm... just running out
of ideas as to how
to make this work. Where's Barry?
I need a taste of that
"walking on sunshine" thing
he's got going on right now.
No no!
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's me, okay?
Breathe. Breathe.
You're okay, all right? You're shaking.
I... I thought I saw him... Zoom...
I thought I saw him right there.
It's just me, okay?
Look at me, he's not here.
He's not here.
I see him everywhere.
Look, you literally
just escaped a psychopath who
kidnapped you, all right,
so I think it's normal for you to have
a severe reaction like this.
This is so much worse than that.
I... I'm afraid all the time.
I don't think I can ever move forward.
You will.
When?
Jay took everything from me.
My confidence, my trust, my sanity.
I don't think I'll ever be whole again.
Of course you will.
I promise.
Stealing is illegal, you know.
Detective West tells me that you've been
fighting Zoom's army on your own.
Yeah. I want to help.
I admire what you're trying to do,
but the best way to help is to just
leave this to the police.
Like you did.
I do have powers, Wally.
It is a little different.
This isn't your fight.
It's mine.
No, it's all of ours.
This is my city too now.
It's up to all of us to protect it.
Barry, we got a major meta-human alert
at 5th and Main... get there.
5th and Main. Got it.
We'll continue this later.
Why is it always so difficult to choose?
Barry, what it is?
It's...
Laurel Lance.
Laurel.
Laurel Lance is dead.
On this Earth, anyway.
Poor Black Canary. Bye-bye, birdy.
Earth-2 Laurel.
You knew her doppelganger?
We didn't just know her, we loved her.
So... what do I call you?
You can call me
Black Siren.
Zoom mentioned that you
might be showing up.
If he told you what I can do,
you should look more afraid.
And so should you.
Tell me,
why did you take down Mercury Labs?
Because I like to watch
things crumble and fall.
Guess what. You're next, red.
Barry?
You okay, Barry?
Look.
Anything over 200 decibels
will kill a human.
Was that too loud?
Perhaps we should quiet
things down a bit.
You know, the sad thing is,
I think Zoom's actually afraid of you.
And I didn't think that
he feared anything.
And you, you're hardly worth the chills.
How many metas did he
send to try and kill you?
Well, it's too bad.
He should have just sent me
because that way,
you would have already been...
Get in.
Thought you might need a lift.
Yeah. Thanks.
You're welcome.
Why do so many villains
that we go against
use sound as a weapon?
- What?
- Nothing.
- You're gonna be fine.
- Thanks.
So Wally just drove on
up into the thick of it?
Must have been some
conversation you two had,
seeing as though he did literally
the opposite of what we wanted.
This I can hear.
It's not funny.
I'm sorry.
I'm in no laughing mood.
Look, Joe, I tried.
I told you I would try, right? I...
Wally's a determined kid.
Yeah, determined to
get himself killed.
Or determined to help people.
And be glad, or you know,
I would not be standing here right now.
Well, he was lucky tonight.
I don't want to see the
day when he isn't.
We've got more than
luck on our side, Joe.
You know you're not invincible, right?
Yes, of course, I know this.
Joe's being...
overprotective, but I get it.
Yeah, but it's like
you think that nothing can touch you.
Like nothing bad can get in your way.
That's not true for any of us.
What are you saying?
Look,
I know that you had an
experience in the Speed Force.
And I'm happy that you think
we're gonna win the day.
But I think a little fear
can be a healthy thing.
It helps you determine which
risks are worth taking.
I think that's something for both
you and Wally to take to heart.
T+U+S+U+B+T+I+T+U+L+O
I met your little red friend tonight.
Aren't you going to ask
me if I killed him?
You didn't.
You're good but not that good.
And yet I seem to be
the only one of your top
lieutenants still standing.
Like I said, you're good.
So why don't you go knock
down a few more buildings?
Like I ordered.
What's the point?
The point is so that
it seems random.
That way The Flash and his merry
band won't realize what I'm up to
till it's too late.
What are you up to?
No good.
Sorry.
There we go.
Are you kidding me with this?
Hey, at least it works.
Tremendous.
What is it exactly?
It's just a small source of joy,
but more importantly, it's how
we're gonna stop Zoom's army.
By giving them all
electroshock therapy?
dimensional shock therapy.
This is where I play stupid
and you explain science.
Okay. Fair enough.
So all matter vibrates at its
own unique frequency, right?
You disrupt that frequency,
you disrupt the matter.
Like how an opera singer
shatters glass with her voice.
Exactly. So we found out that
all Earth-2 people vibrate at their
own, more erratic frequency.
Higher frequency.
- Different frequency.
- Higher.
- Higher frequency than we do.
- Right.
So I ran this all past Hartley, right?
And he postulated that we
could create a sort of
dimensional tuning fork ... here ...
Okay, you didn't do it yourself.
Just let me have this one, okay?
- Have it, have it.
- Thank you.
So if you run around the city
fast enough to create
a refracting field,
the device can send out
a pulse
that'll bounce off of it, split apart,
and collide with itself over and over.
Amplifying it to an erratic
frequency on the Earth-2...
- Higher. Higher frequency.
- Higher frequency
on the Earth-2 spectrum.
And when that pulse hits
anyone from Earth-2...
It'll disrupt their nervous system.
Earth-2 metas go night-night.
- Even Zoom?
- Even Zoom.
Harry and Jesse are from Earth-2.
How do we keep the pulse
from hurting them?
Oh, Detective, I
didn't know you cared.
Yes you did.
We designed these headphones
to protect us from the pulse.
Beats by Wells.
BLACK SIREN LOCATED
Cisco, it's your meta-human alert app.
That's the high-rise
development on the west side.
Hundreds of people live there.
Ramon, we're up. Let's go.
Set that pulse off right now.
Allen, you need to start
generating that refracting
field right now.
But Black Siren can take down
this building at any point.
Wha... all those people, Wells.
How many more people are
gonna die while we wait?
Guys, which is it?
I think I just got the
worst idea of all time.
I don't think I've taken down
so many buildings at once.
Maybe you're not as
powerful as you think!
What are you two doing here?
Why should you have all the fun?
I thought you two were dead.
Zoom thinks that too.
And we'd like to keep it that way.
For now.
You think you two can
pull one over on Zoom?
Well, enjoy being dead.
I told you.
Give her a chance.
What chance?
She's not ready.
Excuse me.
Do you know what I'm capable of doing?
Try it, and I'll shatter your entire
nervous system without breaking a sweat.
Wow, you really think
you can take on Zoom.
We can.
You don't even know
how powerful you are.
With a single call, you
can take down a building.
I'd call that impressive.
But why... stop...
there?
Why serve a master when
you can be a master,
when you can be a god?
We... could be gods.
- All right!
- All right.
We're synced up with whatever
the heck that thing is.
Finally something
we're both baffled by.
I'm kidding. That, my friend,
is a 75KTSB 40,000-watt
reverberating sound amplifier
designed to single out
the operating frequency
of every single Earth-2
being on this planet...
which, went contained and magnified
by The Flash creating
a sound pressure wall
around the city, will render all of us
Earth-2 beings unconscious.
Hence...
the safety precautions.
I'm baffled by it.
Are we ready?
- Yes, we are.
- All right.
Here... we...
go.
If I were interested
in forming an alliance with you two,
what's your plan?
Exactly?
We ambush Zoom at CCPD.
With our three powers combined,
he'll be no match for us.
Well, I like the sound of that.
Great.
Then let's go.
There's just one more thing.
Reverb... catch.
E*X*C*L*U*S*I*V*E*
^T^U^S^U^B^T^I^T^U^L^O
You know, all doppelgangers...
they're mirror images of themselves.
But you two, you didn't
know that, did you?
Reverb is left-handed.
Well, I just... I just happened to...
catch it with my right... run!
Oh, no.
What are we gonna do?
I don't think that there's
anything you can do.
What the what?
I don't know.
Well, do it again!
Cisco...
We're a go.
There's nothing on this Earth
that can stop us!
It's working.
Dad?
Dad, it hurts.
- No... no... stop...
- It's okay.
- No...
- It's okay, honey.
Turn it off! Turn it off, it worked!
It's okay, it's okay,
we'll take care of him.
It's okay, Jesse.
He's gonna be okay.
Barry. We did it.
Bring them all in.
Copy that. I'm on clean up.
What's that? I can't...
I can't hear you
through the double-paned
soundproof glass.
It's... it's kind of hard to
make out what you're saying.
So should we tell Sara and
Captain Lance about her?
No, I've seen what interacting with
your family's doppelgangers can do.
It's not even Laurel.
No. It's just a poor imitation.
Speaking of, that was a pretty good
Killer Frost you did back there.
Guess I was in the right head space
to play a cold, vicious killer.
How you doing, are you okay?
No.
But I think I'm gonna be.
Being out there with you guys,
fighting meta-humans,
saving people...
It's the first time I felt
normal in a long time.
Come here.
- This is a group hug moment.
- Yeah.
It is.
So all of Zoom's meta-humans
are locked up in Iron Heights?
Most of them. Some are somewhere else.
I don't want to know.
No you don't.
And Zoom?
The metas we spoke to said Zoom
created a breach and escaped.
And how did he do that again?
Who knows, but he's
back on Earth-2 now.
Earth-2?
That something else I
don't want to know about?
No.
All right. Well, Flash, thanks.
The man who saved Central
City once again.
No, we're all just
part of the same team.
Speaking of teams,
where the hell is Allen?
Sorry, man, sorry... hey.
Heard my name. What's up?
Good, well, you've got about
100 meta criminal cases
to get through, so I would get
to cracking if I were you.
I will get right on that.
Captain.
- Well done.
- Thanks.
Listen...
I've been thinking
about Wally some more.
Are you gonna talk to him again?
No, I'm not.
Why not?
Because he's your son, Joe.
I know he's my son.
I... look... what I mean is
he's got your values.
He's got your inner drive to
help people do what's right.
We're supposed to think
we're something we're not
until we become that thing.
That's the path that Wally's on.
I'm not gonna stop him
from being the hero
that he's gonna become.
I really don't think you should either.
I can't wait till you have
kids and they torture you.
I'ma laugh in your face.
All right, gramps.
Stern.
What?
My grandkids are
gonna call me "poppa".
All right.
What in the world?
What is this?
- Blame Iris.
- Okay.
I just figured that since Henry
is officially back for good,
we should celebrate.
And since Zoom is gone and
the city is quiet right now.
Oh, I appreciate it, Iris.
Thank you.
- Hi, Tina.
- Hello, Henry.
- Jesse.
- Hi.
T'U'S'U'B'T'I'T'U'L'O'C'O'M'
Good to see you.
Good to see you too.
- You look... great.
- Thank you.
I hope you don't mind
that I invited Dr. McGee.
Seems like somebody's glad you did.
So I guess you are invincible.
Told you.
The Speed Force is with us.
Since I'm...
feeling extra invincible lately,
what do you say
you and I
give this a shot?
Yeah, I would like that.
So is it true?
You saved The Flash's life?
Oh, I mean, I was
just in the right place
at the right time.
Proud of you, Wally.
You did good.
Thanks, Dad.
What?
I'm just... I'm proud of you too.
- Soup's on.
- Hey!
Taking out a city full of monsters
makes a man hungry.
First,
a toast.
To family.
That's my kind of
toast, short and sweet.
Let's eat.
You guys.
Great.
Earth-2.
Cisco?
What... what is it?
What'd you see?
What do you mean "see"?
Cisco gets visions.
I don't understand.
What Cisco?
Earth-2 splitting in half.
Straight down to the poles.
Tell me I didn't just vibe the future.
Please tell me I did not
just see the end of the world!
Our story continues,
Flash.
- Henry!
- Oh, my God.
Dad?
It's poetic, returning
to your childhood home.
Jay.
Don't do this.
I'm begging you.
I'm begging you! Take me.
- Kill me!
- No!
You still won't believe me
that you and I are the same.
- Come on.
- Barry, look at me, son.
So I'm gonna have to
make you believe me.
Whatever happens you have made me
the happiest father...
Dad...
This time, you're gonna
watch your parent die
just like I did.
- No, no!
- And this
is what's gonna make you
just like me!
Your mother and I love...
Jay!
No!