Good morning.
Morning.
I'm Jake, we met last week.
Yes, we did.
I was just gonna get some juice.
- Hope you don't mind. - Are you a drummer?
Am I a drummer? No. No, I'm a chef.
Well, actually, just a cook, but --
Lea dates drummers.
I played clarinet in junior high.
What are you doing out here?
I told you to stay in my room.
I just snuck out to grab some O.J.
I was really thirsty.
I'm sorry.
I should've told you he was spending the night.
I like Jake.
That's nice of you to say.
I know it's difficult to have a stranger in your home.
I have to drive Dr. Glassman to his chemo appointment.
He's five days in and doing very well.
I'm helping him.
Jake is very sweet.
You know, when you get to know him, i'm sure you really will like him.
I said I like him.
Will he be spending the night here a lot now?
No, not a lot.
But...
would that be a problem?
- No. - So is it cool
if I have him over tonight to watch a movie?
It's cool.
I have to go.
Good morning, Dr. Glassman.
I let myself in. I'm downstairs.
How are you feeling today?
Good, actually. Better than yesterday.
Yes, your skin was a bit pale yesterday.
Today your color looks much better.
I brought you your electrolytes.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Why did you do that?
I don't like the flavor, the grape.
Are you experiencing nausea?
No, I didn't like the flavor, I told you.
I'm fine.
I'm glad you're feeling well.
Let's go, or we're going to be late.
Yep. Cancer's not gonna kill itself.
I was just thinking about you, too.
Actually, can I call you at lunch?
I'm with some people right now, and --
Yes, exactly.
We'll talk later.
Love you.
New girlfriend?
Still in the call-each-other-the-next-morning phase?
Yeah, you got me.
Actually, no. It was Mia.
We're giving our relationship another shot.
Park, that's great.
Yeah, I told you because part of the thing with Mia is...
I'm trying to be more open.
Thanks. You didn't need to explain,
but sounds good.
She sounds like she's good for you.
Yeah.
Of course, if it doesn't work out,
I'll have to talk to you about that, too,
admit I failed.
Or I can be a supportive colleague
regardless of what happens.
70-year-old female. Neighbor saw her collapse in her yard.
Unresponsive. No heartbeat. EKG is flatlined.
Then she'd be cyanotic.
Good capillary refill -- she's perfusing?
Stop CPR.
And she's breathing. Your EKG must be broken.
Worked fine on our call right before her.
Everything works fine up until it doesn't.
- Nothing. - Told you.
Hook her up, let's check her vitals.
Blood is definitely flowing to her extremities.
Should we push epi, get the crash --
Wait. Everyone quiet.
Listen.
Is that...?
She doesn't have a rhythm
because she has a mechanical heart.
Lana Moore. 34-year-old female,
was slurring her words, symptom passed,
but we found a grade two arteriovenous malformation in her brain.
Are we going to do
endovascular embolization
or stereotactic radiosurgery or resection?
Endovascular embolization.
Patient requests she's only served green Jello
and that we dim all of our incandescent light bulbs?
Lana has autism.
What're you looking at him for?
It's not like they all know each other.
I was just curious what his thoughts might be.
I think we should go with endovascular embolization.
Now you know.
The AVM is dangerous, but the embolization
is a relatively minor procedure.
We'll make a small incision in your leg
so we can insert a catheter into your --
Are you okay, Javi?
The lights aren't bothering you too much?
A little.
Please continue.
We'll insert the catheter into your femoral artery.
Then we'll feed it up into the arteriovenous malform--
You brought a dictionary?
Uh, is there something I'm saying that you don't understand?
Lana loves learning new words.
She's memorized the scientific Latin name
of every bug in South America.
Go ahead, name any six-legged critter.
I love being quizzed.
Rhinoceros Beetle.
Megasoma Actaeon. Found in Guyana.
It's the heaviest insect in the world
and weighs as much as 300 grasshoppers.
Is she right?
I have no idea.
I have to go.
Javi
Javi.
Where are you going?
It's 11:15. I have to be home by noon
to watch "Judge Judy" before work.
I-it's important to us
that your girlfriend doesn't get stressed out,
so we'd prefer it if you stayed with her as long as you can.
Lana's not my girlfriend. We're just roommates.
Still stable?
The diuretics have her O2 SATs up,
- but she's hypotensive. - And we checked every center
approved to implant mechanical hearts,
but none have any record of her as a patient.
Check overseas. I'd start with --
Mom?
Is it her heart?
The implanted device appears to be malfunctioning.
Do you have any contact information
for the surgeon who implanted it?
Yes, of course.
Dr. Li Wei. He's in Beijing.
When did she have it implanted?
A little over nine months.
She just went back for a follow-up exam last month.
She was fine.
Can you fix it?
I'm gonna find out.
Hello.
Don't be stupid.
What? There's no cameras in here.
Dr. Lim, Dr. Melendez.
How was your respective weekends?
Good. Checked out some bikes.
- Brushed up on some reading. - Excellent.
I hear the search for Chief of Surgery is back on.
As is our legal department's response
to the DPH complaint against both of you,
so I wouldn't get your hopes up.
Probably just as well.
I'd rather not see the two of you competing again.
You seem to be getting along better.
It's weird.
Is it weird?
They act like a couple, right?
I live with Lea, but we're not a couple.
Yeah, but you wish you were.
Do you?
Lea has a new boyfriend.
You must be a little jealous.
Why?
Lea's my friend and Lea's happy.
Okay.
Jake, Lea, and I can all be friends together.
Shaun, Lea's new boyfriend doesn't want to hang out
with the three of you.
If Lea really likes this guy,
she's gonna want to spend time just with him.
I know.
For the sex.
Her AVM has microbleeds.
Her risk of rupture is doubled.
They paged Sunny's surgeon.
He's gonna call you in an hour.
Tell them I can't wait that long.
- Her cardiac output is low and - Got it.
He's in surgery.
Excuse me. Uh, Dr. Melendez?
I'm Grace Lee. Sunny Lee's daughter.
They told me downstairs that you're my mother's doctor.
Yes. Get them to send her records
and everything they can about the device.
Manufacturer, model number, manuals.
Your mother's stable, but we're struggling
to get the information we need from her doctor in China.
I don't understand. Her doctor's in China?
Like on vacation?
No, her cardiac surgeon.
Your sister can fill you in on everything we've done so far.
- I really need to get back on this phone call. - Wait.
I don't have a sister.
We met 10 years ago
while I was volunteering at a senior center.
We hit it off.
Neither of us had anyone in our lives at the time.
People assumed we were mother and daughter
because we did everything together.
After a while, we just went with it.
She'll be glad to see you.
You look like you've put your problems behind you.
Problems?
She told me about your issues with drugs.
Oh, my God.
She caught me smoking pot.
Once. I was a teenager.
- So you're fine? - Of course I'm fine.
Then you don't really have an excuse
for not calling for 15 years, do you?
They want her back.
They've arranged for transport
they'll do the repairs in Beijing.
Is that safe?
Can she travel for that long in her condition?
It's a specially equipped plane for patients
requiring urgent medical assistance.
And 20 hours in the air is much safer
than at least that long on an operating table here
while we basically fly blind.
- Okay. - Okay.
Prep her for transport.
The microbleeds indicate
that it may already be starting to rupture.
If it goes,
you could suffer permanent brain damage or death.
Because of that,
embolization is no longer our preferred approach.
We want to open you up and cut it out.
Can you try talking to her?
Just because I have autism doesn't --
I'm not asking you because you have autism.
I'm asking you because you're her doctor
and I'm getting nowhere.
The sting of the Japanese Giant Hornet
can dissolve human flesh and attack the nervous system.
Recommended treatment includes oral antihistamine
and acetaminophen.
Comforting choice of words.
It's 6:30. Dinner time.
I brought burgers and Jello. This one's yours.
Lana can't eat now.
We're trying to schedule a surgery to --
I could die.
The surgery sounds scary but necessary,
so I'll do it.
"...big feet got there first. Johnny stumbled caught himself
and swung silently about at Dove.
'Gosh, Johnny, I'm sorry,'
snickered Dove.
'Sorry, eh, you're going to be a lot sorrier.'
'I just didn't notice.' 'You do that a...'"
Shaun.
What are you doing?
Reading to you from "Johnny Tremain."
You're reading words. You're not reading sentences.
This edition of "Johnny Tremain" is 320 pages long.
To get through the entire thing,
I need to read 270 words per minute.
You don't have to finish the book in one sitting.
Oh, yes, that's how I read novels.
I want to know where the characters end up.
You know what? Let's just stop.
I can go slower.
I-I'm not listening, anyway.
Are you in pain?
- No, no, I'm not -- - You seem fatigued.
You know what? I have a good idea.
Why don't you take out the garbage?
Thank you.
Where is your recycling?
It's under the sink.
Dr. Glassman, this cannot be recycled.
If it's broken, it cannot be recycled
because shards of glass...
I don't care, Shaun!
I didn't ask you to re-sort the garbage.
I just asked you to take it out. Can you do that?
Your call light is on. How can I help you?
Any new symptoms or discomfort?
Lana?
Rhinoceros Beetle...?
I'm gonna get Javi on the phone.
You can talk to both of us.
Do these doors lock?
No.
Do you want them to?
Is there someone you're worried about?
Is it Javi? Or someone else?
I'm nervous about the surgery.
Dr. Lim is an excellent surgeon.
I've seen her do...
I'd like Javi to come and have sex with me.
I think an orgasm would help calm me.
Do the blinds close?
She's gonna need a norepinephrine drip
to maintain her pressure during transport.
Mom?
You look pretty.
Mom, I've been so worried.
You shouldn't have. Teresa takes good care of me.
I'm so glad.
Why did you never call me?
You made it clear you wanted nothing to do with me.
I just wanted to live my own life.
So that's what you got.
Your own life -- without me.
This isn't a good time to --
You were so good,
straight A's, always so smart.
- You threw it all away... - You never understood.
Dad did. Dad wanted me to be happy...
He wanted you to have fun...as a child...
not waste your life.
Singing is not a career.
Sunny, you need to calm down.
Grace, your mother cannot handle this stress right now.
Teresa... Teresa is a teacher.
Mom, stop. Listen to the doctor.
You forgot about me.
I wish you'd... stayed away.
Would...have...
Her arterial blood pressure is dropping.
Start bagging and give her 40 Lasix.
I'm calling a code.
BGM: Say, Can You Hear by Men I Trust
♪ Say, can you hear ♪
♪ Is there a meaning to your grief? ♪
♪ Where there is pain ♪
♪ You see grace ♪
- Shaun? - Yes, it's Shaun.
I've picked out a very good movie
that we can all watch together.
Not the... not the time, Shaun.
I made popcorn.
That's okay. You just stay here.
Stay here. Sorry.
Shaun, we kind of need some privacy right now.
I also bought orange juice for Jake.
He was looking for some in the fridge.
Okay.
I thought you said you were okay with this.
Jake will like the movie, Lea.
It's about a chef who...
Shaun, but you're not respecting boundaries.
If Jake and I are friends,
then we can all spend time together.
Shaun...
Of course, we can all be friends.
That would be great.
It's just sometimes it's gonna be just me and Jake.
Without you.
For the sex?
And some other times, too.
Okay?
Okay.
Just give us a minute
and we can watch the movie in the living room together.
Okay.
Having sex right now is extremely dangerous
for someone in Lana's condition.
I studied the pre-op list of things I couldn't do.
Sex was not on the list.
We'll update the list.
Anything that elevates her blood pressure
could rupture the AVM before we get a chance to remove it.
You'll definitely need to abstain
until you're fully recovered.
Seems like you two are more than just roommates.
Why?
You care for each other, you have sex...
It's convenient. He's available.
And it's frequently better than masturbation.
- High praise. - And he leaves afterward.
She doesn't like being touched when she sleeps.
Are you two exclusive?
Lana and Javi don't have to define their relationship
in order to make it more digestible for you.
Clearly whatever it is, is working for them.
Now, you need to get some rest.
We're gonna do - your surgery at 10:00 A.M.
Sunny's on full life support.
Unfortunately, she can't be flown to China.
Her condition is beyond the scope
of the plane's medical facilities.
Dr. Melendez is discussing next steps
with Sunny's surgeon in China.
No daughter would treat a wonderful woman
like Sunny the way you did.
Does a wonderful woman refuse
to go to her daughter's recitals?
Then, when she gets accepted to Juilliard,
cut her off? Tell her she'll never make it,
that she'll wind up broke and on the streets?
Gently incise the dura.
Nicely done.
And there's our AVM.
Aneurysm clips.
It'd be nice to have what Lana and Javi have.
All the benefits of a relationship
without the emotional baggage.
The emotional baggage is the relationship.
Everybody has their issues --
the point is to sort them out together.
Yeah, that's all it takes --
agreed all the single people in the room.
I can't get under the AVM.
It's much closer to Broca's area than the MRI indicated.
Any damage could destroy her ability to speak.
What if we use stereotactic image guidance?
That would only show us where we are.
It wouldn't tell us if we're affecting function.
But if we track Lana's vocal function during the operation,
it will help us avoid the speech center nerve tracts.
You want to operate on her while she's awake?
We can barely get answers out of her at the best of times.
How do you think it'll go while her skull is open
in the middle of an O.R.?
Well, it's a good thing she has a "roommate" who can help.
It's hard to walk away.
We get angry, we want to run away, but
when it's family...
I'm not angry.
When I got the call telling me she was here,
all I could think about was how my lousy, bitter mother
was about to die alone.
That it wasn't her fault, it was just her nature.
So I needed to be here to let her know
that she was loved in spite of everything.
And then I found out about Teresa.
Saw them together.
Saw that my mother was capable of caring...
...capable of warmth... and love.
Just...not for me.
Dr. Park, please report to ICU 2.
She's bleeding from her cannula site.
She's intolerant to the ECMO.
We can't wait for the new heart.
We have to try and repair this one ourselves.
China thinks Sunny's heart failure is most likely due
to a broken blade in the impeller.
They're suggesting we weld it back together
using an intraoperative device...
which we don't have.
We could repair it with fibrin bioglue.
The blade spins at 1,200 RPMs --
the glue won't hold.
What if we used the schematics to 3D print a new impeller?
The plastic replacement probably wouldn't hold up long-term.
We don't need long-term.
We just need it to work until
the replacement arrives from China.
Let's get these to the lab.
You need me in the O.R.?
Yes.
While you operate on her brain with her head open?
You wouldn't be able to see what we're doing.
You won't see any blood --
What's the central illuminance of the O.R.?
- I don't know. - 140,000 Lux.
140,000 Lux is way worse than a grocery store.
I can't go to grocery stores.
We can provide you with protective gear
and eye shades that can filter out some of the lights.
Bright lights are like needles in my eyes.
Megasoma Actaeon.
Found in Guyana.
It's the heaviest insect in the world
and weighs as much as 300 grasshoppers.
Do you like playing insect trivia with Lana?
This is crazy.
You shouldn't do it because of trivia night.
You should do it because...
you love her.
Your life is better with her.
You are a better person with her
Y-you need her. That's what love is.
Do it because you love her.
I don't love her.
She's my roommate.
Impeller blades are fine.
The bearings are functioning properly.
Electrical consumption is good.
Maybe the machine isn't the problem.
Heart failure is either caused
by insufficient pumping or a constricted outflow.
Since her "pump" is fine...
She doesn't have valvular stenosis.
The surgeons removed her aortic valve
when they implanted this device.
It could be the aorta itself.
If it narrowed, that would reduce her outflow,
cause her pressure to drop.
If we do an intraop-angio,
we'd see evidence of that.
Call X-ray have them bring a C-arm, STAT.
Dr. Glassman?
I got you cherry Gastrolyte.
Shaun, I'm fine. You can go back to work.
At the Nathan County Fair, I was 14
and you got a cherry slushee and said it was your --
Why do you have an I.V.?
It's just fluid, Shaun, with potassium.
I had a nurse come by from the hospital.
I could have done this.
You're busy.
I'm helping you.
You wouldn't need the fluids
- if you listened to me. - I know.
You didn't drink the Gastrolyte I brought you.
- But now - Shaun.
My head really hurts right now.
How long have you been experiencing pain?
It pretty much never stops.
That's not true.
I asked you if you were in pain last night,
and you said you weren't.
I was in pain last night, Shaun.
I just didn't want you to worry.
Why would you lie about a symptom?
Why would you lie, Dr. Glassman?
- This c-- - This is why, Shaun.
This is why.
I can handle the pain. I can handle the nausea.
- You have nausea? - Yes. Yes, I have nausea.
Okay, you should stop the PCV Chemo.
- Shaun. - Okay, you should stop.
I'm going to call Dr. Blaize.
No. Shaun! No!
I am trying to help you!
I am trying to help you,
but you are not a compliant patient.
- You don't rest... - Shaun...
...when I tell you to rest.
You don't follow
- Will you please go?  - the diet that I am giving you.
Shaun, will you just go, please?
- Will you just go? - I-I promised that I would help you!
You're not my doctor, Shaun!
I don't...
I don't want you here.
I'm sorry. I don't want you here.
I don't know how to help you.
Then stop trying.
You're not helping.
You can't help, Shaun.
He's in pain and frustrated and nauseous,
and taking it out on you.
He's in pain and frustrated and nauseous, and I can't help him.
- That may be true. - So what do I do?
When there's nothing you can do,
you have to accept that.
You have to stop trying to help.
That's what he said.
Thank you, Lea.
My life is better with you.
Mine, too.
- We're in the aorta now. - If there is a narrowing,
we should see a sudden rise in pressure.
We should be able to replace the narrow part with a graft.
Metz.
This is a...
Horse.
Lana, what do you see here?
We need you to keep talking to us.
Have we already done damage?
It's too soon, I think.
We need to stop.
If we leave the AVM intact and it ruptures,
it will kill her.
Lana, do you understand?
I have to keep going, but if you stop talking,
you may never talk again.
Hand me the bipolar forceps.
Dr. Lim.
There's a Javi Maldonado insisting he should be in here.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
The surgery was a success.
You can see her when she wakes up.
Thank you.
She wasn't great with you,
but she's great with Teresa.
That doesn't mean she loves her more than you.
It may just mean...
she's not the same person anymore.
As soon as she saw me, she started giving me crap.
The same crap.
Actually, the first thing she said was...
...you look pretty.
Lana, what's on the screen?
A lion.
And what is that?
Lana, what's on the screen?
Javi...?
Madagascan Hissing Cockroach.
Gromphadorhina portentosa.
One of the few insects
who give birth to live young,
rather than laying eggs.
Keep going. You both are doing great.
Long-tailed South African Scorpion.
Hadogenes troglodytes.
Reaches a length of over 8 inches,
the longest scorpion in the world.
You'll still need to fly to China to get checked out --
but everything looks great.
Thank you.
Mom, Grace is outside.
I think you should talk to her.
Why?
Because...
she's your daughter.
- I'll step out. - It's okay.
Mom.
Since we stopped talking,
there hasn't been a day I haven't thought about you.
That I haven't missed you.
I'm sorry.
For everything.
I sat in the back.
At the Troubadour.
You were singing "I Wish It Would Rain"
with that band.
I cried.
It was beautiful.
Can you tell me your name?
BGM: Window by The Album Leaf
You remember your name?
Of course I remember my name --
Lana.
And you're Javi.
I think I love you.
I think you do, too.
Do you want to stay in bed with me after we have sex?
No.
Dr. Glassman?
I'm not here to help.
BGM: No Expectations by AG (feat. Brian Fennell)
♪ Take me to the station ♪
♪ And put me on the train ♪
♪ I got no expectations ♪
♪ To pass through here again ♪
♪ Once I was a rich man ♪
♪ Now I am so poor ♪
♪ But never in my sweet, short life ♪
♪ Have I felt like this before ♪
Thank you.