- My name is Barry Allen,
and I am
the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help
of my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
- Previously, on "The Flash"...
- Is this why you
came to Central City?
This nonsense.
- I don't actually
have to explain myself to you.
- This is illegal.
I'm a cop.
- The detective
who didn't know he had a son.
- I saw Mom today.
She says you haven't
been by in a while.
She thinks it's because
you're angry with her.
- I have every right
to be angry.
- I'm leaving Central City.
- What?
- I was accepted into
the Forensic Science program
at Midway City University.
- Got Turtle locked up
in the pipeline.
All we got to do is use him
to figure out how to steal
Zoom's speed, and then
we'll get your daughter back.
- That might take longer
than we thought.
- Because Turtle's dead.
- Now, decide in return
for your daughter's life.
- I will help you steal
The Flash's speed.
- People think of tar now
as mainly a roofing product.
Fun fact: it's also been used
as medicine and flavoring
for candy and liquor.
I bet what you're
thinking right now
isn't "yummy," is it?
What I hope you're thinking is,
"Wow, Clay is serious
about wanting to know
"where I put that money.
"I think I'll give him
that account number now,
so he doesn't drop me into
this vat of boiling tar."
- [muffled moaning]
- Hmm?
I'm sorry, what?
- [gasping]
Central City Bank
account 5463728.
[panting]
Please, please, pull me up now.
I'm so sorry!
Aah!
- I thought you said
you weren't gonna kill him.
- I say a lot of things.
[suspenseful music]
- Where's Joey?
- Wishing he was somewhere else.
Let's go.
[explosions]
Dude, get in the car!
Let's go!
Drive!
[engine turns over]
♪ ♪
[workers chattering]
[rumbling]
♪ ♪
- There's this
song lyric I like.
"All the broken hearts
in the world still beat.
"Mine's beating, but bruised.
"Hopefully not for long.
"The one thing I do know is:
time changes everything."
- [laughs]
- I didn't think
about how many
crazy things police see.
- And can't unsee.
- You always wanted to be a cop?
- Yeah, my dad was one.
He was my hero,
so I never thought
of being anything else.
What about you?
- No, I wanted to be
an astronaut.
- Wait, that's what
Barry wanted to be.
- [chuckles]
- Really?
Probably not for
the same reasons.
Going to space
is like the fastest
a human being can go,
so it was either an astronaut
or, like, have you
heard of scramjets?
- Mm-mm.
- Okay, they're like
supersonic on oxygen, dude.
It's nuts.
- You're right.
Not the same reason as Barry.
- You are really
all about the speed, huh?
- Yeah, I mean,
it's what I love.
- Is that why you're
still drag racing?
You are, aren't you?
Isn't that a little dangerous?
- Yeah, for the people
that race against me.
Sure is.
Look, thanks for the hang,
but I got to go.
- It's early.
Don't leave yet.
- No, I got some stuff to do.
I'll see you later.
- Why'd you do that?
- "Thanks for the hang?"
Is he your son or
age-inappropriate buddy?
- Look, I know
the dynamic is weird.
I'm just trying
to figure it out.
- From my perspective,
it seems like
you're ignoring
something that could,
oh, I don't know,
get Wally killed.
- The fact that Wally
even wants to get to know me
is the big win here,
so in the future
could you try not
chasing him out of the house?
- Look, Dad, I'll play along
if that's what you want,
but which you exactly are you
trying to let him get to know?
Because the person
that I saw tonight,
I don't recognize that dad.
- Journal entry 1-14:
Turtle's brain.
So, what I learned
from Turtle's brain matter
and the Reverse-Flash,
as it turns out,
has allowed me
to complete a device
that when installed
inside The Flash's suit,
will let me harness his speed,
so that the next time
he taps into the
Speed Force...
[sighs]
I could begin...collection.
I wish there were another way,
but there's not.
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
- You're here late.
- As are you.
Shouldn't you be out...
doing whatever it
is that 26-year-olds do
on a Thursday night?
- Um, I am recently single.
- Ah.
- So, I thought I would
tackle the breach problem.
See if I could figure out
how to close them.
Looks like you had
the same idea.
- Right.
I work better alone.
- Oh, no, haven't you
heard the expression
"two heads are better than one"?
- No.
- Must be an Earth-1 thing.
- You understand, for me,
that my Earth is Earth-1?
- Yeah.
- Your Earth has yet to create
CFL quark matter, and so
it would take you too long
to catch up on the science haul.
Do it by myself.
- This science?
- Yes, that science.
- Watch this.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
- That's annoying.
- Wow.
All right, I'm all caught up
for the next, like,
30 minutes, give or take.
Looks like I missed one though.
- All right, you can assist,
but I'm in charge.
- Yeah, you're in charge.
[Jill Scott's
"Run Run Run" playing]
♪ Na na na na na
na na na na na na ♪
- ♪ Baby, Mama be back ♪
- Check that ass.
- ♪ In a minute ♪
♪ Got to hustle
and handle my business ♪
♪ I'll be right back
when I'm done. ♪
- Hey.
What the hell
are you doing here
aside from trying
to send me to therapy?
- I told you,
I did some research.
I thought it would be
a good idea
for a story for the paper,
plus I thought this would be
a great way for us to really
get to know each other.
I mean, I want to know
what's so great about this
that you can't let go, bro.
- No one here is eager
to get their picture
in the paper,
you got me?
- And which part of the paper?
- [sighs]
- The front where they put
the mugshots or in the back
in the obituary section?
- Yo, why don't
you just take a page
out of your dad's book.
Let me do what
I'm gonna do, okay?
I don't need a big sister.
- I know, you're gonna
need an undertaker.
- Last race of
the night, people.
Our reigning champ: Tail Lights.
[cheers and applause]
[car honking]
- [chuckles]
Oh.
What?
No good luck?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[car engine turns over, revs]
[camera clicks]
♪ ♪
- We'll have the latest
on Oliver Queen's
mayoral campaign
coming up.
In local news,
Roofing Tar Industries,
which was devastated
by the S.T.A.R. Labs'
particle accelerator explosion
two years ago,
is finally set to reopen.
[tense music]
[tar grumbling]
♪ ♪
- Guys, clean up
before you leave!
♪ ♪
[tar grumbling]
- Two years!
Two years I was trapped
in the ground,
in that blackness.
I couldn't see,
I couldn't feel,
but I could still hate.
♪ ♪
- Joey?
- Did you ever wonder
what it felt like
when you dropped me in
that vat of boiling tar?
Since I went in headfirst,
I actually felt
my ears and nose burn off.
The pain of my eyeballs
searing was unimaginable,
but it was the way that
it burned down my throat
as I tried to breathe that
I thought was really special.
- Please.
- Why don't I just show you?
♪ ♪
- Excuse me.
Barr, you good?
- Hey.
Yeah, yeah, no,
it's just, you know,
it's weird Patty's not here.
- Oh, not for the same reasons,
but I miss Patty too.
- What do we got?
- Victim's name is Daniel Burge.
Not exactly a Boy Scout,
but managed to buy
this garage two years ago.
It looks like
he was dipped in a volcano.
- Oh, yeah.
Actually the depth
and uniformity
of the burn pattern
is something you would see
if the body was covered
in something like lava,
but with a lower burn temp
and an added
chemical characteristic.
- The fire investigator didn't
find a secondary accelerant.
- Yeah, he probably wouldn't
with a meta.
All right, I'm gonna take
a sample back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Have Cisco run some tests.
- Good, I'm gonna go
meet Iris for lunch.
She wants to talk
to me about Wally.
- Yeah, how's that going,
you and him?
- Great.
Well, good.
I don't know, baby steps.
I'm trying to give him space.
I mean, he just lost his mom.
Just met me and his sister.
He's got a lot on his plate.
- Yeah, he just found
the best dad
he could've wished for.
- Oh, you say that now,
but you didn't
always think that.
- [chuckles] Well,
you were pretty strict.
That's for sure.
- [chuckles]
- But strict isn't
always a bad thing,
especially when you know
it's coming from love.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Yeah.
It's disgusting.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
[beeping]
- Okay, now click here.
Bam, that's my app.
See, the app just went live.
♪ ♪
So, you can sink up
all social media postings
about meta-human activity.
Somebody sees something
cray in Central City,
I get an alert about it.
- Yo, man,
you have too much time
on your hands.
- Oh, I thought you were
gonna say it was cool.
- [laughs]
♪ ♪
[beeping]
- I'm just saying,
you can't judge me.
Didn't your girlfriend
just break up with you?
- Yeah, pretty sure
she just did.
Hey, Harry.
Wait, so if that app gives you
eyes and ears all over the city,
then why don't you use it
to find the next Ms. Right?
- Did I just make
the meta-human Tinder?
- Mm-hmm.
- Nope, not starting
that fetish.
It's about
checking your profile.
This is not a place for that.
- Hey, baby.
- Hey.
- You look like
you're working hard.
- I am.
I'm researching a story.
One that you'll
find interesting actually.
- Mm.
- This is Curran Roberts.
After his head went
through the windshield
of his hot rod, he was
in a coma for six months.
This kid, he died.
He wrapped his car around a tree
at 110 miles per hour.
They were all
street racers, Dad,
and Wally could be the next one.
- What do you want me
to do, Iris,
lock him up?
- Or stop the races.
- Look, I learned
a long time ago,
you can't stop your kids
from being who they are.
- Really?
Why won't you
be his parent, Dad?
What are you so afraid of?
- All right, you're right.
I'm afraid.
I'm afraid he'll reject me, us.
Like the last time
I confronted him
about the races, it didn't
go so well, remember?
And I need it to
go well with Wally.
I mean, after all
these years lost,
I want him in our lives,
but let me get him to trust me,
then I can do
something about it.
- Okay.
- [sighs]
- What's the matter?
- Um, not--I can't remember,
is the helicity of
a particle left-handed
if its spin and motion
is the same, or opposite?
- It's--
- No, hold on, I got it.
Hold on, don't answer that.
[pages whirring]
Opposite.
I knew that.
- You know that's
really annoying?
- Uh, it's, you know,
just got to...
[clicks tongue]
Recharge the old short-term
every once in a while.
[sighs]
You know,
this feels like old times.
- Okay.
- Yeah, I mean,
I know, obviously,
this is our first time
working together,
but I am learning
a lot from you.
The last Wells
was a real mentor.
- [sighs]
- He believed that
I could do anything.
Made me believe it.
- [sighs]
Okay.
- He opened up whole
new worlds to me.
Guess he really was like
another father almost.
- [sighs]
Stop it, all right?
- What?
- I did not ask
for you help, okay?
I certainly did not ask
to be your mentor.
- Okay, relax.
I was just talking about--
- Hey, you know what?
I have a kid already.
I don't need another one,
so scram.
Let me finish this by myself.
- All right.
[tense music]
- [sighs]
- Hey, I ran your crime scene
samples six ways from Sunday.
What's wrong with you?
- I was...
Uh, nothing.
What's up?
- Two things, very strange.
One, definitely
meta-human cells in the oil.
- And two, he didn't
die from his burns.
It was suffocation.
- Suffocation?
That makes sense actually.
The burns indicated that the
body was covered in something.
- Cross-referencing O2 levels
in the organic matter,
I found a direct match
to animals trapped
and preserved
in an asphalt seep.
The guy was fossilized.
- Whoa.
So whoever killed him
is like a walking--
- Tar pit.
- Mmm, too slow.
It's okay.
- So, he's basically
drowning them in tar.
God, that's a horror show.
Why did he target Daniel Burge?
[phone alerting with
suspenseful music]
- Oh, that's my meta-human
social media app.
That's right.
There's an attack in progress.
6th and Bell, downtown.
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[electric buzzing]
- Remember me, Clay?
- We killed you.
- I bet right now
you're not thinking...
"Yummy."
- Yo, are you guys seeing this?
- Oh, yeah, we see it.
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- All right, any ideas?
- Viscosity of asphalt lowers
as its temperature lowers.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah,
and it hardens.
Hey, find a way
to cool him down.
♪ ♪
- Hey, barbeque!
Hit me with your best shot!
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
[electric buzzing]
[grunts]
- [laughs]
Oh, yeah!
Team Flash!
- Hey, buddy.
I've got some questions for you.
Let's go.
[electric buzzing]
- You're coming home, Jesse.
You're coming home.
- All right, so Tar Pit--
Tar Pit, that's what
we're calling him?
- That's right.
- Tar Pit was after
one Clay Stanley.
Stanley, as it turns out,
is a suspected hit man
that the CCPD
has been trying
to track for a while,
but they haven't been able
to make anything stick.
- [chuckles]
- No pun intended.
- Do we know why
he was attacked?
- Uh, Stanley wouldn't
answer any of my questions.
He was pretty scared.
- When a hit man is scared,
you know something's wrong.
- Hey, did you get an ID
on our meta-human?
- Yeah, I'm running
it through five different
facial recognition
systems right now,
so it should take a minute.
[computer beeping]
And there it is.
Who's the best hacker
in the world, people?
both: Felicity Smoak.
- What is wrong with you two?
That's not friendship.
- Our meta-human's name
is Joseph Monteleone.
- Oh, he looks friendly.
- "Monteleone was
reported missing."
Surprise, surprise,
the night of the
particle accelerator explosion.
- And what's the connection
between Monteleone
and the two victims?
- I'll call Joe.
Have him run background checks
on all three guys.
- Okay, I'm gonna run some tests
on the tar samples.
See if I can find his weakness.
- Hey, are you feeling okay?
- Yeah.
Why?
- You're going slower
than normal.
You clocked in at
1,450 miles an hour.
- But, I'm sorry,
how fast do I usually run?
- 1,500.
Are you getting enough to eat?
- Yes, yeah, dude,
I'm fine, seriously.
The difference
seems negligible.
Fast is fast, right?
See ya.
- Yep.
- Harvick up to fifth place
by Edwards.
A valiant effort.
- Just overtake him, you idiot.
[race commentary continues]
- Clark Bronwen?
- Who's asking?
[groans]
[TV silences]
[sighs]
You're that chick who was
hanging around Tail Lights.
- I'm a reporter for CCPN.
I want you to stop
holding the races.
- [chuckles]
Sweetheart,
unless you could find me
another way to make
five grand a night,
it ain't gonna happen.
- Here's a preview of
the exposé that I am writing.
You are the star of the piece.
I had a little chat with some
of your previous associates
and dug up some revealing
details about you.
Like the gambling rings you run
or the thefts
you've been involved with.
I'm sure the CCPD will be
interested in this one.
- You're forgetting
something in here.
Aggravated assault.
You think you're the only one
that can play this game?
I could find out where you live,
what you eat, when you sleep,
every little detail
about your life.
Hmm?
Publish that trash,
we'll see what happens
to you, hmm?
- This entire conversation
is being recorded
and sent to CCPN.
If you or any of your people
lay a hand on me,
my colleagues will send this
to cops immediately.
- Get out of my office.
- [whimpers]
[tense music]
- You got a death wish?
- You are not the first person
to accuse me of that, so maybe.
- Going down there,
threatening them?
These people, Iris,
they live in the dark.
They're cockroaches,
except they don't scatter
when someone
turns on the lights.
They're looking to bite.
- If they are
so dangerous, Wally,
then why are you in
so deep with them?
- I'm not.
I can stop when I want.
- So why don't you?
You said that you were
only street racing
to earn money for
Francine's medical bills.
Well, there are
no medical bills anymore,
so why are you still doing it?
Look, I am not going to pretend
that Francine meant to me
what she did to you,
but in the short time that
I got to spend with her,
I saw what kind
of person she had become.
She was smart
and kind and loving,
so I can't even imagine
how much you miss her.
- You don't know
what I'm feeling.
- Well, let me tell
you how I feel.
I know that you were
trying really hard
to convince everyone
that you were a badass,
but I know that
you're a good kid, Wally.
And you didn't get that
way raising yourself.
You had a single mother
who cared for you,
so my dad and I care whether
you wrap yourself around a tree
or get shot by one
of these gangsters.
Having someone care
about your well-being
cannot be a new
sensation for you.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Show up there again,
and I won't be able
to protect you.
♪ ♪
- Just going over
some research.
- Ten-year-old determination.
- What?
- When my daughter
was ten she...
Science teacher had her
do a project, you know,
and this project--
I spent every waking hour
tinkering and perfecting
her solar-powered oven.
Anyway, ten-year-old
determination,
you remind me of her.
[sighs]
- Did you scold her as well?
- Yes.
- Mm.
- Look, I know that this
has been hard for you,
but you're not in it alone.
- Yes, I am.
Hell yes, I am.
I--as much as you all want me
to be part of your team,
that's never going to happen.
I'm always going
to be a father first.
And one day, Zoom is gonna
make me choose between you
and my daughter, and every time,
unblinkingly, unflinchingly,
I would choose my daughter.
I will betray you.
- That's binary thinking.
It doesn't have to be either-or.
- Life is either-or--
yes/no, black/white, love/hate--
from the dawn of time
to this moment right now.
- I guess I just have
more faith in you
than you have in yourself,
and by the way,
I came up with an idea or...
a notion rather, on how we could
close the breaches for good.
♪ ♪
- This is...
This--who wrote this?
- You did.
Yeah, the other you.
Evil, not stupid.
I think the answer
might be in
the electromagnetic insulator
of the quark matter.
Like I said,
we are a team.
[rousing music]
- I'm gonna take a look at this.
- I'm going to stick
around and run some
computer sims on the formula.
- I'll see you tonight.
- Yeah, see you later.
[dark music]
[electric buzzing]
♪ ♪
- Drink up.
[electric buzzing]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
Aah.
[electric whirring]
[growls]
- Had enough?
- Not even close.
- Give me back my daughter
and I'll get you the rest.
- You're not in the position
to negotiate.
- You won't kill me
and you won't kill my daughter
because if you do, then
you won't get what you want.
- I don't need to
kill your daughter.
- [groans]
- I can torture her.
Bring her right up
to the edge of death,
so I can do it again
the next day
and the next.
Bring me the rest of
Flash's speed.
♪ ♪
- Hey.
I ran background checks
on everyone involved
in this Tar Pit mess,
came up empty.
I mean, they all have records,
but they're sealed,
so I can't read them.
- Well, that's 'cause you're
bound by ethics, Detective West.
- How many felonies
are we committing
breaking into
sealed court records?
- Eh, three or four.
Nope, five.
- Well, they were sealed because
the records are
all juvenile offense.
- They weren't
arrested together.
- No, but look at this.
They served in the same
juvenile detention facility.
Actually, Monteleone
and victim one were bunkmates.
- Who do we have
shacked up with vic two?
- Bronwen, comma, Clark.
Good luck finding him.
He has a ton of addresses
and I can't seem
to find anything current.
I'll run his picture
through facial recognition.
- That won't be necessary.
In this case,
I am facial recognition.
I know exactly where
we can find that guy,
and, Dad, you are
not gonna like how.
- Okay, you can tell me
about it on the way.
What is that?
- Breach implosion reactor.
- Sorry I asked.
- You ready?
- Yeah, let's do it.
- Have fun fixing
the universe, you two.
- Hey, hey, hey,
what's going on?
You seem like you're in pain.
- What?
No, no, I have a...headache.
If our calculations
are correct--
- And they are.
When this device detonates,
it will collapse
the event horizon
on this side of the breach,
thereby shutting off
any connection
to Earth-2 permanently.
- [yawns]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm just a little tired.
I don't feel like myself.
I'm good though.
- Yeah.
- It's gonna work, Harry.
- Yep, yep. Okay.
You ready?
- Yeah, give it to me.
[stirring music]
♪ ♪
Come on.
We did it!
[laughs]
Come on!
You just rewrote
the laws of physics!
Don't smile or anything.
- I guess that was pretty cool.
- Yeah, I'd say so.
One down, 51 to go.
- Yeah.
Allen...
- Yeah?
- Thank you.
- It's just the first step
in getting your daughter back.
Come on!
[hip-hop music]
♪ ♪
- Welcome to the wrong side
of the wrong side of the tracks.
- So where's Clark?
- That's him.
- Oh.
♪ ♪
- Come on, man.
- There's Wally.
- Now, if our fly
flag girl can step up,
we're ready to begin.
[cheering]
[car engines revving]
[tires screeching]
[road crackling and rumbling]
- What the...?
[people exclaiming]
Call Barry.
- Okay.
[phone beeping]
- We good?
Been a little quiet ever
since we closed the breach.
- Listen, Allen...
[phone buzzing]
- Hey, sorry, it's--real quick.
Hey, let me call you back, Iris,
I...
I got to go.
[dramatic music]
[tires screeching]
♪ ♪
- [grunts]
- Iris!
Get her to the hospital!
♪ ♪
[somber music]
- [moans]
♪ ♪
- Hey, baby.
- Hi.
- You all right?
- What happened?
- Piece of glass from that car
pierced your shoulder.
- Mm.
- But you're gonna be all right.
- I hate hospitals.
[both chuckle]
[knock on door]
Wally, hi.
- Hey, can I come in?
Uh...
I got you some flowers.
I don't know what kind
or anything, I just...
Or maybe you're allergic--
is she allergic to flowers?
- No, I'm not, Wally.
Thank you.
- Cool.
Um...
I'll just leave them here.
♪ ♪
- It's okay, Wally.
- Feel better.
- I'll be back.
Hey, hey, hold up a minute.
- I got somewhere to be.
- Yeah, you do.
At your sister's bedside.
Iris came to that race
last night
because she cares about you.
- Look, man, this ain't on me.
I didn't tell her
to go to that race.
- Look, I know you didn't.
This ain't a blame thing.
Just hear me out, okay?
Look, I know you just
lost your mother
and you just found us,
it's been like a whirlwind.
Now, I--I can't tell you
how to live your life,
but I can tell you this:
you're not alone.
You have people that sit up
at night worried sick about you,
and they're not going to
stop worrying about you.
That's what a family does.
They put up with each other
and they put each other first,
before ourselves.
- So you're not mad at me?
- For being reckless
with your life?
Yeah, hell yeah, I'm mad at you.
But I'm more mad at myself
for being something I'm not.
I'm not your friend, Wally.
I'm your father.
I ain't letting you go.
- Okay.
[phone buzzes]
- Oh, it's Barry.
- Go.
I'll stay with her.
- You sure?
- Well, she's my sister, right?
- That's my boy.
- Don't worry,
we're gonna get him.
- I'm sorry, dude.
What?
- Tar Pit.
You shouldn't worry.
We're gonna get him with these.
With these nitrous grenades.
Each of these has ten times
the concentration
of a hot rod's nitrous tank
and is triggered
by extreme heat.
We're talking 650 degrees.
That's the boiling point
of asphalt,
so one of these puppies
makes contact,
you got a Tar Pit popsicle
for dessert.
- All right, that's great.
Um...
Hey, look, I think that
maybe you were right.
I felt slower tonight.
You know, not by much,
but enough.
Well, do you think
there's something wrong
with the suit maybe?
- It's unlikely.
- The readings from
the suit are normal.
You know I take care
of that thing.
- Yeah, what?
Am I sick?
- I don't know, dude.
Feel any different?
- No, not really.
I mean, I know that I'm slower
in the moment, but I can't tell
by how much.
- 2%.
Tests on the components
in your blood
show the Speed Force at a 100%
for the last 60 days
until today,
it dropped to 98.
- Zoom stole Jay's speed.
Do you think maybe,
during your fight with Zoom,
yours might have diminished?
- But that was weeks ago.
Why would I just be feeling
those effects now?
Dr. Wells?
- Yeah.
- You've studied the Speed Force
more than anyone.
What do you think
could have happened?
- It could be any
number of things.
- Yeah.
All right.
I just looked, I mean,
Iris could have died tonight.
- She's gonna be okay, Barry.
- You know, this time,
but the fact is, she is hurt
right now because of me.
I wasn't fast enough
to protect Iris
just from some
meta-human tonight.
When Zoom attacks again,
I need all of my speed
and then some.
I can't lose anyone else.
- You won't.
I did it.
- What?
- Whoa, whoa, what is that?
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I stole your speed.
I gave it to Zoom.
- No, no, no, this isn't...
What--you're working with Zoom?
- No, not at first.
- We trusted you.
I trusted you!
♪ ♪
- Joe, stop!
Why did you put him in there?
- Because if I didn't,
I would've kill him.
Let's go find this tar freak.
♪ ♪
[door whirring]
- Yeah, what the hell, man?
- Shut up.
- I thought I was
being transferred.
- [chuckles]
You're not being transferred.
You're the bait.
- What?
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- This is for
two years ago, Clay.
♪ ♪
[crackling]
- Stay.
- [grunts]
♪ ♪
- You know, it's ironic.
I was just saying
how much you remind me
of the old Wells,
and now, here we are,
just like I did with him,
standing on either
side of this glass
with me asking you, "Why?"
- I'm doing what I have to do
to save my daughter.
- Yeah, at any cost, right?
The cost of Joe's daughter.
- I told you,
"I would betray you."
I told you,
"I would have to choose."
- You chose wrong.
- Really, did I?
Because I just
sacrificed my daughter.
Because I just sentenced
my daughter to death
to save your son.
- You want a pat on the back?
- I want you to send me home.
Send me back to Earth-2.
Think about it.
Zoom wants you to get faster.
He wants you to have
more Speed Force in you,
for when he finally takes it,
send me back,
use the implosion reactor
to shut down the breach.
Shut down all the breaches.
Close them all
and Zoom will never
be able to crossover,
ever again,
and that'll be the end of it.
- What about your daughter?
- Jesse's my battle
to fight, not yours.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
[beeping]
[door whirring]
- [moans]
- Hey, how are you feeling?
- Like I could use
some pizza right now.
[both laughing]
- Well, they're letting
you out tomorrow,
so I can get you
any kind you want
from anywhere you want.
- Deal.
- You know...growing up,
we didn't have a lot of money
to go to the movies or buy toys.
Instead, she would just
take me in the car,
we'd would go for
these long drives.
Just her and I and her music.
I remember being
on the road with her
and just watching
the scenery flash by
and feeling so happy.
♪ ♪
And now, when I race,
feeling that rush of speed
it's like...
It's like I get to back
to those days.
♪ ♪
I didn't want to stop
because if I do...
♪ ♪
[sighs]
- See, that wasn't so hard.
- Actually, it was pretty hard.
[both chuckle]
- This is a sample
of Barry's cells
after whatever Harry
did to them.
As you can see, not only is it
drained of the Speed Force,
but it's also presenting itself
as chromosomal damage.
If Harry kept doing
what he was doing,
he could have taken
your powers permanently.
- Even Evil Wells couldn't
figure out how to do that one.
- Well, look, somebody better
send his ass back
to where he came from
or I'm gonna shoot him.
- Amen.
- No.
- What do you mean, no?
- What would we have done
if we were in his position?
I mean, what would you do
if it was Iris, Joe?
And Cisco,
when Snart kidnapped you,
threatened to kill your brother
unless you helped, you did,
and none of us
judged you for that.
We still don't because
when it comes to family,
when it comes to the people
that we all love,
we're all vulnerable.
None of us are above
making a wrong decision.
He could have done it.
He could have stolen my speed,
gotten away with it.
None of us would
have even known,
but he didn't, and now
his daughter's gonna die
and we're okay with that?
I can't just give up on her.
I can't give on a world.
This is a world full of people
who are facing death.
I don't know,
I may not be fast enough
to beat Zoom yet,
but I'm not gonna just
close the breaches
and forget about it.
We have to help Wells.
Look, guys, I...
I was the one
that trusted him first.
I own that.
I let him stay
when literally all of you
told me not to,
so everything that's happened
up until this point, it's on me,
but this has to be
a group decision.
[tense music]
[computer beeping]
♪ ♪
Come on.
- Well...
I guess this is good-bye.
- No, it's not.
I told you, we're a team.
Now you're a part of it.
We're gonna help you save Jesse.
We're not sending
you through alone.
We're going to Earth-2.
- Greg, move your head.