My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
When I was a child, I saw my mother killed
by something impossible.
Run, Barry, run!
My father went to prison for her murder.
Then an accident made me the impossible.
To the outside world, I'm
an ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, I use my speed to fight crime
and find others like me.
And one day, I'll find
who killed my mother...
Mom!
And get justice for my father.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
If you love me,
you'll tell me what is going on with you.
Keeping her in the dark keeps her safe.
I don't agree.
Harrison Wells is the Reverse-Flash.
15 years ago, Harrison and I
were thick as thieves.
We were promising young scientists,
and then everything changed
after Tess died.
- Who are you?
- My name is Eobard Thawne.
In the year 2020, you and your wife
successfully launched
a particle accelerator
that changed the course of history.
I need it to happen a bit sooner
if I'm going to get back.
After that day,
Harrison Wells became
a completely different person.
I'm getting faster,
faster than I've ever been,
and I wonder if it's because
lately something's chasing me.
I know what it is that's stalking me.
It's my past.
It's getting closer, and as fast as I am,
I can't help but feel like my past
has almost caught up with me.
- Where's Barry?
- He should be here any second.
I sent him out for...
Pizza!
- What?
- From Coast City?
Supposedly the best in the west.
Why did I not think of this before?
Come to papa.
Caitlin?
I'm not hungry.
Okay, six months
of investigating Harrison Wells
has led us nowhere, so we're going back
to the beginning to see
what we can find out.
What does that mean?
Road trip, baby.
Joe and Cisco are going
to go to Starling City.
Starling City? What for?
To investigate the car accident
that Dr. Wells was in
with Tess Morgan 15 years ago.
I... I don't understand. Why?
Dr. McGee said that after Wells's accident,
he became like a complete stranger.
Just a different person entirely.
Because the love of his life died?
You of all people can understand how grief
can change a person.
Caitlin, we believe that Dr. Wells
is the Reverse-Flash
and killed Barry's mother,
and he may have done
the same thing to Tess Morgan.
We have to learn everything
we can about that night.
See where it leads us.
Oh, um, can you cover for me
with Dr. Wells?
You mean lie?
Yeah.
I need some air.
Whoa... hey, Caitlin...
Doesn't look like Caitlin's with us.
No, she's with us. I'll talk to her.
What do you want us to do here?
Business as usual while we're gone.
Copy that.
Well, I want to wish you
good luck over there,
but I'm also scared of what you might find.
Scared is a good thing.
Scared keeps us alive.
Can you get the door, Nina?
- Nina?
- Oh.
Sorry.
Wrapped up in my own little world.
Late night?
Just one more thing to do
before I make my escape.
- See you tomorrow.
- Night.
So let's go over this again.
This is you on the
surveillance footage, correct?
It looks like me.
But it's not me.
I left work early yesterday.
Ask my husband.
Footage doesn't lie. Your husband might.
That's not me.
No priors, no arrests,
not even a speeding ticket.
And everyone who knows this woman,
coworkers, neighbors,
say she's the kindest, nicest,
most honest woman they've ever met.
So, unless she woke up this morning
and out of nowhere
decided to become a criminal...
Maybe we should be
looking for a meta-human.
Yeah.
One that can control people's minds.
Coerce them into becoming thieves.
Is that possible?
Is that a real question?
Hi, Barry.
Hey.
Have you, um, seen my dad?
Captain Singh says he took a
couple of days off,
and he hasn't been home.
I didn't ask.
Apparently he's taking
a couple of personal days.
Like father, like daughter I guess.
I'm sorry.
When are you coming home?
When it starts to feel like a home again.
You better pray Joe and Cisco
find something on Wells
at that accident site, Barry,
because I am just about done lying to Iris.
About all of this.
Yeah.
I recently inherited the entire collection.
Beautiful.
Let me grab my microscope.
Of course.
9-1-1. Emergency.
This is Dominic over at Abbott Jewelers.
I've got a guy in here
trying to sell stolen diamonds.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
Hey, look, uh...
can we talk about last night?
There's nothing to talk about.
Yeah, there is actually. Caitlin, look,
I know after everything Dr. Wells has done
for all of us, it's hard to wrap
your head around this,
but I need you to see the truth.
The truth?
The truth is that he saved
your life multiple times.
Look, I know. But if I'm right about this...
If, Barry, if.
And before I can believe any of this,
I'm gonna need to see some proof.
Proof?
Proof of what?
W... we may have another
meta-human case on our hands.
Ah. We are always happy
to help, Barry, as you know.
Have you heard from Cisco?
He hasn't arrived yet.
Uh, he has to help Dante, his brother.
He might need a few days off.
Ah, well.
All right.
Eddie.
Hey, I got a call about a guy
selling some of the jewelry
stolen from the bank last night.
Could be the teller's partner.
I think he's made me.
I could use The Flash's help.
Be right there.
Oh!
You can't outrun me.
I won't have to.
Well, that was new.
A shape-shifter?
Yeah, I literally saw a grown man, like,
m... morph into a teenage girl.
That's fascinating.
Today's physicists have always regarded
programmable matter
as nothing more than a theory,
but I guess your shape-shifter
proves it can be done.
Wait, so he, or she, or I... whatever.
This person can actually transform
into anyone they touch?
Yes, it appears so.
That includes you, Mr. Allen.
Dr. Wells is right.
If you are touched while
you're the Flash,
and he transforms into you,
we run the risk of him exposing
that Barry Allen
is the man behind the mask.
Because at this point we don't know
if the shape-shifter
is capable of absorbing more
that just your physical characteristics.
Like he might be able to copy my speed?
That would be bad.
Got it. Hands off the meta-human.
Hands off the meta-human.
So how do we find someone
who can transform into anyone?
We, I guess like any problem,
you just go back to the beginning.
In this case, that would mean
finding the first person
the shape-shifter morphed into
when they discovered their powers.
Yeah, can you pull up the CCPD records
of cases where the perpetrator
plead innocent,
even thought they were caught
on camera committing the crime?
You're good, Barry Allen.
You're very good.
Look at this.
Multiple crimes of this manner
all dating back to a month
after the particle accelerator explosion.
And the first one was?
Jacob Fisher. A teller at the
Federal Credit Union.
Claims he was innocent, and was
framed by his best friend,
a Hannibal Bates.
I'll pass this along to the CCPD,
see if they can track him down.
- Good.
- Thank you, Dr. Wells.
Always here to help, Barry.
There it is.
This is all you have?
Well, it's a pretty
cut and dry case, Detective.
Harrison Wells, Tess Morgan
are out on a Sunday drive,
the tires blow, Wells loses control,
and, uh... sadly Tess dies on the scene.
Couldn't imagine carrying
that kind of guilt around.
So, uh... what are you two hoping to find?
We're not exactly sure yet.
You come all the way from Central City,
you don't know what you're looking for?
Just following a hunch.
Uh, can you take us to the accident site?
It's been 15 years.
I think the pictures will
serve you better.
Still, we'd appreciate a look.
Whatever you need.
Captain, I need those witness statements
for the Joshua Brown trial.
Um, yeah, well,
like I told you, end of day.
Sorry, uh, Detective West, Cisco Ramon,
this is A.D.A. Laurel Lance.
Related?
Daughter.
- Hi. Hi.
- Hey there.
You work at S.T.A.R. Labs
with Barry Allen, right?
Uh, yeah.
Can I talk to you privately for a minute?
Sure.
So, uh... how is Allen?
Not too messed up from getting
hit by that lightning, I hope.
No, no.
How do you know Barry?
Are you guys, like, friends or something?
Not really.
We met last time he was in Starling City
visiting my friends.
John Diggle, Felicity Smoak,
and Oliver Queen.
Three people who have
absolutely nothing in common.
As far as I know.
Cisco, I know Barry's The Flash,
and Oliver's The Arrow.
How do you know that?
Because I'm the Black Canary.
- Stop playing.
- It's true.
You stop it right now.
No.
Okay, okay. Calm down.
I love you.
I mean, I love the way
that you beat up criminals.
Wait.
Why are you telling me this?
Because I need some technical expertise.
I've been using my sister's sonic device.
I was hoping you could help... modify it.
Yeah. I think I've got some ideas.
Great.
What... are you spying on me now?
Caitlin, what were you doing
at Wells's house?
I was gonna talk to him
and get some answers of my own.
You can't. You cannot talk to him.
Oh, so I'm just supposed to stand by
and watch all of you ruin this man's life?
Ruin my life?
What are you talking about "your life?"
Those nine months that you were in a coma
were the worst of my life.
I lost my reputation, my fiance,
and through all of that,
Harrison Wells stood by my side.
He told me everything was going to be okay.
If Dr. Wells is who you say he is,
everything I've done since the minute
I stepped foot in S.T.A.R. Labs
has been a lie.
Caitlin.
If I am right about all of this,
and you tell him what's been going on,
I'll never be able to get
my dad out of prison.
Barry.
If not for me, just do it for him.
I can't believe
you're pulling the dad card.
That's dirty pool, Barry.
Just until Joe and Cisco get back.
Please.
Turns out Hannibal Bates hasn't
been seen in well over a year.
Only remaining relative is his grandmother.
She took out a missing person's report
a couple of days after
the Jacob Fisher arrest.
Figure we could ask her a few questions.
Like why anyone in their family
thought that naming a kid Hannibal
wouldn't mean he'd grow up
to become a criminal?
Have you heard from your
grandson, Hannibal, recently,
Mrs. Bates?
- Recently?
- Uh-huh.
No. Why do you ask?
Oh, please.
Um...
because you filed a missing person's report
over a year ago.
Oh, yes, I certainly did.
You'll have to forgive me, Detective.
My memory is not quite as it used to be.
Of course.
Uh, neither apparently are my manners.
May I get you two something?
Coffee, tea?
Uh, no thank you, ma'am. We're fine.
Oh, please.
It'll only take a minute.
It's nice to have visitors.
Coffee'd be nice.
Thanks.
Ma'am, would you happen
to have a recent photograph
of Hannibal?
Ma'am?
She's gone.
I'll take the front.
Hey, we located Bates.
He was impersonating his grandma.
Barry, do not let him touch you.
Or let him see you use your super speed.
Well, how am I supposed to catch him?
The old-fashioned way.
Run like a normal person.
Okay, all right.
Oh, man.
What do you want us to do, Thawne?
Die.
Barry, call 911.
What do you want us to do, Thawne?
Die.
I know what this looks like, Cecile.
It looks like one of your detectives
shot two of your cops,
both of whom are now
fighting for their lives.
That's not what happened.
David, I am the district attorney.
I can't ignore what I just watched
because you want me to.
We both know there are things going on
in this city that can't be explained.
Come on, David. Until you show me something
incontrovertible, the best that I can do
is promise to keep him out of
gen pop at Iron Heights.
Do you have any way to explain this, Allen?
I'm working on it.
- Barry.
- Iris.
What is going on?
Everyone at CCPN is saying
that Eddie shot two cops.
How is that even possible?
We're not sure yet.
You don't think he did this, do you?
- No, of course not.
- I need to see him.
You can't... you can't see him, all right?
They're not gonna let you. Look...
I'm gonna do everything I can to help him.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay, I'm so sorry.
It's gonna be okay.
- Okay.
- I promise.
All right?
This is definitely the place.
Cisco, let's see what we can find.
What is that? A, uh, metal detector?
Uh, essentially.
Only instead of listening
for metal objects,
I'm listening for anything
that emits a abnormal sound wave.
Right.
Where'd you find this kid?
It's a long story.
So, it must be interesting
having a daughter
who is also the D.A.
Yeah, interesting's the word.
- I have a daughter of my own.
- Same line of work?
No, I wouldn't let her
anywhere near this nonsense.
Smart guy.
Overprotective.
You two get along?
We don't always see eye to eye,
but no matter how mad she gets at me
or how mad I get at her,
there's a strong bond.
Why?
You two have a bit of a rough patch?
Yeah, she, uh...
she kept something from me,
you know, something important.
Lied to me about it for months.
Hard to come back from something like that.
Mm. She give a reason?
Not one I could accept.
Ah. Well, sometimes we lie for love.
Especially when it comes to family, right?
- Joe!
- Yeah?
I think we got something.
Tachyons. Little bits of time travel.
You sure?
Pretty sure, yeah.
I didn't shoot those officers.
Yeah, the Captain certainly
plead your case.
The results of the GSR swab.
Detective Thawne's
hands are completely free
of lead, barium, and antimony.
Yet no one can seem to explain
how the surveillance video clearly shows
Thawne firing his weapon.
It only looked like Detective Thawne.
Mr. Allen, no.
Aren't you supposed to be
the scientist around here?
It's hard to blame her.
That video is pretty damning.
No. No, we just have to convince her.
Seeing is believing, Barry.
They're gonna put me away.
Okay, look, you get to S.T.A.R. Labs.
They'll set you up with a burner phone.
- I'll contact...
- No.
I run now, that surveillance video
is the least of my problems.
No way I don't smell guilty.
No way they'll let me stay on the force.
Look, you said it yourself,
if we don't find Hannibal Bates,
you go to prison.
For a crime you didn't commit.
I'm not gonna let that happen. Not again.
This isn't like your dad, Barry.
Eddie, look.
When you dad was put away,
you were a kid.
There wasn't anything you could do.
But you're not a kid anymore.
You're a scientist.
Hell, you're The Flash.
You are going to find Bates,
and you are going to clear me.
So go do it.
All right.
Get me out of here the right way.
I promise, Iris.
Now, I'm just here to shower and change,
and then I'm going right back to my lab.
I swear I'm going to get
Eddie out of this, okay?
I'll call you later, all right?
Eddie? What in the world?
How did you get out?
Captain Singh called in a favor.
Got a judge to sign my release.
I was just on the phone with Iris.
Why haven't you called her? Hold on.
I have no idea who she is.
Barry, it's me.
Hello... you.
I think I figured out
a way to stop our shapeshifter
from morphing into other people.
Oh, really?
What if I create a serum
that will terminate
the polymerization reaction,
essentially forcing the bonds
to revert to their original form
stopping him from being able
to control his power.
You can do that?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Okay.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing.
Look, about last night,
I can't imagine
how hard this must be for you.
I mean, I know how desperate you are
to solve your mom's murder.
But let's just bury the hatchet,
and we'll go back to S.T.A.R. Labs.
Figure out how to catch this everyman.
"Everyman?"
Bad nickname?
No.
No, I kinda like it.
Okay, good. Me, too.
Wait, hold up, Cisco.
Please tell me that's not
what I think it is.
Okay, that is definitely a hand.
Okay, see, I thought it was a foot,
but a hand is just as bad.
That is freaky.
That is proof, Cisco.
I'll need to test it to be certain.
I'm gonna grab my kit.
Okay, I'm gonna have to call this one in.
I can't let you do that.
Now I'm asking you, cop to cop,
keep this under wraps.
Forget you ever saw it.
- West, I can't do that.
- Listen, Lance,
if this is who I think it is,
anybody that knows about this
is in a hell of a lot of danger,
including my daughter.
As mad as you are at Laurel,
I can't imagine you wouldn't do anything
to protect her.
Hey. Good to go.
Just need to give it a little spin.
Oh.
Right. Yes.
A spin.
So this, uh...
serum that you're making,
is it a temporary fix,
or will it take away his power permanently?
Not permanently.
Just long enough so we can stop him.
And how long is it going to take?
Not long.
We just need...
What are you doing?
Something I think I should have done...
a long time ago.
Mm.
Barry, uh...
Oh, my God.
Look who's here.
Yes. Her.
Hi, I have been looking for you everywhere.
Here I am. What's up?
Look, whoever is framing Eddie,
I got to thinking.
What if they've done
something like this before?
I went through CCPN's crime archives,
and in the last 11 months,
there have been six crimes
committed by people who later swore
that they were innocent.
None of them had priors,
all of them had rock-solid alibis.
- All right.
- So...
I hacked into my dad's CCPD account,
and went through the footage
of Eddie shooting those cops.
Look.
What do you want us to do, Thawne?
Die
What's wrong with you?
Huh? Nothing.
I didn't do anything.
I don't know.
Seems pretty convincing to me.
Look again.
Eddie is not left-handed.
Look, Eddie is being framed,
and we need to figure out
who is behind this.
And believe me,
when I get my hands on them,
they are going to be...
Oh, my God. What did you do?
Your observations about the
shooter were spot on, Miss West.
He was indeed left-handed.
As is this man.
Our Barry... is right-handed.
Oh, I knew it.
- Never mind.
- Then this is him.
It is indeed.
I need to take him in to the police.
If they can see what he can do,
then maybe they'll let Eddie go.
Perhaps it might be best
if Dr. Snow and I handle this.
Mm.
What are you two going to do?
No. No, no, no. I'm taking him in.
Of course.
Well, at least let me help you.
There is a reporter at work who kept a file
of these sorts of things.
You know, all of the unexplained
events in the city.
This guy...
definitely belongs in that file.
That's gonna be a pretty big file.
You know who else is in that file?
The Burning Man.
Oh, really? What about him?
I thought he was just some urban legend.
Help me! Help me, help me, help me!
- Oh, no.
- Someone, please, help me!
Help! Help! These bad ladies
have kidnapped me!
- What's going on here?
- I need help!
I need help! These bad ladies kidnapped me!
We did not kidnap her.
- No.
- Iris, drive.
- I can't.
- Call the police.
No. No, no, no. She's dangerous.
Hey!
She's dangerous. No!
Hey! Where are you going?
Oh, Barry.
Aah!
For real?
- Why did you slap me?
- Because you were unconscious.
Smelling salts work just as well.
Sorry. You okay?
I think so, yeah.
Wait, Caitlin. Bates, he was here.
- Uh, yes, I know.
- Okay, let's go.
You sure there's nothing else
I can do for you, Detective?
You have done more than enough.
Thank you for everything, Captain.
Listen, I should be thanking you
for getting me out of the office for a day.
Pushing papers, reviewing budgets
public all over my ass.
It's been a nice change.
I'd still be detective
if I could, but, you know,
body just can't take it anymore.
What you gonna do when you got a bad heart?
I can think of something
that might make things better.
Cisco.
Laurel, hey. Uh...
We're just about
to head back to Central City.
Were you able to make that item?
I think this will do the trick.
I bumped up the specs.
Quadrupled the range,
tripled the resonance.
You should be able to do some
serious damage with this thing.
I can't believe you were able
to make it so quickly.
Eh. I've had some practice
with sound waves recently.
I think you should call it
"The Canary Cry."
I like it. Thank you.
As promised.
Hey, you show this to anyone,
I'll kill you.
That's just an expression,
right?
Nope.
Cisco? You good?
Oh, I'm good.
So this Hannibal Bates has turned into
quite the meta-human. Take a look.
His cells have the ability to transmogrify
at quite the rate.
- Which is how he can become anyone.
- Which is how he can look like anyone.
Because he cannot appropriate
your memory or your powers.
Got it. Hands on the meta-human.
Hands on the meta-human.
And to help you do that,
Dr. Snow has concocted a
solution we believe will stop him.
Yes. I've made a serum that will create
a cortical reaction around his cells.
Deprive those cells
of their electrical charge,
his shape-shifting days are over.
Wow, that's great work.
Thank you.
Um... no need for a hug
or anything like that.
Okay.
Oh, Barry.
We got a ping from your cell phone.
Looks like Hannibal Bates
is at the airport.
Payback time.
Guys, are we sure he's at the airport?
According to the GPS
on your phone, he's there.
Yeah, but...
he could be any of these people.
I'm not seeing him.
Gotcha.
Hannibal Bates.
I think you've mistaken me
for someone else.
Wait. It's me.
Please don't hurt me.
Not so hero-like.
Treat all your women like that?
Well, look at that.
I'm The Flash.
You may look like me...
but you're not as fast.
You're done imitating innocent people.
Aah!
- Barry?
- Yeah.
The one and only.
Detective Thawne has been released.
I have to admit this
is new territory for me.
This is new territory for all of us.
I certainly don't think the law is prepared
to deal with this kind of criminal.
Hopefully we can catch up fast.
It's hard to believe we live in a world
where this kind of impossible even exists.
Luckily it's also a world
where The Flash exists.
Uh, speaking of...
he left this list of all the robberies
that Hannibal Bates was involved in.
That's a long list.
With just as many innocent people
whose names need to be cleared.
You know, I saw The Flash once.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
I was on my way to the courthouse.
He blew past me. It was...
it was just a blur of red
and a gust of wind.
But it was pretty damn cool.
Iris.
Oh.
All charges have been dropped.
I'm clear to go.
Oh, thank God.
Iris...
I need to tell you something.
You know what?
It can wait until we get home.
You were right.
I was hiding something from you,
and you deserve to know the truth.
The reason I've been so distant lately...
I've been working with The Flash.
Let me out of here!
Hey, cutie. Want to let me out of here?
Like anyone would be
dumb enough to fall for that.
Seen a lot of things that you can become,
but who are you, Hannibal Bates?
I, uh...
I can't remember.
Well, let's lock up shop.
Good night, everyone.
What about Dr. Wells?
Come here.
I need to show you something.
This isn't possible.
Caitlin, I ran the DNA test twice.
It's a perfect match.
This body is the real Harrison Wells.
If this is Dr. Wells,
then who have we been
working for this whole time?
Dr. McGee said that after the accident,
Wells became a completely different person.
It's because he is a different person.
Dr. Wells.
You here on business?
Business, no. I came to give my regards
to Detective Thawne.
Glad it all worked out.
Yeah. Crazy day for him.
Yeah.
Crazy day for us all.
Oh.
Detective, did you enjoy
your time in Starling City?
Not much time for sightseeing.
I was working on a case.
- Oh.
- You used to live there.
I did.
You ever go back?
No.
Too many memories of Tess.
That's right. Sorry.
You, Detective, are one of
the few people I know
that truly understands that kind of loss.
Iris's mother, you never
talk about her, do you?
No.
I don't.
No?
You and I, Detective,
are members of a rather
exclusive club, I suppose.
One who's membership is too expensive.
Maybe we should have
another drink sometime.
Talk about it.
Yeah.
Yeah, we should do that.
What are you doing?
After the accelerator exploded,
I built a 3-D model of S.T.A.R. Labs
so that I could pinpoint exactly
what caused the malfunction.
And you never ran this test?
Of course I did.
I just never had any reason
to look at any areas outside
of the pipeline or the cortex.
It's a big building. Lots of places
for Wells to hide something.
What is that?
That shouldn't be there.
I'm picking up more activity around here.
Tachyons.
There.
Oh, my God.
Guys.
What the frak?