- Last season,
on "the flash"...
What's happening to me?
I wasn't the only one
affected, was i?
- We've been searching
for other meta-humans,
Like yourself.
- Don't be afraid, cisco.
You were affected, too.
- Once upon a time,
you agreed to marry me.
- Yes, i did.
- What do you say we do that?
- Harrison wells
is the reverse-flash.
[knife sinking in]
- you killed my mother!
Why?
- We're enemies, rivals,
opposites,
Reverses of one another.
- Just tell the police
what you did.
Get my dad out of prison!
- You could go back
and save your mother.
- A wormhole,
opening the gateway
Into time itself.
- I always win, flash!
- Eddie!
- Eddie's his ancestor.
If eddie dies,
He'll never be born.
He's being erased
from existence.
- The singularity won't stop,
Not even after
the earth is gone.
- We have to
disrupt the motion.
- It cannot be stopped!
- I have to try.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[suspenseful music]
- He's coming back around!
- Yeah, to die!
[both grunting]
I swear one of these days
i will kill you!
[grunts]
[groans]
- I was late again,
wasn't i?
- [laughs]
right on time.
[sirens wailing]
- whoo!
- [laughs]
- Two down at the same time?
Superhero
double play, baby!
- Didn't do it alone.
- You're never alone, barry.
- Neither are you,
mrs. Raymond.
- [groans] thank you
for not doing that
When i was inside you.
- It happened one time.
Let it go.
- Snart and rory.
You're gonna put a
cop like me out of a job.
- Just trying to help.
- You do more
than help, barry.
You give the people
of this city hope.
- You're the hero, barry.
- Congratulations, everyone.
A spectacular victory.
A milestone, if you will.
Mr. Allen, i believe there's
nothing left i can teach you.
I believe...
That you're ready to do
all of this on your own.
[quiet beeping]
- My name is barry allen,
And i am
the fastest man alive.
When i was a child,
i saw my mother killed
By something impossible.
My father went to prison
for her murder.
Then an accident made me
the impossible,
And i became the flash.
I used my powers
to find the man
Responsible
for my mother's death.
I thought i would finally get
justice for my family,
But i failed.
It's been six months
since the singularity.
I'm on my own now.
Decided it's better that way.
Keeps the people
i care about safe.
There's only one thing
i can do now.
I run.
- How's it going?
- Hey.
Uh, good.
How you doing?
- Good.
So, the victim.
His name is al rothstein.
He's a welder here
at the nuclear plant.
Co-worker found him
this morning.
So, what do you got?
- Petechiae on his face and
the whites of his eyes,
And this bruising
around his neck...
- Oh, so he was strangled.
- Mm-hmm.
By someone very strong
and very large.
- Or something?
- This wasn't grodd.
- Oh, thank god.
[sighs]
- look,
I'll let you know
When i find more.
- So this flash day thing.
I'm hoping you're planning on
making an appearance.
- Ah...
I haven't decided.
- Bar, i heard
the mayor's trying
To give you the key
to the city.
- Yeah, i don't need
an award.
- You love getting awards.
Like all those science trophies
you got in high school?
- Those i deserved.
I'll let you know
what i find, all right?
- All right.
[camera shutter clicks]
- Flash day is almost here.
A special downtown rally
To honor the man
who saved central city.
It's been six months since the
flash saved central city
From the freak black hole
that erupted in the sky.
- Joe, where are we at with
the murder at the nuclear plant?
- Barry's still analyzing
the evidence,
But there was definitely
something weird.
- Yeah, which is
why i let you have
That anti-meta-human
task force.
Speaking of which, where's
your scientific advisor?
- Ho, ho, ho!
Fear the beard!
It's a very
distinguished look...Sir.
- What is all this, mr. Ramon?
- Oh, this right here?
This is a little
something i'm working on.
I'm cooking it up for joe
And the task force
to take down meta-humans.
I'm think i'm going
to call it the boot.
Oh, here are the receipts.
- [sighs]
- Oh, um, captain,
one more thing.
- You are not getting
a badge, mr. Ramon.
- [chuckles]
- He's really stingy
with those badges, isn't he?
- Yeah, cops are
funny that way.
So you really think
you can get this to work?
Don't have me caught out on
the streets with my pants down.
- Yes, once i finish
the boot,
Ccpd will totally have what it
needs to take down a meta-human.
Especially now that
barry has decided to go all
Lone wolf mcquade
and fight crime by himself.
- I know, right?
Have you spoken to him?
- Not really.
Haven't even heard from caitlin
Since she started work
at mercury labs.
- Hey cicso. Hi, dad.
- Hey, baby.
- Hey, i was wondering if you'd
talked to barry about the rally.
- We was just saying.
[both chuckle]
- I'm sorry, but,
i can't believe
They're gonna give the flash
the key to the city.
Although technically,
as members of team flash,
We should all
be getting keys.
- Well, you know barry.
The more we try to convince
him to do something,
The less he's gonna
want to do it.
- Yeah, but he should go.
Someone should try and
get through to him.
- Maybe his best friend.
- Joe, believe me,
i've tried.
- I meant her.
- Bye, baby.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
[whooshing]
[fast hammering]
[drill whirring]
[whooshing]
[exhales]
- You know,
if you ever decided
That you didn't want
to be the flash,
You have a good future
being a contractor.
- [chuckles]
thanks.
Yeah, i'm just trying to
put it all back
Exactly how it was
before the--
You know.
[clears throat]
- Seems like a lot
of local businesses
Are being rebuilt
at night.
In secret.
I was thinking about writing an
article about it for the paper.
- Don't. Please.
- Look, people have
heard the stories.
They've read the articles.
They've maybe even seen
the red streak racing past them.
But they've never seen
the flash, barry.
- So that's
why you're here?
You came to talk me into
going to the rally?
'cause i'm--i'm not gonna go.
- People just want to thank
the man who saved central city.
- Well, they can't,
'cause that's not me.
You should know that,
better than anyone.
[sighs]
- Central city
believes in the flash.
So do i.
[crowd panicking]
[rumbling]
[wind blowing]
[thunder rumbling]
[debris crashing]
[crowd screaming]
[woman screams]
- Brilliant!
He's contained
the singularity
By adding to its
angular momentum!!
- Barry, it's stabilizing.
Keep doing what
you're doing!
- I'm not sure
how much longer i can.
Cisco!
- Now what?
- We have to merge the inner
and outer event horizons.
- How do we do that?
- By separating
in the eye of it.
The amount of energy from the
fissure should do the trick.
It's our only hope,
ronald.
- Ronnie, no!
It's too dangerous.
What if you can't
escape the inrush?
- Cait,
we have to try.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Ronnie...
Professor...
No!
[panting]
- Ronald...
Ronald...
- I'm so sorry.
[emotional music]
♪ ♪
[marching band plays]
[crowd cheers]
♪ ♪
- Are we expecting trouble?
- Cops always expect trouble.
In this city, i expect
super evil flying monsters.
- That's a solid
expectation.
- [chuckles]
- Well, i'll be.
[crowd cheering]
- Good morning, central city!
A year ago,
our world changed.
Our city became
ground zero for...
Some pretty weird stuff.
We got
a new breed of criminal:
Men and women who defied
not only our laws,
But physics and reason.
But we got
something else, too.
We got the flash!
[crowd cheers]
Our wounds run deep,
And i know
many of you are afraid
Of what threats
tomorrow may bring.
But the flash doesn't
just protect us,
He restores hope
where it was lost.
That's why i'm honored
to present the key
To the man who saved
central city: The flash!
[crowd cheers]
[whooshing noise]
[crowd chants "flash!"]
- Flash. Flash.
[crown continues to chant
"flash!"]
[emotional music]
[crowd continues chanting]
♪ ♪
- The doors to central city
Will forever be open
for you, flash.
[people scream]
- Look out!
[crowd screams]
- You all right?
- I got this, all right?
- The man who
saved central city,
Hate to rain on your parade.
- Oof!
[tires screech]
- Cisco!
Cisco!
The boot!
- Right!
[gun shots]
Locked and loaded.
Go!
Booted!
[buzzing noise]
[grunts]
[roars]
- Cisco, you said this thing
would take him down.
He's not going down.
- He went up.
- Run! Run!
- What are you doing?
- I'm throwing, you're shooting.
[grunts]
[roars]
- That's al rothstein.
The body we found
at the nuclear plant,
He's alive!
- According to
the coroner's office,
Al rothstein's body was
in the morgue all night,
So we can scratch off
"zombie attack."
- Rothstein have a twin brother?
- Nope.
Only child.
And get this, the night
the accelerator exploded,
Rothstein was on
his honeymoon, in hawaii.
- Huh. So we're looking for
a guy who's really strong,
Can grow twice his size,
and just happens to look
Exactly like the guy
he murdered?
- I would think this meta
was really cool
If everything about him didn't
just terrify me to my core.
- Is that what
happened to you?
You looked really spooked
there for a minute.
- Uh...
- I actually see
The guy that i can
ask about it right now.
Call you back, okay?
Hey.
So, the hospital next
to the flash day rally,
The x-ray and ct
machines all failed at once.
Was that because of you?
- I did not do anything
that would cause that.
I'm 92% sure.
I'm going to go make that 100.
Excuse me.
- You okay?
- We need to talk.
- Okay.
- Barry can't do this
alone anymore.
- [sighs]
that's his plan
And i don't know how
to talk him out of it.
At this point,
i'm just trying
Not to push
him farther away.
- Well, maybe barry
has been so successful
At pushing you,
me and everyone else away
Because we keep letting him.
Let's not let him.
- What do you suggest?
- Well, "if you keep getting
'no' for an answer,
Stop asking questions."
- I say that.
You quoting me to me?
- What can i say?
You are a very smart man.
- [chuckles]
- So this is what it looks
like inside mercury labs.
Security here is way better
than it was at s.T.A.R. Labs,
What with people
walking in and out
Of the cortex all the time.
- Hi cisco.
- Sweet sarek.
Is that
a 6k proton splicer?
- Yes, it is.
Dr. Mcgee insists on having
all the latest technology.
- Wow.
You deserve it.
[chuckles]
I spotted you,
at the rally today,
And i'm guessing
you saw what happened.
- Cisco, i can't come back.
- Okay, check this out:
We found this on a victim
At the nuclear power plant,
But the badge shows
absolutely nothing at all,
Which is so weird.
What's also weird is that at the
same time that meta-human grew,
All the x-ray machines within a
mile radius just went belly-up.
- Cisco.
- Just--if you could just...
See if the badge was tampered
with or something.
I mean, if it's broken, or...
Whatever.
It'll really help.
- Mr. Allen.
Barry allen?
- Yeah.
- I'm greg turk.
I'm an attorney at
weathersby and stone.
I don't usually make house
calls, but i've been trying
To get in touch with you
for several months.
- Yes. Yeah, i'm sorry
about that.
I've just, um--
I've been really busy
with police work.
- We need to talk
about s.T.A.R. Labs.
As you know, harrison wells
left the property to you
As part of his living trust.
- Yeah, which i did not
ask him to do,
But i've been
keeping the place up.
Well, it's going to take more
than cleaning the floors
To retain it,
i'm afraid.
The facility and the
real estate are scheduled to go
Into receivership at
the end of this week unless...
You watch this.
- What is this?
- A video message
drafted by dr. Wells.
- What's on it?
Have you seen it?
- No.
He was very specific.
It was
only to be watched by you.
The device will send me
a notification
After you've viewed it.
And at that point, i'll have
everything ready to execute.
- I'm not going
to watch that.
- Well, that's up
to you, mr. Allen.
I'm only here to represent
harrison wells' final request.
Good day.
[quiet music]
♪ ♪
[beeping]
- What are you guys
doing here?
- Working.
- So, caitlin was right.
- Yes, all humans contain
small amounts of radiation
Due to contact with
cell phones, microwaves,
Televisions, et cetera.
Our bodies are
natural conductors.
- I think our meta's been
sucking up all the radiation
Around him and using it
to power himself.
- Which is why the x-ray
machines at the hospital
Failed the day
of the rally.
- So if we want
to find him,
We gotta look for
places without radiation.
- All right, guys, i don't want
any of you here right now.
- Tough. You need your partners.
You need your friends.
- Barry, everyone in this room
cares about you,
But we also care
about this city.
We all want to
make a difference,
And that means fighting
meta-humans,
And that means working
with the flash.
You can't deny us that.
Not anymore.
- Got him.
There's a three
block dead zone
Near a hazardous
waste reclamation plant.
It should be blooming with rads,
and right now it's at zero.
- That's where you'll find
your atom smasher.
[chuckles]
Because he absorbs
atomic power,
And he, well, smashes.
- Come here.
- [chuckles]
- That's a great name.
Welcome to the team.
- Thank you.
- Great, guys, thank you.
You can go now,
all right?
- Barry, you need
to let cisco and stein
Figure out a way
to stop this guy.
- No, i don't.
[all sigh]
Barry left his
comm system behind.
We can't talk to him.
He's on his own.
- [sighs]
- [exhaling]
[inhaling]
[exhaling]
Well, this
is a curve ball.
I thought i was going to
have to come looking for you.
- I'm not gonna let you
hurt anyone else.
- I'm only here
to hurt you, buddy.
- Yeah?
Then why'd you kill
albert rothstein?
And why do you
look like him?
- You wouldn't believe me
if i told you.
- [chuckles] try me.
- I'm about to.
- Is there really no way
of knowing
What's going on in there?
- I'm looking for
the security cameras.
Booyah.
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
- My turn.
[choking]
- Dad.
- Maybe i can make it there.
- No, you won't, and what are
you gonna do when you get there?
The boot didn't work on him.
- Alarm!
- Believe me, we're all alarmed.
- No, the alarm system.
You've tapped into the
surveillance cameras, correct?
- Correct!
"come on, feel the noize.
- [grunts]
[grunting and choking]
- He said you were
some kind of big hero,
But you don't seem worthy
of him, or this city.
[alarm blares]
- [sighs]
- Professor stein,
you are a genius.
- I believe that's already
been well established.
- [laughs]
- [gasping]
- No, thank you.
- Iris says mac and cheese
is your favorite.
- I'm not hungry.
- It's been
six months, barry.
You gotta eat, son.
[sighs]
it's a good move,
Being angry all the time.
I get it.
You miss your mom and dad,
and you want
To show them that
you're strong.
Being mad makes it easier.
Tougher thing to do would be
to let yourself feel.
It's okay to be sad.
You can be sad, barry.
Your parents will understand
If you're not strong
all the time.
That is why i'm here.
It's okay, son.
I got you.
[heart monitor beeping]
- You're good.
I got you.
- Where is everyone?
- I figured you wouldn't want
an audience when you came to.
- [scoffs]
yeah, thanks.
- Iris is right.
You're not gonna do
this anymore.
For the last six months
i've given you your space
To work all this out,
come back to us.
But today proved that you'd
rather just get yourself killed.
- [chuckles]
It's better than
getting my friends killed.
You want me to tell you
that it wasn't your fault?
I can't. It was.
Guess what?
You weren't the only person
making decisions that day.
All of the rest of us
were there too.
Eddie and ronnie,
They chose to
help you stop wells,
And stop that--
- Singularity.
- Singularity thing.
It's on all of us, barry.
So stop with this hogging
all the blame and regret.
We gotta live with it.
Move on.
- What do i do now?
- Well, i know
that you've been
Rebuilding central city
at night.
It's just bricks
and paint.
Maybe you should start
trying to rebuild...
Things that really matter.
- What are you doing here?
- Sorry, i should've called
or something.
I just--i wanted to
see you.
- It's been a while.
- Yeah, cisco said
that he saw you
At the flash day
celebration.
I was surprised.
You, better than anyone,
know i wasn't the hero that day.
- Of course you were.
- No.
[sighs]
Cait,
ronnie died saving me.
And i should've saved him,
and i'm--i'm so sorry.
- Barry, i know that you did
everything you could.
It wasn't your fault.
I don't blame you
for ronnie's death.
I blame myself.
- Why?
- When ronnie first
became firestorm,
He asked me
to leave central city,
And go somewhere that
we could have a normal life.
And i said no.
I couldn't leave s.T.A.R. Labs,
dr. Wells...You.
If i had gone with him,
ronnie would still be alive.
Being at s.T.A.R. Labs
just made me think of that
Every single day.
- Here.
- Oh, you carry
a handkerchief now?
What are you, 80?
[object clatters to floor]
What's that?
- Ah, it's uh...
Apparently,
in case of his death,
Wells had some kind of
a living will.
- And you haven't
watched it yet?
- No. No, i've...
Been too afraid.
- What if we watched
it together?
- All right.
- [sighs]
Hello, barry.
If you're watching this,
That means something
has gone horribly wrong.
I'm dead and the last 15 years
have been for nothing.
Bummer.
15 years.
You know, when i realize that
in all those years
Helping raise you,
We were never truly enemies,
barry.
I'm not the thing you hate.
And so, i want to give you
the thing that you want most.
It won't matter.
You'll never be truly happy,
barry allen, trust me.
I know you.
Now...
[clears throat]
Erase everything i said
up to this point.
Give the following message
to the police.
My name is harrison wells.
Being of sound mind and body,
I freely confess
to the murder of nora allen.
In her home, on the night
of march 18th,
In the year 2000.
I attacked nora allen
in her dining room.
- Oh, my god.
- I stabbed her in the chest
With a large butcher knife--
- he confessed.
- From the drawer to the left
of the sink in the kitchen.
- This is it.
[laughs]
This is what i need
to free my dad.
Hey, joe.
Yeah, hey.
Can you have everybody meet me
at s.T.A.R. Labs?
Yeah.
All right, thanks.
All right, bye.
[exhales]
- I'll drive.
- Okay.
- You think the video's enough?
Mm-hmm.
Well, sure.
- What's she saying?
- Hold on.
Wells gave all
the right details.
It's not a done deal yet,
but the d.A. Says it looks good.
Yeah, i'm here.
- Is it good news?
- I think so.
- Henry's coming home?
Oh!
[laughs]
- Okay, well...
That still leaves atom smasher
to deal with.
- Last time you faced him,
it did not go well.
- No, it did not.
I clearly can't stop him
by myself.
So how are we
gonna beat him?
- Well, ever since i was shown
a drained radiation tag,
Which i haven't been able
to stop thinking about.
- Thank you, cisco.
- You're welcome, caitlin.
- If this guy likes radiation
so much,
I say we give it to him.
- [sighs]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Showtime.
- What's up?
I see you got my message.
- That light was perfect bait.
What made you think of that?
- I don't know, i think i saw it
in a comic book somewhere.
- You want me?
You're gonna have
to catch me.
- [growls]
- It's working, dude.
Rothstein's following you.
- I must say, he's quite agile
for a man his size.
- Run, barry, run.
- Come on.
[crashing noises]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Didn't think
i could catch you, huh?
- No, i knew you could.
Now, cisco!
[beeping]
[alarm blares]
- The amount of radiation
about to flood that room--
- Atom smasher won't be
able to absorb it all.
[alarm blares]
- [growling]
[heroic music]
♪ ♪
[roaring]
- The radiation's
been cleared.
It's safe for you
to go in.
- I'm sorry.
I couldn't let you
hurt anyone else.
Why?
Why did you want
to kill me?
- [gasping]
- He promised
he'd take me home...
If i killed you.
- Who?
Who promised you that?
- [gasping]
Zoom.
[panting]
[birds chirping]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[gate buzzes]
- Let's get out of here.
- I'll race you.
- [laughs]
You will lose.
[both laugh]
[x ambassadors'
"renegades" plays]
All: Welcome home!
[cheers and applause]
♪ run away-ay with me ♪
♪ bu-dum-dum-dum,
bu-dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ bu-dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ lost souls in revelry ♪
♪ bu-dum-dum-dum,
bu-dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ bu-dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ running wild
and running free ♪
♪ bu-dum-dum-dum,
bu-dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ bu-dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ two kids, you and me ♪
♪ bu-dum-dum-dum,
bu-dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ and i say
hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
♪ living like
we're renegades ♪
♪ renegades ♪
♪ ♪
[finger clinks against glass]
- Gather round,
everyone, please.
Looking at all of you,
Thinking how far
we've all come,
And remembering those
who are no longer with us,
I'm reminded of a hebrew word
used during times of graduation.
Kadima.
It means, "forward."
Forward.
- Forward.
- Well said.
- Thank you.
[clears throat]
- You good?
- Ah, yeah.
- [laughs]
- Stuff goes to your head after
being away from it for 14 years.
- I bet.
All right, well, look.
I was thinking,
what if, in the morning,
The two of us started looking
for an apartment for both of us,
And iris has actually been
doing some research on
How to get
your medical license back
So you could start
your practice up again,
Or, if you wanted, come work
with us at s.T.A.R. Labs.
I don't know.
I mean--
What's wrong? You okay?
- Yeah, it's a party.
Come on, we can talk about
all this tomorrow.
- Talk about what?
- Barry...
- Are you not planning
on sticking around?
- Okay.
Okay, do you think--
Can you be all that
you are becoming...
With me here?
- [chuckles]
You're the only family
that i have left.
- Well, that's not
really true, is it?
Don't you have another
family in this room?
They need
your help too, barry.
When you need me,
i will be here,
But right now,
central city doesn't need you
To be henry allen's son.
It needs you to be
the flash.
My kid.
The superhero.
[sighs]
I have to go.
I need you to tell me
that it's okay.
- Yeah.
[melancholy music]
♪ ♪
[elevator dings]
- Hey.
Your dad get off
okay?
- Yeah, i just dropped
him at the station.
- You good?
- I don't know, i--
Just feels like every time
i win, i still lose.
- Well...
It's not bad.
- No,
it's not bad.
It's pretty cool.
- It's real cool, come on!
- Hey!
- Hey.
- Ho ho!
- Hey, guess what?
I added a little upgrade
to your suit.
- [chuckles]
It's just like the one from
the future newspaper
Gideon showed us.
I was thinking, you know,
You shouldn't fear the future
anymore, right?
- No, and it'll be here
faster than we think.
- Well, see, i like it.
The lightning definitely pops
More against the white.
- And s.T.A.R. Labs
is now safer than ever.
Increased security
and surveillance.
- Re-coded, double firewalled,
electronic lock sets.
Nothing is getting through here
without us knowing.
- So people can't just waltz
in and out of here.
- Exactly.
- [gasps]
For real?
- Stay where you are.
- Who are you?
- You don't know me,
but i know you...Barry allen.
- Take one more step, it'll
be the last step you take.
The man asked you
a question.
Who the hell are you?
- My name is jay garrick,
And your world
is in danger.
- Greg, move your head.