My name is Barry Allen,
and I am the fastest man alive.
To the outside world, I'm an
ordinary forensic scientist,
but secretly, with the help of
my friends at S.T.A.R. Labs,
I fight crime and find
other meta-humans like me.
I hunted down the man
who killed my mother,
but in doing so, I opened up
our world to new threats,
and I am the only one
fast enough to stop them.
I am The Flash.
Previously on The Flash...
Why are you here?
Because I want to go faster,
and you're the only
one who can teach me.
Everything you need is on this drive.
It means a lot, you
looking after Barry.
Barry's not the only person
here I'm keeping safe.
We found Barry's double,
so where the hell am I?
Reverb.
You don't even know
how powerful you are.
My name was Hunter Zolomon.
I thought that if I could find
my doppelganger on this Earth,
I could replace my damaged cells
with some of his healthy ones.
I've been vibing Zoom, and
every time it's happened,
I've been near that thing.
I saw Jay. He's Zoom.
15 YEARS AGO
Sometimes terrible things happen
to us when we're children.
Things that can define who we become,
whether we want them to or not.
Run, Barry, run!
Some of us become stronger.
The people who took
me and helped me heal
and move past everything that happened.
They're responsible for
who I've become today.
But I know that I'm one
of the lucky ones.
Come on, Barry.
Not everyone gets
that kind of support.
Without it, I don't know
where I would have ended up
or what I could've become.
EARTH TWO
MANY YEARS AGO
- James...
- Who do you think you are?
Do you know what I went
through over there?
Do you know the sacrifices
I made for you?
I come back after years of
fighting for this country
and this is my welcome home?
You think you can walk out on me?
I'm your husband!
You're not my husband.
I don't know what you are right now.
I am a hero, Ashley.
No. You're a monster.
Run, Hunter, run.
Stay, boy!
It's okay.
Please. Please don't do this.
- Shut up!
- No, please.
No.
You're gonna want to see this, son.
No, James!
Please.
No. No, James.
No!
CENTRAL CITY
ORPHANAGE
- Name?
- Hunter Zolomon.
Father killed the mother.
Kid saw the whole thing.
Next of kin?
No relatives wanted him.
He is all alone.
Follow me.
And don't dawdle.
KEYSTONE CITY
OPENING SOON FOR PREVIEWS
Okay, you guys. I'm here.
- You got my location?
- You're good?
You don't need to, like,
stretch or something?
No, no, no, I'm good, I'm good.
Let's take this tachyon
enhancer out for a test drive.
All right.
Yeah. I feel that.
That is the tachyon device
powering up the Speed Force
in your cells like a
quick charge battery.
- How do you feel?
- Different.
Let's see how long it
takes you to get back here.
On my count.
Three, two, one.
Go!
This thing got you cruising.
- How fast does he normally go?
- Not this fast.
Not even close. Are his vitals okay?
Yeah, they're perfect.
Cool. It's like having a
pit-stop attached to your chest.
Guys, I can go faster.
Do it.
I'm back.
What... how long was I gone?
Let's put it this way,
you just annihilated your old record.
Yeah, you went four times
faster than you have ever been.
Four times?
- That's as...
- Fast as Zoom.
Well, faster actually.
Hey... do we think that...
we can get this thing smaller?
It kind of sucks.
If it sucks, then, yeah.
All right, so now all we have to do is
figure out how to get back to Zoom.
Yes... just a minor issue.
We closed all the breaches
and have no idea how to reopen them.
We don't... Wells?
Yeah, I have an idea, Allen.
Let's keep the breaches closed forever.
Forget about the breaches.
Forget about Zoom.
Wait, I'm sorry,
I thought that you were
on board with this.
No. No. I said I would
help you get faster.
I did not say I would
help you give the man
who kidnapped my daughter and
tortured her a chance to do it again.
Hey, we are not gonna let that happen.
Oh, you're not gonna let that happen.
Gosh, I wish I'd known
that the first time.
You don't understand Zoom
is different than us.
Zoom is not tied to anything.
Zoom does not care for anyone.
I do.
My daughter's out here
on this Earth somewhere.
I have to find her. We all have people
that we care about. Zoom
will use that against us.
Believe me.
Maybe we should just leave it be.
No, no. Look, no. Look, we're...
We're not turning our
backs on another Earth.
We're not gonna let Zoom
get away with everything that he's done.
Right now, there is no way
to another Earth, Allen.
Let's keep it that way.
We're getting back to Earth-2.
With or without his help.
Let's go to work.
Hey, where are you going?
We could use your help.
Yeah, I would.
It's just I have a date with Scott.
- That's the editor?
- Yeah, yeah.
That's good. No, I'm glad
that you're finding a way
to move on without
anything holding you back.
You deserve that.
Yeah, and well, I would have been able
to do it without your support.
It means a lot to me, so...
- Of course.
- Thanks.
Yes, for sure.
Well, hey, I mean, if you don't get this
breach problem fix by tonight...
bets me on for tomorrow?
I can do that.
Okay.
Man, I love it when you
train in Keystone City.
Hey, you sticking around after dinner?
Me and Wally are gonna watch Formula 1.
No, I can't.
I got to get back to the lab.
I'm still trying to find
a way back to Earth-2.
Can't you just stick Wells on it?
No, he refused.
Doesn't want me or anybody
opening the breaches again.
Well, I can't believe I'm saying this
about a man I shot at...
and punched in the face,
but I think you should listen to him.
Why?
Barry, it worries the hell out of me
the thought that you want
to go back to Earth-2.
I'm faster now. I'm
faster than I've ever been.
I'm faster than Zoom.
I can take him down.
All I'm saying is,
you already escaped the
hornet's nest once.
Why go back and kick it again?
- Hey.
- Wally!
We got some pizza here all
the way from Keystone City.
Hope it's cool I
brought my laundry over.
Of course. Barry used
to do his laundry here
all the time when he was in college.
That's cause those machines in the dorm
always eat your quarters, right?
Actually, I'm not...
living on campus anymore.
What? Since when?
Since room and board became way
more expensive than I thought.
Man, I can help you out with that.
I mean, I figured your
money must be tight
after paying all your
mother's medical bills.
How much more is it?
No, it's... it's cool.
Come on, Wally, let me help you out.
Plus I got that mini-fridge
in the garage.
You can use that, too, if you want.
Joe, I'm good. Really.
All right.
Let me just put
these in real quick.
Man, I can't figure
that kid out sometimes.
I wonder if his doppelganger's
that complicated.
Hey.
Any ideas?
Well, the best plan
we've come up with so far
is to set off a nuclear warhead
next to the city's
electrical grid, so...
We're not gonna do that.
I think I thought of something though.
Tell me everything that you know
about Cisco's doppelganger.
Reverb.
What were Reverb's
powers on your Earth?
He could tap into the multi-dimensional
energies between Earths.
He could see through dimensions.
Find breachers, like Ramon.
I mean, we... we saw Reverb do
more than that though, right?
I mean, we saw him shoot
vibrational bursts
out of his hands. Really painful ones.
What do you mean?
I-I mean, Reverb had
the ability to somehow
manipulate that
multi-dimensional energy.
- What's your point, Allen?
- My point is...
if his powers are linked to the energy
that ties together the multi-verse...
if he can manipulate it...
Then he can open a breach
to any Earth he wants.
Exactly. And if Reverb could do it...
I could do it too.
Cisco, I think the way
back to Earth-2 is you.
I got nothing.
Try again, okay?
Barry, what if he can't do it
because he thinks he can't do it?
He can do it though. You can do it.
You... it's gonna work, okay.
Maybe we're just not in the right place.
Or maybe I'm just not the
right man for the job.
Right? Let's go.
Cisco.
I'm sorry, Barry.
It's gonna work.
Detective...
I need to ask you...
Oh, you've got company.
No, it's... cool. I
should be studying anyway.
Do you know you kind of
look like that guy...
- I'm not him.
- Okay.
Later, Joe.
Thank you. Look...
I apologize for dropping by unannounced.
I just...
have you had any luck
locating my daughter?
Not yet, but I circulated her picture
through every department in the region.
And I reached out to some
friends in Keystone.
She's smart.
She's gonna know how to stay hidden.
- She's...
- We'll find her.
Right.
There's another thing also, Detective.
A favor.
I would ask you to talk Barry out
of reopening the breaches to my Earth.
I can't do that.
No.
You can't find a way to change his mind
for both our children's sakes?
Look,
I think it's just as dumb as you do.
but I learned a long time
ago that I can't talk Barry
out of anything once he
sets his mind to it.
Zoom is terrorizing this other world...
your world.
He can't let it go.
But look, why don't you do me a favor?
Go with Barry.
Help him.
Help him?
Why would I do that?
'Cause he's got a much better
chance of defeating Zoom
if you're involved.
This area has the highest levels
of residual trans-dimensional energy.
Should be able to open the
breach that used to be here.
It's right here. This is it.
For real? In this Patch
Adams nightmare right here?
- Yeah.
- Love it.
All right.
Look, dude, if this doesn't work,
I'll stop asking you
to do this, all right?
Okay.
What?
I can't do it.
That's right.
You can't.
What are you doing here? You said...
I know what I said.
But you're not gonna stop, are you?
No.
Okay, Barry Allen, then
I'm gonna do what I can
to make sure you don't get killed.
I recalibrated these
to the electromagnetic
frequency of this Earth.
It should help you access enough
of the trans-dimensional energy
to manipulate it.
Just like Reverb.
All I'm missing is the guyliner
and the transformation's complete.
Take 'em out for a spin.
(T)(U)S(U)B(T)IT(U)L(O).(CO)M
It's working.
Keep coming, Cisco. Keep coming.
Hey, what... what happened?
You were doing it.
No, no, no, no. I-I can't do this.
- What?
- I can't. Don't.
Please, don't ask me to do this.
Please.
Hey. What do we got?
It's your tachyon
absorption enhancer upgrade.
Retrofitted from when it was
used to steal your speed,
to now give you more of it.
Almost done.
That's amazing. Thank you.
You're welcome.
Is Cisco back yet? Have we seen him?
- I haven't seen him.
- Check his workshop.
Yeah, all right.
- Hey.
We just came by to see if
you guys needed some help.
Sure.
- Yeah. - We can always use
an extra set of hands.
- Do you want to help me in the med bay?
- Yeah.
Some advice?
This whole Wally thing...
He won't let me help him.
It's probably 'cause you're not
offering the right kind of help.
Wally doesn't want your help
paying for a place to live.
He wants you to offer
him a place to live.
- Why didn't he just say that?
- I don't know.
So he does want to live in our house?
Yeah, man.
Look, Wally's never lived
with his father before.
And trust me, that is a big deal.
And you're good with it?
I mean, you know, it's been you
and me for so long, and I love that,
but having Wally around
would be cool too.
Just we won't get to have as
much pizza from Keystone.
Yeah, it kind of sucks. I'm sorry.
Have to get used to that.
They really have a
special bond, don't they?
Yeah, they sure do.
Are you okay?
I don't know what I am.
Last night, I was
supposed to go on a date.
My first real date since Eddie died,
but at the last second, I just...
I couldn't do it.
Is it because of Eddie
or because of Barry?
I've noticed the way you've
been looking at him recently.
Is it that obvious?
Only to a woman who's been
through the same thing.
Everything seems to be telling me
that Barry and I are
meant to be together.
I mean, on Earth-2 we're married.
In the future, we're supposedly married.
And now that I'm finally
ready to move on,
I just wonder if that
should be with Barry.
Everything seems to be
pointing in that direction.
Do you believe in destiny, Caitlin?
Maybe for you.
Hello?
- Joe?
- Wally, I'm up here.
- Hey.
- What are you doing?
It's not done yet.
I mean, you can decorate
it how you like.
- Make it your own.
- Wait, Joe.
What is this?
Wally, forgive me.
When Barry and Iris went to college,
they couldn't get away fast enough.
They wanted nothing to
do with their old man.
It didn't even occur to me
that you might feel differently.
It's embarrassing, but it took
Barry to help me see that.
So, if you still haven't
found a place to live,
live here.
I mean, it's yours if you want to.
You're serious?
I'm not gonna do your laundry.
And I'm not washing dishes after you.
And this bed is going to be made
every morning before you leave.
And there will be no
beer in that fridge,
but yeah, it's yours.
When can I move in?
Whenever you want.
All right.
Thanks, Dad.
Hey, man.
Look...
I know what it's like...
Zoom, getting in your head,
how scary that can be.
It's not Zoom.
It's me.
What do you mean it's you?
It's like right now
I'm Anakin Skywalker.
I got the midi-chlorians.
I've got the goods.
The force is strong with me.
That is something I can feel.
But if I start opening
breaches into other worlds,
doing all this other crazy stuff
Reverb was doing, then...
what if this is how I become Vader?
Dude, you're never
going to become Vader.
You don't know that. That
is what happened to Reverb.
He learned how to use his abilities,
and when he felt that,
when he felt that power,
he succumbed...
to the dark side.
Look, I get it. I-I really do.
Every time I've learned a new ability,
I've been terrified about
what it might mean for me.
What it could do to me, you know?
But you were there with me
when I learned how to run on water,
when I ran up a building,
or traveled through time.
Just like I'm gonna be there
every step of the way with you.
You got something that Reverb never had,
and that's Caitlin and Joe
and Iris and Wells and me.
Friends who are gonna look out for you.
And we're more than just friends.
We're your family.
So what do you say?
Ready to put those things on
again, and go another round?
Let's do it.
All right.
You're all set.
He won't even know it's there.
'Cause whoever said
aesthetics aren't important.
Not me.
Let's go.
Hey, Cait, I know how hard
this is gonna be for you,
but we have to stop him.
I know, and I want to be supportive.
I just... I can't face Jay.
Or whatever his real name is.
What does that mean?
Well, you remember when I was looking
for his doppelganger, right?
Yeah. And you couldn't find him.
Because there is no Jay
Garrick on this Earth.
His doppelganger's name
is Hunter Zolomon.
Hunter Zolomon?
Are you sure?
Yeah, why?
Well, because on my Earth,
Hunter Zolomon was a
convicted serial killer.
That's Jay?
No, that is Hunter.
Last public photo of Hunter Zolomon.
Instantly recognizable. And
people from my Earth...
on my Earth, serial
killers are an anomaly,
so a lot of media attention to this.
There was a podcast.
When Hunter was 11, his
father killed his mother
right in front of him.
Father sent to prison,
Hunter grew up in the
foster care system.
Years later he was convicted
on 23 counts of murder.
23? That's, like, some real
Hannibal Lecter type level.
After the trial, Hunter was sent
to the Saint Perez Mental Asylum
for the Criminally Insane...
given daily electroshock therapy.
Cure him of his urges and
then faded from view.
Until the night your
particle accelerator exploded.
That's right. The dark matter
crept into the mental asylum.
I had thought...
piping the explosion underground
would limit exposure.
I was wrong.
All it did was create
an unstoppable monster.
NOTORIOUS SERIAL KILLER CAUGHT!
He's not unstoppable.
Jay doesn't know that we
know who he really is.
He thinks that his past is a secret.
- So?
- I think I have an idea
of how we can stop him.
Are you sure Jay can't get in here?
Pretty sure, but just in case.
How do you use this?
All right, so you aim it,
- and then you pull the trigger.
- Smart ass.
Barry and Cisco are in position.
Let's hope this thing works.
- You ready, buddy?
- Yeah.
You've always believed in me.
- Thank you.
- You got this.
Reverb's doppelganger
has increased his powers.
Hatred is a strong motivator.
You were unwise to reopen the breach.
I'm not gonna let you terrorize
another world anymore.
Without your speed,
you won't be able to stop me.
Let's see.
- Zoom's gaining on Barry.
- He can't catch him.
He better not.
- That was close.
- Too close.
The tachyon device is working.
Here they come.
They're here.
You've gotten faster.
Good. There'll be more for me to take.
You want my speed?
Catch me.
You're gonna want to see this, son.
- Get him, Barry.
- It's working.
No!
How did you figure out who I was?
You made a mistake.
You told Caitlin who
your doppelganger was.
I had to do something to get
her to stop trying... to fix me.
She's a smart girl.
- And that I was Zoom?
- The Velocity-9.
When you run fast enough,
it turns a speedster's lightning blue.
We would have helped you.
We would have done anything
we could to save your life.
Not everything.
Caitlin found you a cure!
A temporary one!
I'm dying, Barry!
There's only one thing that
can get me what I need.
And you just don't care
how many lives you destroy
trying to get it?
- How many people you kill?!
- No, I don't!
That feeling was taken
from me a long time ago.
We're not so different, you know.
What happened to us when we were kids.
You could have just as easily become me.
No.
I'd never become like you.
I got to say...
that was smart using...
my parents against me.
Oh, family. Such a weakness.
Not for all of us.
Well, that's where you're wrong.
It's time I get what I came for.
You're not getting anything from me.
You're not getting anything
from anybody ever again.
On any Earth.
You can't lock up the darkness.
What did you just say?
No!
- He was right there.
- I know.
I mean, we had him.
We had him. I can't believe it.
- Wally?
- Up here!
YOUR SPEED FOR WALLY
Hey, hey, hey. Where are we?
Where are we?
Help! Somebody please help!
There's only one person
who can help you now.
The Flash.
The Flash? Why would he help me?
He doesn't even know who I am.
Someone he cares about...
cares about you.
Dad?
Dad.
Coffee?
We're gonna get him back.
What if we could stop Zoom
through a vibe somehow?
We could weaponize the goggles...
Not enough time to weaponize, Ramon.
Okay, what if we modify the pulse
rifle to emit a low-level EMF?
We don't have the equipment
to modify the pulse rifles now.
Then we do another
snatch and grab mission.
By the time we scale those
cliffs, Zoom could already...
I need a minute!
Barry, I know you...
can't give up your speed
to that monster, but...
I also know that I want
to get my son back,
and I don't know what to do.
I do.
Wally, he's... he's part of the family.
He's... he's a part of...
our family.
And we do whatever we have to
to keep the ones we care about safe.
No, you...
you can't give up your speed.
That's not your decision.
This is the only way, Joe.
- Barry, are you sure?
- I'm sure.
I mean, we don't even know
if he'll be able to hear me.
He'll hear you.
I see him.
Wally's alive.
Thank God.
Do you see Jay?
I see him.
He can sense me.
Jay?
Vibe.
He'll do it.
Barry will give you his speed.
Babe.
- Dad?
- Wally, hold on.
Let him go.
We had a deal.
My speed for Wally's life.
Hand him over, and it's yours.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
You need to get out of here now.
- Okay.
- Go fast.
- Cisco!
- Let's go.
Let's get this over with.
This thing is how I stole
The Flash's speed the first time.
Now all he needs to do is run,
and his Speed Force will
transfer into this vial.
but only as long as I calibrate it.
Get to work.
Wells.
One day...
I'm gonna knock that smug
expression clean off your face.
So this was your plan all along?
Ever since the skies parted
and showed me another world...
with another speedster.
Once I saw you, I came here,
figured out what I had to do.
How are you still alive?
We saw you die.
You did.
So what was that? A speed mirage?
Speed mirage?
No. Even I'm not that fast.
I knew that I couldn't be on
two Earths at the same time,
so I went back in time and...
met another version of myself.
Your time remnant.
Like the Reverse-Flash.
I also knew that the only way
to make Barry become faster
was if you all witnessed
your old pal Jay die.
When did you decide to do that?
Oh, once you closed all the
breaches, went to Earth-2.
Believe me, getting my time remnant
to agree to me murdering him
took a bit of convincing.
But once he saw the... well,
the genius in my plan,
he was all for it.
Who's the man in the iron mask?
You wouldn't believe me if I told you.
Why the charade?
Running around dressed like The Flash?
To give people hope, Detective.
Hope?
So I could rip it away from them.
It's so fun
pretending to be a hero.
You are no hero.
You're nothing but a monster.
You're a monster.
No!
- Barry.
- It's all right, Joe.
He's slowing down.
The Speed Force is leaving his body.
He's becoming human again.
SPEED FORCE SAMPLE
100%
Barry, are you okay?
I'm okay. I'm okay.
- Thank you, Flash.
- Jay, stop.
Please.
If anything you ever
said to me was true,
or anything we ever shared was real,
then please just let him go. Please.
I know some piece of
you did care for me,
so if you have any humanity left,
then please, let him go.
Caitlin!