Out there.There's a world outside of Yonkers
Way out there beyond this hick town   Barnaby
There's a slick town   Barnaby
Out there.Full of shine and full of sparkle
Close your eyes and see it glisten   Barnaby
Listen   Barnaby...
Put on your Sunday clothes  there's lots of world out there
Get out the brillantine and dime cigars
We're gonna find adventure in the evening air
Girls in white in a perfumed night
Where the lights are bright as the stars!
Put on your Sunday clothes   we're gonna ride through town
In one of those new horsedrawn open cars
We'll see the shows at Delmonicos
And we'll close the town in a whirl
And we won't come old until we've kissed a girl!
·
Too much trash!!! Earth covered
wall.e working to dig your own
Too much garbage in your face?
There is plenty of space out in space.
BNL sky lightener living each day.
We will clean up the mess while you're away
The jewel of BNL fleet   the exisium
spin your fine and your cruise style
waited on 20 per hours a day
by our fully automated crew
while your captain and auto pilot try to ?
non-stopping entertainment
fine dinning
and with all access to auto chairs
and even grandma can join in the fun.
There is no need to walk
The exsium   putting the star in an excutive stylator
Because the BNL space is the final frontier
Put on your Sunday clothes when you feel down and out
Strut down the street and have your picture took
Dressed like a dream your spirits seem to turn about
That Sunday shine is a certain sign
That you feel as fine as you look!
It only takes a moment
To be loved a whole life long...
And that is all that love's about...
It only takes a moment
To be loved a whole life long...
Cancel.
Why zone? Many? Are you monger?
Directive?
- Direc... tive?  - Directive?
Classified
Name
Wa... Wall-E.
Wall.e.
Wall.e?
Eve
Eva?
Eva
Eve
Wall.e
Eva
Here.
Look.
Pop.
You pop.
Where is Wall-E!
Eva
Eva?
Eva?!
E....e...eva!!!!
Eva!
Eva.
Foreign Contaminant
Eva
Eva.
Eva!
So let's go to over the driving range
and had a view of virtual race in the space.
Nah   we did that yesterday
I don't wanna do that.
well.then let's do you what you wanna do.
i don't know
something
A cup. over here.
hello.
i didn't hear you.
Buy N Large
everything you need to be happy.
your day is very importmant to us.
here  take the coke.
hey  take the cup.
please remain stationary.
A service robot will be here to assist you momentarily
Stewards! Help!
please remain stationary.
A service robot will be here to assist you momentarily
what's it?
What's going on?
Walle
John
Eva.
No.John.
Bye  Walle.
A for axiom.
Your home  sweet home.
B for Buy N Large
Your very best friend.
Time for lunch.
In a cup.
Feel beautiful!
I know honey.
Attention.axiom sharpers.
Try blue.
Try blue   it's the new red.
The date after
we started to date...
every holiday I've been spending time on the virtual disaster
- Why he wasn't so superficial   you know?  - Yeah   I know my dear.
There's a lot of men out there.
Well   I know   I know because I... What the?... Because i spoke...
Walle
Mary.
Eva.
Sure.
Go ahead.
Eva.
Shade!
I didn't know we had a pool!
Captain   you're needed at the bridge.
I haven't done that.
Morning.
Just a trim?
i see
i know honey  i know.
i'm good
i'm good.you look gorgeous.
Sir.Coffee.
Sir.
Protocol   Auto. first things first
Computer. starts to reports.
- Mechanical systems?
Unchanged.
- Reactor core temperature?
- Passenger count?
Unchanged.
- The general food refill?
- Probe repair grounds?
Unchanged.
- Atmosphere conditions?
- Conditions values?
Unchanged.
Ok.Adam.
Twelve thirty.Adam.
why didn't you wake me for morning announcements?
Honestly   it's the one thing that I can deal on this ship
Well  good moring  everybody.
And   uh.Welcome the day of 255  642 on board in the  Axiom.
As always.
Weather's above ...
22 degrees and sunny and...uh.Oh  hey.
I see the ship's log is showing that
today's our 700 annual anniversary of our 5 years cruise.well.
I'm sure our four fathers will be proud to know that
700 years later we've been doing the exact same thing they were doing.
So  be sure next meal time to ask for your free
."Sep tu a centennial"
cup cake in a cup!
Wow  look at that.
Also today we have a ...
Adom  what is that flashing button?
captain.
probe Eve return a positive.
positive?
Eva.
but.
No probes
ever come back positive.
Before.
Greetings and congratulations captain.
If you're seeing this that means
Your Extraterrestrial Vegetation Evaluater
Or EVE Probe
Has return from earth with a
confirm specimen of on going photosynthesis
That's right.It means it's time to go back home.
Home?
We're going back?
Now the eath is restore to a life sustaining status.
my buddy We could be get our region recolonize.
Simply follow this manual instructions.
To place the plant
In your ship's holo-detector.
And the Axiom.
will immediatly navigate your return to earth.
It's that easy.
But the effects of microgravity
you and your passengers may have suffered some...
slight bone lost.
but i'm sure a few laps around in ship's jogging track
We'll get you back in shape in no time.
We have a jogging track?
If you have any further questions
Just consult your operation manual.
See you back home real soon.
operation manual.
manual.relate instructions.
manual?
Wow  will you look at that.
Eva.
Walle.
Well  Let's open now.
Step one  voice command confirm...
acquisition.
confirm acquisition.
Voice authorization required
accept.
Whe... Where's the that thing?
Plant.
Plant   right   right.
Where is it?
Maybe we missed a step.
Let's look it again.
Plant?
Walle.
Are you ok?
- Eva? - Quiet!
Use your scanner to be sure.
Contains no specimen.Probe's alert is faulty.
So  then.We're not going to earth.
negative.
I guess thing's go back to normal  huh?
correct  captain.
false alarm.
Probe must be defective.
GO-4!
Send it to repair ward.
And I have the one diagnostics on her make sure she's not...
Walle.
Have Walle cleaned.
- Eva  - what
analyse.
analysis.Foreign contaminan
Substance is a three base system..composed various combinations of natural derived elements
subject is most comminute reference to soil  dirt or earth.
earth.
define earth.
Earth  the surface of the world  it's distinct from the sky or sea.
define sea.
Sea  an expensive salt water that covered most of the earth's surface.
and surround...
Foreign Contaminant
You look gorgeous!
Eve!
Clear! Clear! Clear!
Eva!
Wall-E!
Oh  my.
Hold.
Caution! Rogue robots.
Walle.
Eva.
Earth.
directive.
Walle.
Plant.
Eva.  Walle.
Cruising speed
You are now creative movement in cabin
20 seconds to self destruct
10 seconds to self destruct
ten.
nine.
eight.
seven.
six.
five.
four.
three.
two.
No.No.
Eva.
Walle.
Oh  so many stars.
Hey  that's...what's the name?
Hey
what the...
Look.
Look at that.
I know that guy.
It's...um...Walle.
That's it.Walle.
Hi  Buddy.
It's your buddy John  Hi.
Hi.
Define "hold down".
Hold down. A social gathering in which
In which likly dancing will take place.
Adam  This is amazing!
These are called farms.
Humans put seeds into the ground.
put water on them...
...and they grow food   like pizza.
Good night  Captain.
Computer.
Define dancing.
Dancing.A series of movements.
Involving in two partners
With speed and rhythm mulch harmonic with music.
The leader deck is now closing
I didn't know we had a pool
no splashing no diving
No splashing... no...
Deliver to axiom superior
Eva
Directive
A perfect landing!
We're here everybody
yeah captain
captain we're home
it's so beautiful
no it's nothing guys
I was pleased to this
it's all about you people
not about me
how
how did you find it
we can go back home
for the first time
what's it like now
no no...don't tell me
I wanna see for myself
wait
that doesn't look like earth
where's the blue sky
where's the grass
I know that song
they're...dancing
yes dancing
You made somehow   huh   little guy?
you didn't give up  did you
wait a minute
activating security camera
eva
wall-e
foreign contaminant
there you go   little guy
you came a long way for a drink of water
Just need someone who will look after you
that's..
we have to go back
auto come down here
aye aye sir
wall-e
auto we found the plant
Porne I holo-detector.
not necessary captain
i will make it for you
you know what?I should do it myself
captain
Sir
I insist you give me the plant
AUTO   get out of my way
We can not go home
what are you talking about
why not
this's classified
Captain   give me the plant
what do you mean classified
you don't keep secret from captain
give me the plant
tell me waht's classified
Give me plant.
tell auto
that's the order
aye  aye  sir
Hey dear autopilots
got some bad news
Operation Clean Upheads...Well   uh   failed.
You know   raising toxics levels made life unsustainable on Earth
unsustainable?
what
I'm afraid we gonna have to cancel "Operation Recolonize". So...
so just stay the course
rather than trying to fix this problem
it will be just easier for everyone to remain in space
easier
Mr.president  I think
we have to go
okay
I'm giving overide directive A113   go to full auto pilot...take control of everything
and do not return to the earth
repeat do not return to the earth
let's get the heck outta here
now
the plant
no wait a minute
Computer   when was that message sent to Axiom
Message received in the year 2110.
That's... That's nearly 700 years ago!
auto thing've changed
we gotta go back
Sir   the orders are
"Do not return to Earth"
But life is sustainable now
Look at this plant
green and growing
its living proof he was wrong
Irrelevant   captain
What completely relevant?
out there is our home
home auto
and it's in trouble
I can just sit there and do nothing
it's all I ever done
That's all everyone in this blasted ship has ever done!
nothing
on the Axiom you will survive
I don't want to survive I want to live
Just following my directive.
I am the captain of Axiom
we are going home today
GO-4
this is mutiny
eva arrest him
EVE   you have to put this plant   straight in the holo-detector
no
eva
wall-e
Throw the plant! Throw it to me!
eva
give me the plant
no
All communications are terminated
You're confined in your quarters.
no
reboot
wall-e
Caution! Activating airlock disposal
Activating air-lock disposal
wall-e
Caution! Activating air-lock disposal
Activating air-lock disposal
wall-e
foreign contaminate
all clean
wall-e
M-O.
Directive.
directive
earth
earth?
earth!
mo
wall-e
Wrong!
Please hold. we are currently having...
eva
Oh   that style suits you.
Caution! Rogue Robots!
Not possible!
Auto! Hear me!
You stupid wheel!
Caution! Rogue Robots!
the plant
we'll see who's powerless now
Testing   testing.Is this thing on?
this is the captain
i'am locked in my room
eva wall-e
bring the plant to the leader deck
Go back and activate the holo-detector
now hurry AUTO is probably gonna cut me out
halt
haha look what I got auto
no possible
it's right the plant
oh you want it
Come and get it blinky
no
captain
Let go
for you?
You're not gonna get away from me when I...
Halt!
- I insist. This is not good.- Come closer. Gotcha!
Remain calm
Ladies gentleman
this is captain speaking
We have a little slight malfunction with the auto-pilot
Please remain calm
Enough.
- Grab it!  - no no...
Grab on!
I got you!
john get ready to have some kids
Look out!
no
wall-e
auto
you're leaved of duty.
wall-e
foreign contaminate
Plant origin verified
wall-e
course set for earth
10 seconds to hiper jump
wall-e
ho no
eva
wall-e
Put on your Sunday clothes when you feel down and out
Wall-E   you're home!
wall-e
eva
go go go
this's called farming
your kids are gonna grow all kinds of plant
vegetable plant pizza plant haha
no it's good to be home
come on ready to be in love
...a whole life long!