[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.0.4
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: DBfansub
ScriptType: v4.00+
PlayResX: 1280
Video Zoom Percent: 0.5
Scroll Position: 0
Active Line: 8
Video File: Brooklyn.Nine-Nine.S02E07.720p.HDTV.x264-KILLERS.mkv
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
Video Aspect Ratio: c1.77778
Video Position: 2110
PlayResY: 720

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,微软雅黑,58,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00030304,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,0
Style: Image,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H0000FFFF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,7,0,0,0,0
Style: 工作表,Arial,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 背景,Arial,20,&HA0FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 片尾,方正喵呜体,20,&H00FFFFFF,&H000000FF,&H00000000,&H00000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,1,2,2,10,10,10,1
Style: 片名,方正兰亭粗黑_GBK,80,&H00FDFFFD,&H000000FF,&H00030301,&H001F2F4B,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,0,0,2,10,10,10,1

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:05.00,工作表,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H666562&\b1}{\fn时尚中黑简体}翻译: Amber 钻井美 汉汉头 自心
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.00,0:00:10.00,工作表,NTP,0,0,0,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\b1\3c&H666562&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)}{\fn时尚中黑简体}校对: 恭喜哎呦哥哥
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.00,0:00:15.00,工作表,NTP,0,0,0,,{\c&HFFFFFF&}{\an8\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体}后期: 怪查理
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.00,0:00:20.00,工作表,NTP,0,0,0,,{\c&HFFFFFF&\an8}{\fs32\fad(800,800)\b1\3c&H666562&}{\fn时尚中黑简体\b1}压制: 怪查理
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:20.70,背景,,0,0,0,,{\fs34}{\p1\c&H96955E&\fscx4200\fscy410\an8\fad(800,800)\pos(642,0)}m 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 4 0 9 0 13 b 4 13 9 13 13 13 b 13 9 13 4 13 0 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.57,0:23:44.25,片尾,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正喵呜体}{\fs70\c&H20F0FF&\b1}电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}官方网站:www.dbfansub.com\N{\fs34}\N{\fs65\b0}新浪微博:@电波字幕组
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.04,0:01:09.50,片名,,0,0,0,,{\frz5.095\move(12,357,641,301,0,125)\i1}神烦警探
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.04,0:01:09.50,片名,,0,0,0,,{\frz5.095\fs50\move(1275,485,810,527,0,125)}第二季 第七集
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.77,0:01:28.02,片名,,0,0,0,,{\i1\move(1270,679,642,645,0,125)\frz357.5}电波诚译
Dialogue: 0,0:00:01.00,0:00:02.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,早上好\N{\fs38}Morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.84,0:00:04.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这花是给谁的\N{\fs38}Who are those for?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.37,0:00:06.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警监的叔叔去世了\N{\fs38}Captain Holt's uncle passed away.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.21,0:00:08.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,虽然他们不亲 但我还是想聊表心意\N{\fs38}They weren't close, but I wanted to do something.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.23,0:00:10.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有意思\N{\fs38}Interesting.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.23,0:00:12.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,送花是很大胆的选择 Santiago\N{\fs38}Flowers are a bold choice, Santiago,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.87,0:00:14.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我还是能打败你\N{\fs38}but I can still beat you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.26,0:00:16.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在表示哀悼这件事上打败我吗\N{\fs38}Beat me at expressing condolences?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.74,0:00:17.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错 比赛开始了\N{\fs38}Yup, it's on.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.14,0:00:20.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,花属于礼物 警监最讨厌别人送礼了\N{\fs38}Flowers are a gift, and Captain Holt hates gifts.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.75,0:00:23.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得一封体贴的邮件是个好主意\N{\fs38}I think a thoughtful email is the way to go here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.56,0:00:27.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"亲爱的警监 我们对你的不幸表示同情"\N{\fs38}"Dear Captain, we were all so sorry for your loss."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.24,0:00:29.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来自大家的安慰 很有意义\N{\fs38}Group sentiment, very meaningful.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.32,0:00:32.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"如果有什么需要 请一定告诉我们"\N{\fs38}"Please let us know if there's anything we can do."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.08,0:00:33.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无私的举动\N{\fs38}Selfless act.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.36,0:00:34.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恭敬有礼\N{\fs38}Very respectful.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.57,0:00:37.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错 我就是恭敬之王 小婊砸\N{\fs38}Correct, I am the King of respectfulness, bitches!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.88,0:00:41.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对了 你这封邮件是用私人账号还是工作账号发的\N{\fs38}Hey, did you send that from your personal or work account?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.03,0:00:42.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然私人账号啦 这是一件关于\N{\fs38}Personal... It's a personal matter
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.75,0:00:44.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,私人朋友和他私下的叔叔的私事嘛\N{\fs38}involving a personal friend and his personal uncle.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.82,0:00:46.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你没忘记取消你的默认签名吧\N{\fs38}So you remembered to turn off your signature, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.78,0:00:48.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大事不好\N{\fs38}Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.30,0:00:53.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗨 警监 我刚给你发了一封邮件\N{\fs38}Hey, Captain, I just sent you an email, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.79,0:00:56.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"亲爱的警监 我们对你的不幸表示同情"\N{\fs38}"Dear Captain, we were all so sorry for your loss.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.51,0:00:58.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"如果有什么需要 请一定告诉我们\N{\fs38}"Please let us know if there's anything we can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.22,0:01:00.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发送自我的臭屁屁"\N{\fs38}Sent from my stinky butt."
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.75,0:01:01.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的邮件被黑啦\N{\fs38}I was hacked?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.97,0:01:04.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你发的邮件 对我来说意味良多\N{\fs38}Thank you for the email. It means a lot to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.22,0:01:06.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用客气\N{\fs38}You're very welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.39,0:01:08.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是对你的臭屁屁说的\N{\fs38}I was addressing your stinky butt.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.26,0:01:31.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了各位 警监和我\N{\fs38}Okay, guys, Captain and I are going
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.93,0:01:33.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要去布莱顿海滩参加一个慈善活动\N{\fs38}to a charity event in Brighton beach.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.89,0:01:35.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,祝你们感恩节快乐\N{\fs38}Have a great Thanksgiving.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.35,0:01:36.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,啊咳\N{\fs38}Ahem.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.18,0:01:37.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思 Boyle 火鸡节快乐\N{\fs38}Sorry, Boyle. Turkey day.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.61,0:01:39.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等我和Jeffords警长走了\N{\fs38}Once sergeant Jeffords and I are gone,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.22,0:01:41.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Peralta就是这里的管事人\N{\fs38}Peralta will be the officer in command.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.08,0:01:42.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Jake称大王 盲击来一个\N{\fs38}Jake in charge. No-look five.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.78,0:01:43.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哇噢\N{\fs38}Whoo!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:44.86,0:01:45.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可不是你的手耶\N{\fs38}That's not your hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.28,0:01:47.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等\N{\fs38}Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.24,0:01:49.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是愈合后的耳洞吗\N{\fs38}Is that a healed-over earring hole?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.27,0:01:51.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你难道也有不羁的过去\N{\fs38}Do you have a scandalous past?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.44,0:01:53.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在执行任务时被刺中了\N{\fs38}I was stabbed in the line of duty.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.06,0:01:55.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伤疤从耳垂延伸到脖子\N{\fs38}The scar extends through the lobe into the neck.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.49,0:01:56.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这样真是不可爱\N{\fs38}No one likes it when you do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.81,0:01:59.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总之 谢谢你在节日帮我管理这个警区\N{\fs38}Anyway, thank you for taking command of the precinct over the holiday.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.63,0:02:00.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小意思\N{\fs38}Not a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.50,0:02:02.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家都知道 我讨厌感恩节\N{\fs38}As you all know, I hate Thanksgiving.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.14,0:02:05.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那些清教徒是一群凶手 火鸡尝起来像餐巾纸\N{\fs38}The pilgrims were murderers, and turkey tastes like napkins.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.14,0:02:05.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs38}感恩节起源于乘"五月花号"到达普利茅斯的英国清教徒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.14,0:02:07.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只希望你选我没选Amy\N{\fs38}I just hope that no Amys feel bad
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.21,0:02:08.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有让Amy觉得不开心\N{\fs38}that I was chosen over Amy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.49,0:02:12.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其实呢 警监是先找的我 不过我有事\N{\fs38}Actually, Captain asked me first, but I had plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.16,0:02:14.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Teddy自己酿了感恩节啤酒 今天可以装瓶了\N{\fs38}Teddy brewed a Thanksgiving pilsner, and it's bottling day.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.90,0:02:15.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,装瓶的日子\N{\fs38}Bottling day?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.68,0:02:17.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你还来这里干嘛\N{\fs38}Why'd you come in at all?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.04,0:02:18.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说实话 警监 你的首选居然不是我\N{\fs38}And frankly, sir, I'm a little hurt that
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.63,0:02:20.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我心里有点受伤\N{\fs38}I wasn't your top choice to be in charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.27,0:02:21.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,需要我提醒你上次让你\N{\fs38}I'd like to remind you of what happened
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.65,0:02:23.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去开献血车的时候发生什么了吗\N{\fs38}when I asked you to run the blood drive.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.46,0:02:26.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我忘记把海报贴出去了 所以没人来献血\N{\fs38}So I forgot to put up the posters, and no one came,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.21,0:02:30.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过别担心 我一个"淫"就献了将近三升血\N{\fs38}but don't worry, because I donated 5 pints all by me-self.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.47,0:02:33.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就值十二小时的班而已\N{\fs38}It's one 12-hour shift.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.79,0:02:34.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有什么可担心的\N{\fs38}What are you afraid is gonna happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.98,0:02:37.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,受伤 死亡 各种灾祸 \N{\fs38}Injury, death, general calamity.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.11,0:02:38.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别把这里烧了\N{\fs38}Just don't burn the place down.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.79,0:02:41.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,包在我身上了 警监 感恩节快乐噢\N{\fs38}You can count on me, sir. Happy Thanksgiving.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.46,0:02:42.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 是火鸡节  - 抱歉 Boyle\N{\fs38}- Turkey day. - Sorry, Boyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.33,0:02:45.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你们一小时后就下班了\N{\fs38}I know you're all leaving in an hour,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.83,0:02:47.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过在那之前 你们都归我管\N{\fs38}but until that time, you're under my command.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.74,0:02:49.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,作为领导者 我有责任\N{\fs38}And as leader, it is my job
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.20,0:02:50.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我的下属过上更好的生活\N{\fs38}to make my employees' lives better,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.01,0:02:53.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么可以为你做的 Gina\N{\fs38}so what can I do for you? Gina?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.81,0:02:57.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想要用爱理不理的口气接电话\N{\fs38}I would like to answer the phone always just like, "Eh-heh?"
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.71,0:02:59.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题 Charles\N{\fs38}Done. Charles?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.05,0:03:02.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,解除我不能在整个警区范围内说"味美多汁"的禁令\N{\fs38}Lift the precinct-wide ban on me saying the word "Succulent."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.12,0:03:02.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题\N{\fs38}Done.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.66,0:03:03.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想去休息室工作\N{\fs38}I want to work in the break room,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.62,0:03:05.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就不用听Charles说"味美多汁"这个词了\N{\fs38}so I don't have to hear Charles say "Succulent."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.19,0:03:07.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题 没问题 丹泽尔(没问题)·华盛顿\N{\fs38}Done, done, Done-zel Washington.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.19,0:03:07.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs38}丹泽尔·华盛顿 好莱坞著名黑人演员 
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.22,0:03:08.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果她去休息室工作\N{\fs38}If she's working in the break room,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.39,0:03:10.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我能把午睡沙发搬去候审室吗\N{\fs38}can I move my nap couch out into the bullpen?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.29,0:03:11.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,布鲁克斯和邓恩(没问题)\N{\fs38}Brooks and done.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.29,0:03:11.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs38}布鲁克斯和邓恩 美国著名乡村二重唱组合
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.52,0:03:14.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 所以你就准备在这瞎搞咯\N{\fs38}Oh, so your plan is to not take this seriously at all?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.10,0:03:15.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,才不是 我的严肃程度堪比心脏病发作\N{\fs38}Oh, I am as serious as a heart attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.74,0:03:16.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无意冒犯 Scully\N{\fs38}No offense, Scully.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.48,0:03:18.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事 我的心脏病也不严重\N{\fs38}Eh, mine are never that serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.35,0:03:19.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我管我的病叫"哎哟没事"\N{\fs38}I call 'em "Oopsies."
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.48,0:03:20.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能在这对大家有求必应 Jake\N{\fs38}You can't just grant wishes, Jake.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.83,0:03:22.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是老大 不是许愿精灵\N{\fs38}You're a boss, not a genie.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.22,0:03:24.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我两者都是 我是精灵老大\N{\fs38}I am both. I am a boss-genie.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.02,0:03:26.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个办公室就是我的神灯 支持我的举手\N{\fs38}And this office is my lamp. Who likes me being in charge?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.88,0:03:29.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,味美多汁\N{\fs38}Succulent.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.66,0:03:32.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你来参加这个活动 警长\N{\fs38}Thanks for coming to this event, sergeant.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.69,0:03:34.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很乐意和你一起 警监\N{\fs38}Always happy to spend time with you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.48,0:03:35.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多谢\N{\fs38}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.22,0:03:37.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且 我今天在外面待得越久越好\N{\fs38}Plus, the longer I stay out of my house today, the better.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.47,0:03:39.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我大舅子Zeke来了\N{\fs38}My brother-in-law Zeke is in town.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.24,0:03:42.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 我记得Zeke 很高大的一位绅士\N{\fs38}Oh, I remember Zeke. Large gentleman.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.50,0:03:44.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总叫你小Terry\N{\fs38}Calls you tiny Terry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.63,0:03:49.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不止 还有迷你Terry 超小型Terry娃和小笨笨\N{\fs38}Also teensy Terry, teeny-weeny Terry-Berry,and Li'l Dum-Dum.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.66,0:03:51.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最后这个绰号的不走心程度\N{\fs38}You know, it's the lack of effort on that last one
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.50,0:03:52.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真是让我生气\N{\fs38}that really gets me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.90,0:03:55.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是个成人了 警长 成长得橡木一样坚挺了\N{\fs38}You're a grown man, sergeant, strong like an oak.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.87,0:03:57.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,橡树确实是种好树\N{\fs38}That's a pretty good tree.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.37,0:03:59.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是非常强大的树\N{\fs38}It's a mighty tree.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.41,0:04:01.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那为什么不正面反抗这个Zeke呢\N{\fs38}So why not stand up to this Zeke?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.26,0:04:04.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一看到他就没胆了\N{\fs38}I get so intimidated around him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.00,0:04:07.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多谢你的三明治了 小笨笨\N{\fs38}Thanks for the sandwich, Li'l Dum-Dum.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.72,0:04:11.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你只是不想待在家里\N{\fs38}If you wanted to get out of the house,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.09,0:04:14.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么不提出代替Peralta管理警区呢\N{\fs38}why didn't you just volunteer to run the precinct instead of Peralta?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.09,0:04:16.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我更希望是你来负责啊\N{\fs38}I'd much rather have you in charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.06,0:04:18.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别担心Jake 他会做得很好的\N{\fs38}Don't worry about Jake. He's gonna do great.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.79,0:04:21.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他其实是很有责任心的人呢\N{\fs38}He can be very responsible.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.16,0:04:22.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了 电梯门是球门\N{\fs38}Okay, the elevator door is the goal.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.70,0:04:24.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,向我投球进攻吧\N{\fs38}Try and score on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.20,0:04:27.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,啊 \N{\fs38}Ah!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.20,0:04:28.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,耶\N{\fs38}Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.34,0:04:29.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了 到中午了 我们回去了\N{\fs38}All right, it's noon. We're going home.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.64,0:04:30.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再见了 精灵老大\N{\fs38}See you later, boss-genie.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.01,0:04:32.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,味美多汁的管理啊 Jakey\N{\fs38}Succulent bossing, Jakey.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.64,0:04:35.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要回家给烤鹅填内馅了\N{\fs38}I'm gonna go home and stuff my goose.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.48,0:04:38.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等 Boyle 粉末 这包粉末是什么\N{\fs38}Wait, Boyle, powder. What is that powder?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.88,0:04:40.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道 我不知道 咋办呢\N{\fs38}I don't know. I don't know, what do we do?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.75,0:04:47.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了各位 这里已经被封锁了\N{\fs38}Okay, everyone, we are in lockdown,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.26,0:04:50.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也就是说 没人能进出这个警区了\N{\fs38}which means no one can come in or out of the precinct.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.13,0:04:52.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,据情报 另外三个警区在这个月\N{\fs38}Now, apparently, three other precincts received
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.33,0:04:53.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也收到了同样的包裹\N{\fs38}similar packages this month,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.43,0:04:55.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无一例外 全都是发酵粉\N{\fs38}and they were all baking powder.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.00,0:04:57.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过 危险品处理小组还是要来检查一下\N{\fs38}Nevertheless, Hazmat has to run a quick test,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.67,0:05:00.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过我预计我们能很快撤离\N{\fs38}but I anticipate we'll all be out of here momentarily.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.00,0:05:03.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与此同时 我建议把这次封锁\N{\fs38}In the meantime, I suggest we turn this lockdown
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.34,0:05:05.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当做一次机械舞(封锁)玩\N{\fs38}into a pop-and-lockdown.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.31,0:05:07.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎样 我没说错吧\N{\fs38}Right? Am I right?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.38,0:05:08.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哈\N{\fs38}Huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.78,0:05:11.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 我会实时更新消息的\N{\fs38}Okay, so I'll keep everyone updated,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.65,0:05:13.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家也都舞动起来吧\N{\fs38}and keep working on your dance moves.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.34,0:05:16.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Jake 你在做什么 这可是紧急情况\N{\fs38}Jake, what are you doing? This is a crisis.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.88,0:05:18.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在努力鼓舞士气啊\N{\fs38}I'm trying to keep morale up,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.22,0:05:20.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为处理小组说这基本上就是一个恶作剧\N{\fs38}because Hazmat said it's almost definitely a hoax.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.32,0:05:22.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,基本上吗 万一里面装的是炭疽病毒呢\N{\fs38}Almost? What if it's Anthrax?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.49,0:05:25.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就死定了\N{\fs38}We are all 100% gonna die!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.23,0:05:26.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托 你造成人群恐慌了\N{\fs38}Guys! You're freaking people out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.63,0:05:29.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能不能冷静一下 目前一切正常\N{\fs38}Can you please calm it down? We're doing fine here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.83,0:05:30.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Hitchcock出事了\N{\fs38}Not Hitchcock.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.93,0:05:32.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他被关到阳台外面了\N{\fs38}He got trapped out on the balcony.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.60,0:05:34.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鉴于他过往的行为 不能让他单独待在那儿\N{\fs38}I don't like him alone out there, not with his history.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.97,0:05:36.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,万一他爬窗台上去了怎么办\N{\fs38}I mean, what if he gets up on a ledge?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.61,0:05:37.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么 你觉得他会跳下去吗\N{\fs38}What, you think he's gonna jump?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.63,0:05:39.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那倒不会 他只是很容易摔跤\N{\fs38}No, he's just always falling off things.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.30,0:05:42.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他耳朵里有只虫子 影响了他的平衡感\N{\fs38}He's got a worm living in his ear that affects his balance.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.16,0:05:45.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样说来 他就不算是一个人在外面了对吧\N{\fs38}Oh, well, then he's not truly alone out there, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.07,0:05:47.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了 我要给Holt打个电话 要一起吗\N{\fs38}Okay, I'm gonna call Holt. You want to come?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.96,0:05:49.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 好的  - 不好意思 我没邀请你呢\N{\fs38}- Yeah. - Too bad, you're uninvited.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.30,0:05:50.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在是老大 回见\N{\fs38}I'm in charge. Bye!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.29,0:05:53.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好 随时向我汇报情况\N{\fs38}Okay, keep me posted.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.04,0:05:55.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看来Peralta把局里管得很好\N{\fs38}Peralta seems to have it under control.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.86,0:05:57.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说一切都"棒极了"\N{\fs38}He said things were "Dope."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.92,0:06:00.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想要远程监控他们\N{\fs38}I want to monitor the situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.79,0:06:03.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要去一个有网络又有座机的地方\N{\fs38}I need to get somewhere with an Internet connection and a landline.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.22,0:06:07.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就住这附近 你家有办公区吗\N{\fs38}You live out here. Do you have a home office?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.83,0:06:10.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 有 但是Zeke住在那儿 而且  - 很好 就去那里\N{\fs38}- Well, yeah, but Zeke is in that room, and... - Perfect. Let's go there.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.96,0:06:12.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的邻居外出了\N{\fs38}Or my neighbors are out of town.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.61,0:06:13.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们也可以闯进他们家啊\N{\fs38}We could break into their place.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.32,0:06:17.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 就去我家\N{\fs38}Fine, we'll go to my house.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.69,0:06:21.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或者按照Zeke的说法 "小Terry的霍比特人洞穴"\N{\fs38}Or as Zeke calls it, tiny Terry's hobbit hole.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.34,0:06:26.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉来晚了 有个消息告诉你\N{\fs38}All right, sorry for the delay, but I have some news.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.06,0:06:28.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我必须得说 你的防护服看起来好吓人\N{\fs38}I gotta say, your Hazmat suit is super scary.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.59,0:06:29.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你应该试试用搞笑的声音说话\N{\fs38}You should talk in a silly voice,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.93,0:06:31.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样才不会那么吓人\N{\fs38}so you seem less terrifying.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.13,0:06:32.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们进行了初步检查\N{\fs38}Well, we ran our test.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.53,0:06:33.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿 如果你能学格罗弗的声音说话\N{\fs38}See, even that would be much less ominous
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.53,0:06:33.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs38}Grover格罗弗 美国儿童节目<芝麻街>中的人物
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.00,0:06:35.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坏消息听起来都没那么糟了\N{\fs38}if you just did a grover voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.23,0:06:36.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,像这样 我们作了初步检查\N{\fs38}Well, we ran our tests.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.87,0:06:38.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那不是发酵粉\N{\fs38}And it's not baking powder.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.37,0:06:39.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能是有毒物质\N{\fs38}There's a chance it's toxic.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.57,0:06:41.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fs38}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.53,0:06:45.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,既然那不是发酵粉 那是什么\N{\fs38}We know it's not baking powder. What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.03,0:06:48.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还不清楚 长官 但我们\N{\fs38}We don't know yet, sir, but we are...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.03,0:06:50.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官 你低着头看屏幕也挺累的\N{\fs38}Sir, you shouldn't have to be below eye level,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.16,0:06:52.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我帮你举着\N{\fs38}so I'm gonna hold you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.00,0:06:54.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不错 Amy的紫衬衫挺衬你的\N{\fs38}Okay, you do look good in Amy's purple shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.46,0:06:55.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总之 今天是感恩节\N{\fs38}Anyways, it's Thanksgiving,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.84,0:06:58.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应急部门的实验室关了\N{\fs38}so the emergency services lab is closed.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.25,0:07:00.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们会重新启动 但得至少5小时后\N{\fs38}They're gonna reopen them, but it'll be at least five hours
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.38,0:07:01.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,才能作进一步检测\N{\fs38}till they can run detailed tests.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.96,0:07:03.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Boyle 人员分析\N{\fs38}Boyle, status report?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.22,0:07:04.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们和42个人锁在一块儿\N{\fs38}We're locked down with 42 civilians,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.88,0:07:06.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以把他们分成四拨\N{\fs38}divided into four factions.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.62,0:07:09.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,首先 被关押的12个罪犯\N{\fs38}First, we have 12 perps locked up in holding.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.32,0:07:11.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以叫他们十二罗汉\N{\fs38}Okay, we will call them the dirty dozen.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.35,0:07:12.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好棒\N{\fs38}Oh, I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.79,0:07:15.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第二拨是赶巧来到警局的无辜群众\N{\fs38}Second faction is the innocent people who just had the bad luck of being here,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.89,0:07:17.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有些是证人 有些是受害人\N{\fs38}some witnesses, some mugging victims,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.66,0:07:19.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几个外卖小哥\N{\fs38}couple food delivery guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.29,0:07:21.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好 就叫他们普通民众\N{\fs38}Great, we'll refer to them as the normies.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.96,0:07:24.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第三拨才是麻烦的 线人 疑犯\N{\fs38}Third faction is trouble: Your snitches, your suspects,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.33,0:07:26.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几个来接人的帮派成员\N{\fs38}couple of gang members here to pick up their friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.50,0:07:27.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能给他们取个代号吗 长官\N{\fs38}Permission to give them a nickname, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.84,0:07:28.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,批准了\N{\fs38}Permission granted.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.84,0:07:29.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,淘气小子\N{\fs38}The naughty boys.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.94,0:07:31.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收回批准\N{\fs38}Permission denied.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.27,0:07:33.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要专门称他们为\N{\fs38}We will refer to them exclusively
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.01,0:07:34.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,搅混水大军\N{\fs38}as the doinkmeisters.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.21,0:07:35.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比我的好多了\N{\fs38}Way better.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.21,0:07:37.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最糟的是最后一拨\N{\fs38}The last faction is the worst,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.04,0:07:38.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,由六名律师组成\N{\fs38}six lawyers.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.05,0:07:38.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你猜怎么着\N{\fs38}Ugh, you know what,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.98,0:07:40.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要叫他们大拌菜\N{\fs38}I'm just gonna call them the vegetable medley,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.88,0:07:42.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为那是我能想到的最反胃的东西\N{\fs38}because that's the grossest thing I can think of.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.82,0:07:44.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那计划是什么\N{\fs38}So what's the plan?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.42,0:07:46.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官 我认为该把帮派相互隔离\N{\fs38}Sir, I think we should separate the factions,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.82,0:07:48.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们才不会在人数上占优势\N{\fs38}so we don't become outnumbered.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.16,0:07:49.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开始定量供应食物\N{\fs38}We should start rationing the food now,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.72,0:07:51.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告知他们可能待到很晚\N{\fs38}and we should tell people that we're in for a long night,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.46,0:07:53.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鉴于那包东西不是发酵粉\N{\fs38}because the substance is not baking powder.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.49,0:07:55.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等 那会把大家都吓坏的\N{\fs38}Whoa, whoa, that's just gonna freak everyone out.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.36,0:07:57.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的追求是大家平和又快乐\N{\fs38}We want people to be happy and calm.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.30,0:07:59.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以放Sade的歌\N{\fs38}We should play them sade.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.30,0:07:59.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs38}英国女歌手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.27,0:08:01.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保持平和是很重要\N{\fs38}Keeping the peace is important.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.17,0:08:02.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没法到场了解情况\N{\fs38}I'm not there to read the situation,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.57,0:08:06.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是 不敢相信我要说这话了\N{\fs38}but... and I can't believe I'm actually saying this...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.14,0:08:10.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Peralta现在是管事的 有需要再打给我\N{\fs38}I did leave Peralta in charge, so call me if you need anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.31,0:08:11.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官 还有一事\N{\fs38}Oh, sir, one other thing,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.98,0:08:13.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Hitchcock被困在阳台了\N{\fs38}Hitchcock got trapped out on the balcony.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.71,0:08:15.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好 看来我们躲过了他这一劫\N{\fs38}Good, sounds like we dodged a bullet there.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.38,0:08:16.92,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fs38}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.92,0:08:18.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就这么办吧\N{\fs38}Well, that's settled.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.15,0:08:20.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Diaz和Santiago 你们俩跟我来鼓舞士气\N{\fs38}Diaz, Santiago, I want you out there with me, keeping people's morale up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.52,0:08:22.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Boyle 你去查查监控录像\N{\fs38}Boyle, you go through security footage
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.50,0:08:24.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看能不能找到是谁放了那个盒子\N{\fs38}and see if you can see who brought in that box.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.19,0:08:26.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好 但是 既然现在是你管事\N{\fs38}Okay, but, I mean, I thought since you were in charge,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.09,0:08:28.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许我可以当你的副手 你的小叮当\N{\fs38}maybe I could be your right-hand man, your tinker bell.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.09,0:08:28.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs38}小叮当 迪士尼动画中的小仙女
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.31,0:08:29.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小叮当\N{\fs38}Tinker bell?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.32,0:08:30.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要为小叮当正名\N{\fs38}Let me tell you something about tinker bell.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.76,0:08:32.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小叮当是一个忠实的副手\N{\fs38}Tinker bell is a loyal lieutenant
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.81,0:08:34.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也是对付Hook船长的一大助力\N{\fs38}and a real Thorn in the side of Captain Hook.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.72,0:08:36.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 你是我的二把手了\N{\fs38}Fine, done, you're my number two.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.02,0:08:37.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太好了 我当上二把手(屎)了\N{\fs38}Yes! I made number two.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.75,0:08:40.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听见我的话了 我怎么会那样说\N{\fs38}I hear it. Why would I ever say that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.67,0:08:42.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fs38}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.91,0:08:44.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚和紧急救援组通了电话\N{\fs38}I just got ahold of E.S.U.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.38,0:08:46.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,实验室的人正从纽泽西的家赶过来\N{\fs38}The lab tech is en route from his home in New Jersey.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.65,0:08:50.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警长 有没有东西能换了这个球\N{\fs38}Sergeant, is there any way you can replace this large ball
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.05,0:08:52.45,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比如一把能被称作椅子的椅子\N{\fs38}with a chair that is actually a chair?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.45,0:08:54.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉 长官 我只有这个\N{\fs38}I'm sorry, sir, that's all I've got.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.39,0:08:55.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但它能锻炼你的核心肌肉\N{\fs38}But it's good for your core.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.99,0:08:58.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确实 我的核心肌肉都被调动起来了\N{\fs38}Yes. My core, it's engaged.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.96,0:09:01.14,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可不会听这小子的健身建议\N{\fs38}I wouldn't take fitness tips from this shrimp.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.60,0:09:04.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官 你还记得我的大舅子Zeke吧\N{\fs38}Sir, you remember my brother-in-law, Zeke?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.38,0:09:05.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 记得 你好  - 你好\N{\fs38}- Yes, hello. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.70,0:09:08.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我之前在录的比赛呢\N{\fs38}What happened to the game I was dvr-ing?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.52,0:09:09.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还想晚点看的\N{\fs38}I was recording it for later.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.85,0:09:12.07,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警监想看新闻\N{\fs38}Well, the Captain wanted to have the news on,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.07,0:09:13.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就把你的录像关了\N{\fs38}so I stopped the recording.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.07,0:09:16.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反正那比赛打得很烂\N{\fs38}Well, the game was a blowout anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.31,0:09:19.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有人都死了 活动也被取消了\N{\fs38}I mean everyone died. Sports are canceled.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.04,0:09:20.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最好是这样\N{\fs38}You better hope that's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.92,0:09:24.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好 他终于走了\N{\fs38}Good, he's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.39,0:09:27.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在干点正经事吧\N{\fs38}Now, let's get serious and focus up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.93,0:09:32.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是想蹦到打印机旁边\N{\fs38}Just trying to get to the printer.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.32,0:09:35.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿 大家伙\N{\fs38}Hey, hey, hey, people.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.06,0:09:38.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麻烦各位过来一下\N{\fs38}How about everyone come on, bring it in here, gather around?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.91,0:09:41.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家感觉怎么样\N{\fs38}So how we all holding up?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.35,0:09:43.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不太好 我们可是在感恩节被困在这儿\N{\fs38}Not good. We're trapped on Thanksgiving.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.71,0:09:44.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到底怎么回事\N{\fs38}What's going on, man?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.71,0:09:45.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好 首先\N{\fs38}Okay, great, first off,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.91,0:09:47.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,感恩节快乐\N{\fs38}happy Thanksgiving, everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.20,0:09:48.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为火鸡欢呼吧\N{\fs38}Shout-out to turkey.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.61,0:09:49.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喔呼\N{\fs38}Whoo-whoo!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.95,0:09:52.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢 好了 是这么回事\N{\fs38}Thank you. All right, so here's the deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.00,0:09:54.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还在等初步检测结果\N{\fs38}We are still awaiting the initial test results,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.37,0:09:55.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望最终能知道\N{\fs38}but hopefully, we'll hear soon
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.61,0:09:57.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那包东西是无害的 我们就能马上回家了\N{\fs38}that it's all harmless and we can all go home soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.64,0:09:58.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你干得很\N{\fs38}You're doing a great...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.23,0:09:59.37,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在干嘛\N{\fs38}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.37,0:10:01.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在对你耳语呀 二把手都这么干\N{\fs38}I'm whispering in your ear. It's what a number two does.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.59,0:10:02.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,靠太近了吧\N{\fs38}It was way too close.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.89,0:10:04.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就小点声说不行吗\N{\fs38}Can you say it quietly to me, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.33,0:10:05.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事情进行得很顺利\N{\fs38}This is going really well.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.87,0:10:07.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了\N{\fs38}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.23,0:10:10.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总之 我觉得这段时间内\N{\fs38}At any rate, I figured we could pass the time
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.74,0:10:13.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以找点好玩的事 也许来个电影之夜\N{\fs38}and do something fun, maybe a movie night.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.01,0:10:16.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第一选择是 Diane Keaton经典电影\N{\fs38}Our options are a bootleg copy of the Diane Keaton classic,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.01,0:10:16.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs38}Diane Keaton 美国女演员 代表作<教父> <呆头鹅>
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.63,0:10:17.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,<爱是妥协>的盗版碟\N{\fs38}something's gotta give.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.60,0:10:18.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,电影不错\N{\fs38}Movie's hilarious.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.57,0:10:19.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 很出乎意料的观点\N{\fs38}Okay, surprising opinion.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.53,0:10:20.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们待会再议\N{\fs38}We'll talk about that later.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.61,0:10:23.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第二选择是看Amy Santiago警探\N{\fs38}And our second option is surveillance footage of
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.19,0:10:26.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,言辞正经地去买毒品的录像带\N{\fs38}Detective Amy Santiago soliciting drugs using perfect grammar.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.33,0:10:28.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,礼貌地问"能给我一些可卡因吗"不会很奇怪吧\N{\fs38}It's not that weird to say, "May I have some cocaine?"
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.68,0:10:30.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 会  - 这些选项无聊死了\N{\fs38}- It is. - Those options suck.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.78,0:10:33.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 那我们要不在这儿举办场达人秀呗\N{\fs38}Fair enough, why don't we have a talent show then?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.15,0:10:34.32,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁有才艺可以表演\N{\fs38}Who has a special talent?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.32,0:10:36.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚学了<Single ladies>的舞\N{\fs38}Oh, I just learned the single ladies dance.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.16,0:10:37.62,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿 太好了\N{\fs38}Hey! Yes!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.93,0:10:40.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家看得很开心啊\N{\fs38}People love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.43,0:10:43.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看呀 两个妓女也加入了\N{\fs38}Look at that, two painted ladies just joined in.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.26,0:10:44.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不得不承认\N{\fs38}You got to admit,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.67,0:10:47.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Boyle很懂怎么扭动他的盆骨部位\N{\fs38}Boyle really knows how to move his pelvis.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.67,0:10:49.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不敢相信这是我有生之年能看到的\N{\fs38}I can't believe this is one of the last things
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.60,0:10:51.44,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最后一个场面\N{\fs38}I'm ever gonna see.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.47,0:10:52.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实上 中了炭疽 你在最后看到的\N{\fs38}Actually, with Anthrax, the last things you'll see
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.87,0:10:57.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,将会是医生 血 医生 脓 痂 没了\N{\fs38}will be doctor, blood, doctor, pus, scab, nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.85,0:10:59.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么要这样说\N{\fs38}Why are you saying that?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.01,0:10:59.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你的反应太夸张了\N{\fs38}'Cause you're being melodramatic,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.77,0:11:01.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 所以我在嘲笑你  - 好吧\N{\fs38}- so I'm making fun of you. - Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.08,0:11:02.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要把你从我的遗嘱里去掉\N{\fs38}I'm writing you out of my will.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.48,0:11:06.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟两只"美邹豹"做爱的雕像说拜拜吧\N{\fs38}Say good-bye to my sculpture of two "Jag-u-ars" Making love.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.32,0:11:09.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,呼 就是因为这个我才当警察的\N{\fs38}Whoo! This is why I became a cop.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.22,0:11:11.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 真的吗  - 大家可喜欢达人秀了\N{\fs38}- Really? - People love the talent show.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.59,0:11:13.13,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,律师男在表演单口相声\N{\fs38}Lawyer guy's doing stand-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.13,0:11:14.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 他确实是个好苗子  - 喔\N{\fs38}- He's got really good material. - Oh.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.86,0:11:17.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,世界上有两个职位的人可以完全控制\N{\fs38}There are two jobs where you have total control
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.06,0:11:19.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,付钱给他们的人 国家总统\N{\fs38}over the people that pay you: President of a country
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.93,0:11:21.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和清洁女工\N{\fs38}and cleaning lady.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.10,0:11:25.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不敢相信你竟然给了一群暴民一个扩音器\N{\fs38}I can't believe you gave the mob a megaphone.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.51,0:11:27.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 首先 我们没有话筒可提供\N{\fs38}Okay, first of all, we didn't have a mic,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.94,0:11:29.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其次 他们不是暴民\N{\fs38}and second, it's not a mob.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.58,0:11:31.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而是一个由怪咖们组成的欢乐群体\N{\fs38}It's a happy group of unlikely friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.78,0:11:33.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能没你说的那么欢乐\N{\fs38}Maybe not so happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.15,0:11:35.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们开始喊饿了\N{\fs38}People are starting to get hungry.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.42,0:11:37.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的 没问题\N{\fs38}Oh. Okay, not a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.15,0:11:39.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就给他们弄点吃的来吧\N{\fs38}Let's get them some food.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.42,0:11:41.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,瞧 从两个和我们一起被困在此的\N{\fs38}Voila, a Thanksgiving feast
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.56,0:11:43.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,外卖小哥那儿得来的感恩节大餐\N{\fs38}from the two delivery guys who are trapped in here with us,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.76,0:11:46.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是由我付的Boyle的钱\N{\fs38}and paid for by me with Boyle's money.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.43,0:11:47.76,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先记在账上\N{\fs38}Put it on the tab.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.76,0:11:49.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我呢\N{\fs38}What about me?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.90,0:11:51.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,呃 我应该可以找个朋友\N{\fs38}Uh, I guess I could have a friend
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.90,0:11:53.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从街上给你扔上来点椒盐卷饼吧\N{\fs38}throw some pretzels up to you from the street?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.00,0:11:55.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也会有汽水吗\N{\fs38}And soda too?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.20,0:11:57.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 我会找个人冲你\N{\fs38}Fine, I'll have someone blindly throw
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.60,0:11:59.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,瞎扔冰凉铁皮听装汽水的\N{\fs38}ice-cold metal cans of soda at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.14,0:12:03.41,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Jake 我知道你觉得事情进展的很好\N{\fs38}Jake, I know you think this is going well,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.44,0:12:05.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你不能再这样走一步看一步了\N{\fs38}but you can't keep putting out fires as they come up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.55,0:12:07.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得立些规矩\N{\fs38}You need to set down some rules.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.35,0:12:08.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的 大家都很开心\N{\fs38}It's fine. Everyone is happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.82,0:12:10.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我们只要坐等警报解除就好了\N{\fs38}Now we just coast to the all-clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.48,0:12:13.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里冷死了 我们要暖气\N{\fs38}We're freezing in here! We want heat!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.02,0:12:14.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要暖气\N{\fs38}We want heat!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.86,0:12:16.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要暖气\N{\fs38}We want heat!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.49,0:12:19.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要暖气 我们要暖气\N{\fs38}We want heat! We want heat!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.63,0:12:20.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么\N{\fs38}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.73,0:12:22.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很高兴我给了他们扩音器\N{\fs38}I'm glad I gave them the megaphone.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.10,0:12:23.50,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我更容易倾听群众的心声了\N{\fs38}It helps me hear their concerns.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.53,0:12:25.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在 不好意思\N{\fs38}Now, if you'll excuse me,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.33,0:12:28.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要去找几袋 暖气来\N{\fs38}I need to go find a couple bags... of heat.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.75,0:12:33.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Charles和我几年前以售卖山寨\N{\fs38}Charles and I arrest the guy a couple of years ago
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.43,0:12:35.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,名牌大衣的罪名逮捕了一个人\N{\fs38}that was selling knock-off designer coats.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.23,0:12:36.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只需要找到装衣服的箱子\N{\fs38}We just gotta find the box they're in,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.60,0:12:38.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家就会温暖又开心了\N{\fs38}and everyone will be warm and happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.46,0:12:39.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能让他们这样联合起来欺负你\N{\fs38}You can't let them gang up on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.97,0:12:41.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得男人一点\N{\fs38}You need to man up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.10,0:12:43.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,男人一点 性别歧视\N{\fs38}Man up? Sexist.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.30,0:12:46.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很抱歉 但是我不靠性别评判人 长官\N{\fs38}I'm sorry, but I don't see gender, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.24,0:12:47.61,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉他们关于粉末的真相\N{\fs38}Tell them the truth about the powder,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.64,0:12:49.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉他们他们需要在这儿呆上一会儿\N{\fs38}tell them that they're gonna be here awhile,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.51,0:12:50.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后告诉他们 他们可能会\N{\fs38}and tell them that they might have to be
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.74,0:12:51.94,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一点不适\N{\fs38}a little uncomfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.94,0:12:54.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我看起来太帅而引起的不适吗\N{\fs38}Uncomfortable because of how amazing I look in this?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.55,0:12:58.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Zeke我很抱歉 但警监觉得\N{\fs38}Zeke, I'm sorry, but Captain thinks
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.65,0:13:00.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得再多用一会儿你的房间\N{\fs38}we're gonna have to use your room for a little longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.72,0:13:01.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题\N{\fs38}No problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.72,0:13:03.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 真的吗  - 是啊 我理解你\N{\fs38}- Really?- Yeah, I feel you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.72,0:13:06.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也有一个那么混蛋的上司\N{\fs38}I got a boss that's a jerk like that too.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.66,0:13:08.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fs38}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.09,0:13:09.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警监最讨厌了\N{\fs38}The Captain's the worst.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.73,0:13:13.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有时候 我叫他呆瓜Holt\N{\fs38}Sometimes, I call him Holt the dolt.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.38,0:13:15.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这叫法不错\N{\fs38}That's cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.43,0:13:16.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,继续坚持 兄弟\N{\fs38}Stay tough, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.87,0:13:18.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,兄弟\N{\fs38}Brother?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.74,0:13:21.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,兄弟 我会的 兄弟\N{\fs38}Brother. I will, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.14,0:13:22.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fs38}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.58,0:13:23.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等下再聊 兄弟\N{\fs38}Talk to you later, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.84,0:13:25.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,回见 兄弟\N{\fs38}See you, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.01,0:13:28.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜 兄弟\N{\fs38}Bye, brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.58,0:13:33.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了 我写好我的遗嘱了\N{\fs38}Okay, I have finished my last will and testament.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.32,0:13:36.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对于Rosa 我什么都不给\N{\fs38}To Rosa, I leave you nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.33,0:13:37.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,弃权\N{\fs38}Pass.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.02,0:13:38.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你本来就没得到东西所以不能说弃权\N{\fs38}You can't pass on me leaving you nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.89,0:13:39.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚就这么说了\N{\fs38}Just did.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.93,0:13:41.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这都最后一天了别这样 Rosa\N{\fs38}Not today, Rosa.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.49,0:13:45.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对Charles 我给你留下了关于我柔软的身段的记忆\N{\fs38}To Charles, I leave you the memories of my supple form.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.26,0:13:48.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我让所有人记住了我丢人的床史\N{\fs38}I'm reminding everyone of my embarrassing sexual past
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.94,0:13:50.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我希望这种善意之举\N{\fs38}'cause I'm hoping it's the act of charity
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.77,0:13:52.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能够让我上天堂\N{\fs38}that gets me into heaven.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.27,0:13:53.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么她在说天堂\N{\fs38}Why is she talking about heaven?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.77,0:13:55.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里发生了什么我们不知道的坏事吗\N{\fs38}Is there something wrong here we don't know about?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.78,0:13:57.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不不不 她只是个搞笑怪人\N{\fs38}No, no, no! She's just being a funny weirdo.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.81,0:13:58.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一切正常\N{\fs38}Everything's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.81,0:14:00.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,更重要的是 我找不到\N{\fs38}More importantly, I was not able
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.55,0:14:03.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"暖气" 因为这只是个概念\N{\fs38}to find any "Heat" Because it's more of a concept,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.08,0:14:04.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们找到了这些美物\N{\fs38}but we did find these beauties.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.82,0:14:07.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些都是人造皮草且都来自最好的牌子\N{\fs38}They're all faux fur and all the best brands.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.59,0:14:11.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么香萘儿啊 古脐啊 屎特拉麦卡特泥啊\N{\fs38}We've got ChanelB, Grucci, Stella McCarKeys.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.39,0:14:12.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要有袖筒的这件\N{\fs38}I want the one with the muff.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.89,0:14:14.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不错的选择 先生 但实际上只有五件大衣\N{\fs38}Great choice, sir, but there's actually only five coats,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.83,0:14:16.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我们得想个办法大家一起分享\N{\fs38}so we're gonna have to figure out a way to share them.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.36,0:14:18.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在想智力竞赛或许可行\N{\fs38}I was thinking maybe a trivia contest.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.20,0:14:20.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别管大衣了 我想要更多吃的\N{\fs38}Screw the coats. I want more food.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.03,0:14:21.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有趣的事实 原来\N{\fs38}Interesting fact there... It turns out
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.57,0:14:24.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那桌只有一次的大餐就是我们全部的食物了\N{\fs38}the one-time-only feast was all the food that we had.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.64,0:14:26.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么 你竟然没有屯好粮\N{\fs38}What? You didn't ration the food?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.77,0:14:28.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是不会干坐在这里饿肚子的\N{\fs38}I'm not gonna sit here and starve.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.27,0:14:29.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天是感恩节 你说这只是个骗局\N{\fs38}It's Thanksgiving. You said it was a hoax.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.58,0:14:31.54,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只是为了一些愚蠢的规章条例被困在这里\N{\fs38}We're only here because of some dumb protocol.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.54,0:14:34.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要走了 直接从那个门出去\N{\fs38}I'm leaving. I'm walking out that door.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.51,0:14:35.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Jake 你得逮捕他\N{\fs38}Jake, you have to arrest him.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.84,0:14:37.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不 这样只会让事情更糟\N{\fs38}No, it'll only make things worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.52,0:14:39.52,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着 我们按我的方法做 现在的警监是我\N{\fs38}Look, we're doing this my way. I'm the Captain now!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.55,0:14:41.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这话听起来很像电影台词\N{\fs38}That totally sounded like a movie ref,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.25,0:14:42.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我是认真的\N{\fs38}but I was actually being serious.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.09,0:14:44.69,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思 先生 嗨\N{\fs38}Excuse me, sir? Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.69,0:14:46.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能来我办公室聊一下吗\N{\fs38}Can I talk to you in my office for a sec?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.13,0:14:49.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是什么大事 只是轻松聊聊天\N{\fs38}It's nothing serious, just a fun chat.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.20,0:14:50.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着 如果你不来的话\N{\fs38}Look, if you don't come with me,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.33,0:14:51.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她就会逮捕你\N{\fs38}she's going to arrest you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.56,0:14:53.47,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿 你们在说悄悄话吗\N{\fs38}Hey, are you guys whispering?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.47,0:14:54.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是Charles Boyle\N{\fs38}I'm Charles Boyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.70,0:14:56.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大概在这儿算个二把手\N{\fs38}I'm sort of the number two guy around here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.67,0:15:01.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,首先 我要给我们的谈话营造一下气氛\N{\fs38}Okay, so first of all, I'm just gonna set the mood for this meeting,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.57,0:15:03.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,轻柔的曲子或许管用\N{\fs38}perhaps a smooth jam.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.59,0:15:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fs38}背景音乐为<Doin' that Thing> - Raphael Lake,Aaron Levy & Jane Afrilu Sammut
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.01,0:15:06.72,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个不错\N{\fs38}Yeah, it's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.59,0:15:08.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了 情况是这样的\N{\fs38}All right, here's the deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.63,0:15:10.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有毒物质人员做了些初步鉴定\N{\fs38}The Hazmat guys did run some preliminary tests,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.98,0:15:13.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后发现那个物质并不是发酵粉\N{\fs38}and the substance is not baking powder.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.22,0:15:14.79,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,噢 那是炭疽吗\N{\fs38}Oh. Was it Anthrax?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.79,0:15:16.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们还不确定 但我向你保证\N{\fs38}They don't know yet, but I promise you,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.66,0:15:19.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要他们告诉了我 我就会第一个告诉你\N{\fs38}as soon they tell me, you'll be the first to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.19,0:15:21.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其实是在我之后第二个 所以总的来是是第三个\N{\fs38}Well, second after me, so third overall.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.30,0:15:22.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但还是不错了\N{\fs38}Still pretty good.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.23,0:15:23.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是不想让大家惊慌\N{\fs38}I just don't want people to panic,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.66,0:15:26.05,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我想让你帮忙保密\N{\fs38}so I'm asking for your help to keep this thing quiet,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.05,0:15:29.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好让我们有一个最淡定的生化危害隔离 好吗\N{\fs38}so we can have the chilliest biohazard lockdown in Brooklyn, yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.94,0:15:32.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然 我理解\N{\fs38}Of course, I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.00,0:15:33.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太好了 谢谢你\N{\fs38}Great, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.87,0:15:35.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你正常待人的话\N{\fs38}See, if you talk to people like humans,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.98,0:15:37.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人都是讲理的 都是懂得\N{\fs38}they'll be reasonable. I mean, it's just good...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.64,0:15:38.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他怎么站到椅子上了\N{\fs38}Oh, why is he standing on that chair?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.95,0:15:41.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家听好了 他们骗我们\N{\fs38}Hey, everyone! They lied to us!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.31,0:15:42.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是他妈的炭疽病毒\N{\fs38}It's friggin' Anthrax!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.89,0:15:51.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你做的什么 零嘴吗\N{\fs38}Oh, what you making, a snack?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.02,0:15:54.09,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是警监要吃的四份三明治\N{\fs38}Oh, the Captain wants four sandwiches.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.09,0:15:56.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,蛋黄酱一勺 均匀涂抹\N{\fs38}A spoonful of Mayo, spread evenly,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.26,0:15:58.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要中间的面包 两头的不要\N{\fs38}middle-loaf pieces of bread only.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.30,0:15:59.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真难伺候\N{\fs38}What an ass.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.00,0:16:01.53,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还用你说\N{\fs38}Tell me about it...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.53,0:16:02.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,兄弟\N{\fs38}Brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.14,0:16:09.24,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我快忘了 他还只要整块的派\N{\fs38}Uh, I almost forgot. He wants a whole pie too.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.24,0:16:11.91,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真是个大老爷\N{\fs38}This dude is the worst.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.08,0:16:15.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有时候看不懂Peralta的短信\N{\fs38}I don't always understand Peralta's texts.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.68,0:16:17.58,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说他们还在等实验室报告\N{\fs38}He says they're still waiting on the lab,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.58,0:16:20.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一"确"顺利 "切"打成了"确" \N{\fs38}and "It's allz good." "Alls" With a "Z."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.62,0:16:23.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后是一个带问号的方框\N{\fs38}Then a box with a question mark inside,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.32,0:16:24.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一个带问号的方框\N{\fs38}another box with a question mark,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.56,0:16:26.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一个带问号的方框\N{\fs38}another box with a question mark,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.03,0:16:27.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一个带问号的方框\N{\fs38}another box with a question mark,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.49,0:16:28.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一个带问号的方框\N{\fs38}another box with a question mark,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.96,0:16:31.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,又是一个带问号的方框\N{\fs38}and yet another box with a question mark.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.40,0:16:33.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后还是一个带问号的方框\N{\fs38}Then a box with a question mark.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.74,0:16:34.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这什么意思\N{\fs38}What does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.77,0:16:37.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,意思就是你手机不支持表情符号\N{\fs38}It means you don't have emojis on your phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.27,0:16:44.21,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家静一静 静一静\N{\fs38}All right, everyone calm down! Just calm down!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.24,0:16:46.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放我们出去 不然我就砸东西了\N{\fs38}Let us out, or I'm gonna start breaking things!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.81,0:16:48.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这有违人权\N{\fs38}This is a human rights violation!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.25,0:16:49.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们不能把我们关起来\N{\fs38}You can't keep us here!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.68,0:16:53.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我才23岁 我是名人 今天居然就要命陨于此\N{\fs38}I'm 23, I'm a celebrity, and today, I'm gonna die!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.79,0:16:55.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没一句是真话\N{\fs38}Not one word of that is true.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.79,0:16:57.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,疼\N{\fs38}Ow!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.32,0:16:59.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Hitchcock受伤了\N{\fs38}Ooh, Hitchcock's bleeding!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.23,0:17:00.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他被汽水瓶子打中了\N{\fs38}He got hit in the head with a soda can!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.63,0:17:02.23,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他没看见它砸过来了\N{\fs38}He never saw it coming!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.23,0:17:04.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Jake 我们必须开始关人了\N{\fs38}Jake, we have to start putting people in detention.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.33,0:17:05.46,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得把他们镇压下去\N{\fs38}We have to quash this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.47,0:17:06.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不 让他们冷静下来\N{\fs38}No, we need them to calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.97,0:17:09.17,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得播放<爱是妥协>\N{\fs38}We need to put on Something's Gotta Give.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.17,0:17:11.04,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好主意 好电影\N{\fs38}Great idea. Great movie.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.07,0:17:13.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有 我们应该把那火给灭了\N{\fs38}Also, we should probably put out that fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.58,0:17:23.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警监 我有事要说\N{\fs38}So, Captain, I have some news.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.85,0:17:25.38,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事\N{\fs38}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.38,0:17:27.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记得你叫我别把警区烧了吗\N{\fs38}Well, remember when you told me not to burn down the precinct?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.68,0:17:29.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你把警区给烧了吗\N{\fs38}You burned down the precinct?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.42,0:17:33.03,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哪有 我分分钟就把火给灭掉了\N{\fs38}No, I had the fire put out almost immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.03,0:17:34.55,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,完全是正面教材\N{\fs38}This is a success story.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.55,0:17:36.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,老实交代发生了什么\N{\fs38}Tell me exactly what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.19,0:17:39.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 故事始于Boyle试图用"味美多汁"这个词\N{\fs38}Well, it started with Boyle wanting to say the word "Succulent."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.20,0:17:41.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 不是吧  - 结束于一场小暴乱\N{\fs38}- Oh, no. - And it ended with a small riot,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.67,0:17:44.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其中某混蛋把Hitchcock小憩的沙发给烧了\N{\fs38}in which a dirtbag set Hitchcock's nap couch on fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.63,0:17:45.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,够了\N{\fs38}Enough!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.77,0:17:48.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Jeffords和我立马动身回去\N{\fs38}Jeffords and I will come right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.27,0:17:51.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我对你很失望\N{\fs38}I'm very disappointed in you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.01,0:17:53.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说了什么\N{\fs38}What's he saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.11,0:17:54.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说他对你很失望\N{\fs38}He said he's very disappointed in you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.78,0:17:56.68,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唉\N{\fs38}Oh, man!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.58,0:17:59.98,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想见我\N{\fs38}You wanted to see me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.98,0:18:01.02,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对\N{\fs38}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.05,0:18:04.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你高傲到说不出"我就说吧"这种话 所以我就\N{\fs38}I know you're too proud to say "I told you so," So I'm just gonna...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.27,0:18:05.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就说吧 也没那么高傲\N{\fs38}Told you so. Not too proud.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.96,0:18:06.96,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就对了\N{\fs38}That seems right.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.96,0:18:08.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着 我搞砸了\N{\fs38}Look, I screwed up,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.46,0:18:10.39,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且我觉得警区应该由你来管辖\N{\fs38}and I think you should take over command of the precinct.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.39,0:18:11.95,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等你说这句话都等了一天了\N{\fs38}Been waiting to hear you say that all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.95,0:18:12.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fs38}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.77,0:18:15.00,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 所以你才不应该说出口  - 什么\N{\fs38}- Which is why you shouldn't say it. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.00,0:18:17.27,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还在试图取悦别人\N{\fs38}You're still trying to make people happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.27,0:18:19.20,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用向我道歉\N{\fs38}Don't apologize to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.24,0:18:21.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿出领袖的样子 告诉我该怎么做\N{\fs38}Be a leader and tell me what you need me to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.44,0:18:24.87,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉所有人他们应该怎么做\N{\fs38}Tell everyone what you need them to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.88,0:18:26.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是警监 Jake\N{\fs38}You're the Captain, Jake.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.51,0:18:28.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我是警监了\N{\fs38}I'm the Captain now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.48,0:18:31.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 菲利普船长  - 菲利普船长\N{\fs38}- Captain Phillips. - Captain Phillips!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.25,0:18:32.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,原来是这样\N{\fs38}That's what it was.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.35,0:18:33.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"看着我 看着我"\N{\fs38}"Look at me, look at me."
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.35,0:18:33.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs38}菲利普船长里的经典台词
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.35,0:18:35.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 像吧  - 像\N{\fs38}- Right? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.09,0:18:36.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 大家听好了  - 听好了啊 各位\N{\fs38}- All right, guys, listen up. - All right, listen up, people.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.82,0:18:38.25,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Boyle 你不再是我的二把手了\N{\fs38}Boyle, you're no longer my number two.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.29,0:18:40.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你给他灌了什么魔药 Amy\N{\fs38}What did you say to him, Amy?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.29,0:18:41.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你一开始就想抢走我的职位\N{\fs38}You've been after my job this whole time.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.89,0:18:43.83,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是Amy的错 我不需要小叮当了\N{\fs38}It's not Amy. I don't need a Tinker Bell.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.83,0:18:45.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你给我找出那粉是哪来的\N{\fs38}I need you to find out where that powder came from.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.21,0:18:47.99,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Scully 你来协助Boyle\N{\fs38}Scully, I need you to help Boyle.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.99,0:18:49.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别担心Hitchcock 他没事的\N{\fs38}Don't worry about Hitchcock. He'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.73,0:18:51.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有次见他摔下三层楼梯 站起来\N{\fs38}I once saw him fall down three flights of stairs, get up,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.67,0:18:53.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接着吃他的热狗 跟没事人一样\N{\fs38}and keep eating his hot dog, like nothing happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.67,0:18:55.67,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说得对 他是我见过最坚强的男人\N{\fs38}You're right. He's the strongest man we know.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.71,0:18:57.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是 Gina 我知道你现在很害怕\N{\fs38}No. Gina, I know you're scared,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.34,0:18:59.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是你不能再吓唬这些人了\N{\fs38}but you got to stop freaking out the civilians.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.31,0:19:01.31,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对 我影响力很大\N{\fs38}Yes, I am very influential.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.35,0:19:04.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Diaz 你别再取笑Gina了 帮帮她\N{\fs38}And, Diaz, you need to stop making fun of Gina and help her.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.21,0:19:06.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- 好吧  - 好了 大家听好了\N{\fs38}- Fine. - All right, everyone, listen up!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.25,0:19:07.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这不是好消息 但是我们还是不知道\N{\fs38}I know this is tough to hear, but we still don't know
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.92,0:19:10.49,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那白粉是什么 我们可能还要再待一会儿\N{\fs38}what the powder is, and we may be here for a while yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.52,0:19:13.06,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有 复印室现在是拘留中心\N{\fs38}Also, the copy room is now a detention center
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.06,0:19:14.59,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁不守规矩就关进去\N{\fs38}for anyone who gets out of line.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.63,0:19:17.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里是被封锁的警局 可不是什么夏令营\N{\fs38}This is a police station in a lockdown, not a summer camp.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.23,0:19:18.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要不要玩抢旗子\N{\fs38}Ooh, should we play capture the flag?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.63,0:19:20.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- Jake  - 好吧\N{\fs38}- Jake! - Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.16,0:19:22.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请静待接下来的信息 暂时就这么多\N{\fs38}Stay tuned for more details. That'll be all for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.67,0:19:27.34,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在就下楼感谢你的家人收留我们\N{\fs38}I'm just gonna go downstairs and thank your family for accommodating us.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.17,0:19:31.84,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可绝对不行\N{\fs38}You will do nothing of the sort.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.84,0:19:34.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是Zeke第一次对我这么好\N{\fs38}Zeke is being nice to me for the first time ever
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.65,0:19:36.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为他以为你跟他上司一样都是混蛋\N{\fs38}because he thinks you're a jerk just like his boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.68,0:19:39.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等我们下楼了 我要你冲我大喊\N{\fs38}When we go downstairs, I want you to scream at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.75,0:19:42.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你在我家人面前让我丢脸\N{\fs38}I want you to really degrade me in front of my family.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.93,0:19:44.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样你就开心了吗\N{\fs38}And this will make you happy?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.86,0:19:47.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是你能给我最好的感恩节礼物了\N{\fs38}It's the best Thanksgiving gift you could give me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.29,0:19:51.86,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说的什么蠢话 谁在感恩节送礼啊\N{\fs38}What an idiotic thing to say. What's a Thanksgiving gift?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.98,0:19:55.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是提前进入角色\N{\fs38}I'm just getting in the zone.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.00,0:19:57.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太好了\N{\fs38}I love it!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.70,0:20:00.40,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有 我说是你把派全吃了\N{\fs38}Also, I said you ate all that pie.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.40,0:20:02.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能在嘴边抹抹派屑吗\N{\fs38}Can you put some around your mouth?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.74,0:20:05.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧 给我抹上\N{\fs38}Fine. Crumb me up.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.34,0:20:10.01,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有消息了 各位\N{\fs38}I have news, everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.25,0:20:12.65,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,白粉对人无害\N{\fs38}The powder was not harmful.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.32,0:20:17.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Scully\N{\fs38}Scully!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.39,0:20:19.89,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得说 这一幕还挺甜蜜的\N{\fs38}Aw, I gotta say, that's pretty sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.92,0:20:23.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,门在他身后关上了 这下他俩都被锁外面了\N{\fs38}Oh, the door closed behind him. Now they're both locked outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.36,0:20:24.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事 发生了什么\N{\fs38}What happened? What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.56,0:20:26.10,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,封锁正式结束\N{\fs38}Lockdown's officially over.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.13,0:20:27.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警队要回家庆祝感恩节\N{\fs38}Squad's heading home for Thanksgiving.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.73,0:20:28.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我搞不明白了\N{\fs38}I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.77,0:20:30.63,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,之前我还听说警区着火了\N{\fs38}Last I heard, the precinct was on fire,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.67,0:20:33.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且三小时之内都拿不到实验结果\N{\fs38}and we wouldn't get lab results for another three hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.34,0:20:35.64,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Boyle帮忙加快了进展\N{\fs38}Boyle sped things up.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.64,0:20:39.11,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,监控录像里有个两年前被解雇的技术人员\N{\fs38}I noticed an I.T. Guy we fired two years ago in surveillance footage.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.11,0:20:41.48,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,结果他也被别的警区解雇了\N{\fs38}Turns out he was also fired from the other precincts.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.48,0:20:43.28,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,危机行动小组突袭了他家\N{\fs38}E.S.U. raided his home and found
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.28,0:20:48.18,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杆链球什么的 我不会读\N{\fs38}bacillus streptomoo-cocomo... I can't pronounce it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.22,0:20:50.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总之 他供了出来 那东西没毒\N{\fs38}Regardless, he confessed, and it wasn't poisonous.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.75,0:20:53.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就好 看来你力挽狂澜了\N{\fs38}All right, it seems like you turned it around.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.19,0:20:55.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊 我们要清理现场了 警监\N{\fs38}Yeah, actually, we're trying to clean up here, Captain,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.23,0:20:56.93,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以如果你帮不上忙的话\N{\fs38}so unless you have something meaningful to contribute,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.93,0:20:58.56,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有多远走多远吧\N{\fs38}you can get the hell out.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.56,0:21:00.43,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哦 对了 不好意思 \N{\fs38}Oh, right, sorry, you weren't here
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.43,0:21:02.30,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我转换管理风格的时候你们不在\N{\fs38}when I switched up my management style.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.30,0:21:03.97,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们肯定困惑极了\N{\fs38}That must be so confusing for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.97,0:21:06.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总之 大家各回各家 感恩节快乐\N{\fs38}Anyways, everyone head on home! Happy Thanksgiving, guys!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.70,0:21:08.60,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,- Jake  - 火鸡节快乐 各位\N{\fs38}- Jake. - Happy turkey day, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.61,0:21:09.57,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会在我的办公室里\N{\fs38}I'll be in my office.
